Chapter 695: Four Person Representative Group

Loulan Slash and the other three guild leaders gathered together, but Lord Grim was still missing from their friends list. Ever since they became allies, they promised to meet up at a certain time everyday. However, when the four met up at the designated time, God had yet to log on. They suddenly became very anxious.

“Why hasn’t God arrived yet?” The four were worried. After hearing about the reports for the three battles last night, they all knew that God’s existence was indispensable. They wouldn’t be able to do anything without him!

At this moment, all four guild leaders received a friend request at the same time. The friend requests were all from a player called Enlightened Lord. They also saw the reason for the request: Lord Grim.

“Hm?” The four were puzzled, but they still accepted the friend request.

“It’s me.” The Enlightened Lord guy messaged as soon as he was added.

“God?” The four expressed their uncertainty all at once.

“Yeah!”

“Why did you change accounts?” The four couldn’t understand.

“It doesn’t matter.” Ye Xiu replied unhurriedly. Of course, there was a reason for using an alternate account. Ye Xiu reckoned that if they fought for bosses, the moment Lord Grim came out to the front, all of the big guilds would go over and eliminate him at all costs. This was very disruptive towards the balance! Everyone was there to snatch bosses. It wouldn’t be convenient to provoke everyone to kill him first. As a result, Ye Xiu decided to use an alternate account if he really needed to.

They had a quite a lot of alternate accounts. Wei Chen and Chen Guo bought them with Wei Chen’s earnings. In the end, Chen Guo gloomily discovered: why did she ask others to help build a guild?! Couldn’t she just make up for their lack of numbers with all of these alternate accounts?

Thus, Guild Happy was established once they gathered all these side accounts together. However, it was quite lonely because apart from Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze and the Battle Mage who left Excellent Era with her, Forest Landscape, there weren’t any other live players in the guild. Everyone else was just alternate accounts. The account cards were lying neatly in the drawer, without any trace of life or use.

It still hadn’t been five days since Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion left Heavenly Justice. The friends that Chen Guo urged to join weren’t enough as well.

Today was good though. A third live name had finally been added to the guild: Enlightened Lord, a Cleric among the bundle of accounts they bought. The original equipment on him was pretty bad. The three had gained quite a lot from their diligent scrap picking during these past few days. However, Ye Xiu was to lazy to pick equipment from their harvest, so he asked Chen Guo for some gold so he could directly buy his equipment from the market. Just like this, he gathered together a some mediocre equipment.

After that, he sent friend requests to the four guild leaders. After the request was accepted and everyone was now in touch again, they were ready to kill any bosses that appeared.

After Samsara and Blue Brook Guild calmed down, everyone finally stopped fighting. Even though there were still a few clashes from time to time, the scale of the conflict between them wasn’t big enough for a scrap picking ground. Ye Xiu’s group of three had free time since there was nothing to do. Ye Xiu was casually walking around with his Enlightened Lord, while Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were practicing.

Yes, practice. Those two were no longer casually mucking around like normal players in the game. Ye Xiu was researching and organizing a set of specialized training programs.

Pro teams had their own training programs, but practice naturally relied on a variety of programs through the computer. Ye Xiu didn’t have any of the programs on hand, but he understood the reasoning behind the practice drills. As a result, he adopted a primitive method by using Glory’s in-game environment to design different kinds of drills. Although they weren't as targeted or effective as those specialized programs, he didn’t have a better way.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun needed these kinds of repetitive systematic training methods in order to strengthen and consolidate their skills. It also helped to raise their awareness in the game. These drills weren’t effective if they were only practiced for a day or two. Like exercising the body, they required repetition. These repetitive practices were relatively dull, after they passed their phases of newness. However, hard work was necessary if one wanted to become a true professional player.. If one only played for fun, they could only become a skilled online player at best.

Professional player. The word before player was professional. If one wanted to become a pro player, he or she must have a professional attitude. These kinds of repetitive drills would build up one of the required attitudes for a professional players. These drills would accompany the player throughout their whole career. The players relied on these training methods to improve and strengthen their skills, while older players needed them to adjust and maintain them. It seemed as if Ye Xiu never specifically trained for these? This was because with his skill level, he was able to apply the theory into practice. As long as he was aware, he was able to complete these practices daily, through killing mobs, PK, and even when he was hurrying along his way. He didn’t need to use things like computer software. For him, training opportunities were everywhere.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were still new to the training, so they were enthusiastic. However, the two didn’t practice for long today before Martial Awareness, Parade’s guild leader, sent everyone some news. A boss had spawned.

Level 70 Wild boss, Dolaki Stadium, Gladiator Vitalivis.

This boss was geared towards the Assassin from the Night Walker class. However, it possessed a shield like a Knight. It was a boss’ speciality to be able to have a mixture of classes. The players had gotten used to it, so they didn’t have too many sentiments. Like facing every other wild boss, the boss itself was never the hard part. The hard part was snatching the boss from all of the other guilds.

“Let's hurry.” They had already lost three bosses last night due to God’s absence. Now that he along with the other four guilds were here, they could finally strike with their full power. In addition, this was after their period of convenient pickings. They could finally formally compete with the big guilds for the boss.

Level 70 wild bosses. It went without saying that the big guilds would go at full power. Their success or failure this time would truly determine whether their alliance was worth it.

“Let's set off!” Ye Xiu called for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun and advanced with his Cleric, Enlightened Lord. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun also switched to their alternate accounts. Even though Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion drew less enmity than Lord Grim, the big guilds would definitely know that these two were sworn followers of God Ye Qiu. They wouldn’t be any better, when they were on the battlefield. Ye Xiu felt that it was better to stay low-key. After the three had switched to their side accounts, did they have to hide their title as part of Guild Happy? Although it was just recently established in the Heavenly Domain, the news must have spread out from the tenth server. The big guilds most probably knew whose guild this belonged to.

This time, there were no longer only three people who represented Guild Happy. There was a fourth person.

Little Cold Hands.

He already left Tyrannical Ambition and was considered to have transferred to Happy officially. However, his character was similar to Lord Grim. It still hadn’t been five days since he left, so he couldn’t join the guild yet.

He was already a member of the team, so Ye Xiu didn’t hide the current situation of the guild. The wild boss was also something they had to compete for in the game. After hearing that Guild Happy was about to fight, Little Cold Hands hurried over, despite not being part of the guild yet.

Dolaki Stadium was near Maluo City and the teleportation portal there was destination that had to be passe, so the two sides agreed to meet up here. By the time Little Cold Hands rushed over, he saw many players with the title of the big guilds. Players with exceptional equipment were constantly teleporting here and rushing towards the same direction.

Little Cold Hands saw these players and knew this was going to be a big event. Then, he spun around, searching for the person who called him to come here and soon heard a voice: “Little Hands, this way!”

Little Cold Hands spun around once again. He could hear the voice, but he couldn’t find the person. However, he soon received an invitation to join in their group. The invitor was Enlightened Lord.

“Hm?” Little Cold Hands spun around again and finally three characters at the foot of the wall beside the portal. Enlightened Lord was a Cleric among the three, alongside a Battle Mage and Brawler. The three players together seemed unalarming yet scary. If someone told him in the past, that these three were prepared to snatch a wild boss with these equipment, he would definitely die of laughter.

After accepting the invite , Little Cold Hands saw a message in the group chat that put away his doubt: “It’s us.”

Little Cold Hands walked over to meet with the three. Ye Xiu took the initiative to explain: “Our main accounts are too obvious. We need to stay low-key.”

“......”

“Alright, let’s set off!” Ye Xiu said.

“Just the four of us?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“The allied forces will arrive soon.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s just the four of us?” Little Cold Hands obviously didn’t treat the allied forces as his own people.

“Do you have any problems with that?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No…… aren’t our numbers a bit too few?” Little Cold Hands sweat. A bit too few? It was way too few! All of the leveling areas near Maluo City were Level 70. The wild boss would definitely be Level 70 as well. Even though Little Cold Hands had never joined such a high-level battle, but coming out of a big guild, even if he had never eaten a pig, he had still seen one before. The guilds would definitely send out the strongest elite groups to face the Level 70 wild boss and they were planning to compete with just four of them?

“It’s quite a lot. There were only three of us before you joined.” Ye Xiu said.

“......” Little Cold Hands didn’t know what to say. Could this be the temperament of a professional team?

As they traveled, Ye Xiu got in touch with the four guild leaders. After asking everyone for their location, they chose a place and soon met up. Loulan Slash, Yue Ziqin, White Stream, and Martial Awareness were only leaders of a mediuml guild in the eyes of top guilds such as Blue Brook Guild, Herb Garden and Tyrannical Ambition. On the other hand, in the eyes of normal players, they were worthy of being looked up to..

The four guild leaders brought their troops with them. They all valued this boss, so they brought their strongest elites. This could be seen just from their equipment. In comparison, Guild Happy only had four people and their equipment only got worse after one another. This was called…… a five guild alliance? Little Cold Hands was in a trance. Of course, he knew very well that they weren’t a part of the alliance because of the guild’s strength, but rather because of God Ye Qiu God. Even so, now that everyone had gathered together, just from the sheer number of players that had gathered, their own side seemed much weaker. As for the other three on his side, they didn’t seem to feel any discomfort towards this matter at all.

Yes…… They even had more people this time!

Up until now, they only ever had three people.

Chapter 696: Guild Feature

“What’s the situation like over there?” Ye Xiu’s Englightened Lord didn’t stop moving, after meeting up with the four players. He continued to head towards the Stadium, while asking them. Loulan Slash and the other three respected figures in the game purposefully stood to the left and right of Enlightened Lord, placing him in the center. Afterwards, Parade’s guild leader, Martial Awareness, who had first discovered the boss, explained the situation.

“The situation is looking grim. Three guilds located the boss before us. From our observations of the teleport formation, three other guilds are en route.” Martial Awareness introduced.

“Six guilds? That’s okay. That’s not too many.” Ye Xiu said.

For wild bosses, there were usually be around ten or so Club guilds with the strength to compete. Only six guilds participating could be considered a small number.

“Six guilds is just for now.” Martial Awareness expressed.

“Yeah, I know. Stay on the lookout. Have the three guilds ahead made any movements yet?” Ye Xiu said.

“They haven’t for now. They haven’t finished gathering their troops together.” Martial Awareness said.

“Which three guilds arrived first?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Tyrannical Ambition, Misty Castle, and Howling Heights.” Martial Awareness said.

“How strong are these three guilds exactly?” Ye Xiu asked. He didn’t have a deep understanding of the game. He knew that Blue Brook Guild, Herb Garden, and Tyrannical Ambition were the strongest guilds and had been christened the Three Great Guilds. He only knew about these sorts of common knowledge. As for how each guild stacked against each other, Ye Xiu believed that no one knew better than the guilds competing against them.

As expected, Martial Awareness replied clearly: “Tyrannical Ambition is a bit stronger than the others. In a large-scale PK battle, Tyrannical Ambition stands out. If you compare Misty Castle to Howling Heights, Howling Heights is slightly stronger.”

“What are the class compositions of each of the three guilds’ elite teams?” Ye Xiu asked.

“That……” Martial Awareness wasn’t sure. Yue Ziqin and White Stream were also stunned. It wasn’t difficult to find out the class composition of the three elite groups, but it was just that their smaller guilds rarely competed against the top guilds. Their wild boss hunts were considered “poaching.” Directly competing was called snatching.

They could get information on these guild elite groups, but they just never placed much importance on it. None of the three guild leaders could answer. However, Loulan Slash stood out. His team’s original intention had been to become champions. He had arrogantly considered these big guilds as their pretend rivals and had thoroughly prepared to fight against them.

“God, I’ll send over the information to you!” Loulan Slash said as he forwarded the document to Ye Xiu on QQ. Ye Xiu took a look. It was information on the elite groups of every Club guild. Not just the class competition, but even the names of the characters.

“That should be around what they have.” Loulan Slash said. He wasn’t completely certain. Groups sometimes changed players.

“Mm, let me see!” Ye Xiu continued to rush forward with Enlightened Lord, while skimming through Loulan Slash’s document. Loulan Slash had done quite a diligent job with this document. He even had information on what equipment many of the group members wore. These details were a bit excessive. Finding the composition of the group was enough.

“Who will be the first one to finish gathering all of their members together?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Tyrannical Ambition.” Martial Awareness said.

“Tyrannical Ambition will probably try to kill it fast as possible. Let’s hurry.” Ye Xiu guessed.

No one questioned him. The four guild leaders began to urge everyone to speed up. Sprinting used up stamina. No one could keep sprinting for a long period of time. Speeding up required switching between sprinting and recovering at appropriate intervals as well as utilizing stamina potions. As a result, there were differences between different characters. Ye Xiu and the other guild leaders ran at the front. When Ye Xiu turned around to look, he discovered that Little Cold Hands was actually able to keep up.

“Not bad!” Ye Xiu praised.

“You talked about this in the materials you gave me. I thought that it would be be useful, so I’ve been practicing.” Little Cold Hands said.

Little Cold Hand’s strong points were his ability to judge the situation and his surroundings. His mechanics weren’t anything special. It was only because he had played the game for longer that he was better than someone new like Concealed Light. As a result, he had also given Little Cold Hands a training plan to follow like he had with Concealed Light. These two had poor mechanics. They were far from being at Tang Rou’s or Steamed Bun’s level. Their starting points were different.

The training plan that Ye Xiu had given Little Cold Hands was more fundamental, but also more all around. For example, something like utilizing stamina optimally was naturally very basic. It was one of the items talked about in the training packet. Ye Xiu never told Little Cold Hands which of these things he should prioritize. Little Cold Hands learning how to utilize stamina without being told to do so showed his attentiveness and insight. He had clearly thought of how he would only be able to keep up with everyone else if he could maintain his movement speed. If he couldn’t keep up, then there was no point talking about any sort of coordinating. He was a Cleric. If he wasn’t with the team, he was useless.

Ye Xiu didn’t know he had done this kind of practice before. He didn’t know how long it took him to be able to reach a level, where he could completely keep up with Ye Xiu and the others.

“Not bad, not bad. As a Cleric, flexibility is important. Only by being flexible can you cover a wider range. If the Cleric is flexible, the team can also be flexible. A good Cleric doesn’t require his team members to deliberately look for his position. A good Cleric will always appear where he should appear.” Ye Xiu gave a lecture.

“Tyrannical Ambition has started attacking the boss!” Martial Awareness said.

Martial Awareness also kept up with them. After all, he was a guild leader and utilizing stamina was a part of the basics. In reality, players in the Heavenly Domain paid attention to their usage. It just depended on their level of skill.

“As expected.” Ye Xiu wasn’t surprised, “What are the other two guilds doing?”

“They’ve started fighting.” Martial Awareness said.

“The three guilds are fighting?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It seems like it.” Martial Awareness wasn’t at the scene. He was just receiving reports.

“Hurry.” Ye Xiu didn’t say anything else. They weren’t there yet. Saying anything was pointless.

。

As Gladiator Veta attacked the surrounding players. The three guilds began fighting with each other too.

The first to move was Tyrannical Ambition. Their players were the first to arrive, so they had more players. In addition, they were slightly stronger than the other guilds, so they didn’t care too much about Misty Castle or Howling Heights. Jiang You gave the order, and the elite group began attacking the boss. Even if the other two guilds didn’t attack, Tyrannical Ambition wasn’t going to ignore them. As soon as Tyrannical Ambition attacked, they also attacked the other two guilds. Tyrannical Ambition seemed to be quite confident in beating the boss and the other two guilds.

Tyrannical Ambition had the qualifications to be confident. The Three Great Guilds weren’t called that for no reason. Whether it was the number of players, guild storage, uncommon materials, or their elite group’s strength, they undoubtedly stood at the top. Especially because these things all complemented one another. If their elite groups weren’t strong, how could they get any materials? Without a huge number of players as their foundation, how could they build up their guild storage?

After Jiang You gave the order, his Elementalist, Wandering Shockwave, also entered the fray. He personally acted, building up morale. His magic exploded, specifically aimed towards Misty Castle’s Elementalists.

Team Misty Rain’s ace character was an Elementalist. Influenced by this, the guild had more Elementalists. In their elite group, Elementalists were their main source of damage.

Glass cannon classes like Elementalists had explosive firepower. Jiang You himself was an Elementalist, so he was well aware of it. But he didn’t cower. He personally led his long-range attackers to fire at the Misty Castle Elementalists.

The Elementalists of Misty Castle were outstanding and the Clerics of Tyrannical Ambition were exceptional.

The stars of the teams influenced which classes gathered in the respective guild. It had already become a feature of the big guilds. Their elite groups displayed this feature.

With the support from skilled Clerics, Jiang You didn’t fear the attacks from Misty Castle’s Elementalists. His decision was clearly correct. After the two sides fought, Misty Castle couldn’t hang on. Tyrannical Ambition also had skilled Strikers just like Han Wenqing, who they admired. They imagined themselves as the King of Fighting and quickly tore through Misty Rain’s formation. Once they got close, Misty Castle’s Elementalists were practically trampled to death.

Misty Castle wasn’t able to win. Their leader quickly ordered everyone retreat. Misty Castle’s guild leader, Misty Lock, wasn’t even there yet!

After quickly defeating Misty Castle, Jiang You felt very good. He turned around was about to give Howling heights a good lesson. But when he looked, he saw an Elementalist standing high on one of the stone pillars in the stadium. He was dressed in a blue-green robe. Jiang You recognized it as the Level 70 Orange equipment, Clear Sky Magic Robes. To be able to wear a full set of Orange equipment, this person wasn’t an ordinary person.

But this person….. Guild Howling Heights. His name: Hazy Scene.

Even though Howling Heights wasn’t considered one of the Three Great Guilds, they were at least a guild that could often compete with them. Jiang You recognized their experts, but he didn't recognize this name. But seeing his arrogant appearance, Jiang You felt an indescribable anger. As Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader, Jiang You was someone who stood at the top of the game. Just by wearing a full set of Level 70 Orange equipment and standing at a high point, did he think he could scare him?

No, definitely not!

Jiang You was just about to order his troops to kill this arrogant guy, when that Elementalist made his move first. He lifted his hands, pointed his staff towards Jiang You’s Wandering Peak, and fired a Fireball.

Chapter 697: Best Rookie

Fireball!

It was a low-leveled Elementalist skill. Jiang You didn’t put it into his eyes. He simply stepped to the side and dodged it while counterattacking. Then, he saw that Haze Scene had leapt down from the stone pillar.

I’ll still fight you even if you’ve jumped down!

Jiang You didn’t hesitate. He finished casting a spell and aimed at Hazy Scene. Suddenly, he heard a boom. A pillar of fire erupted into the sky. Elementalist skill: Raging Flames.

The spell didn’t hit Jiang You’s Wandering Peak, so he didn’t need to dodge it. However, this Raging Flames caused him to lose sight of his target. When the pillar of fire erupted, Hazy Scene was enveloped in it. Not even a shred of his equipment could be seen. Jiang You was originally about to click on his target, but he suddenly didn’t know where to click.

Hazy Scene couldn’t have just disappeared though. Jiang You relied on his experience to guess his general location and cast his spell.

Elementalist skill: Piercing Lightning!

A flash of lightning shot out from the tip of Wandering Peak’s staff. The lightning crackled as it moved in a straight line, piercing through the pillar of fire and hitting the stone pillar on the other side of it.

It didn’t hit!

Jiang You thought to himself. He suddenly felt like something strange was going on around him. The air surrounding Wandering Peak seemed to be emitting tiny sparks as if lightning had passed through. The ground below him was becoming darker and darker. His view was becoming hazier too, as if he were in a steam cooker.

F*ck!

How could the experienced Jiang You not know what was going on? He immediately tried to cast Teleport, but…...

It didn’t work!

All of Wandering Peak’s skill icons turned completely gray. Below his character’s health and mana bar, a debuff symbol appeared.

Elementalist Darkness skill: Magic Prison.

No spells could be cast within the range of the prison. The prisoner wouldn’t be able to use any spells for 4 seconds.

4 seconds sounded short, but Jiang You knew that, let alone 4 seconds, 1 second was more than enough.

Lightning and fire instantly enveloped Wandering Peak.

Elementalist skill: Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. Jiang You could see the signs of this spell being cast, but he wasn’t able to dodge it because the other side had countermeasures set up to stop him. Magic Prison completely silenced his spells. Using his two legs to run out of Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire’s range was impossible.

Under the barrage of lightning and fire, Jiang You could see the fire pillar from the Raging Flames begin to disappear. Hazy Scene stood on the ground with his staff pointed towards him.

An expert! An incredible expert!

Jiang You had the eyes to see that, even more so for someone with the same class as him. His opponent had been able to complete two spells during the short animation time that it taken to jump down from the pillar.

Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire, Magic Prison…...

No, three spells! There was Raging Flames too!

Casting while in the air wasn’t anything new. As long as one had Mobile Cast activated, any spell could be cast while moving. The problem was that it only took the blink of an eye to jump down from that height. Let alone being able to cast three spells, Jiang You was certain that he wouldn’t have even been able to cast two before landing.

For someone to be able to do something far surpassing his abilities, what type of expert was this?

Jiang You only had one answer: a pro player.

As a Club guild leader, he obviously knew that during the competitive scene’s summer break, pro players would sometimes hop into the game, perhaps to help the guild or perhaps to pass the time. If a pro player came out, how could he not participate in something as important as snatching wild bosses?

A pro player from Team Wind Howl?

Which pro player in Team Wind Howl used an Elementalist?

In the blink of an eye, he recalled a name: Zhao Yuzhe.

This very season eight’s Best Rookie: Team Wind Howl’s Zhao Yuzhe. His character was called Beautiful Light. Wasn’t that also an Elementalist?

Jiang You himself was an Elementalist, so he paid more attention to pro players of the same class, even if they weren’t from Team Tyranny. As a result, he was instantly able to guess his opponent’s identity.

Jiang You’s heart fell. He hadn’t expected Howling Heights to have a pro player participate. If a pro player came, the guild would obviously provide an account for him to use. The character would be wearing a complete set of Orange equipment too.

Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire was something Jiang You couldn’t dodge. His opponent didn’t show any mercy and cast several spells consecutively. By the time Heavenly Lightning dissipated, Jiang You was basically dead. Jiang You had previously attacked Misty Castle from the front lines, so the other side knew his identity and would obviously place great importance on him. Wandering Peak hadn’t been at full health at the start of the fight either. Now a pro player was specially taking care of him.

Run!

The instant Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire dissipated, Jiang You was about to escape by using Teleport to hide among his people. Before he could even cast his spell, his character could only complete a turn when lightning struck Wandering Peak from behind, piercing through his chest.

“F*ck……” Jiang You cursed. Wandering Peak’s health fell to zero. He died from his opponent’s Piercing Lightning, the very same skill that Jiang You had initially used to counter attack.

“Hmph…..” When Wandering Peak fell, Hazy Scene didn’t even glance at him as he coldly humphed and headed towards a different location.

Jiang You didn’t guess wrong. The player controlling Hazy Scene was from Team Wind Howl and season eight’s Best Rookie, Zhou Yuzhe.

The selection for season eight’s Best Rookie wasn’t as easy as season seven. In season seven, the Best Rookie was given to Sun Xiang, who also became a God that season. Every other rookie that year knelt before him. Sun Xiang had even been a candidate for that year’s MVP. However, the MVP award wasn’t given just based on his own record, but the team’s performance as well. Sun Xiang had been on Team Conquering Clouds, a relatively weak team. They didn’t even make it to the playoffs. How could he be qualified to be that season’s MVP? However, for the Best Rookie award, even a blind person would have given it to Sun Xiang.

But for season eight, Zhao Yuzhe had to win it over two other candidates. It wasn’t by a large margin either.

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t think about that though. To be able to win the award was enough to prove that he was an outstanding player for his first year in the competitive scene. Zhao Yuzhe was very excited to be able to win this award because it gave him a lot of confidence. He felt like his position on the team would certainly improve. Team Wind Howl’s current situation also gave him a lot of confidence for his future.

Team Wind Howl’s original ace player and captain, Lin Jingyan’s ability was declining due to age. In the All Star Weekend, he was defeated by Tang Hao and his popularity fell by quite a lot. Even his own team’s respect towards him worsened. Zhao Yuzhe only gave his captain respect on the surface, but in his heart, he never accepted it.

As for the other All Star on his team, Fang Rui, his skill level wasn’t low. His character Doubtful Demon was praised as the Number One Thief in all of Glory. However, the problem was that Fang Rui was the representative for all those who played dirty. Besides playing dirty, he knew of no other way to play. Support for playing dirty was very one-sided. There were a lot of supporters, but there were even more haters too. Putting this kind of player as an ace player meant that the team would gain, but also lose a significant number of fans.

Winning fans in this way wasn’t bad for new teams, but Team Wind Howl was a fairly strong and popular team, so dancing on the edge of a knife like that was too risky. As a result, Fang Rui’s playstyle prevented him from becoming an ace player.

Then who would be given the title of ace player in Team Wind Howl?

Selecting the Best Rookie was one option.

After being chosen as Best Rookie, Zhao Yuzhe imagined all sorts of things. He even dreamed that his team would buy him the number one Elementalist character, Windy Rain. He even thought that it was very likely. It was already widely known that Team Hundred Blossoms had purchased the number one Brawler Three Hits for Tang Hao. Why wouldn’t his team spend the money to buy him Windy Rain?

Zhao Yuzhe was excited from his own imaginations. He thought of his future as limitless. He gave up his vacation and ran over to the game to help his team improve. He already thought of himself as the team’s ace player. When there weren’t any matches, he should run to the game and contribute.

While the team buying Windy Rain for him was a bit excessive, Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t overstepping his bounds. Lin Jingyan was old. Fang Rui wasn’t suitable to become their ace player and pillar. Teams with someone who won Best Rookie would raise the Best Rookie to become their ace players. This line of thinking was completely reasonable. Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t the only person thinking about it. Others agreed too.

Such as the guild leader West Riding Wind. When Zhao Yuzhe ran over to the game to help him, he regarded him as the future ace player of Team Wind Howl. This made Zhao Yuzhe extremely comfortable. He took the character and equipment provided by West Riding Wind and helped the team snatch a boss.

As a result, he met Tyrannical Ambition in his first battle.

Zhao Yuzhe treated West Riding Wind’s introduction of Tyrannical Ambition’s strength with disdain. So what? Tyrannical Ambition’s elite group were just experts at a game level. Even if they were elites, how good could they be? To catch a band of thieves, first catch the leader. After killing off the other side’s leader, what were they going to do afterwards?

Thus, Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene stood up high. He was provoking the other side, so he could kill off their leader in one go and lower the other side’s morale.

He clearly succeeded. As soon as Jiang You and him faced off, Jiang You was killed. Zhao Yuzhe became even more delighted at his achievements. How could anything in the game be difficult for the Best Rookie and the future ace player of Team Wind Howl?

Chapter 698: Arrival

After Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader fell, the troops fell into disorder. It wasn’t like no one could take over and lead the troops. However, their morale had taken a heavy hit. The other side simply lifted his hands and their guild leader disappeared. What type of expert was this?

With Zhao Yuzhe leading the way, Howling Heights was actually able to suppress Tyrannical Ambition. Misty Castle saw that the situation had changed and immediately went over to help Howling Heights. They would first take revenge on Tyrannical Ambition and then see what to do from there.

At this moment, Howling Height’s guild leader, West Riding Wind, ran over to Zhao Yuzhe’s side: "We’ve discovered people from the four guilds."

"The four guilds?" Zhao Yuzhe asked. The four guilds that the guild leader mentioned referred to the alliance formed by Ye Xiu. Zhao Yuzhe had obviously never of it before.

"Heavenly Justice, Conquering Clouds, Parade, and Radiant." West Riding Wind explained.

"What’s so special about them?" Zhao Yuzhe didn’t understand. A guild’s strength was about the same as that respective team’s strength. Of those four guilds, Heavenly Justice was a newcomer that would be joining next season, while the other three guilds were weaker teams. Why was he making such a big fuss over them?

"They’ve allied together." West Riding Wind said.

"So what if they’ve allied together?" Zhao Yuzhe really looked down at the person in front of him, who represented Team Wind Howl in the game. He saw him occasionally in the Club, but he had never interacted with him before. Why was this guy so lacking?

"The alliance itself isn’t too scary. The leader of the alliance is the truly scary one!" West Riding Wind said.

"Who?"

"Ye Qiu." West Riding Wind said in a low voice.

"Ye Qiu?" Zhao Yuzhe stared blankly, "One Autumn Leaf’s Ye Qiu?"

"That’s the one. He’s started over with a new account called Lord Grim. Lord Grim is classless, an unspecialized character." West Riding Wind introduced Ye Qiu’s situation in the game, but he was certain that Zhao Yuzhe also knew about it. It had been a very hot topic this year. The Best Rookie of the season in front of him didn’t seem like someone who stayed inside all day, never looking outside his window.

"Ha ha." Zhao Yuzhe laughed: "You’re still scared of him with me here?"

"Uh..." West Riding Wind didn’t know what to say for a moment. He had experienced Zhao Yuzhe’s arrogance before. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t care at all about a top force in the game like Tyrannical Ambition. He had the qualifications to do so, of course. A pro player’s might far surpass a normal player, but this was Ye Qiu! Known as the Encyclopedia of Glory, with three championship wins under his belt, and countless other titles awarded to him. Any of these was enough to decimate a "Best Rookie".

What was Best Rookie? That was a award given to the Best Rookie of that season. Not every Best Rookie was like Sun Xiang, who could immediately contend for the MVP title. A Best Rookie award was certainly something to be proud of, but Zhao Yuzhe shouldn’t be that confident!

"Where’s Ye Qiu? It’s a rare opportunity to be able to receive a lesson from a senior in the game. I just don’t know what his level is at after having retired for half a year." Zhao Yuzhe was eager to fight him. He couldn’t help but think of Tang Hao’s junior succeeds the senior. What an incredible moment that was! Even though the loser of the match had been his team’s captain, Zhao Yuzhe only had feelings of admiration and envy for Tang Hao. He also hoped that he could one day replicate such a beautiful scene.

He had already tried looking for this type of opportunity in his matches. Now, he had found one in the game. As soon as heard that he could contend with a God, Zhao Yuzhe immediately got fired up.

West Riding Wind was speechless at this kid’s arrogance. He had been managing Howling Heights for several years. He could be considered Zhao Yuzhe’s senior, but the problem was that even though pro players didn’t have any official authority over others in the Club, everyone treated them like superiors. While West Riding Wind didn’t like Zhao Yuzhe’s satisfied look, it wasn’t like he could order him around either.

In the end, West Riding Wind felt like he shouldn’t invite humiliation onto himself. He heard that Zhao Yuzhe didn’t even listen to his team captain Lin Jingyan’s words!

"Their people are coming closer, but we haven’t seen any sight of Ye Qiu." West Riding Wind reported obediently.

"His character’s called Lord Grim? Okay. I’ll wait for him here." Zhao Yuzhe proudly stated.

You’re waiting for him….. Does he even f*cking know who you are? West Riding Wind ridiculed him in his head. His mouth, on the other hand, moved in a different manner: "Thank you for your hard work." And then he went over to lead his troops.

There were still parts of Zhao Yuzhe, which he appreciated. For example, Zhao Yuzhe didn’t require him to give up any of his authority as a leader. He simply took an account and rushed to aid their troops. Of course, he didn’t rule out the possibility that he might just be thinking of showing off his skills in front of everyone.

Ye Xiu and the others finally arrived at Dolaki Stadium. Because they had rushed over at full speed and everyone had different skill levels, the troops weren’t very organized upon arrival. The difference wasn’t too big though. Even for the small Club guilds, their elites weren’t bad. In addition, Ye Xiu was using a temporary account with make-do equipment, so he wasn’t too far ahead of everyone else either.

Dolaki Stadium wasn’t a small place. It had a diameter of 40 coordinate points or 400 units. It had multiple levels too. It wasn’t like modern-day stadiums with just one large open field, but rather many smaller sites separate from one another. It looked like there were streets and alleys. The monsters here were the ghosts of the ancient warriors who died in the stadium. The wild boss Gladiator Vitalivis was the strongest among them.

To put it plainly, this was a gathering place of undead monsters. The Glory world wasn’t limited to history. There were magicians, swordsman, and even people with guns. Some cities looked like ancient cities from the past, while others looked like steel forests of the modern-day era. It was rumored that, in the next expansion, apart from levels, equipment, skills, and other necessary updates, there would also be mounts.

The Glory world was so vast, yet there wasn’t a way to quickly move around. It was something the players often complained about. Glory would soon have such a method of transportation.

Mounts were what players liked to call such transportation tools. The official name didn’t use the word mounts, but simply transportation tools. According to the leaks, the transportation tools in Glory wouldn’t just be limited to things that could be mounted such as cars.

Once Ye Xiu and the others arrived at Dolaki Stadium, they weren’t yet at their final destination. They still needed to locate the boss. They soon found the battlefield. During this time, quite a few reinforcements from Misty Castle and Howling Heights had arrived. Tyrannical Ambition had paid a huge price to deal with these two guilds. Tyrannical Ambition was currently in a very disadvantageous position. The Gladiator Vitalivis had already fallen into Howling Height’s grasp.

West Riding Wind might not like Zhao Yuzhe, but he had to admit that this Best Rookie title wasn’t just for show. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t lead any teams. He only contributed with his individual strength, yet he was still able to win a lead for Howling Heights. His attacks were difficult for the opponents to deal with, allowing their own side to smoothly realize their goals. His eyes were precise and his decisions were accurate. Even though he was up against elite players, they weren’t able to defend against his attacks.

Misty Castle even began helping Howling Heights deal with Tyrannical Ambition, but after Howling Heights firmly took control of the boss, Misty Castle suddenly realized that they were on the wrong side. Howling Heights had seized a huge lead for themselves, yet Misty Castle was still fighting Tyrannical Ambition! It was as if they were doing free labor for Howling Heights!

Misty Castle immediately switched sides. They had initially been beaten up by Tyrannical Ambition. Then, they were unclear about the situation. And now they were fighting against Howling Heights…...

All the guilds were here to snatch the boss, but Misty Castle’s showing so far made them seem like stirring shit sticks. Misty Castle appeared to have no interest in the boss, instead they only seemed to want to add fuel to the fire.

"What are they doing?" When Ye Xiu and the others arrived, Ye Xiu surveyed the situation and gave Misty Castle an evaluation.

"Howling Heights has control over the boss!" The four guilds leaders were mainly concerned about the boss. They were quite surprised that the boss wasn’t in Tyrannical Ambition’s hands.

Apart from their four guilds, three other guilds had also arrived, but they were fewer in number. Even though they were elites from the big guilds, when they saw the troops of the other guilds, they didn’t dare to make any rash movements. They were all hiding in different places, where others wouldn’t notice, and waiting for more troops to gather.

Those three guilds were in an intense battle. Ye Xiu and the four guild troops were fairly close to the battle, but no one had time to pay attention to them. Ye Xiu was still observing the situation, but the other four guilds were in a hurry to act. They were afraid that, if they waited any longer, the boss would be killed.

"Okay. Let’s make arrangements." Ye Xiu watched for a bit, before finally saying something. The four guild leaders immediately listened attentively.

The four guild leaders heard the arrangements. Yue Ziqin, White Stream, and Martial Awareness lead their guild’s troops and separated. Ye Xiu’s group joined up with Loulan Slash. They would be the main attackers in this battle.

"Charge!" Ye Xiu didn’t have too many words to his troops. They would first join the battle, before doing anything else.

"Charge!"

Loulan Slash shouted and took the lead. Homeward Bound, Ocean Ahead, Night Tide, and Thousand Falling Leaves followed behind him. They were in a team together. Any fight together was an opportunity for them to practice their coordination with each other.

How could no one respond to their arrival? Howling Heights currently held the advantage. They were naturally afraid that Cheng Yaojin would suddenly come out, while they were attacking the boss. The scouts dispatched by West Riding Wind obviously noticed the incoming attackers. Now that the four guilds had finally arrived, West Riding Wind and Zhao Yuzhe began paying more attention to this side.

"Lord Grim….. It seems like he didn’t come….." West Riding Wind carefully observed the incoming attackers. He didn’t see anyone with that name though.

"He didn’t come?" Zhao Yuzhe was disappointed.

"Over there! Heavenly Justice’s, Loulan Slash! He’ll be joining the Pro Alliance next season." West Riding Wind pointed out Loulan Slash.

"Really? Then I’ll go over and teach them a lesson!" Zhao Yuzhe spoke as his Hazy Scene casually walked over.

Chapter 699: Revive Him in a Bit

Zhao Yuzhe always sounded like he was invincible, but how could West Riding Wind let him go in alone against so many people? He hastily dispatched troops to assist him.

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t say anything, but he clearly knew that this was common sense. He didn’t stop West Riding Wind from providing helpers. If he actually thought he could stop them singlehandedly, his arrogance would have truly reached the heavens.

The two sides clashed. Without exchanging any sort of pleasantries, Loulan Slash jumped up and initiated with an Earth-Shattering Slash.

In front of normal players, Loulan Slash still felt a sense of superiority. He knew his skill level was far better than those so-called elite experts, but this time, he had miscalculated. He didn’t think he would be facing the season eight Best Rookie.

Boom!

A pillar of fire shot up into the air. Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene flicked his sleeves and cast a Raging Flames. This time, the spell’s purpose wasn’t to conceal himself, but rather to arrogantly show Loulan Slash his might.

The pillar of fire enveloped Loulan Slash, but according to skill priority, Raging Flames lost to Earth-Shattering Slash. Loulan Slash staggered momentarily after being hit by the pillar of fire and lost a bit of health, but he was already falling.

"F*ck!" Loulan Slash cursed. His stunning blade was unexpectedly stopped by someone’s Raging Flames. It made him feel like he had been disgraced. He turned his character around. As he slashed downwards with his Earth-Shattering Slash, he thought of looking for that Elementalist, who shot him out of the sky.

The tip of his blade crashed to the ground.

Cracks in the earth appeared, where the tip of the blade struck. At the same time, Loulan Slash found the Elementalist he was looking for, because the Elementalist had taken the initiative to run towards him.

The Elementalist’s jump avoided the shock wave produced by his Earth-Shattering Slash. Loulan Slash was still in the middle of his skill’s animation lag. Hazy Scene landed next to him along with an Electric Ring, shocking Loulan Slash.

Once Lightning Ring hit, Loulan Slash was launched into the sky. Of all the knock-up skills, Elemental Power took the longest to execute. However, Loulan Slash actually failed to notice it. Unable to control his body, Loulan Slash was thrown into the air.

Boom!

Light flooded Loulan Slash’s screen. Hazy Scene had tossed out a Flame Explosion at him. Not waiting for him to fall, Hazy Scene flicked his hand and a shadow flew out. This was an Elementalist Darkness skill: Dark Missile. When the shadow touched Loulan Slash, it seemed to grab at him, pulling Loulan Slash back up into the air. Once Loulan Slash started to fall towards the ground again, he heard sounds of crackling. A Frost Ball flew over, where Loulan Slash landed. In an instant, frost iced over his screen.

Electric Ring, Elemental Power, Fireball, Dark Missile, Frost Ball…..

In just that short amount of time, Loulan Slash had been bombarded by a chain of spells. Loulan Slash no longer regarded this person as just another elite player. He already knew that he had encountered an expert.

Hazy Scene?

Loulan Slash had played the game for a long time now. He recognized the top experts from the various guilds, but had never heard this name before…..

His character was about to hit the ground. Loulan Slash refocused and immediately used a Quick Recover. Surrounding him was the pitter patter of ice and snow. Hazy Scene had already cast Blizzard to surround and isolate him.

Loulan Slash didn’t panic. He crouched down and made a move. In order to break out of this situation, one usually had to use quick moves with short cooldowns. Loulan Slash decided on Collapsing Mountain. He leapt out of Blizzard’s range towards Hazy Scene.

But when the tip of his sword struck, all he hit was an afterimage. Hazy Scene had instantly teleported backwards. Loulan Slash soon discovered that he was surrounded by enemies. Who knew how many skills were raining down on him at this moment? Loulan Slash seemed to hear a snicker from the other side as if mocking him since his move had been so obvious.

Loulan Slash was furious!

Falling into a trap was obviously bad, but he wasn’t alone. Behind him was his team’s Cleric, Thousand Falling Leaves. God Ye Qiu was also using a Cleric account called Enlightened Lord today too. Even though Enlightened Lord had crappy equipment, Loulan Slash didn’t doubt that his skill could make up for it. With God Ye Qiu backing him, how could he die?

Loulan Slash didn’t think that it was possible. He also laughed in ridicule. He grabbed his sword with both hands and spun around, using a Whirlwind Strike to fight with the enemies that had closed in on him.

The greatsword slashed through the air, creating a whirlwind. Wielding his greatsword, Loulan Slash was actually able to send numerous enemies flying away. He also saw his health wavering back and forth. The Clerics behind him were working hard to keep him at high health. Sure enough, he couldn’t die! Loulan Slash was filled with confidence. After using Whirlwind Slash, he targeted that Hazy Scene and shot forward with a Colliding Stab. He was about to teach this guy a lesson.

"Slow down!!!"

Thousand Falling Leaves hastily shouted, but it was too late. Loulan Slash tore his way through the enemy ranks. The Howling Height players cut off his retreat and swallowed him up.

The light from Thousand Falling Leaves’s cross died down. Loulan Slash had broken out of her healing range. She looked at God Ye Qiu standing next to her and saw that he had also put his cross away.

"What do we do?" Thousand Falling Leaves asked him.

"Oh. Revive him in a bit." Ye Xiu said.

"D*mn!" Thousand Falling Leaves sent out an emoji with sweat pouring down its face. She didn’t think Loulan Slash would be discarded so easily. Her gaze stopped over where Loulan Slash was located. God Ye Qiu was already directing his troops to break through from a different side. Gladiator Vitalivis appeared before them. It had ash-colored skin with its hollow eyes staring at them. It held a dagger in its right hand and a bone shield in its left. The Gladiator was currently locked in intense battle with Howling Height’s players.

The break through their defences surprised Howling Heights. Their guild leader and Zhao Yuzhe had personally went over to block them. How were their defences broken through so easily?

"That Knight. Attack!" As soon as Ye Xiu’s voice fell, a white flame ignited around the Knights facing Gladiator Vitalivis. Cleric skill: Sacred Fire.

The annoying part about Sacred Fire wasn’t the damage that it dealt, but the 3 second silence. Ye Xiu’s Sacred Fire had been cast at the perfect moment too. That Knight was just about to get an opportunity to use Maelstrom Counterattack to return damage to Gladiator Vitalivis. All of a sudden, his shields burned and a white fire instantly covered his body. He had already finished the actions needed for Maelstrom Counterattack. His shield had been ready too, when he discovered: F*ck! The skill didn’t activate. My skills are all grayed out!

Silenced!!

Silence was a CC effect, which stopped a character from activating skills. If a player was put into this condition, players usually said they were "silenced".

The Knight couldn’t use any of his skills. The Gladiator Vitalitivis’s dagger still slashed at him. Caught off guard, that Knight was sent flying away. Not only did Ye Xiu’s Sacred Fire stop him from using his skills, but it also put a marker on him. Heavenly Justice’s players heard Ye Xiu’s orders and immediately bombarded that Knight with their attacks.

Even though the main tank was the main healing target, the healers weren’t prepared for this type of sudden attack. Numerous players were focusing their attacks on the main tank. The boss didn’t stop attacking either. The tank was still silenced. How could their heals be enough to keep him alive? In an instant, the Knight was killed.

"Off tank!!!"

Howling Height’s players anxiously roared. Everyone knew what happened when the main tank died. If the off tank didn’t hurry up and pick up the aggro, it would be disastrous.

But where was the off tank?

Their off tank had died too!

Who knew when, but a Brawler and a Battle Mage without any guild tags were currently beating up their off tank.

Anyone who could be a tank had strong endurance, but the problem wasn’t whether the off tank would die or not. Howling Heights needed someone to hurry up and quickly control the aggro, but their off tank was being pummeled into the ground. Everyone knew: not good!

"Third tank….." The leader shouted, but the third tank wasn’t ready. He was like everyone else and hadn’t noticed that the off tank was out of commission. He wanted to hurry and cast a Provoke, but he was too late. After Gladiator Vitalivis killed off the tank, it spun around with a Shining Cut.

This low-leveled skill was extremely powerful when used by the boss. The Shining Cut looked as if it could slice apart the skies. Quick and fierce! No one was prepared. The Shining Cut passed and instantly removed three characters from the fight. Three other characters had dropped to critical health and immediately ran away.

Level 70 wild bosses were the most powerful monsters in Glory. Instantly killing a player wasn’t anything special.

The third tank’s Provoke was finally used, but he had taunted too many attacks. Apart from Gladiator Vitalivis’s attack, Heavenly Justice had focused their attacks on him. The instant that the third tank died, he was at a loss: did I make a mistake? I used a single-target Provoke and not an AoE Roar. Why did all of those Heavenly Justice Players attack me?

"Fourth tank!!" Two voices shouted at the same time.

"F*ck!" The person leading Howling Height’s attack against the boss hastily called the fourth tank over, but their enemies called it out at the exact same time and slaughtered their fourth tank.

"Stop them! Stop them!" The leader quickly reacted. With Heavenly Justice making a mess, they had no way of retaining control of the boss. They had to kill them off first.

Chapter 700: Concentrate

Howling Height’s fourth tank was panicking, when he heard both shouts calling him out. The tank, off tank, and third tank leaving the stage let him know that standing out like an iron wall was definitely not a good option, so when he heard both sides yell out "Fourth tank!", he decisively withdrew.

His actions didn’t incite any criticism from his guild because their leader immediately switched plans. Peace must be maintained at home before foreign aggression could be resisted. The internal conflict between players hadn’t been resolved yet. How could they worry about the boss?

The leader ordered the Howling Height players to block Heavenly Justice. At the same time, he urgently notified their guild leader, West Riding Wind, about their circumstances.

West Riding Wind’s side had slain Loulan Slash awhile ago.

Loulan Slash had been completely confident that he would be safe, so he had decided to charge into the enemy ranks with a Colliding Stab, but his health bar never increased. He wanted to show off his might and take revenge on Hazy Scene, when he quickly realized that something wasn’t right. He soon figured out the issue. It was because he had rushed in too quickly! Loulan Slash immediately tried to retreat, but it was already too late. How could Howling Heights let him go just like that? The guild leader tag floated above his head. Howling Heights would do everything they could to kill him!

Howling Heights originally thought that the other side would try and rescue him, but the other side unexpectedly ignored him and threw their guild leader aside.

West Riding Wind wasn’t just here for fun like Zhao Yuzhe was. He was very startled by this unusual move.

"Could he have been bait?" West Riding Wind couldn’t help but think. After killing Loulan Slash, West Riding Wind received a message saying that there was an emergency going on at the boss’ end.

"F*ck!" West Riding Wind was gloomy. Directly using a guild leader as bait to lure their attention was too crazy! But how much time could Loulan Slash stall for? In just that short amount of time, the other side was able to make a complete mess out of the boss’ side. These enemies were very difficult to deal with!

Even though Lord Grim still hadn’t been spotted, there was always a shadow in West Riding Wind’s heart. Their big guilds had been tussled around by Lord Grim from the start of the tenth server, all the way to the Heavenly Domain. West Riding Wind knew that the alliance had been created by Lord Grim and was worried that this alliance would be stronger than the Three Great Guilds. How could the Three Great Guilds compare to God Ye Qiu?

"Quickly!" West Riding Wind hastily rushed back to save the situation. He also looked for Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene: "Maybe Ye Qiu is among them." Fortunately, he had a pro player helping him out, which put West Riding Wind at ease.

"Oh? Really?" Zhao Yuzhe initially heard that Ye Qiu wasn’t there, so he had been disappointed. Now that he heard that Ye Qiu might be there, he immediately became spirited again. This guy was clearly someone who liked to pursue big name targets such as Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader and Heavenly Justice’s guild leader. However, none of those could compare to Ye Qiu.

"Where?" Zhao Yuzhe impatiently asked.

"We still haven’t seen Lord Grim, but he might be using an alternate account." West Riding Wind didn’t have proof, but he had a feeling that the other side’s offense was too abnormal. Ye Qiu leading them would be the only explanation.

"Okay. Let me pick him out." Zhao Yuzhe said haughtily. This time, West Riding Wind didn’t feel too disgusted. He was actually feeling quite gratified. He really needed someone like this Best Rookie by his side right now.

West Riding Wind quickly led his troops back to the boss’ location. They had been close by the entire time. but by the time he arrived, the situation with the boss had already changed. The Gladiator Vitalivis was no longer in the grasp of Howling Height’s. Heavenly Justice was now leading the boss around by its nose.

"How did this happen?" West Riding Wind was shocked. It had been a while since they snatched the boss away from Tyrannical Ambition. Pulling back the boss’s aggro so quickly shouldn’t be possible! Yet how did Heavenly Justice do it?

West Riding Wind looked more carefully. He discovered that Heavenly Justice hadn’t taken the boss just yet. They were relying on skills like Provoke and Roar to forcefully taunt the Gladiator Vitalivis into attack them. The tank responsible for the boss was following Gladiator Vitalivis along the entire time, attacking it nonstop. West Riding Wind knew that this tank was establishing aggro. Once the boss turned towards this Knight, Heavenly Justice would have full control over the boss.

West Riding Wind saw through the situation in a single moment. He didn’t think that the person in charge of this side, nor any of the elite players wouldn’t be able to see through it. When he looked more closely, he saw that the players from Howling Heights recognized the issue and were trying to snatch it back, but there didn’t seem to be any effect.

Charging at the enemies wasn’t enough to defeat them and when their Knights used Provoke or Roar, it seemed to be completely useless, leaving the Knights puzzled. It was their first time experiencing such a situation, which required such precision and timing. How could they know that Ye Xiu was leading Heavenly Justice, paying attention to their usages of Provoke and Roar, and stopping the effects from working.

West Riding Wind was worried. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t care about any of that though. He warped a few times and jumped onto another very high stone pillar. He shouted loudly: "Ye Qiu! Come out and fight me!!"

He also typed it out in words too. Everyone on the scene saw it. West Riding Wind immediately searched Heavenly Justice’s troops. He also wanted to know where Ye Qiu was hiding! With a God like Ye Qiu leading them, someone like Loulan Slash was worthless. West Riding Wind thought in this way.

"Ye Qiu! Come out and fight me!"

"Ye Qiu! Come out and fight me!"

Zhao Yuzhe shouted non-stop. The messages in chat kept on being spammed. Everyone saw it and some people wanted to go out to shut that guy up. Ye Xiu kept on commanding the troops, while doing his job as a Cleric. Next to him, Ocean Ahead was casting spells. Seeing that God Ye Qiu was very busy, he couldn’t help but remind him: "Someone is challenging you to a fight!"

Zhao Yuzhe was too arrogant. Even West Riding Wind felt uncomfortable, let alone the enemies. Everyone wanted to see this guy fall. And this guy didn’t seem to know what was good for him and kept challenging God Ye Qiu to a fight. Ocean Ahead felt like this punk needed to hurry up and die.

"Mm." Ye Xiu nodded.

"To the front!! Berserkers, move to the vanguard. Paladins, pressure the rear! Knights, don’t be negligent! Don’t rely too much on the Clerics!"

"Thieves, keep placing traps on the ground along our retreat path."

"Mages, don’t just think about dealing damage! Use more crowd control skills."

Ye Xiu gave a simple reply and then continued commanding the troops. At the same, Enlightened Lord’s cross kept flashing, healing others.

"Someone’s calling you out!" On the other side, Thousand Falling Leaves also came over to remind him.

"We’re here to kill a boss. Ignore that lunatic and concentrate!!" Ye Xiu berated.

When he said this, there just happened to not be any huge explosions from skills. Ye Xiu didn’t lower his voice either and shouted it out like an order. His voice seemed to echo throughout the entire battlefield. At the very least, many people heard it.

The battle instantly turned stiff. Zhao Yuzhe was standing so high up and spamming the chat too. Everyone knew who was shouting, so they knew who Ye Xiu was calling a "lunatic". At this moment, everyone’s eyes turned to look at Hazy Scene, who was still flooding the chat with the same message and shouting from up high.

The battlefield suddenly seemed to become silent.

There was a reason for this. The players from Howling Heights all knew that this person was this season’s Best Rookie and their team’s rising star, Zhao Yuzhe, but now he had been called a lunatic. It was quite a harsh remark.

Heavenly Justice obviously didn’t know who this person was. They thought he was some idiot who didn’t know his place. To think that he would actually challenge God Ye Qiu. Look. Ye Qiu doesn’t give two farts about you.

As for Zhao Yuzhe? He heard these words loud and clear. He was furious! Pro players truly weren’t ordinary. He was able to tell the direction in which the voice had come from. When he looked in that direction, he could see Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord standing out.

Everyone had a guild tag, except for him. In a chaotic battle, no one would take notice, but Zhao Yuzhe was specifically looking for anything abnormal, so he immediately noticed it. Zhao Yuzhe found his target and made his move. Hazy Scene pointed his staff at him and cast a Piercing Lightning.

This skill had a quick cast time and a fast missile speed. Very few normal players had the ability to dodge it. When the lightning shot out, Zhao Yuzhe saw that Enlightened Lord didn’t seem to move. He just seemed to stand there. He was happy that the attack would hit, but if it hit so easily, maybe this person really wasn’t Ye Qiu? Even if he had retired because of his age, he should still be more skilled than normal players.

Zhao Yuzhe was somewhat disappointed, but then Enlightened Lord suddenly turned his body. The cross in his hands flashed and a healing light showered towards somewhere else. At the same time, the lightning passed through him and hit the ground.

No way?

Zhao Yuzhe thought it was a coincidence at first. Enlightened Lord had turned around and cast a spell on his target didn’t seem like a dodging motion, but he did dodge it…..

If it wasn’t a coincidence…..

Zhao Yuzhe thought to himself. Hazy Scene activated Mobile Cast and leapt down from the stone pillar, similar to when he had fought against Jiang You’s Wandering Peak.

Chapter 701: Elementalist Charge

Raging Flames!

A pillar of fire shot up from beneath the stone pillar and enveloped Hazy Scene. Zhao Yuzhe really liked this move. It was a very flashy entrance and it also made it difficult for the opponent to grasp his whereabouts. Zhao Yuzhe felt great just thinking about it.

It would be the same as before, right?

Zhao Yuzhe thought to himself. When he quickly cast his spell and prepared to attack his target, he suddenly discovered that he couldn’t find his target!

He could see a lot of players in his field of view, but none of them were his target. Where did that Enlightened Lord go?

Zhao Yuzhe had been delighted at himself because he thought the opponent wouldn’t be able to find him, but he didn’t think that he himself would be the one to be unable to find his opponent. The pillar of fire from Raging Flames would hide him from view, but it also obstructed his line of sight. During that time, Enlightened Lord unexpectedly disappeared from view. There were players running around and fighting everywhere. Just where did he go?

He had already cast the spell and the skill went on cooldown. If he didn’t throw the spell somewhere, it would be a waste. Zhao Yuzhe was helpless. He could only place the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire at the position where he remembered Enlightened Lord being at.

Hazy Scene soon landed on the ground. There was still no sign of Enlightened Lord inside Heavenly Lightning’s area of effect. Finding a specific person in such a large-scale fight wasn’t easy, even for a pro player. Pro players wouldn’t practice this sort of combat awareness. The team competitions were five versus five. Why would he ever need to practice large-scale battles like the one taking place here?

However, all pro players came from the game. If the pro player never played the game, how did the pro player get noticed? Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t a stranger to large-scale battles. He didn’t care about which side won the battle. He only wanted to hurry up and find that Enlightened Lord.

Zhao Yuzhe thought in this way, but who else did? Anyone with a Howling Height guild tag was a target for Heavenly Justice. As soon as he landed, several players started attacking him.

Zhao Yuzhe was truly quite skilled. Hazy Scene landed on the ground and did a 180 degree turn. His Elementalist chanted several instant-cast spells, stopping the incoming players from closing in on him. Then, he formed an Elemental Power, launching three players into the air. Zhao Yuzhe had no plans on tussling with these players and dashed into the enemy ranks. His Elementalist charged into battle like a Battle Mage. Zhao Yuzhe clearly didn’t think much of these players.

Of course, if he really was up against so many enemies alone, he wouldn’t be so rash. However, he knew that he wasn’t a lone soldier fighting an army. He might not admit it, but he was very satisfied with how Howling Heights coordinated with his movements.

It was the same as before. West Riding Wind knew that he couldn’t order Zhao Yuzhe to do anything, so he dispatched a group to assist Zhao Yuzhe. It was very effective. Zhao Yuzhe’s skill level was much higher than the enemy players and he easily tore through Heavenly Justice’s formation. West Riding Wind immediately ordered his troops to charge through that opening.

Even though Zhao Yuzhe’s target wasn’t the group battle, West Riding Wind still fully utilized his skills.

"Cut off their contact with the boss. That Knight!!" West Riding Wind shouted.

He hoped Zhao Yuzhe would see this point and help him attack that Knight, but he knew that it was just an extravagant hope. Zhao Yuzhe was only thinking to kill that God to show off his skills. How could he care about a boss?

Who would have thought that before he even finished yelling it out, he saw a spell hit that Knight. It hit that Knight right when the boss was attacking him too. Not only did both attacks hit and deal heavy damage, but it also interrupted the Knight’s rhythm. Gladiator Vitalivis’s direct hit knocked the Knight to the ground.

That attack was too beautiful!

West Riding Wind praised. It was unexpectedly Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene, who executed that attack. West Riding Wind’s impression of Zhao Yuzhe improved by a lot. When it mattered, that punk was really dependable!

"Protect him!" On Heavenly Justice’s side, eighty percent of Ye Xiu’s attention was on the boss. How could he not have seen that attack? Don’t look at how their Knight group was leading the boss along, the crucial moments depended on that Knight called Knight of the West. The other Knights were relying on their taunt skills to hold the boss. Those taunts couldn’t chain together for very long. A steady control over the aggro still depended on Knight of the West.

Heavenly Justice had failed to protect Knight of the West, but then again, Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t an ordinary person. His attack had been extremely precise. He borrowed Gladiator Vitalivis’s attack to put the Knight of the West in danger. Knight of the West wasn’t always Gladiator Vitalivis’s target. His aggro was constantly being split between the other Knights. Knight of the West just happened to be in the way. The boss wasn’t so stupid that he wouldn’t care about any other players when he was heading towards his target.

Right when Gladiator Vitalivis happened to be attacking Knight of the West, Zhao Yuzhe attacked. A pro player truly did know how to seize opportunities.

Ye Xiu immediately ordered players to go up and protect him. At the same time, he healed Knight of the West. Fortunately, Gladiator Vitalivis’s aggro wasn’t on Knight of the West at that time, so he didn’t continue attacking. If not, even an immortal would have trouble saving Knight of the West.

Gladiator Vitalivis didn’t continue. How could Howling Heights miss this opportunity? West Riding Wind had his troops charge ferociously to do anything they could to take down Knight of the West.

Ye Xiu had predicted it though. After Knight of the West was rescued, he didn’t continue attacking the boss and instead retreated to the protection of his allies. If he didn’t attack, the boss’s aggro on him would slowly decrease, but his life was much more important right now.

Ye Xiu was prompt with his decisions. Although Howling Heights pounced on him fiercely, the target was quickly protected. No matter how fiercely they fought, they wouldn’t be able to kill their target. As the two sides fought, Ye Xiu finally noticed Hazy Scene. That attack was perfectly timed. If it was on purpose, then no matter if it was his mechanics or his awareness, this player was very skilled. Any player could see that.

"Who is he?" Ye Xiu asked Thousand Falling Leaves. He was using a Cleric, so he often stood with Thousand Falling Leaves, who was also a Cleric.

"Who?" Thousand Falling Leaves didn’t know who Ye Xiu was talking about.

"That Elementalist, Hazy Scene." Ye Xiu said.

"No idea. I don’t recognize him." Thousand Falling Leaves said.

"He’s quite skilled." After Ye Xiu noticed him, he could tell that he was an expert. That previous attack wasn’t a coincidence.

"He is." Ocean Ahead walked over and commented. Players of the same class liked to compare themselves to one another. Ocean Ahead had been comparing himself with Hazy Scene ever since he started noticing him. He was quite surprised because this person wasn’t an ordinary expert.

While Ye Xiu and the others were observing him, Zhao Yuzhe was constantly searching. In the end, he finally found Enlightened Lord.

He really is still here!

Zhao Yuzhe was delighted. West Riding Wind thought his attack was to help him win this battle for the boss, but in reality, Zhao Yuzhe wanted to injure the enemy’s core in order to lure Enlightened Lord out. Now that he finally found his target, he tossed the boss aside and directly went after Enlightened Lord.

West Riding Wind wasn’t ready for such a sudden change in target. Although the two sides didn’t communicate, he always sent out players to assist him. It was a crucial moment for the boss right now, but Hazy Scene was suddenly going somewhere else…..

West Riding Wind turned around and saw Enlightened Lord.

He’s still trying to go after the leader? West Riding Wind thought about it. That was good too. If they could get rid of the leader, their victory would be that much easier.

As a result, while he continued to have his players cut off Heavenly Justice from the boss, he also sent out a portion of his players to assist Zhao Yuzhe’s attack.

"He’s coming!" Ocean Ahead cried out, when he saw Hazy Scene charging over.

He’s charging over!

These words were rarely used to describe an Elementalist!

"He’s coming for you, God!" Thousand Falling Leaves shouted.

"Protect me." Ye Xiu said.

This was very normal for a Cleric, but it felt weird for Ocean Ahead and Thousand Falling Leaves, hearing it come out of Ye Xiu’s mouth…..

Thinking was one thing, but they still did what they had to do.

Ocean Ahead waved his staff and cast a Fire Wall towards Hazy Scene to push him back.

Hazy Scene flickered and warped through the Fire Wall with a Teleport. He waved his staff and returned a Fire Wall to push Ye Xiu and the others towards him. The other Howling Height players ignored the fire wall. They had Clerics. That little amount of damage was nothing.

With a Fire Wall coming at him, Ye Xiu had Enlightened Lord retreat as he continued to instruct the Knights on the other side.

"Pull it towards the trap zone!" Ye Xiu didn’t shout this order out and instead typed it into the team chat.

The Knights understood. They had prepared this set-up beforehand. The Knights checked the direction and pulled Gladiator Vitalivis over

The eyes of the Thieves, who had set up the traps, lit up. They had been waiting for this moment for a long time!

Chapter 702: Just This Guild?

"Don’t run!" Zhao Yuzhe shouted loudly, when he saw Enlightened Lord retreating.

Ye Xiu ignored him. He focused on instructing the Knights on dealing with the boss because the boss would soon enter the trap zone set up by their group’s Thieves.

Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene chased after Ye Xiu. Ocean Ahead noticed that this enemy Elementalist was very skilled and wanted to confirm it for himself. After sending players out to block any enemy support, the two Elementalists began fighting each other.

On the boss’s side, Gladiator Vitalivis was chasing after the taunting Heavenly Justice Knights. The Howling Height Knights followed after the gladiator liked idiots. No matter what they tried, they couldn’t get the boss’s attention. Helpless, they could only use their bodies to block the gladiator from advancing. The boss wouldn’t just lock onto their target and ignore everything else. When it needed to attack, it would attack. The Howling Height Knights stalled for time using their bodies as meat shields. The rest of their group charged over and tried to disrupt the enemy’s control over the boss’ aggro. Heavenly Justice was obviously trying their hardest to prevent that from happening.

Characters fell one after another. Equipment dropped all over the ground, but not many paid too much attention to these pieces of equipment. The wild boss was way more important than anything else right now. Any losses in the battle would be compensated by the guild, so no one complained.

Gladiator Vitalivis had difficulty advancing because of this Knight blockade. There were always Howling Height players in front of him risking their life to block its path. A huge number of players slowly moved forward in this way. Ahead of them was the trap zone. Heavenly Justice was well aware of it and tried their hardest to conceal it. Howling Heights didn’t notice it though. They continued to tussle with the boss until the first trap activated!

Bang!

A blaze exploded into a lotus flower: a fire trap. That wasn’t the only trap in the area. As soon as the first trap triggered, two other traps next to it also triggered. A sea of fire instantly engulfed any surrounding players.

The Heavenly Justice players wouldn’t take damage from the triggered traps. Gladiator Vitalivis was a powerful Level 70 wild boss. Let alone three traps, thirty traps were nothing to him. The Howling Height players suffered though. They were focusing on blocking the boss from reaching Heavenly Justice’s players and had no idea that there would be traps placed here.

The damage from three Fire Traps wouldn’t be enough to instantly kill anyone, but Heavenly Justice wasn’t just standing around, watching the flames burn. When the traps triggered, Heavenly Justice immediately barraged Howling Heights’ knights with AoE attacks, instantly killing numerous players.

"There are traps!" Howling Heights finally noticed them.

"Disarm them!" Someone shouted. Several characters rushed out from the troops and ran forward into the area of traps. Not long afterwards, a few traps had already been disarmed.

Thieves could place traps and disarm traps. In addition, Thieves were Howling Height’s specialty. The Alliance’s number one Thief player, Fang Rui, was a part of Team Wind Howl. Whether it was playing dirty or using Thieves, Howling Heights were the experts of it all.

At this moment, the Thief group skillfully disarmed numerous traps, making Heavenly Justice’s Thieves quite gloomy.

"Have people leave the group and trigger the traps!" Seeing how skillful Howling Heights was at disarming traps, Ye Xiu gave a ruthless order. Because he wasn’t familiar with the players in the group, it wasn’t good to pick out names for this kind of suicidal tactic. He simply passed it on to Thousand Falling Leaves and had her arrange it.

Don’t look at Thousand Falling Leaves as a girl. She was quite decisive. Without any delay, she gave the order in the group. The names didn’t matter. It was more important that the ones who undertook the task would be compensated.

The dirty Thieves immediately became brave after knowing that they would be compensated for their actions. Thousand Falling Leaves obviously couldn’t have them swarm out into the field and make a mess, so she picked out names and made arrangements. The first willing player from Heavenly Justice headed back to the battlefield. The Howling Height Thieves were still disarming traps, when suddenly "Bang!" Numerous traps triggered and exploded. All of the traps were AoE attacks. In an instant, poison, ice, and fire swallowed their group....

The Thieves from Howling Heights were all experts! No one questioned whether one of them had been careless. They guessed that Heavenly Justice had directly dispatched players to trigger the traps.

In an instant, all of the Thieves knew that their situation wasn’t looking up. They weren’t tanky classes in the first place. After being caught up in the explosion of several traps, their health bars had drastically fallen. Heavenly Justice had naturally made arrangements beforehand. Heavenly Justice’s executioners launched their attacks and wiped out the Howling Height Thieves.

The boss wasn’t affected in any way. Heavenly Justice’s Knights were heavily protected. They didn’t need to come any closer to the traps either. For now, Howling Heights had no way of disrupting them. Many of their troops were supporting Zhao Yuzhe and coordinating with him. And now, when they needed him the most, instead of helping them stop Heavenly Justice from killing the boss, he just had to go over and kill the other side’s leader.

There was nothing wrong with this type of strategy, but they had been trying for a long time now, yet the enemy leader wasn’t under any pressure. It was hard to avoid people from criticizing it.

Howling Height’s Thief group didn’t dare to move forward again. If they did, the other side would launch suicide attacks again. It was pointless to force their way through the traps.

"The boss is still advancing." Howling Heights didn’t have any choice left. In the end, instead of blocking the boss from advancing, they would let the boss move through the traps before trying to snatch the boss back.

"Watch their Thieves carefully!" As the guild leader, West Riding Wind couldn’t only give orders. He had to survey the entire battlefield. Right now, their forces were split into two sections. One side was fighting with Zhao Yuzhe and trying to kill the enemy leader, while the other side was trying to block the boss, but neither side was going well.

If neither side was working, why not try focusing on one side?

West Riding Wind decided to concentrate their forces towards one side, but which one? It was too easy to choose. He couldn’t order Zhao Yuzhe to do anything and since Zhao Yuzhe refused to give up, wasn’t that the only side he could choose?

He obviously wouldn’t shout this order for everyone to hear. West Riding Wind gave the order in the team chat. Howling Heights quickly shifted their attention and began coordinating with Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene.

Ocean Ahead was attempting to measure Zhao Yuzhe’s skill, but in such a chaotic battle, who would give them a peaceful environment to fight in? As they fired spells at each other, their respective allies also rushed forward. A chaotic battle wasn’t a bunch of one versus one fights taking place simultaneously. Just attack wherever there was an opportunity to. Who could care about all the other details?

In the midst of the chaotic battle, Zhao Yuzhe once again created an opening in Heavenly Justice’s formation. Ocean Ahead’s attacks didn’t seem to be stopping him, which made Ocean Ahead very shocked. Not being able to beat God Ye Qiu was whatever, but where did this guy come out from?

"Who are you?" Ocean Ahead couldn’t help but ask.

Zhao Yuzhe was slightly surprised. He was so confident that he had forgotten about his circumstances. He thought that after being awarded the title of Best Rookie this season, everyone would recognize him. Now that he was asked this question, he suddenly realized: he was in the game, using an alternate account. His enemies didn’t know who he was.

However, this question also confirmed that his skill level far exceeded that of a normal player. Of course, it would be surprising to see someone with such skills in the game. Zhao Yuzhe had no intention of keeping a low profile. He had been very happy after receiving the award. There were also no matches to be played during their vacation period, which was why he had gone to the game to show off in the first place. Now that someone had noticed his existence, he suddenly became even more prideful.

"Zhao Yuzhe." After saying this name, Zhao Yuzhe mercilessly returned a spell at his opponent.

Zhao Yuzhe!

Ocean Ahead was surprised, when he heard this name. He wasn’t too surprised now that he was having trouble against him.

This season’s Best Rookie!

Even though it couldn’t compare to something like the MVP title, since it was restricted to only pro players in their first year of their career, being called the Best Rookie proved that he was an outstanding talent.

Ocean Ahead adjusted his position. He didn’t dare to underestimate any pro player, let alone one with such an impressive award.

"Best Rookie, Zhao Yuzhe???"

When this name came out, Ocean Ahead wasn’t the only one who heard it. Because he was an Elementalist, he was more familiar with pro Elementalist players, so he immediately recalled this name. The other players took a bit longer, but they quickly realized who was in front of them.

Best Rookie!

Even though he was still a rookie, he still won this award. He had already garnered quite a bit of attention during the season. Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t a new name. Even more people remembered it after he won the award. Now that Heavenly Justice’s players finally realized who it was, they were slightly stunned from astonishment.

Not bad. Not bad at all.

Zhao Yuzhe was very satisfied by the shock that his name brought to the other players. West Riding Wind was crafty. He knew that when Zhao Yuzhe shouted out his name, Heavenly Justice would certainly pause for a very short moment.

"Charge charge charge charge charge!!"

How could he let this opportunity slide? That instant, West Riding Wind gave a loud roar. The Howling Heights players all charged forward and broke apart Heavenly Justice’s formation. Enlightened Lord, who was suspected to be God Ye Qiu, wasn’t he standing right there?

"Retreat!" Ye Xiu also gave the order. Heavenly Justice quickly pulled back. When all of the Heavenly Justice players gathered together, West Riding Wind suddenly felt like something wasn’t right.

Four guild alliance! Why is there only Heavenly Justice? Where are the other three guilds???

"Relay!" Ye Xiu typed out.

"KILL!!!"

The cries of countless players echoed out. Conquering Clouds suddenly popped out from the incline. With Conquering Clouds behind and Heavenly Justice in front, Howling Heights had been successfully flanked.

"F*ck! This stupid place!!" West Riding Wind was furious! Dolaki Stadium’s terrain allowed the other side to set up an ambush, and he hadn’t noticed it at all.

Chapter 703: Support

Heavenly Justice had already started falling apart from their attacks, when Conquering Cloud suddenly rushed out and disrupted the balance of the battlefield. They were like the Great Wall. They suddenly popped up from the incline and blocked the way. Heavenly Justice knew about them beforehand and calmly left the battlefield.

Zhao Yuzhe saw that his target was running away and attacked with a flurry of spells in anger. West Riding Wind didn’t care about any of that. Heavenly Justice can run however they liked to, but don’t bring the boss with you!

Yes, Conquering Clouds was standing between Howling Heights and Heavenly Justice, but how could Howling Heights just let Heavenly Justice go so easily? Of course not. However, both sides had been cut off. The side going after the boss was also being blocked by Conquering Cloud’s sudden appearance.

The few players still near Gladiator Vitalivis were scattered around and surrounded by enemy troops. Before they could do anything, the enemy killed them off. West Riding Wind saw Heavenly Justice’s Knights continue Provoking the boss, leading the Gladiator farther and farther away. And them? They could only watch helplessly. How could they break through the carefully prepared defense set up by Conquering Clouds so easily? Even with Zhao Yuzhe, it wouldn’t be possible to do it so quickly. Zhao Yuzhe was starting to lose his patience too. He was randomly firing off attacks to vent his anger, making it impossible for West Riding Wind to coordinate with him. Afterwards, Hazy Scene suddenly disappeared.

Where’d he go?

For a moment, West Riding Wind really couldn’t find him with so many people out there. He didn’t have time to worry about him though. Gladiator Vitalivis had completely escaped from their attack range. As time went on, their aggro on the boss would slowly decrease. Heavenly Justice would then be able to easily take the boss for themselves.

West Riding Wind was becoming anxious. He wasn’t in the mood to waste time fighting with Conquering Clouds. He looked closely at the direction Heavenly Justice was heading towards and immediately ordered his troops to pretend to retreat. They would switch directions and cut them off. He wasn’t willing to lose the boss just like this! It hadn’t been easy winning against Tyrannical Ambition and Misty Castle.

Tyrannical Ambition?

Misty Castle?

He suddenly thought of these two guilds. West Riding Wind realized that he couldn’t ignore these two guilds either! These two guilds hadn’t given up yet. After Howling Heights snatched the boss from Tyrannical Ambition with the help of Zhao Yuzhe, Tyrannical Ambition had been counter attacking fiercely the entire time. Misty Castle glared at them like a tiger watching its prey as well. Howling Heights had been defending against them the entire time, but now?

Right when West Riding Wind was thinking about this, he saw Tyrannical Ambition and Misty Castle players enter his view. Heavenly Justice’s sudden interference disrupted the balance. Howling Heights had invested more and more resources into dealing with Heavenly Justice. With their defenses weakening, they finally couldn't defend against those two guilds any longer.

West Riding Wind obviously wasn’t so stupid as to think that they could win a 1v3 with just Zhao Yuzhe. It was just that since they had the boss and weren’t having trouble fighting it, he thought they would be able to last until the boss was killed. However, he didn’t think that Heavenly Justice, with God Ye Qiu leading them, would be so fearsome. After rushing into battle, they directly took the boss from the hands of the tank, secondary tank, and third tank, instantly turning the tables on Howling Heights.

The situation didn’t end up in a deadlock like West Riding Wind had expected. Instead, they had been led around by their noses. Under such circumstances, how could Howling Heights care about Tyrannical Ambition or Misty Castle?

Tyrannical Ambition’s and Misty Castle’s goal wasn’t to take down Howling Heights. They wanted the boss too. They had been delighted when Heavenly Justice suddenly interfered. They thought that they could use this opportunity to win the upperhand. However, they didn’t think that Heavenly Justice would be so quick. Heavenly Justice charged in and charged out with the boss without tussling with them.

The two guilds thought they could take advantage of the situation when they saw the boss being taken away. The two guilds also hastily chased after it, when they saw this scene as well. The other side had set up hidden troops to provide support, blocking any pursuers and allowing them to make a smooth escape.

These two guilds didn’t go and fight with Conquering Clouds. They reacted faster and immediately circled around to cut Heavenly Justice off. West Riding Wind saw these two guilds running in that direction and immediately knew what they were planning. How could he rest? Without any delay, he ordered everyone to also give chase, but they were in a tougher spot. Conquering Clouds was following them like a ghost, refusing to leave. If they turned around to fight, they would lose time. If they ignored them, wouldn’t they get wiped out? If they split forces, they wouldn’t be able to beat Tyrannical Ambition and Misty Castle. West Riding Wind also didn’t forget this time. Heavenly Justice and Conquering Clouds had appeared, but the other side still had two other guilds in their alliance. Where were Parade and Radiant?

West Riding Wind deeply felt the disruption towards the wild boss competition brought by this alliance. It seemed like, in the future, all of the guilds would need to dispatch more troops. If not, it would be way too difficult to fight against these four guilds.

However, that was all in the future. It was too late now. West Riding Wind finally decided to split his troops. A portion of his troops would fight with Conquering Clouds and the other portion would carefully pursue the boss. The other side still had two guilds that hadn’t shown their faces yet. West Riding Wind hoped that these two guilds would stop Tyrannical Ambition and Misty Castle.

Everything happened as West Riding Wind wanted it to.

When the portion of his troops circled around to cut off Heavenly Justice’s path, they saw Tyrannical Ambition being blocked by Radiant. Tyrannical Ambition was quite ferocious though. They seemed prepared to directly charge through Radiant’s defenses. Their elites were truly very powerful. Many players in Tyrannical Ambition were fearless men. It was all related to their team’s playstyle.

West Riding Wind obviously wouldn’t go and join the battle. He led his group to circle around them, when he saw Misty Castle and Parade fighting with each other. Misty Castle wasn’t as tough. They wanted to shrug off Parade, but Parade refused to let them go. West Riding Wind didn’t join them and was prepared to circle around them. But this time, he felt a bad premonition.

Circle circle circle!

Circle to where? Did he still know where Heavenly Justice was? West Riding Wind thought of the direction Heavenly Justice had headed off towards and his current location. His heart suddenly froze. Now he understood the intentions of these three guilds.

To block them?

Yes, but more importantly, it was to stall for time. The other side didn’t plan on simplifying matters and attacking the boss, while defending against their enemies. The other side was very careful and crafty. They repeatedly blocked their pursuers until no one knew where Heavenly Justice had led the boss to.

"F*ck! This d*mn terrain!!" West Riding Wind cursed again. This Dolaki Stadium had medium-size fields inside large fields and small fields inside medium-size fields, all separated from one another. There were also plenty of drains and moats everywhere. It currently looked like a perfectly straight path, but there might be holes and tunnels along the sides, leading to other places.

It was very easy to hide in this map. Heavenly Justice had a hundred players attacking the boss. Even though the target was big, Gladiator Vitalivis didn’t have much health left. Heavenly Justice now had control over the boss too. The boss would probably be dead very soon. If he sent out scouts to search for them, by the time they found them and sent their troops over, would the boss even be alive?

West Riding Wind was gloomy. He even had reports saying so and so guild had arrived, but West Riding Wind knew that no matter how many guilds arrived, it would be useless. If he received these reports, Heavenly Justice certainly received them too. If they avoided these guilds, they would certainly have enough time to take down the Gladiator.

Their boiled duck flew away in the end!

West Riding Wind had already lost all hope. He saw that his troops were still anxiously searching around. He didn’t want to ruin everyone’s mood, so he thought about how he should tell everyone their current pickle, when he suddenly received a message. West Riding Wind opened it listlessly. It was Hazy Scene, Zhao Yuzhe’s character. There were no words, just two numbers and a period: coordinates;

"Ah! Is that the boss’s location?" West Riding Wind replied.

"Hurry." Zhao Yuzhe replied.

West Riding Wind dind’t mind this harsh reply. His bad impression of Zhao Yuzhe immediately went away.

"We’ll be there immediately!" West Riding Wind replied. Afterwards, he gave a shout and told everyone to rush towards the coordinates sent by Zhao Yuzhe.

He really was an expert and a talent! West Riding Wind kept thinking to himself. Zhao Yuzhe was able to figure out the enemy’s location all by himself. Had he silently followed them at that time? West Riding Wind thought. He was happy that Wind Howl had such a talented player. The duck that flew away had just landed back in their hands.

At some place in Dolaki Stadium, Heavenly Justice finally escaped from danger and took control over the boss. They had more than enough players left to finish off the boss. Everyone’s morale was high. Right when they were about to take down the boss, the Elementalist Hazy Scene suddenly appeared in front of them.

"Zhao Yuzhe!!" Quite a few players shouted.

"Mm?" Ye Xiu asked. He had been busy commanding the troops earlier, so when Zhao Yuzhe shouted out his name, so he hadn’t noticed.

"Best Rookie!" Ocean Ahead said solemnly.

"Oh. From Wind Howl?" Ye Xiu said.

"Yes." Ocean Ahead was wary of Hazy Scene. The other side didn’t seem to have any intentions of charging at them. After all, he was just one person. Challenge everyone all by himself? What a joke! Even so, he wasn’t standing so far as if he had people backing him.

"That little kid’s like a ghost who refuses to leave. Kill him!" Ye Xiu said.

"You go!" Ocean Ahead was excited. Two experts were about to fight!

Enlightened Lord turned around to look at him: "Bro, I’m a Cleric right now! You go!"

"God, don’t joke with me!" Ocean Ahead cried.

Chapter 704: Unafraid Against Ten

Ocean Ahead and Zhao Yuzhe had fought against each other earlier. Although it wasn’t a true 1v1 and no winner was decided, Ocean Ahead had experienced Zhao Yuzhe’s skill for himself. The notion, which Ye Xiu helped him realize, that "pro players aren’t as simple as you think" was once again reinforced. God Ye Qiu suddenly called him to go and fight him. Ocean Ahead wasn’t confident at all though.

"What are you afraid of?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I don’t think I’m his opponent." Ocean Ahead admitted honestly.

"You have a hundred players backing you. What are you afraid of?" Ye Xiu was gloomy.

"Oh, that’s true!" Ocean Ahead suddenly understood. It turns out Ye Xiu wanted him to bully Zhao Yuzhe with numbers. He thought Ye Xiu wanted him to duel him!

"Hurry! If he’s here, Howling Heights will probably be here soon too. We’ll first stop him, while the rest continue to move the boss." Ye Xiu made a decision.

"Understood." Ocean Ahead didn’t hesitate this time and lead the attack. At the same time, he called out a few players in the chat to support him. Everyone else prepared to move the boss away.

One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten…...

Zhao Yuzhe’s eyes swept over the field and he saw ten players rushing towards him. The rest were preparing to move.

Ten players? Zhao Yuzhe sneered. This sneer was towards Enlightened Lord, who was among those ten players. A great God like Ye Qiu actually had to bring ten other players with him before daring to attack. What a joke!

Zhao Yuzhe looked down on this God, but he didn’t dare to treat these ten players lightly. He had fought against Ocean Ahead before, and he still had an impression of him. Although Ocean Ahead’s skill level wasn’t anything amazing, he still recognized that it exceeded a normal player’s skill. If it were just ten normal players, Zhao Yuzhe wouldn’t pay any attention to them. However, there was someone with some skill among these ten players, so Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t be careless. However, Zhao Yuzhe had no intentions of retreating. Long-ranged classes like Elementalists had an innate advantage when fighting against many. Kiting from afar allowed him to do just that.

The composition of the team being sent to deal with him was a bit troublesome. Zhao Yuzhe really wanted to show off. He wanted to see just how much ability a retired God and a somewhat skilled player had.

The ten players rushed forward. The first to attack was actually from Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene, showing his boundless confidence.

"Oh, how wonderful. He actually didn’t run." Ye Xiu was delighted.

Ocean Ahead had asked Ye Xiu how many players he should ask to come with him. At that time, Ye Xiu told him that if he brought too many, they would scare off the other side. If he brought too few, they wouldn’t be able to bully the other side with their numbers advantage. In the end, Ye Xiu told him that they should have around ten players. He was certain that Zhao Yuzhe wouldn’t retreat against this number.

Even though Ye Xiu hadn’t paid too much attention to Hazy Scene today, when Ocean Ahead told him that he was Zhao Yuzhe, Ye Xiu knew very well who this person was. He didn’t need to see it for himself to know the skill level of Howling Height’s Best Rookie.

Zhao Yuzhe took the initiative to attack. He cast a spell directly targeted at Enlightened Lord.

Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord was the only healer among these ten players. When fighting one against many, if the opponent’s side had a healer, it was common sense that there was no way of winning. In order to have a chance, killing the healer was crucial. Zhao Yuzhe was very courageous. He saw a healer among his opponents, yet he still dared to fight. He clearly didn’t care about anyone other than Enlightened Lord and Ocean Ahead. In his eyes, it was pretty much a 1v2.

Enlightened Lord sidestepped the spell. Among the ten player team, there were two long-ranged attackers, Ocean Ahead and a Launcher. When they saw Hazy Scene attacking, the two didn’t hesitate to return fire.

Hazy Scene dodged while retreating. No matter how confident Zhao Yuzhe was, he wasn’t so stupid as to let his Elementalist get surrounded by them. He had to keep his distance.

Retreat while casting! Pro players could utilize their hand speed to gain time. It was very scary for normal players. Hazy Scene directly cast a high-leveled spell: Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire.

"Scatter!" Ye Xiu had given the order earlier. He didn’t say it out loud, but rather typed it in the team chat.

The instant Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire rained down, the ten players scattered. In the end, only two players, who reacted slowly, were trapped inside. Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t happy at his result. It seemed like he had been too obvious, allowing the other side to see through his intentions. No matter the case, a retired God had plenty of experience. Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t fight so simply anymore.

Ye Xiu cast a heal-over-time spell, which healed health every three seconds for twelve seconds, on the two players who were trapped inside Heavenly Lightning’s effective area and then left them alone. He instructed the other eight to surround Hazy Scene.

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t think of using this opportunity to kill off those two trapped players. That sort of delay could put him in a dangerous situation. He wasn’t stupid. He needed a better opportunity. When fighting one against many, he had to keep his distance while dealing damage. He needed to be patient. Understanding the situation, Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t rash. Seeing the other side closing in, he chose to move backwards. At the same time, he noticed the other side moving the boss away and guessed the other side’s intentions. Zhao Yuzhe obviously wouldn’t let their plans go smoothly so easily. As he kited the enemy pursuers, he also planned on chasing after Heavenly Justice. His retreat direction would be in the same direction as Heavenly Justice.

"Attack him from all sides. Cover his back. Three swordsmen close in on him in a triangular formation. Don’t be in a hurry to chase after him. We have to restrict his movements." Ye Xiu instructed.

A method like mindlessly chasing after a character and attacking wouldn’t be effective against a pro player. Not only would their attacks not hit, they wouldn’t be able to disrupt the enemy’s goal either. If they blindly chased after the enemy, the enemy would just be leading them around by the nose, especially in a situation where they were fighting against one person with many. Blindly chasing after the target and attacking was a waste of their numbers advantage.

After being instructed, Ocean Ahead cast a Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire around Hazy Scene. Zhao Yuzhe saw it and gave another nod towards Ocean Ahead’s skill level. In front of him was a Berserker and two Blade Masters. The three didn’t stay close to each other. Instead, they spread out in a triangle formation as if they were planning on trapping him inside a net.

You want to stop me like this?

Zhao Yuzhe sneered again. He instantly saw through the other side’s intentions, but he didn’t care about these three characters. Even if these little characters were arranged in a solid formation, did they have the ability to keep him here?

Forcefully charge through them!

Zhao Yuzhe decided. Hazy Scene didn’t avoid them. Instead, he directly charged at the three swordsmen. As he ran, he used his quick hand speed to quickly cast low-leveled spells. These spells were almost instantaneous casts. Hazy Scene’s staff traveled in a circle, shooting three spells at each of the three targets. Hazy Scene rushed towards the Berserker following behind the Frostball he sent out.

The Berserker ignored the Frostball and met with him face to face. Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t surprised. The Berserker didn’t need to care about this tiny bit of damage, but did that Berserker really think that this Frostball was to open up a pathway for him?

The Berserker closed in on his target. He was about to use a skill, when he heard a bang and his character flew up into the air.

Raging Flames!

Zhao Yuzhe had used Frostball to hide his Raging Flames. The Berserker wasn’t prepared at all. He didn’t think that Hazy Scene’s attack would come out ahead of his. The Berserker was launched into the air and Hazy Scene sprinted under him. He also left an Elemental Power under him.

This was a feature of the Elementalist class. The spell covered a large area and had a long duration. During these three seconds, any character that was in Elemental Power’s range would stay in the air for longer. Zhao Yuzhe thought the Elemental Power he threw down was very well done, but before he could finish being happy, he heard an explosion from behind him. Zhao Yuzhe looked back and saw that the Elemental Power had been blown apart by the enemy Launcher.

A powerful knock-up skill like Elemental Power naturally had a lot of counterplay. After being thrown down, it could be broken apart in such a way.

The enemy side reacted so quickly, surprising Zhao Yuzhe. Before he could regain his composure, he suddenly felt something abnormal beside him. Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t turn to look in time, so he rolled to the side first. When he looked over, he saw a rectangular object at his former location.

Brick Throw!

This Brick came out of nowhere, giving Zhao Yuzhe a fright. Seeing where this Brick was coming from, it would have definitely been a back attack and induced a stun... if he were stunned, he would be surrounded. Even if he could escape, he would be in a sorry state.

Under Ye Qiu’s lead, the coordination between these guys was very tight.

Zhao Yuzhe thought that the Brick and the Launcher’s attack on the Elemental Power was all because of Ye Xiu.

He turned around to look for Enlightened Lord, when he saw sand coming towards him. Sand Toss!

Zhao Yuzhe deserved to be a pro player and the Best Rookie of the season. He didn’t use an unsophisticated method like looking away. While he was still in his roll animation, he rolled again to dodge the Sand Toss.

When he was about to get up, he saw the light around him start to dim. Someone had blocked his path in front, a Brawler! His two hands were extended to push down Hazy Scene.

Tyrannical Chain Punch!!

Zhao Yuzhe was from Team Wind Howl. Which class was Team Wind Howl’s best character? A dirty Thief was one, but the other was their team captain’s Brawler, Three Hits.

And the character who was just about to beat him down was a Brawler. If he were hit by Tyrannical Chain Punch, he would be pinned to the ground, giving them more than enough time for them to surround him.

He had to roll again! Zhao Yuzhe reacted incredibly fast. He rolled again and actually dodged the attack.

"Steamed Bun, don’t be in such a hurry."

Zhao Yuzhe heard someone say.

Chapter 705: So Many High-Leveled Skills

“Steamed Bun, don’t be in such a hurry.”

When Zhao Yuzhe heard this voice, he looked around, even while rolling. He quickly swept through the names on the surrounding enemies.

He was looking for that Steamed Bun. From what he just heard, this Steamed Bun played a crucial role in this fight. The person leading wanted him not to be in a hurry. Zhao Yuzhe needed to be wary of him. Hazy Scene had been forced to roll several times in a row without being able to get up to counterattack. He was in a dangerous situation, yet the other side unexpectedly didn’t immediately follow up with further attacks and instead was told to slow down. Knowing that there must be some sort of card up their sleeve, Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t help but be alarmed. He wanted to hurry and find that Steamed Bun, so he could prepare himself for whatever came next. But when he looked around at the ten enemies, there was no one named “Steamed Bun.”

Zhao Yuzhe was gloomy. He now knew that the Ye Qiu wasn’t calling out a character’s name. Which one was Steamed Bun?

Then, he heard a “Okay.” from in front of him.

It’s this Brawler?

Zhao Yuzhe had good hearing and instantly determined where the voice came from. The Brawler, who had just narrowly missed his Tyrannical Chain Punch, was Steamed Bun. After this Steamed Bun replied, he didn’t follow up.

Ye Qiu was telling him not to attack?

Zhao Yuzhe was surprised. This Brawler had forced him to roll continuously in order to survive. He had to admit that this Brawler wasn’t as weak as he had originally assumed him to be. Even though Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t a Brawler player, he wasn’t a stranger to it. After all, he was a member of Team Wind Howl. Team Wind Howl had the number one Thief, but the more famous character was their team captain, Lin Jingyan’s character: Three Hits.

Although Lin Jingyan was a declining figure, Three Hits was genuinely the number one Brawler character in the Alliance. Zhao Yuzhe clearly knew how powerful Three Hits was. Having been trained in this kind of team environment, he naturally took more notice on the habits of Brawler players. And this “Steamed Bun” had actually been instructed to not follow up despite forcing him into an ugly situation? What did he have planned?

Pro players were on a relatively higher level and thought more when playing. Zhao Yuzhe was bewildered and paid full attention to this person in front of him. Then, he saw this Brawler suddenly extend his hands.

Strangle!

Zhao Yuzhe immediately had Hazy Scene retreat. When fighting one versus many, an attack with CC was far more terrifying than a high damage attack. He was also worried about any high-leveled skills from his opponents. He could have dodged the attack with just a single step backwards, but he retreated three steps back and continued to watch this Brawler’s moves carefully.

The Brawler raised his hands and threw a Brick. Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene tilted his head and dodged it.

These two attacks…...

Zhao Yuzhe pondered. Truthfully, he couldn’t see anything strange about these two attacks, which made him feel even more uneasy. He subconsciously looked around and saw a Battle Mage behind him raise his spear.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

This Battle Mage’s equipment wasn’t anything good, but this Dragon Breaks the Ranks didn’t feel weak. Elementalists didn’t have any skills that could directly face such a high-priority move like Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Teleport!

At the crucial moment, Zhao Yuzhe teleported. Dragon Breaks the Ranks passed by, but Hazy Scene was already gone. Zhao Yuzhe was able to cast the spell in time, but was left frightened and unsettled in his heart.

Difficult. Really difficult.

His usage of Teleport hadn’t been graceful at all. He had used it to run away. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t have time to analyze how he had been forced into such a state when he heard a loud sound from behind him. Flames engulfed his screen.

How!

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t even have time to check his surroundings after teleporting, when the explosion arrived. No, to put it more accurately, this explosion had arrived the moment Hazy Scene arrived, not giving him any chance to dodge. He had walked into a trap.

The fiery light from the explosion still hadn’t faded, but Zhao Yuzhe was a pro player, after all. He still had the senses he should have. Hazy Scene had been in the center of the explosion. The shockwaves from the explosion sent him into the air. Zhao Yuzhe hastily adjusted his view. He knew that being in the air would give the enemy many opportunities. Once he landed, he might drop into the middle of the enemy’s encirclement.

The other side had guessed correctly as to where he would choose to teleport to. Was this a coincidence?

Zhao Yuzhe remembered that God Ye Qiu was there. He understood that it was something that could be done with the experience he possessed. His teleport had been done in haste. He simply teleported, wherever it was convenient to. It wasn’t something difficult to guess.

Zhao Yuzhe adjusted his viewpoint in a bit of a fluster, while quickly activating Mobile Cast. He felt like the following situation wouldn’t be easy. He might not have time to stop and cast any spells, so he decided to activate Mobile Cast, which would allow him to move and cast spells with greater ease.

Fire Wall.

During his brief duration in the air, Zhao Yuzhe pushed his hand speed to the limit. When Hazy Scene landed, he finished his spell. The moment he landed on the ground and got up, he raised his staff and a Fire Wall rose up.

Fire Wall didn’t hit any of the enemies. That wasn’t why he used the spell, nor was it to block them. The other side had greater numbers. The bit of damage dealt by the Fire Wall was insignificant to them. Zhao Yuzhe simply wanted to block the other side’s line of sight, so that they wouldn’t be able to see his position. For normal players, such a reason might sound pointless, but in a high level battle, it might be enough to turn around the situation.

Zhao Yuzhe became cautious. He clearly didn’t dare underestimate those ten enemies anymore. He wanted to win some time, so he could adjust his attitude and start the battle again with a new mindset.

The moment the Fire Wall rose up, flames spouted out from near Hazy Scene. Dark clouds started to condense above him. Lightning flashed. In the blink of an eye, the lightning above began to weave between the fire spouting from the ground.

Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire was more complicated to execute than Fire Wall and it naturally had a longer cast time. If the Heavenly Lightning rained down at the same time that Hazy Scene erected a Fire Wall, there was only one possibility: the other side had predicted where he would land and started casting the spell earlier. Zhao Yuzhe had been trying to erect a Fire Wall to cover himself. How could he have known the other side had already placed a Heavenly Lightning at his landing position?

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t appear to be too flustered after having been caught though. He was an Elementalist, so he was naturally very familiar with Elementalist skills. Normal players thought that standing still would allow them to take less damage than if they rushed out of the spell’s range, but in the pro scene, the damage taken wasn’t their only concern. There were many other things they had to consider.

For example, if Zhao Yuzhe wanted to take less damage from Heavenly Lightning and stood still, waiting for the spell duration to end, he might be surrounded by his enemies. The small amount of extra health he earned from standing still wouldn’t be worth it. As a result, he obviously wouldn’t make such a decision. The instant he discovered that Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire was being formed, Hazy Scene never stopped moving. Zhao Yuzhe knew how to deal with this attack and prepared to break out of the spell’s range. As soon as he stepped forward, he immediately realized that this Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire wasn’t being automatically controlled by the system, but rather being controlled by the caster.

Controlling the spell by hand would naturally cause the spell to be more focused on the target, but the effectiveness depended on the caster’s skill level. Zhao Yuzhe had only taken two steps and he was already feeling truly bitter. The other side’s control over Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire couldn’t be considered amazing, but it was better than the system’s automatic control. The advantages of controlling the spell by hand could be seen. Zhao Yuzhe was still confident in breaking out of the spell’s range before the duration ended, but it would definitely take longer than he had originally anticipated.

I need to break through forcefully!

With no other alternative, he could only go with the heroic option and charge forward, while ignoring any damage taken. He figured out which direction he wanted to move towards and instead of dodging, he directly charged through the spell range.

Success!

The area ahead was vast and open. Hazy Scene finally made it out from the flashes of lightning and fire. Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire still hadn’t ended yet. Zhao Yuzhe turned around to look at the surroundings, when he saw his surroundings turn red like blood. This time, the Berserker skill Crimson Storm was waiting for him.

Without a doubt, the other side must have prepared this ambush ahead of time. A high-level skill like Crimson Storm had a long start-up animation. Hazy Scene had just broken through Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. It was impossible for the Berserker to have executed the skill in an instant, but in his current situation, Crimson Storm was waiting for him. The Berserker’s greatsword crashed into the ground. No matter how capable Zhao Yuzhe was, this time, he couldn’t avoid it.

At the same time, two brilliant sword lights came flying at him. The two Blade Masters directly executed Formless Phantom Blades on his two sides. The Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire behind him still hadn’t ended yet. The caster had concentrated the attacks behind him as if forming a wall.

Hit!

In this situation, even Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t escape from being hit. The two Formless Phantom Blades intertwined around him. Up above, a thick pillar of light descended from the skies, enveloping Hazy Scene. Launcher high-leveled skill: Satellite Beam.

Zhao Yuzhe finally fell into despair. So many high-leveled skills against one person. Unable to escape, he could only cast some spells to throw some resistance towards his enemies. When he turned around to find a target, he saw that Enlightened Lord and that Steamed Bun standing on the side idly, watching the spectacle. At the same time, Enlightened Lord was instructing him: “That Tyrannical Chain Punch from before was too rushed. Go carefully watch the video of Lin Jingyan that I sent you last time and see how he uses it compared to how you use it just now.”

F*ck! Zhao Yuzhe listened. Whatever spells Hazy Scene was about to cast went up in smoke.

Chapter 706: Come Again

The blow was too heavy!

Zhao Yuzhe thought the words "Steamed Bun, don’t be so rushed" was some sort of tactic aimed against him. As a result, he became wary of Steamed Bun and stepped back an extra two times to dodge a low-leveled skill like Strangle. In return, because of these three steps, he ended up placing himself in a position that was within the range of that Battle Mage’s spear.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Zhao Yuzhe was certain that if he hadn’t dodged this attack, he would have ended up in an even more miserable state than he was in now. However, because he dodged it, he stepped into a path fraught with high-leveled attacks.

Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire, Crimson Storm, and two Formless Phantom Blades.

Elementalists stacked Intelligence, so their Magic Resistance was decent at best. However, of these four high-leveled attacks, only Heavenly Lightning dealt magic damage. The other three purely dealt physical damage. Elementalists had low health and weak defense. After taking so many high level skills, he was practically at death’s door.

This was just the damage dealt to his character. Zhao Yuzhe had taken a heavy blow to his mental state too. Those words "Steamed Bun, don’t be so rushed" brought a calamity upon him and now he knew that Ye Qiu was just commenting on Steamed Bun’s usage of Tyrannical Chain Punch.

Zhao Yuzhe finally realized that, in the eyes of his opponents, he wasn’t as intimidating as he thought he was. He thought that defeating ten players by himself was something within his capabilities, so he dared to challenge them directly, but it turned out that ten players was more than enough to deal with him. God Ye Qiu had only cast two heals so far and his Hazy Scene was already almost dead. God Ye Qiu even had the time to stand off to the side and give Steamed Bun pointers! Ye Qiu didn’t even seem to be looking in his direction at all.

Zhao Yuzhe was furious!

He felt like he shouldn’t be receiving this kind of disdain. Wasn’t the reason he fell into this tragic situation because of those sudden words? Wasn’t it because he misunderstood those words that he retreated three steps instead of one? If he hadn’t taken those three steps, he wouldn’t have been forced to teleport away from that Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Everything was because he misunderstood those very words!

Zhao Yuzhe was upset. He refused to admit defeat in such a way. Although he didn’t have much health left, nor could he see any chance of victory, he still had to prove his strength. He had to make these guys understand that their reason for winning wasn’t because he wasn’t good enough, but because they got lucky.

These four attacks failed to kill Hazy Scene. He still had a chance!

Zhao Yuzhe made his decision. His right hand firmly grasped his mouse, and he turned to look at the Brawler and Enlightened Lord. He would win back his pride through these two players, but at this moment, Zhao Yuzhe suddenly felt something coming from behind him. Before he could turn around to look, Hazy Scene suddenly flew out as if he were gliding across the ground.

He obviously wasn’t making these movements. Zhao Yuzhe saw the magic undulations coiling around his Hazy Scene. He hastily turned his viewpoint to see that the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire was slowly beginning to fade away. In the middle, the figure of a person could be seen. However, the figure was growing smaller and smaller because his Hazy Scene was being pushed farther and farther away.

This figure had a spear with magic undulations shooting towards Hazy Scene’s direction.

Battle Mage, Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.

After four high-leveled skills, a fifth one finally came.

Zhao Yuzhe hadn’t expected it at all. Relying on the visual effects from other skills to hide was originally what he excelled at, and now he had fallen for such a ploy.

Bang!!

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky crashed into Hazy Scene. This skill was a two-stage attack. The first attack dealt physical damage and the following explosion would deal magic damage. After taking the brunt of four high-leveled skills, Hazy Scene didn’t have the health to survive this Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.

"F*CK!" Zhao Yuzhe slammed his keyboard, but that couldn’t stop his screen from turning gray. From his ghost’s viewpoint, Zhao Yuzhe saw those guys glance at his corpse. None of them took much interest in it. On the other hand, they were much more interested in the items that had dropped from his corpse. After picking up the dropped items, they immediately left without staying for even another second.

Contempt!

They were absolutely treating him with scorn! Did those guys actually think they beat him so easily by chaining five high-leveled skills?

"Stop! Don’t leave!" Zhao Yuzhe shouted. However, ghosts couldn’t speak. No matter how loud he shouted, he couldn’t explain to those guys about this misunderstanding.

Besides, telling them about the misunderstanding with his mouth? It was as if he were looking for some sort of excuse. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t want to do that. He needed to prove it with actions and not words.

Revive!

Zhao Yuzhe moved his cursor to click on the revive back at the city option. Right when he was about to click on it, he suddenly thought of messaging West Riding Wind. Howling Heights should be here soon. If he had the Clerics revive him, he would save a lot of time. By the time he revived back at the city and traveled back here, the battle might already be over. Zhao Yuzhe also didn’t know which city this character had set its revival point to because he didn’t even think he would die, so he had never checked his character info page for such information.

He didn’t click on the option and moved his cursor away.

Zhao Yuzhe hesitated. Reviving here naturally saved a lot of effort. but when West Riding Wind arrived and saw his corpse, wouldn’t that be too embarrassing? But then again if he revived back at the city, he wouldn’t be able to cover up his death anyways. Hazy Scene’s red stats were proof. In this instant, Zhao Yuzhe hated how Glory reduced experience and stats upon death.

In any case, he wouldn’t be able to hide it, so he made his decision and waited.

West Riding Wind led his troops over to the coordinates. On the way over, he told everyone how Zhao Yuzhe was truly skilled. They would need to rely on him in the future.

When they got near the area, West Riding Wind didn’t see Heavenly Justice fighting the boss like he had imagined. West Riding Wind had his second thoughts, when one of his players shouted: "Hazy Scene!"

"Where?" Everyone asked. Finally, they saw a corpse on the ground.

"Zhao Yuzhe died!" Someone cried out in astonishment. At this moment, none of them said the character’s name. They all said the name Zhao Yuzhe. It wasn’t strange to see a character dead, but Zhao Yuzhe’s character dying was something worth being surprised over.

"Was he discovered..." West Riding Wind paid a silent tribute as he told a Cleric to revive him.

White light scattered and Hazy Scene stood up. West Riding Wind looked at his screen and opened his mouth. He wanted to say something, but he didn’t know what to say. Hazy Scene didn’t wait for him to speak though. After standing up, he quickly rushed in a certain direction. The Clerics were still hastily healing him back to full health, but he didn't care. West Riding Wind didn’t dare to be slow and immediately told everyone to follow him.

Zhao Yuzhe knew his knowledge was outdated. No signs of Heavenly Justice fighting the boss could be seen in the surrounding areas either. Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t find them, but he didn’t say a word. He continued to move forward. West Riding Wind thought he knew what he was doing and had his troops follow him closely until the system announced: Congratulations Heavenly Justice for killing Gladiator Vitalivis.

The players from Howling Heights were instantly dumbfounded. Not just them, but when this announcement came out, all of the other guilds in Dolaki Stadium were stunned. Because this announcement told them: the boss battle at Dolaki Stadium had come to an end.

The guilds often fought over bosses, so they wouldn’t continue fighting just for this boss. The previous second, they were locked in an intense battle with the other guilds. The next second, the announcement came out and everyone immediately put their weapons away, clearing the field of any pieces of dropped equipment.

The only person who didn’t stop was Zhao Yuzhe. It was as if he hadn’t see that announcement. His Hazy Scene continued to search the stadium. He clearly didn’t have any interest in the boss. He only had one thought on his mind: those guys needed to know that his death was a one time mishap.

"Little Zhao, the boss has already died." West Riding Wind thought he didn’t see the system announcement, so he immediately gave him a reminder.

Zhao Yuzhe ignored it. After passing over a wall, he finally saw Heavenly Justice, who was happily laughing and cheering.

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t have any regrets towards not finding the boss just a bit sooner. He only felt gratified that he managed to find them.

"Look, look. It’s that guy." At this moment, Heavenly Justice noticed Hazy Scene standing on the stone wall as if blocking their path.

The laughter gradually died down. Everyone turned their heads to look at him in confusion.

Ye Xiu also saw him. He had Enlightened Lord walk over until he wasn’t too far away and greeted: "Little Zhao! The boss is already dead. Did you not see the announcement? Try again next time!"

"I’m not here to look for the boss." Zhao Yuzhe said.

"Hm?"

"I’m here to challenge you guys. I want to fight against the same ten." Zhao Yuzhe shouted.

"Oh." Ye Xiu understood what Zhao Yuzhe was thinking and grinned: "It seems like you’re not happy about how you died?"

"Yes. Let’s go again!" Zhao Yuzhe said.

"Another ten?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Correct."

"That number’s too small. How about a hundred instead?" Ye Xiu asked.

Chapter 707: Unrelated Boss

How about a hundred?

Such a shocking reply left Zhao Yuzhe speechless. Let alone a hundred, he didn’t even feel confident fighting ten. During the period of time while he had been dead, revived, and all throughout his pursuit of Heavenly Justice, Zhao Yuzhe had been thinking about the previous fight. Had he really died from those consecutive high-leveled skills because of the unnecessary three steps that he had used to dodge Strangle?

If he hadn’t stepped back three times and instead only stepped back once, what would the outcome have been?

If Dragon Breaks the Ranks still went through, it would just be a difference of two footsteps. If he hadn’t used Teleport, would he have been able to escape from that high-leveled skill’s area of effect?

He wasn’t sure. The speed of Dragon Breaks the Ranks depended on the character’s stats. Zhao Yuzhe also understood another point: perhaps the chain of high-leveled attacks had been arranged because he took three steps backwards. If he had only stepped back once, perhaps the chain of high-leveled attacks would have been set up differently.

If that were the case, the result would have been the same. Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t sure though because there were no ifs.

Zhao Yuzhe wanted to challenge them again because of this uncertainty, but at the same time, he got rid of his initial nonchalant attitude. He decided that he would put in his all against them starting from the very beginning. However, the other side proposed a 1v100. Was that a joke?

"Are you…... joking?" Zhao Yuzhe asked in the end. He thought about it. He didn’t think it was an embarrassing question. Someone who dared to challenge a hundred players alone was someone who didn’t play Glory!　

"Oh, if you don’t dare to, then it’s just a joke! If you do, then it’s not a joke. We can start right away." Ye Xiu said.

"It’s not that I don’t dare, but don’t you think that kind of victory is pointless?" Zhao Yuzhe said.　

"Of course it’s not pointless! Your equipment’s pretty good...." Ye Xiu said.

Zhao Yuzhe wanted to cough up blood. That guy really is here to snatch bosses! Does he think I’m some sort of boss? Since he wanted an account, West Riding Wind obviously wouldn’t be stingy. His set of equipment was top of the line. Everything from top to bottom was Orange. For a Club guild like Howling Heights, getting a character with a full set of Orange equipment wasn’t difficult. The quality of equipment that he dropped really would like those dropped from a boss from one perspective. The value of his equipment was worth more than a dungeon boss too! Dungeon bosses didn’t have a one hundred percent chance of dropping Orange equipment. On the other hand, his Hazy Scene had a full set of Orange equipment! If any of them dropped, it would definitely be Orange!

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t know how to reply. He wanted to challenge them, but the other side was thinking about the issue in a completely different manner than he was. Before, the other side wanted the boss’s material. Now, seeing him, they wanted his equipment! In the end, they didn’t care about his strength as Best Rookie!

While the two sides went back and forth, West Riding Wind and Howling Height’s troops caught up to him. Zhao Yuzhe received his messages, but didn’t reply to them. Zhao Yuzhe seemed to be looking around still, allowing West Riding Wind to more or less guess his intentions. This Best Rookie died and wasn’t happy, so he came to get revenge!

West Riding Wind sighed. Pro players really did care more about winning and losing to an opponent than losing equipment.

Ah, young people are so impulsive. You’re chasing after them, but they have a entire group. How are you going to fight all of them? West Riding Wind thought. Zhao Yuzhe was a part of Team Wind Howl though. How could he not be concerned? Thus, he immediately brought everyone with him and chased after Zhao Yuzhe. From the looks of it, he really had gone and challenged Heavenly Justice. That Enlightened Lord, who was supposedly God Ye Qiu, was standing in front of Hazy Scene.

Were they going to fight?

West Riding Wind sized up Heavenly Justice’s troops. Their numbers were about the same. In terms of equipment though, the elite group of Howling Heights held the advantage. There was no boss to fight, so it would only be a PvP. Truthfully, no Club guild wanted their elite troops to clash. However, a pro player from their team had rushed forward to the front lines, so he couldn’t just sit around and watch. Even if he didn’t order anything, the other players from Howling Heights might not be able to stand still. They were still loyal fans of the team. Zhao Yuzhe winning the Best Rookie Award made him a very popular player among the fans of Howling Heights.

"Little Zhao, what do you plan on doing?" West Riding Wind calculated, while asking Zhao Yuzhe his intentions.　

"The materials dropped by the wild boss have already fallen into their hands. Guild leader, have you never thought of taking those materials back from their bodies and making up for our losses?" Zhao Yuzhe suddenly said. A rookie may be a rookie, but he wasn’t stupid. He wanted to prove his strength, but he didn’t care about what type of environment he had to prove it in. The other side would have had a numbers advantage, treating him like a wild boss. Trying to prove his strength in that kind of situation was a bit too difficult. Fortunately, his guild had just arrived. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t mind starting a huge battle. In any case, the person who would stand out the most would still be him.

Zhao Yuzhe was a pro player, yet he wanted to show off his strength in this type of environment. West Riding Wind felt a bit disdainful towards his intentions, but even though he couldn’t hear absolute certainty in victory from Zhao Yuzhe’s words, he could at least tell that Zhao Yuzhe felt like they had enough players on their side to win.

What could West Riding Wind say? Even if Zhao Yuzhe hadn’t given such a poor reason, if he had just said "Let’s fight", West Riding Wind still couldn’t refuse such a demand. Fighting alongside a pro player was something very meaningful to team fans. If West Riding Wind told everyone to leave and let him play on his own, he reckoned that quite a few players would definitely have objections. If news of that spread, even more players in the guild would be unhappy.

"Ha ha. That makes a lot of sense. If they took the drops by killing the boss, then we just need to kill them and take those drops back." West Riding Wind obviously wouldn’t pick out any flaws in that sort of thinking. He just went along with what Zhao Yuzhe said. It seemed like today he would need to accompany him. In the guild chat, quite a few players were already cheering. As expected, many of them were very excited to be able to play alongside Zhao Yuzhe. This could be seen ever since Zhao Yuzhe had logged onto Hazy Scene and was introduced to everyone.

"Hm? Your helpers finally arrived?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"You snatched away our boss. Did you really think that you could escape so easily?" West Riding Wind truly was a good person. He simply kept going with Zhao Yuzhe’s reasoning.

"It wouldn’t have been the first time and it won’t be the last either. If we keep doing this every time, wouldn’t you find that very annoying?" Ye Xiu said.　

Truth!

West Riding Wind sighed. How could he not understand that sort of reasoning? That was why competitions for wild bosses had unwritten rules set in place, because if everyone did this 74 times every week, everyone would be stuck in an endless war, day after day, year after year.

As a result, if no extremely disgusting behavior occurred in the fights for a wild boss, when the boss fell, everyone would instantly turn over a new leaf. The large guilds had fought countless times. They had pretty much seen everything there was to see, so doing anything extremely disgusting wasn’t easy. For example, they had pretty much already put aside everything that had happened today. West Riding Wind was currently cooperating with Zhao Yuzhe about a matter of the past! When he heard Ye Xiu’s reasoning, he felt a sort of connection with Ye Xiu. He had the heart to lead this troops over and stand alongside him.

Of course, he couldn’t actually do that. He just humphed coldly. In any case, they were going to fight. Saying anything more would be pointless because West Riding Wind knew the reasoning he gave was just pretense. Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t fighting because of this reason anyways, so why keep talking?　

Sparks were already flying between the two sides. At this moment, a bunch of people suddenly excitedly ran over to Heavenly Justice, asking: "What dropped? What dropped?

Guild Parade!

West Riding Wind saw the guilds tags on these guys. Before he could respond, a bunch of people thundered in from behind him. When he turned to look, it was Conquering Clouds.

Conquering Clouds was clearly very surprised at Howling Heights being there. They immediately halted their footsteps. The players crowded over and quickly crammed into the path that Howling Heights had come from.

Two other guilds had arrived so soon after. Radiant must not be too far then. The next second, Radiant arrived. The direction that they came in from didn’t block Howling Height’s path. Even though they saw Howling Heights there, they weren’t too surprised. The boss had just died. Howling Heights lost. Maybe they were cleaning the battlefield?

That was what would happen under normal circumstances, so no one paid too much attention to Howling Heights. Only Conquering Clouds was surprised for a bit before making their way forward. However, Howling Heights was blocking the opening in the wall. Conquering Clouds went over and kept saying "Excuse me, excuse me" as they pushed past.　

Parade’s guild leader, Martial Awareness, and Radiant’s guild leader, White Stream ran over and asked impatiently about the drops before seeing Conquering Clouds stuck over there. The two guilds suddenly jeered: "If you don’t hurry up and come, you won’t get your share."

"Everyone, wait! It’s not over yet!" Ye Xiu finally said.

"What?"

"Howling Heights has expressed their intent on not letting us go so easily." Ye Xiu said.

"Ah!" Conquering Clouds was still trying to squeeze through Howling Heights. Parade and Radiant started hollering even louder.

This was their difference with Heavenly Justice. Even though they were relatively small, they were still Club guilds. Heavenly Justice had only taken its first step into the professional scene. They still didn’t have a proper perspective of all the bosses. Howling Heights lost the boss and wanted to fight for revenge. They thought it was very normal, so they weren’t surprised or anything. They prepared themselves for a battle. On the other hand, the other three Club guilds heard Ye xiu’s words and suddenly went into an uproar. That wasn’t rational at all! Why did Howling Heights still want to fight? What’s wrong with them? Their gossipping spirits started to come out of hiding though…..

"Everyone, let’s not make such a fuss." Ye Xiu spoke again, "This has nothing to do with the wild boss. The real reason is that their Best Rookie was bullied by us."

He must be one of my long lost relatives! West Riding Wind was about to cry . It’s like God Ye Qiu can see through me! Why do his words always move me so deeply?

Chapter 708: Angel Wings

Best Rookie?　

No one in Conquering Clouds, Parade, and Radiant had heard Zhao Yuzhe’s self-introduction earlier, so when they heard his name, they were obviously quite surprised.

"Zhao Yuzhe? Where? Where?" Quite a few people shouted. Even though they weren’t fans of Team Wind Howl, award-winning players always attracted a lot of attention. Very few fans of Glory wouldn’t know their names.

Zhao Yuzhe liked the attention, but his current circumstances just weren’t quite right. He was still thinking about the words Ye Xiu had just said.

Bullied!

That was his image in the eyes of those guys? What had he become? Being bullied and being defeated were two completely different concepts!

He was a magnificent pro player, the Best Rookie of the season! Him, bullied?

Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t tolerate Ye Xiu’s wording, so he was unable to appreciate the attention from the surrounding players at the moment, but how was he supposed to explain it? He couldn’t think of any excuse to use as a cover. In the end, he would still need to fight to prove his strength and let everyone know that he definitely hadn’t been bullied.　

After West Riding Wind sighed at how God Ye Qiu could see through everything, he realized that, after those words were said, even if their guild was at an absolute disadvantage facing four enemy guilds, Zhao Yuzhe definitely wouldn’t retreat.

Moreover, West Riding Wind also had a better understanding now of why Zhao Yuzhe went to look for a fight with Heavenly Justice. Perhaps it was because God Ye Qiu showed such a nonchalant and disdainful attitude towards him, and this proud Best Rookie wasn’t able to bear it.

As a result, West Riding Wind grasped Zhao Yuzhe’s intention to battle. In this battle, victory wasn’t the most important part. He needed to prove his strength to everyone.

West Riding Wind didn’t want to accompany Zhao Yuzhe and prove their guild’s strength, but things had already reached such a stage. They didn’t have any path of retreat either. Their elite group had a good deal of fans and many of them were furious at Ye Xiu’s mocking words. Zhao Yuzhe was even angrier and shouted: "Stop with the bullsh*t!"

"Ah! That’s Zhao Yuzhe?" Several players found him. There was a distinct gap between Hazy Scene’s position and Howling Height’s other players.

"He didn’t come out on his Elementalist, Beautiful Light?" Someone asked.

Beautiful Light was the character that Zhao Yuzhe used for official matches under Team Wind Howl. An account for a rookie usually wouldn’t be very good, but it was still better than many other accounts in the pro scene. It was worthy of being given attention to. However, Hazy Scene was just some character that no one had heard of before. Zhao Yuzhe was only controlling this character. These kinds of situation didn’t usually feel very realistic for most players.

"The situation’s a bit complicated. Should we try and break through the encirclement?" West Riding Wind messaged Zhao Yuzhe, asking him exactly what he had been planning on doing. As of now, the four allied guilds were gathered together. Fighting them head-on would only end in an utter slaughter. In this kind of situation, breaking through the encirclement was the most rational and normal decision. And after grasping Zhao Yuzhe’s intentions, West Riding Wind also understood that Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t seeking a death match. He could show off his skill in this way too. That kind of outcome would be good for both sides.

However, there was also an even more important point, West Riding Wind hoped Zhao Yuzhe wouldn’t think of: they were the ones who proposed the challenge. If they wanted to leave, the other side might not make things difficult and just let them go! An encirclement was also a bit far-fetched. If Howling Heights didn’t plan on fighting them, then the other side didn’t need to surround them, no? West Riding Wind hoped that when they "broke through the encirclement", the other side would hit back a bit and then allow them to quietly leave.

From how God Ye Qiu saw through the last two issues, West Riding Wind was certain that, if God Ye Qiu didn’t want a fight to the death, then when they broke through, they would have a tacit understanding of one another.

"Charge!" West Riding Wind received a reply from Zhao Yuzhe. He wasn’t sure what that meant exactly, but he didn’t have any time to ask,1 because Zhao Yuzhe had already started moving. Hazy Scene waved his staff and pointed forward. From what West Riding Wind saw, even if they were breaking through, it seems like they were choosing the most forceful way….. Hazy Scene fired his magic at Enlightened Lord.

Fire was perhaps not the most appropriate word. A better word would probably be draw.

Elementalist skill: Ice Line.

A line of ice would form after a one second delay wherever the magic drew past. If a player touched the line of ice, there was a one hundred percent chance of being locked in a four second freeze. That line of ice would also stay in effect for 12 seconds. The cast time for the spell was only three seconds. In other words, however many Ice Lines were formed within those three seconds depended on the user’s hand speed.

It was undoubtedly a powerful skill, but one thing of note was that the magic could draw through a position a player or an NPC. In other words, it wasn’t possible to directly draw a line through a character’s body and freeze a character in such a way. The line of ice could only be left in the environment. After the line of ice had been formed, the player or NPC had to touch it for the spell to take effect. While drawing the magic, if the magic hit a character’s body, the skill would be interrupted.

Hazy Scene waved his staff and magic poured out continuously. Ice had already begun forming wherever he pointed. Everyone could instantly tell that he was drawing Ice Lines. However, the speed of the lines being drawn showed everyone that he truly was a pro player.

Under the lead of Zhao Yuzhe’s fast mouse movements, those Ice Line were drawn at speeds which the ice nearly couldn’t keep up with. Quite a few players wanted to have their characters run into the path of the magic and stop the spell, but their characters’ movement speed couldn’t match the magic’s animations.

Moving one’s mouse faster than a character could run was something anyone could easily do, but moving it so precisely was naturally much more difficult.

Zhao Yuzhe had undergone specialized practice. He drew quickly and accurately. He didn’t impatiently aim at Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord. First, he drew lines to block off other players from interfering. As for Ye Xiu? He watched the path of the ice lines carefully and quickly leaped backwards.

Too late? Everyone thought. Enlightened Lord’s movement speed couldn’t compare to the speed of Zhao Yuzhe’s Ice Line. The huge difference made it easy for everyone to determine: Enlightened Lord would definitely be separated from everyone else because of the Ice Lines.

Just when they were thinking of this, Enlightened Lord jumped in place. They didn’t understand why he jumped in place, when the Ice Line suddenly changed paths. Everyone thought that the lines would keep going, cutting Enlightened Lord off, but the Ice Line suddenly curved.　

Everyone thought that this sudden curve was completely pointless. Then, two holy lights suddenly blossomed from behind Enlightened Lord. The two holy lights exploded out to the left and right. Enlightened Lord rose up in the air, but didn’t come down.

Cleric skill: Angel Wings.

The visual effects for this skill were incomparably beautiful. The two wings behind Enlightened Lord were formed completely out of light. The brightness made it difficult to look at directly. Even the clothes on Enlightened Lord became blurry from the contrast, as if he really were an angel descending from the heavens.

However, in comparison to the gorgeous visual effects, the skill’s usage was extremely simple. Everyone could see it right now: it let the character float in the air. The character could move around, but the character could only stay at a certain height, unable to rise any higher or descend until the skill’s duration ended.

Why is he using Angel Wings?

Everyone was puzzled because, even if he used Angel Wings, he still wouldn’t be able to escape from the prison formed by the Ice Line. If not, why would this spell be so troublesome? Otherwise, they could just jump over the Ice Line. The height at which the Ice Line formed couldn’t be determined just by looking at them. After thorough testing from players, it was known that there was a limit. However, there were no methods to directly leap over the limit of the Ice Line. The limit was found by testing the skill at different terrain heights. In practice, there wasn’t really a limit.

No could understand the reason for the sudden casting of Angel Wings, but before anyone could think further, Angel Wings was cancelled. Enlightened Lord suddenly dropped down. The Ice Line formed by Hazy Scene passed by him. However, none of them went past Enlightened Lord’s back. If the Ice Line had failed to reach past Enlightened Lord, it meant that the lines failed to block Enlightened Lord off from everyone else.

Now they understood why Enlightened Lord made those actions.

Enlightened Lord’s coordinates on the map didn’t change with that jump. However, his vertical height changed. By switching positions, he was blocking Zhao Yuzhe’s cursor.

The lines were drawn by holding the right click button while moving the cursor. As long as this were happening, if the cursor touched a character, the skill would end. The players were trying to stop the spell by reading the movement of the Ice Line. They naturally wouldn’t be able to keep up with the speed of the lines. On the other hand, Enlightened Lord’s jump was made by determining where Zhao Yuzhe’s cursor position was and then changed his position to bump into Zhao Yuzhe’s cursor.

As a result, Zhao Yuzhe’s Ice Line suddenly curved. Afterwards, Enlightened Lord floated in the air for a bit with Angel Wings and then quickly fell. These actions were probably done after determining the path that Zhao Yuzhe’s cursor would take. This exchange between two pro players was on a completely different level from anything normal players like them would ever experience.

They only understood one point. For God Ye Qiu to be able to execute such a method meant his familiarity with Glory had reached the greatest of heights. By looking at Hazy Scene’s position, he could imagine the screen that Zhao Yuzhe was looking at. Then, by looking at the movements of the Ice Line, he could determined where Zhao Yuzhe’s mouse was pointing to…...

Chapter 709: A Small Difference

The surrounding players watched the extremely high-level battle, yet without any contact between the two players. They already felt amazed, but in reality, these normal players failed to accurately analyze everything that was going on. The only people who truly understood what had really happened were Ye Xiu and Zhao Yuzhe.

Everyone had guessed why Enlightened Lord jumped in place, but they were only half-right.

Blocking Zhao Yuzhe’s cursor was Ye Xiu’s goal, but if it were just to block the cursor, it wouldn’t have been necessary to jump. Glory was played with a first person perspective. No matter how hard Zhao Yuzhe tried, he wouldn’t be able to see behind Enlightened Lord, let alone trying to wrap around him with his cursor.

A dead angle would always exist in some place, even if Zhao Yuzhe moved Hazy Scene horizontally. That would only cover the previous dead angle. There would just be a different dead angle now that he had moved. Relying on moving around to complete the entire line wasn’t possible. The ice line could only be drawn for three seconds and a character could only travel so far in those three seconds.

As a result, if Zhao Yuzhe wanted to draw his ice line behind Enlightened Lord, he would have to jump. Only by elevating his line of sight would he be able to continue drawing the line behind Enlightened Lord without hitting his body and cut him off from the rest of the players.

Ye Xiu had Enlightened Lord jump just at this moment. He was using this jump to completely deny Zhao Yuzhe chance of jumping and drawing the line behind him.

Zhao Yuzhe was startled when he saw it. Just when he thought of using the difference in timing between their two jumps, Enlightened Lord suddenly activate Angel Wings to float in midair. Zhao Yuzhe noticed the wings and immediately changed the ice line’s path. He tried to draw the line through the space beneath Enlightened Lord’s feet, but then Enlightened Lord cancelled his Angel Wings not even a second after activating it. Enlightened Lord fell down and he had to change ice line’s path again…..

In this confrontation, there had been several ups and downs. Zhao Yuzhe displayed his ability to react and adapt. How could it be as simple as Enlightened Lord jumping up and down to block his cursor?

After a few exchanges, Ice Line’s cast time reached its end. When Enlightened Lord landed back on the ground, Zhao Yuzhe tried jumping again to complete the line, but there wasn’t enough time left. He could move the mouse cursor very quickly, but he had to do it while moving, which made it that much more difficult…..

In the end, Ice Line formed, but when the line reached Enlightened Lord, it suddenly curved as if it feared him. In the eyes of the surrounding players, this wasn’t just a defeat for Zhao Yuzhe, but a very funny defeat. Some of them even started laughing.

The laughter was like a slap to Zhao Yuzhe’s face.

Nothing else but killing God Ye Qiu’s character would be enough to prove his skill now. However, Enlightened Lord was a Cleric, so he definitely wouldn’t go to the front lines and would be protected by others instead. Killing him would be very difficult. It had been a rare opportunity to have a chance at separate him from everyone else. Who would have thought that he would be able to escape from Ice Line without anyone’s help.

Even though Zhao Yuzhe was a pro player, who had experienced many battles, he had never seen such terrifying awareness and judgement from someone else before. For a moment, he somewhat in a daze.

However, in West Riding Wind’s eyes, although Ice Line failed to imprison Enlightened Lord, it still cut off a good portion of people from him. Not utilizing these 12 seconds of time would be a waste. If Zhao Yuzhe decided to forcefully breaking through in the most troublesome way possible, it was pointless to argue, so he might as well just hurry and take this chance to attack!

"Charge!" West Riding Wind ordered in the group chat. The elite players were still normal players of the highest skill level. They saw this opportunity too. When the order came down, none of them hesitated and started firing all sorts of attacks and spells. Enlightened Lord was standing at the very front, so he naturally bore the brunt of the attacks. In a large-scale battle, everyone just attacked wherever it was convenient to. No one really cared who was who.

Ye Xiu couldn’t ignore a hundred people suddenly attacking him. He immediately ran back to his group while healing himself. When facing so many attacks, many people felt like running around in a zig zag was pointless. A straight line would be the best choice. However, Enlightened Lord didn’t duck his head and headed straight for his group. He chose a jagged path. After looking at him run for a bit, they saw the reason.

Enlightened Lord didn’t completely avoid all of the damage, but he dodged the most concentrated attacks. When he rushed back to his group, his health was already red. Then, he said: "Why wasn’t anyone healing me?"

God also needs healing?

Everyone stared blankly. They had been preoccupied with admiring how God would escape from so many attacks that no one had thought of healing him. After hearing his question, everyone suddenly realized: how dangerous! If God Ye Qiu hadn’t chosen to dodge the high damage attacks with his pathing, he probably would have died already.

It seems like even God Ye Qiu felt a lot of pressure when facing so many people.

They were still thinking about this as the Clerics hastily topped up Enlightened Lord’s health. Howling Heights had started ferociously attacking them. Zhao Yuzhe regained his composure. Hazy Scene was fearlessly leading the charge, coordinating his spells with his movements. It almost seemed like his Mobile Cast was constantly active, when it was actually because of his almost perfect grasp of the rhythm. Zhao Yuzhe was definitely worthy of bearing the title of Best Rookie.

In his eyes, Enlightened Lord was still his main target. When Howling Heights began attacking, Enlightened Lord instantly fell dangerously low. However, Zhao Yuzhe had been in a daze at that time.When he woke up, he stamped his feet in anger. That was a perfect opportunity to kill Enlightened Lord! To think he would actually miss it.

He was the only one to be stunned on his side, but on Enlightened Lord’s side, the troops from the three guilds were all also stunned. Enlightened Lord was being chased like mad by a hundred players, yet they were just standing there watching him come towards them....

"Teams one, two, three, and four block the left side. Elementalists from teams, six, seven, and eight strengthen the Ice Line. Everyone else accompany LIttle Zhao and charge!" West Riding Wind kept on instructing his group.

Ye Xiu’s side instinctively resisted against the other side’s charge. However, it went just as West Riding Wind predicted. Apart from Heavenly Justice, the other three Club guilds stood there: if the other side wanted to leave, then go ahead and leave? Why stop them?

West Riding Wind had clearly recognized the small differences between the four guilds. The other three Club guilds wanted to preserve their strength. They didn’t want to fight. Heavenly Justice fought against Howling Heights head-on though. Unfortunately, if it was just them, they were slightly weaker than Howling Heights, whether that was in terms of average skill level or average character strength.

And neither side really had a strategy in mind in this type of conflict. In just a few short seconds, they had already began clashing. The average player’s skill level and character strength eventually became the deciding factor. Heavenly Justice had trouble defending, and Howling Heights soon tore an opening open. Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene was particularly dazzling. He actually didn’t notice that it was because ¾ of the enemies weren’t participating. He thought he alone was making the decisive difference and blasting open a path through the enemy ranks.

Zhao Yuzhe was quite sharp. Unlike a lot of other players, his attacks weren’t random. His attacks were purposeful. They always did damage and his attacks came rapidly too. He really did help Howling Heights gain an advantage.

West Riding Wind had an experienced eye. He saw that those three guilds were just standing there relaxing and God Ye Qiu didn’t seem to be doing anything with Heavenly Justice.

That was good though. If they really had charged blindly, West Riding Wind was really afraid that Zhao Yuzhe would see through the issue and make another terrible move. With the way things were going, it should be enough to make up for the blow to that punk’s pride, right?

"Hazy Scene! Hazy Scene!! Focus your fire on him!!" Heavenly Justice didn’t seem to understand the situation though. From the battlefield, it was easy to see just how useful he was. They were shouting for everyone to kill him at all costs.

"Don’t stop them. Just attack back a bit and let them go." Ye Xiu had given the order awhile ago, but the problem was that he could only give the order. He couldn’t control everyone’s characters. Heavenly Justice had been attacked too fiercely by Howling Heights. It was difficult for them to suddenly stop halfway through. Letting them go was fine, but no one wanted to not put up a fight!

"If you’re low on health, pull back. Knights stand at the front. Healers, heal well. Melee classes scatter to the left and right. Keep backing away as a whole!" Ye Xiu said. If he couldn’t control their characters, he could only give them concrete instructions.

His orders and the shouts from everyone else to kill Hazy Scene weren’t on the same page. However, killing off Hazy Scene was a suggestion given by someone without authority. It didn’t count as a group order. However, Ye Xiu’s words had the tag "Group order" in the group chat. Words with a title naturally held more weight than the some shouting of random players.

Heavenly Justice followed Ye Xiu’s orders. They immediately restrained their attacks as if they were being pushed back by Howling Heights.

West Riding Wind saw the change. For a moment, he wasn’t sure if Heavenly Justice was planning on retreating or preparing for a counterattack. In theory, with God Ye Qiu leading, it should be the former, right?

He was thinking about this, but Zhao Yuzhe didn’t care. The other side was retreating, giving him an opportunity to continue charging forward.

Heavenly Justice had thoroughly experienced the might of this Best Rookie. Seeing him rush over, they started to panic a bit.

"Zhao Yuzhe is coming again!!" Countless players cried.

"Steamed Bun, throw a brick at him." Ye Xiu ordered.

"YES, SIR!" Steamed Bun immediately acted. Only the heavens knew where this Brawler got a brick, but it had once again come out.

Chapter 710: Please Sir, Get Into the Boiling Pot

The brick whistled by!

Zhao Yuzhe was currently very focused. He didn’t dare to slack off even a little. He immediately noticed the brick flying over. He tilted Hazy Scene’s head slightly to dodge the brick. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t care who the brick would strike behind him. He found the guy, who launched the brick, among the opposing crowd and immediately fumed.

You think I’m easy to bully? You steamed bun!

Zhao Yuzhe was no longer fighting alone. The players from Howling Heights coordinated with his attacks very well. He didn’t want to ignore Steamed Bun’s provocation. Hazy Scene pointed his staff at Steamed Bun’s Brawler and fired a spell. The players of Howling Heights beside him instantly matched him and sent over similar attacks.

Steamed Bun hastily controlled his Brawler to dodge. He looked rather vulgar as he rolled and crawled around. Attacks such as the Brawler brick were only mid-ranged attacks and didn’t count as a long-ranged attack. In order to throw it, Steamed Bun had to leave his previous position in the formation. It was easy to come out, but difficult to return. With Zhao Yuzhe making things difficult, Steamed Bun only managed to survive through the desperate efforts of Heavenly Justice’s Clerics.

Zhao Yuzhe felt so satisfied!

He was finally able to fix up the guy who had put him in a sorry situation! He saw Steamed Bun hide behind his allies, while continuing to search for opportunities to throw his brick. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t plan to let him go off just like that.

"Charge!"

This was the first time Zhao Yuzhe coordinated with everyone today. Before, he always fought by himself and waited for the others to coordinate with him. However, in order to take down Steamed Bun, he intended to lead the charge.

At this moment, Enlightened Lord appeared on the frontlines of the enemy side. When Zhao Yuzhe saw this, he burst with joy. Compared to the unknown "Steamed Bun", taking down the character of a God was much more exciting.

Zhao Yuzhe itched with impatience and felt regretful for not being a Battle Mage. Otherwise, he would rush over with a grand and majestic Dragon Breaks the Ranks and give Enlightened Lord a beating. How great would that be?

Even though the damage from an Elementalist wouldn’t lose to any other class, in terms of the satisfaction from a blow, Elementalists couldn’t able to compare with close-ranged classes who made waves with every blow!

"Cover me!" Zhao Yuzhe ordered again. His hand speed increased as he prepared to cast the Elementalist’s skill, Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. In such a chaotic scene, he was the only pro player who dared to move his Elementalist to the frontlines. If he threw Heavenly Lightning into a crowded area, even if it didn’t kill anyone, it would still be very thrilling to watch. This was perhaps a feeling of bliss that close ranged players would never be able to taste.

Who would have thought that Heavenly Justice’s troops would create a gap in their formation on their own? The dust rolled to the side, and a Battle Mage rushed over with her spear.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Zhao Yuzheng wanted to use this skill just a moment ago. In the end, it was someone from Heavenly Justice who used this skill to greet him. He looked at the ID and realized that it was the person who forced him to burn his Teleport, then used Rising Dragon Soars the Sky to kill him.

An enemy! Another enemy!

Even though Zhao Yuzhe somewhat lost his cool, he at least knew that he wouldn’t be able to use his Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks had higher priority. Even though there were characters standing in front of Hazy Scene, Dragon Breaks the Rank couldn’t be stopped by a single person. Wherever it was aimed would surely be the spear’s final destination. Even if there were thousands of men and horses, this fact wouldn’t change.

"Give way!" Zhao Yuzhe gave another firm command.

Since you want to come, then come! But once you get here, don’t even think about leaving.

Zhao Yuzhe’s reaction speed and APM was quick. Hazy Scene jumped aside as he spoke. However, the players that were standing before him weren’t as quick. They had realized it, but were too slow to react. Tang Rou’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks headed right their way. Her spear penetrated through their bodies. Even a heavily-armored Knight wouldn’t be able to slow Dragon Breaks the Ranks down in any way. The Knight was sent flying at once. If Hazy Scene hadn’t dodged, the spear would’ve directly pierced through him as well. However, Zhao Yuzhe had predicted this, so he dodged it cleanly. He was taking his time throwing out his spells, while coldly ordering: "Keep him here."

Did he need to say that? No one wanted to leave such a reckless person alive. However, the Battle Mage was the quickest to react.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks was a rare high-leveled skill, which had little ending animation lag. Although she pierced the Knight in front, she failed to hit Hazy Scene, so Tang Rou cancelled her skill at once. Immediately after the animation ended, her Battle Mage soon struck out with a Falling Flower Palm. She managed to make a move before everyone else.

Once the palm flew out, the unprepared players received the attack and were blasted aside, crashing into those behind them. Howling Height’s formation was destroyed by a Battle Mage’s low-leveled skill. Tang Rou’s fast hand speed allowed for her character to act quickly.

Tyrant’s Destruction!

Tang Rou’s following skills were no longer low leveled. This was a sweeping skill, which targeted the ankle. When it activated, she managed to sweep a majority of the players away with this skill.

When Tang Rou’s Battle Mage used Falling Flower Palm, her left palm pushed out, while her right hand grabbed the end of her spear. She chained this skill after drawing back her hand, so she could swing out her spear after gripping the end. A deep and clear humming sound pierced through the air from behind the Battle Mage. Tang Rou’s Tyrant’s Destruction made a 270 degree arc around her.

"F*ck!"

Countless people from Howling Heights yelled out.

It was unnecessary to mention the range of a sweeping spear. Speaking of a close-ranged weapon’s length, the spear was definitely the longest. How many ankles did this 270 degree sweep strike? Even Tang Rou didn’t know! The Howling Height players who were hit by Falling Flower Palm flew, crashed, tumbled, and fell. However, this was just the beginning. The surrounding players nearby also began to stumble. Those who hadn’t fallen yet soon fell. Those who were swept off their feet by Tyrant’s Destruction tumbled through the air like flying, spinning tops.

"Trash!!" Zhao Yuzhe shouted out in anger. For an instant, no one knew whether he was challenging the opponent, or criticizing the members of Howling Heights for being useless.

Even though his spells hit Tang Rou’s Battle Mage, how high would his damage output be when he fought alone? When Tyrant’s Destruction was used, Hazy Scene was now within her attack range, forcing him to move back another step.

Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t bear taking a step back from an opponent he didn’t respect. He threw out another spell as he shouted. He didn’t expect that this Battle Mage’s spear, that came from the left would suddenly curve upwards towards him.

So quick!

Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t willing, but he had to admit that this Battle Mage wasn’t weak at all. Compared to Steamed Bun, there was less bafflement, but much more ferociousness. She rushed into her opponent’s territory, yet she still had spirit to take him down with her spear. Zhao Yuzhe felt weak facing a hundred players alone, but this person in front of him made him feel like, even if there were a hundred players blocking her, if she wanted you dead, she would attack despite the odds.

Jump back.

Zhao Yuzhe had no other choice. The distance between Hazy Scene and this Battle Mage would already be considered close. He thought that she would panic after rushing into so many enemies alone, so he hadn’t been concerned, but when she arrived, she chained two skills flawlessly and swept away the characters next to him. Afterwards, she immediately closed the distance between herself and his Hazy Scene.

I have to kill her!

Zhao Yuzhe felt anger surge through him. When his Hazy Scene jumped back, he suddenly lost control over his movements and shifted horizontally…..

Last time he died, he had been moved horizontally too. That time, he had been forced aside by that Battle Mage’s Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, but this time? There were no magic undulations around him. Instead, there seemed to be some sort of indistinct force in the surrounding air.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

How could Zhao Yuzhe not realize by now? If not, then how could he deserve the title of Best Rookie?

When he thought of this move, Zhao Yuzhe’s heart immediately sunk.

Where was Cloud Grasping Fist going to bring him? Did that even need to be said? The other side’s sudden one-man charge was a tactic especially for him! And this time, he had been caught once again!

Cloud Grasping Fist…..

Everyone was prepared for this skill. In a large-scale battle, where boths sides could easily be distinguished from one another, Cloud Grasping Fist was a commonly-used skill. Everyone knew that if an enemy Qi Master grabbed you, you were guaranteed to die. As a result, everyone was wary of Cloud Grasping Fist. Zhao Yuzhe hadn’t been negligent. However, the enemy Battle Mage’s sudden charge drew most of his attention. He was then isolated by the Battle Mage and was forced to dodge. Who would have thought that the other side would suddenly make things so difficult for him? Before he even landed on the ground after his jump, he was caught by Cloud Grasping Fist.

Aren’t those all Knights in front of him? Where did the Qi Master come? I don’t see any!

Zhao Yuzhe’s gaze suddenly shifted towards Heavenly Justice. He looked at Enlightened Lord and then felt the urge to cough blood.

How low!

If he had seen a Qi Master nearby, how would he have been so careless? However, Enlightened Lord was standing right in front of the Qi Master, blocking his view. That was why he hadn’t been able to defend against it!

Blocking someone was fine, but you’re even blocking two? Is that so there were no mistakes?

Zhao Yuzhe thought to himself, but realized that he was wrong. The two Qi Masters weren’t both targeting him.

"Who else are they grabbing?" Zhao Yuzhe couldn’t help but take a quick look around, when he saw that valiant Battle Mage was also flying back towards Heavenly Justice.

However, that Battle Mage was being rescued, while he was being sent to his death.

No one can interrupt them?

Zhao Yuzhe hoped someone would be able to, but when he turned around, he lost all hope. After his allies had been swept away by that Battle Mage, they were still clambering around. If any one of them could accurately aim an attack and interrupt the other side’s Cloud Grasping Fist, that person would already be on a pro team.

The enemy troops formed ring after ring around his landing location. In a short few seconds, they had already prepared a coffin and burial spot for him.

F*ck... they even lit up a will o’ wisp for me.

Zhao Yuzhe saw Enlightened Lord lighting up the area with a Sacred Fire just for him.

TL Note: The alternate account that Tang Rou is using is a male Battle Mage, but for consistency and less confusion, we will refer to the Battle Mage as she/her, which will be more directed towards Tang Rou’s actions rather than the character itself.

Chapter 711: All Forces Annihilated

Everyone could see just how dangerous the situation was. Howling Heights wanted to rescue him, but they lacked the strength to do so. Those farther away wouldn’t be able to make it there in time. Those closer had been swept away by Tang Rou’s attack and were trying to find their bearings. Their posture had been destroyed. The swaying motion could be felt too, making it difficult for players to move precisely. Interrupt? That would be completely impossible. As of right now, they could only wait and see if Zhao Yuzhe could escape on his own.

After seeing the enemy Battle Mage charge over and then get pulled back by Cloud Grasping Fist, Howling Heights felt enlightened. Players in the same group couldn’t injure one another, so Cloud Grasping Fist couldn’t be used to pull an ally back. That Battle Mage must have been kicked out of the group temporarily. As a result, West Riding Wind told his Howling Height’s Qi Masters to hurry and pull him back, while also kicking Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene from the group.

Hazy Scene had been kidnapped by Cloud Grasping Fist. Before he landed on the ground, a Sacred Fire was thrown onto his body.

Teleporting away wouldn’t be possible anymore. Having been silenced, his character could only perform basic attacks and maneuvers. Elementalists sought after casting speed, not attack speed. If an Elementalist actually started beating an enemy with their staff, the Elementalist’s attack wouldn’t look like as if it were moving in slow motion, but it was slow enough to make melee classes uncomfortable. Melee classes, even those who used slower attack speed weapons like greatswords and spears, tended to value attack speed in other equipment, so none of them would be as slow as an Elementalist waving his staff around.

Zhao Yuzhe was a pro player though! No matter how much confidence he had in his own skills, as an Elementalist, he couldn’t be completely unprepared for a close quarters combat fight. The instant he had been grabbed by Cloud Grasping Fist and burned by Sacred Fire, he decisively switched weapons from a slow staff to a much more agile magic wand. The difference in speed could visibly be seen. With a click of his mouse, Hazy Scene landed domineeringly on the ground and trembled.

Zhao Yuzhe heard Enlightened Lord speak in an astonished tone: "No way, Best Rookie. Falling Flower Palm is a skill too. You don’t know what Sacred Fire does?"

This time, Zhao Yuzhe’s face actually turned red.

Yes, in that instant, his brain had turned into mush. He had only been thinking about what methods he could use to escape from a close combat battle, so he switched his weapon. Then, he did the motion for a Falling Flower Palm to try and push the enemies in front of him away. He had completely forgotten about Sacred Fire’s crowd control effect.

Sacred Fire sealed all skills, unlike the Elementalist skill Magic Shackles, which only sealed magic-related skills. It had no effect on physical skills.

This mistake from Zhao Yuzhe had purely been because his brain had short-circuited, not because he mixed the two skills up. When he had tried to perform Falling Flower Palm, it obviously failed. The only thing came out of his character was a stupid-looking tremble. Even worse, the other side had completely seen through his intentions…..

Amid the loud laughter, Hazy Scene fell to the ground.

Because of this mistake, Zhao Yuzhe was so ashamed, he couldn’t focus. Tang Rou’s Battle Mage used a Circle Swing and threw Hazy Scene onto the ground. Everyone swarmed him; their hands and feet flying about everywhere. Zhao Yuzhe received the notification that West Riding Wind had kicked him out of the group. He didn’t misunderstand the action though and guessed West Riding Wind’s intentions. However, when he looked around, Hazy Scene was already surrounded by players. Cloud Grasping Fist couldn’t pass through enemies. How would they manage to grab him?

Zhao Yuzhe tried one last struggle and swung his magic wand.

Players had complete control over their normal attacks. When Zhao Yuzhe’s Hazy Scene swung his wand, it looked like it had come from a Battle Mage.

Of course, a normal attack didn’t have the power or priority of a skill, but it could still hit people’s feet. Unfortunately, he had only started his swing, when Tang Rou’s Battle Mage stabbed at the ground, blocking it.

This Battle Mage wasn’t weak at all…...

Zhao Yuzhe had become determined a bit too late. The enemy weapons rained down on him and he died instantly. From his ghost’s perspective, he saw those guys scrambling over to grab his dropped equipment. As for Howling Heights? Their Qi Masters had only just arrived at the front of the group, but they couldn’t see their target at all. West Riding Wind shook his arm and Howling Heights charged, but it was over for Zhao Yuzhe….. Everything was over. How could he have the face to stand up and fight again! He could only blame himself for being too arrogant and not taking the game seriously enough.　

Zhao Yuzhe logged off. His character didn’t revive at all.

This character wasn’t his. It belonged to the Club. After using it, he would need to return it to West Riding Wind. He originally wanted to use his vacation time and show off in game, but who would have thought that things would turn out so badly? He had already died twice... Out of all those Howling Height players, which of them had died twice today?

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t want to show off in the game anymore. Playing together with his fans would only make him feel more embarrassed. He was even somewhat unsure of how he should return this account card. How would those people in the guild studio look at him? Zhao Yuzhe stared blankly at his computer screen.

Howling Heights seemed to have gone insane. Ye Xiu immediately ordered everyone: "Fight back a bit and then retreat. Let’s see if they’ll leave or not!"

Their previous retreat had created some distance between Heavenly Justice and Howling Heights, but now that Howling Heights was charging at them again, they thought in the same way as the other three guilds and fought back a bit before retreating.

Howling Heights charged to the front and immediately saw Hazy Scene’s corpse sprawled on the ground. Many of the loyal fans were furious. West Riding Wind checked his friends list. Little comrade Zhao had since logged off. It seemed like the blow to his pride wasn’t light!

West Riding Wind couldn’t stop his players from becoming furious. It had nothing to do with benefits, but rather their honor. Their team’s player had been killed. Everyone wanted revenge.

"Sigh, what a terrible loss….." West Riding Wind sighed to himself. He could only watch as his troops angrily attacked Heavenly Justice out of revenge. At this moment, he also noticed that Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade had begun to move.

Of course.

They thought Howling Heights would just charge out and leave. Of course, they would quietly let them go, but Howling Heights refused to rest against Heavenly Justice though. As allies, how could they stand still and continue watching?

The guild leaders had given the orders and their troops began to move…..

Half an hour passed.

Zhao Yuzhe was still staring blankly at his screen. It wasn’t like he had never suffered a loss before, but he had never felt so miserable. The game should have been a leisurely place, yet why did he lose face instead?

Just when he was lost in thought, he suddenly heard a knock at his door. Zhao Yuzhe woke up and confirmed that it was his door.

During the break, the Club didn’t mind the player staying in the provided dorms. The majority of players chose to leave though, whether it was for their families or to travel. Even those who still wanted to play Glory might not stay at the Club. In Team Wind Howl, besides him, there weren’t any other players here. Who would knock on his door…...

Zhao Yuzhe opened the door and saw the guild leader West Riding Wind. He immediately fell silent.

West Riding Wind had to muster up the courage to knock on Zhao Yuzhe’s door. Zhao Yuzhe stayed offline and never logged back on. West Riding Wind could imagine how he was feeling right now, but he felt like he should come over. Even though their guild department didn’t need to be concerned about a pro player’s condition or growth, West Riding Wind was still a loyal fan of Team Wind Howl. Their team’s Best Rookie had taken a truly heavy blow. He was in the area, so he wouldn’t ignore the issue and instead went to go console him, especially since he knew that there weren’t any players around besides Zhao Yuzhe.

When he opened the door, Zhao Yuzhe really was depressed. It was as if he wasn’t the same person, who had come running over to him that morning in high spirits.

"Uh….. I saw that you logged off and never logged back on, so I came over to check up on you." West Riding Wind said.

"What’s the situation over there?" Zhao Yuzhe asked.

"Extremely heavy casualties." West Riding Wind told him the truth. Zhao Yuzhe was no longer there. The four guilds had banded together. How could Howling Heights resist? Even more so when very few of them were still cool-headed. In the end, Howling Height’s troops were completely annihilated. Heavy casualties was actually an understatement.

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t ask any further questions. He just suddenly went blank again. He seemed to have forgotten that West Riding Wind was still in his room.

"Ahem….." West Riding Wind coughed to interrupt the awkward silence: "It’s no big deal. It happens in the game all the time."

"Besides, we were against four guilds allied together and even a demon like Ye Qiu. Let alone our Howling Heights, even the Three Great Guilds would have been easily crushed." West Riding Wind said in order to ease the embarrassment in Zhao Yuzhe’s heart. He could tell that this Best Rookie ran to the game thinking he was invincible. Then, he ended up dying twice. He had been singled out the first time, but the second time, he had been the focus of a huge group! Let alone pro players, even guild leaders like Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader Jiang You and Heavenly Justice’s Loulan Slash were priority targets. Pro players should be worth even more than guild leaders!

"You… don’t need to console me….." Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t stupid. He could see through West Riding Wind’s intentions.

"Oh oh...."West Riding Wind didn’t want to say too much. Zhao Yuzhe had high aspirations. He was afraid that if he said too much, Zhao Yuzhe misunderstand and think he was underestimating him. That would not be good.

"Just….. Keep up the good work!" West Riding Word left these words of encouragement. He could mediate arguments between guild members, but he had never provided mental counseling for pro players before!

"That Battle Mage and Brawler with them. Who were they? They seemed to be like Ye Qiu’s Enlightened Lord without any guild tags." Zhao Yuzhe asked.

"Oh, those two. They aren’t using their actual accounts. That Brawler is called Steamed Bun Invasion. The Battle Mage is called Soft Mist. These two have been with Ye Qiu ever since he began in the tenth server." West Riding Wind had noticed them. Looking at their classes, he was certain that these two were definitely them.

"Steamed Bun Invasion….. Soft Mist?" Zhao Yuzhe took note of their names. At the same time, he pointed at the table: "That account card, Hazy Scene. Is it okay if I keep using it?"

"No problem. No problem at all." West Riding Wind immediately replied.

Chapter 712: Worries of the Alliance

Dying in the game had been difficult for Zhao Yuzhe to accept, but it wasn’t a setback he couldn’t recover from. Asking West Riding Wind about Tang Rou and Steamed Bun showed that he recognized that these two players weren’t normal. Keeping the account card also signified that he didn’t plan on giving up either.

Seeing how Zhao Yuzhe hadn’t gotten tilted, West Riding Wind felt gratified. However, he wasn’t sure if he should allow Zhao Yuzhe to keep on hunting wild bosses with them. Having a pro player’s assistance naturally improved their strength significantly, but Zhao Yuzhe alone wasn’t enough to deal with God Ye Qiu and the four guild alliance. In fact, the confrontation resulted in injuring the confidence of Team Wind Howl’s future star. It was a difficult decision to make. After leaving Zhao Yuzhe’s room and returning to his room, he could already feel his head begin to hurt.

Ye Xiu didn’t care about what was happening at Howling Heights.

Snatching the boss was already a victory. Howling Heights didn’t seem to know what was good for them and had continued to persistently attack, ending in their quick demise. Even though it didn’t matter too much for Club guilds, from an emotional perspective, it felt very good. Equipment dropped by Howling Height players scattered the ground. The four guilds had a good time picking them up.

With their statuses as Club guilds, arguing over who should get which spoils of war was a bit meaningless. How to split the boss drops held a higher priority.

The five parties discussed the list of drops and split the goods. A perfectly even split wasn’t possible, but if one party lost a bit this time, that party would gain it back in the next wild boss hunt. The five guilds were quite trusting of each other now, so everything was much easier to agree on.

Afterwards, each party returned to the city and went to do their own thing. The subject of this battle still continued though. After all, this battle had been a bit abnormal. For example, this was the first time the alliance had won a Level 70 wild boss from a powerful guild. The alliance also defeated a guild, which had the assistance of a pro player, and the Best Rookie at that. That guild refused to give up too and was wiped out.

This battle made the guilds, which could usually only "poach", happy for a long time.

This battle was truly eye-brow raising! Many people had these thoughts.

This day, the Alliance kept on receiving news of bosses and continued to fight for them, reaping bountiful harvests, especially for low leveled Level 55 and Level 60 wild bosses.

This had to do with the big guilds not attaching as much importance on low-leveled wild bosses. However, guilds like Parade and Radiant went all out for these Level 55 and 60 bosses.

In truth, with the current development state of these smaller Club guilds, they needed these lower-leveled wild bosses because these guilds recognized their own strength and only did what they could do with that strength. If they needed to use Level 70 wild boss materials for all of their Silver equipment, it would be truly be too difficult for them. They couldn’t grab any in the game and no one sold such materials on the market. In the end, they could only shelve those blueprints. As a result, the smaller Club guilds mainly researched low-end Silver equipment. After all, they had a decent chance at scavenging these low-leveled wild bosses.

Ye Xiu couldn’t care less. They didn’t have any Silver equipment to begin with. Let alone Level 55 and Level 60 Heavenly Domain wild bosses, he still needed wild bosses from the normal servers. He didn’t have the strength to do that right now though.

One day, two days, a week passed.

A total of 74 wild bosses spawned every week in the Heavenly Domain. The Alliance was able to win 33 of these wild bosses, a very impressive number. Up until now, no guild had ever reached such a number. Those Three Great Guilds only got a few more than the other guilds. Being able to reach double digits was already quite amazing. However, because these 33 bosses were split between five parties, each party only got around 6-7 wild bosses each, which was on par with what the top guilds usually got every week. However, for Heavenly Justice, this was a huge breakthrough. Moreover, since only 74 wild bosses spawned every week, if the Alliance took away 33, the other guilds must have gotten much less than before.

The core members of the big guilds had fervent discussions over this topic in the chat group. God Ye Qiu’s destructiveness finally came and this time, it directly touched on the meaning of why Club guilds existed. This wasn’t something they could deal with.

As the Alliance stole the spotlight and snatched bosses this week, the core members of the guilds argued for a week, but couldn’t come up with a solution.

There were only two ways to salvage this situation. The first way was to disperse the opponent’s alliance. The second way was to come out with a force that could compete with the Alliance.

Dispersing the alliance would be way too difficult. It looked practically impossible right now at least.

The alliance guilds gathered together by Ye Xiu used to be pitiful. In the past, they practically never earned any wild bosses. The alliance could be classified as giving medicine to a dead horse. They had nothing to lose, so they were naturally willing to make this gamble. After tasting sweet victory, they had the confidence to continue now. Maybe after they became stronger, the alliance might crumble, but that would be in the distant future. As of now, the alliance was very stable.

As for fighting back against the alliance, the various guilds had tried doing so by sending out more troops. It worked. After all, of those 74 wild bosses, they ended up taking 41, but the results weren’t good. There were around ten guilds capable of fighting for wild bosses and they had to split 41 bosses? Every guild had a noticeable drop in harvests because 33 wild bosses had been forcefully snatched away.

Their solutions weren’t able to increase their respective guild’s competitive strength from the roots. What else could they do? They thought of an alliance, but everyone instantly fell silent at that thought. An alliance would be way too difficult for them. They fought against each other for wild bosses, dungeon records, etc. daily for since the creation of Glory. The accumulated rancor between one another was infinite. Suddenly, they had to let go of their enmity and join hands? That wasn’t something they could accomplish with just a few words.

Finding a reliable partner was difficult among guilds. More importantly, allying with their competitors didn’t fit with their duties as Club guilds.

Even if their guilds weren’t on the road to winning the championships, they at least went for the playoffs. Beating their opponent in the game matched well with their team getting a good record in the Pro Alliance.

They were different from guilds like Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade. These guilds were considered too weak to earn a high placing, but were too proud for a low one. Going for the playoffs? These guilds didn’t have the ability. Staying in the Alliance and not get relegated? They had done this for many years, so they weren’t under much pressure. For these teams, which read books to the princesses, their growth was much more important than beating other teams. In order to grow, they were okay with sharing the benefits with one another. It wasn’t something ambitious teams like Blue Rain, Samsara, or Tiny Herb could do.

For these championship teams, anything that could weaken their opponent could increase their chances at becoming the champions. Victory was accumulated bit by bit. Robbing their opponent’s resources wasn’t enough. Now they would have to share resources with their opponents? How could the group chat not fall into silence?

An alliance was possible, but not between any of the guilds in the chat group.

Besides an alliance, there weren’t too many options. They had to compete against the other guilds too. If it wasn’t done properly, they might give the others an opportunity to take advantage of them.

How difficult!

Although all 74 wild bosses had spawned, the week wasn’t over yet. The various guilds were getting ready for next week’s work.

Radiant, Conquering Clouds, Parade, and Heavenly Justice were in accordance with who these guilds wanted as allies. If they could ally with these guilds, they would weaken their current competitors.

It wasn’t just one or two guilds thinking about it either. Radiant, Conquering Clouds, and Parade suddenly became very popular. Their guild leaders were personally messaged by the leaders of the top guilds.

"It must have felt good getting all of those bosses this week. How about you come and kill bosses with us? With your four guild alliance and Ye Qiu, the drops are split between five parties right? You guys killed quite a lot of bosses last week, but the average number you got is just so-so, no? If you ally with us instead, we can get the same results, but each of us will get 16 wild bosses? Isn’t 16 an impressive number?"

All sorts of persuasive words were said. They really were enticing.

They were only able to get 6-7 bosses this week. If they could get 16-17 the next week, how could that not be an attractive offer?

16-17….. 16-17…...

These two numbers left these guild leaders in a trance. If they could get 16-17 wild bosses every week, they would grow at breakneck speed!

While these guild leaders were at a loss at what to do, they received invites. Ye Xiu had formed a QQ group.

"How is it? You’ve probably received a lot of enticing offers, right?" Ye Xiu got right to the point.

"No? What offers?" Radiant’s White Stream played it dumb.

"Yeah. Quite a few guilds are looking to ally with our Heavenly Justice." Loulan Slash was honest. His past experience taught him that it was better to be honest with Ye Xiu.

The other two guild leaders saw his message, but didn’t say anything. In any case, someone had already said they got offers, while the other one didn’t. They might as well wait and see what Ye Xiu would say.

Ye Xiu typed a smiley face: "Little White, why are you pretending you don’t know?! Did you think that I wouldn’t receive an invite?"

Chapter 713: Excellent Era Card Shuffle

White Stream felt very embarrassed at after being called out by Ye Xiu and hearing Loulan Slash’s honesty. After thinking about it, there was no reason that the others would only look for Radiant. Acting dumb was naive and childish.　

"Ahem...." White Stream wasn’t sure what to say at this moment.

"The reason I added you guys to this chat was to remind you to endure this ordeal!" Ye Xiu said. He didn’t seem to mind White Stream’s conduct.

"What are your thoughts?" Loulan Slash asked.

"Nothing really." Ye Xiu smiled, "This is a good indicator that they’re fearful of our Alliance. They don’t have any effective methods to deal with us, so they resorted to seeking their own alliances. For these guilds, sharing their profits is certainly very painful for them. If they’ve chosen to walk this path, then they must not have any other paths to walk."

"Thus, we cannot renounce our current advantageous position." Loulan Slash clearly stood by Ye Xiu’s side.

"However, our future will definitely be more grim. After all, apart from us, there are other Club guilds to choose from. It’s possible that two competitive guilds will ally together, so I need to confirm whether or not everyone has the confidence to continue cooperating. If any of you have intentions of accepting another guild’s invitation, please say it. What’s the point in hiding? You’ll be exposed the next time a boss spawns anyways. Speak out now and we can part on good terms!" Ye Xiu said.

"I have no intentions of leaving." Loulan Slash expressed.

"I’m satisfied with our current circumstance." Conquering Cloud’s Yue Ziqin confirmed.

"Let’s keep working hard together." Parade’s Martial Awareness said.

"Sigh... it’d be too embarrassing to say otherwise….." White Stream also decided to stay. Ye Xiu never called him out in his speech, but he had still "hid" the matter already, so it was a bit of a slap to the face. The slap was justified though, so he couldn’t say anything about it.

"I want everyone to recognize a cause and effect relation. The guilds are looking to doing something as painful as making alliances because of our existence. If our alliance broke up, their most formidable competitor will have disappeared and everything will go back to normal. If that happened, they wouldn’t bother looking for an alliance anymore." Ye Xiu said.　

"You’re right." This time, Yue Ziqin responded the fastest, "This is probably the scheme that the other guilds have come up with. It’s only by staying together that we can prevent a disaster from unfolding. If we fight amongst ourselves, at best, we’ll only be able to pick up the scraps."

The other three including White Stream agreed as well. Ye Xiu’s reasoning was very clear. As Club guild leaders, if they couldn’t understand this cause and effect relation, their capabilities would be questionable.

"Ha ha, as long as no one has any doubts, that’s good. Let’s keep up the good work next week." Ye Xiu said.

The chat group immediately fell silent. The crisis had been resolved. No matter how the other guilds tried, the four guild alliance wouldn’t budge. Even White Stream, who had wavered the most in the beginning, didn’t make a second mistake.

The alliance held together. The remainder of the day went well for them. When they had nothing to do, they would stare foolishly in joy at their harvest this week. They had never seen such a bountiful harvest before! Yue Ziqin, White Stream, and Martial Awareness had done exceptionally too. Their Clubs felt surprised at their accomplishments. After asking how they achieved it, they realized what these three guilds had done. The three guild leaders received praise from their respective Clubs and their monthly salary would naturally reflect it.

As for Loulan Slash, he was the owner, so his guild’s success and failures depended on him, which saved a lot of trouble.

While some were happy, there would naturally be others that were unhappy.

For example, Howling Heights had tragic results last week. They actually failed to get even a single boss. Speaking of which, Howling Heights had never been considered first-class in terms of guild strength. When they competed for bosses, they usually didn’t hold an advantage. On their first day this week, they had the help from a pro player and managed to crush even Tyrannical Ambition. However, after that battle, Zhao Yuzhe never came back to help them.

When West Riding Wind left Zhao Yuzhe that day, he felt like it shouldn’t be like this, but he felt too embarrassed to ask. This week’s work was over, but he still saw no signs of Zhao Yuzhe appearing. West Riding Wind thought to himself: did he also go on vacation? But when he checked the pro player residential area, Zhao Yuzhe was clearly still there.

He was still there, but he hadn’t logged on in the past few days. Had that guy pretended to be okay that day, when he was actually still depressed? West Riding Wind immediately thought of this possibility.

West Riding Wind knocked a few times on the door to Zhao Yuzhe’s room. When he pushed open the door to look, he saw Zhao Yuzhe in front of his computer, focused on practicing.

Correct, practice!

Zhao Yuzhe wasn’t depressed. After suffering defeat in the game, he felt like he wasn’t skilled enough. Being beat by God Ye Qiu was fine, but that Brawler, Steamed Bun, and that Battle Mage were nobodies, yet they proved troublesome.

Was it because the opponents were strong? Or because he was too weak?　　

Zhao Yuzhe had these kinds of thoughts in the beginning, but he had already discarded those. It didn’t matter if his opponents were strong or if he was weak, the only path was to improve. It wasn’t like he could pray that his opponents would suddenly become weak, right?

Zhao Yuzhe was focused on practicing and didn’t notice West Riding Wind coming into his room. West Riding Wind stood at the entrance and took a few glances. After seeing how Zhao Yuzhe was in the middle of practice, he didn’t bother him. He quietly closed the door and left.

No Club guild would be idle. Facing this week’s struggle for bosses, they had to figure out a way to answer back. They couldn’t just do the same next week as this week and continue watch Ye Qiu take away their resources with his alliance. That would be sitting and waiting for their own death.

This week wasn’t over yet.

The new week just happened to be on the first day of a new month —— July.

That morning, Ye Xiu followed his usual sleep schedule. When he went downstairs to eat breakfast, he saw Chen Guo holding a bowl and standing at the Internet Cafe entrance, looking at something outside.

"What are you looking at so early in the morning?" Ye Xiu wasn’t in a hurry to finish his breakfast. He lit up his cigarette and walked over.

Chen Guo didn’t say anything. She grabbed her chopsticks and pointed. Ye Xiu looked in that direction and saw Club Excellent Era. Numerous fans were gathered there, and quite a few were holding banners up high. Ye Xiu read the words and understood. The fans of Excellent Era were gathered around the Club to welcome Xiao Shiqin. July 1st was the official start of the transfer window for the Glory Alliance. Xiao Shiqin’s transfer to the Club had already been announced, it would naturally be officially completed today.

"He really did come." Chen Guo sighed. They were probably the people who didn’t find Xiao Shiqin welcome in the entire City H. Xiao Shiqin could change the entire Excellent Era into a team, which Ye Xiu might not even be able to recognize anymore.

Club Excellent Era.

Tao Xuan rushed over to the Club early that morning and confirmed everything with the reporters gathered around. Xiao Shiqin’s transfer wasn’t a small matter, especially with Excellent Era having been relegated. This All Star player actually chose to sacrifice a year and invest his time with Excellent Era, which naturally gave Tao Xuan a very good impression of him.

Tao Xuan stood by the window of his office. When he saw all of the fans gathered outside the Club, he felt like the move he made was incredibly beautiful. He hadn’t seen so many fans looking forward to their future in a while. Last season, fans usually gathered outside the Club to shout angrily at their team’s performance, throwing trash and protesting. It was much better now. Everything had ended. Tao Xuan was in an exceptional mood right now.

At the same time, the players living on the first floor such as Liu Hao and He Ming stood by the window too, looking outside at the fans crowded around the entrance. They were gnashing their teeth in anger though.

The three days prior to today, Liu Hao was both conflicted and looking forward to Xiao Shiqin.

At the end of the last season, when Excellent Era’s win record was in shambles, Liu Hao had already started thinking of leaving. After their relegations from the Alliance were certain, he was even more sure of his decision. However, he didn’t think the Club would announce Sun Xiang remaining on the team and Xiao Shiqin joining. This made Liu Hao waver.

Any player hoped to win the championships one day. Liu Hao was no exception. With Xiao Shiqin, even though Team Excellent Era was still a relegation team, on paper, their strength immediately became a contestant for the championships. Although they would need to play a year in the Challenger League, once that year passed, they would aim for the championship cup. It didn’t sound too bad.

The Club’s secret but exciting plan made Liu Hao waver. He didn’t really want to leave Excellent Era, in fact. He was currently Excellent Era’s vice-captain. He had quite some seniority in the team. If he switched to another team, what type of status would he havethere?

However, if Xiao Shiqin came….. Liu Hao felt like his position as vice-captain couldn’t be kept. Xiao Shiqin was clearly more suitable for the position. He even had the qualifications to replace Sun Xiang as the captain. How would the Club arrange everything? Liu Hao tried to search for answers from the manager Cui Li, but he didn’t get a satisfying response.

After thinking about it over and over again, Liu Hao still decided to stay because he had received information from the internal department. Not only was Xiao Shiqin transferring, his Mechanic Life Extinguisher was also transferring over.

An All Star player and an All Star Character. Despite Excellent Era getting relegated, the team’s strength had increased. Liu Hao couldn’t ignore it. He decided that he would sacrifice a year too and continue playing with Excellent Era. Next year, they would return to the Alliance and aim for the championship cup.

He believed that he would win more glory than he could ever achieve before with the current Excellent Era. Even though Xiao Shiqin was a danger to his position as vice-captain, he couldn’t be stripped of his seniority and foundation in Excellent Era. With the team’s current situation, Liu Hao felt like he would still be a senior within the practice room.

The day Xiao Shiqin arrived soon came for the conflicted yet expectant Liu Hao. But three days prior to Xiao Shiqin’s arrival, in a team conference, the Club unexpectedly sent ice-cold notifications to both Liu Hao and his best friend, He Ming.

The two of them had been bargaining chips for Xiao Shiqin’s trade and had been transferred to Team Thunderclap. They had three days to pack up their belongings and leave on the first of July.

Chapter 714: Trade

Besides the news of Xiao Shiqin transferring to Excellent Era, no other details were revealed because the transfer period hadn’t begun yet at that time. Leaking Xiao Shiqing’s transfer was already violating the rules. If they said too much, the Alliance might penalize them..

As a result, no one else besides the higher ups in the Club knew about the concrete details of the transfer up until three days ago, where everyone in the Club was notified that Xiao Shiqin’s transfer wasn’t a purchase, but a trade. Unfortunately, Liu Hao and He Ming had become the bargaining chips. They knew that their departure was a foregone conclusion. Ttraded players had practically no authority over the matter. It was entirely different from a purchase.

In a purchase, the Club and player would talk about breaking off the player’s current contract and then discuss the player’s contract with the new Club. During this process, the player’s willingness was conclusive. If the player refused to transfer, the Club could not do anything about it.

But this problem didn’t exist when trading players. When two Clubs traded players, they could directly trade contracts and continue fulfilling the obligations written in the contracts. The Alliance permitted it with the requirement that the new Club must carry out all of the clauses according to the original contract. During this process, the player had no power besides renouncing his or her current contract and returning to a free agent. In that case, the player would forcefully cancel the trade. However, breaking off the contract would naturally require the player to play the appropriate compensation written in the contract. The Club could also inform the Alliance and apply for other penalizations. The gains definitely didn’t make up for the losses.

Although these were the rules, the majority of Clubs would discuss their intentions with their players even for trades. If the Club was too forceful, wouldn’t it make their other players worry? But for this time’s transfer, Excellent Era didn’t give Liu Hao or He Ming any heads up, showing their decisiveness and determination for this transfer.

Liu Hao and He Ming were naturally furious after being told last minute to pack up their belongings and leave.

Liu Hao understood that this was their boss destroying the bridge after crossing the river.

Liu Hao could be considered as being on the frontlines in the battle to forcefully kick Ye Qiu out of the team. How could the Club not know of him performing sinister deeds up and down the line? He would even intentionally let the Club see his dirty work at times. The Club kept silence though and in these sorts of situations, silence indicated their support. The Club couldn’t openly order him to kick Ye Qiu out. There would be a lot of rumors in that case.

Liu Hao understood all of this, which was why he became he even more resolute in his actions. However, now he understood the Club’s cunning. Even though he helped the Club with their dirty task, there was nothing he could say if they kicked him out after the task was finished. What could he do? Take credit for kicking Ye Qiu out? The Club would simply refuse to admit it. He couldn’t just say "you understand" to clear up the issue.

He couldn’t draw outside support either. He couldn’t tell the public: after the Club is finished using you, they’ll throw you aside!

The public will ask: how did they use you?

You answer: I helped the team kick Ye Qiu out!

The Club would interrupt: When did we let you kick Ye Qiu out? You brute. To think Ye Qiu retired because of you. We have such poor eyes. We actually raised up such a thankless wretch…...

The whole truth would become clear and he would take all the blame. From then on, his name would be slandered, and the fans would find him despicable. How could he continue staying in the scene?

Liu Hao wasn’t stupid. He could only grind his teeth and endure it. Perhaps in the future, after he retired, he may be able to tell everyone of Club Excellent Era’s despicableness, but he had to consider his future as a pro player right now.

Thunderclap... even with Xiao Shiqin, the team had no hopes for the championship title. Liu Hao didn’t want to waste his youth with this kind of team. A player could only be transferred once during the transfer window. Therefore, he could not transfer from Thunderclap to another team this summer. He would need to wait for the next half of the season for the winter transfer period before acting.

This was Liu Hao’s plan for the future. While reflecting over his future for the past three days, he would also think of the scene, when Ye Qiu’s retirement had been announced and his departure from the team. Seven months had passed since then and now he had been forcefully sent away by Excellent Era.

If it were Ye Qiu in his position right now, would Ye Qiu choose to break off his contract and freely walk out from the entrance?

He definitely would…...

He didn’t know why, but Liu Hao was certain. But what about him? Break off his contract? That was just something he and He Ming had privately discussed out of pure anger. During this moment of anger, even he could feel that he was an ass in a lion’s skin. Yes, he didn’t have the courage nor the confidence in a life and death struggle.

In the end, he could only submit to his humiliation. After packing up his belongings and sending them to Team Thunderclap, he and He Ming planned on leaving today to Team Thunderclap.

The final moment before their departure, Liu Hao saw the fans welcoming Xiao Shiqin outside the entrance. The scene only made him more sullen.

Even now, Excellent Era still hadn’t announced the details of Xiao Shiqin’s transfer to the public. They would perhaps announce it once Xiao Shiqin officially joined. But by then, Liu Hao and He Ming would have already left to a new team. They couldn’t even enjoy a send off ceremony. They had a lot of fans in Excellent Era!

"Let’s go?" He Ming quietly said. He didn’t feel any better than Liu Hao. However, Liu Hao had been Excellent Era’s vice-captain and a senior member of the team. That drop in status felt by Liu Hao wasn’t something He Ming could understand.

Liu Hao nodded his head. His gaze moved away from the crowd of fans as he gave one last look at the place he had lived in ever since he had joined the competitive scene. At last, he and He Ming walked out of the room.

The corridor outside of their room was bustling with noise. The employees of the Club were scurrying back and forth. The boss had ran over to the Club early in the morning to inspect everything, so the employees couldn’t help but be prepared ahead of time. They traveled back and forth past Liu Hao and He Ming. None of them stopped to say anything to them.

They might not know about their transfer. But in any case, that wasn’t the main event of today.

When the two passed by the practice room, they saw a large banner inside welcoming Xiao Shiqin and felt the urge to burn it. Excellent Era’s boss, Tao Xuan, was also inside personally watching over the employees arrange everything. Out of the corner of his eye, he saw the two standing outside the door. Tao Xuan turned around and walked over. He extended his right hand with a smile on his face, but it was hard to say why exactly he was smiling.

When the boss walked over, many of the surrounding people tensed up. When they saw the two standing outside the door, they understood. Then, they saw the boss shake He Ming’s hand: "You’re going to leave? I must thank you two for your contributions to the club!"

His words couldn’t be anymore fake, but the boss was personally speaking. The employees behind Tao Xuan couldn’t help but feel moved.

Should he let out some tears? Liu Hao looked in disdain at those workers. Once Tao Xuan shook He Ming’s hand, he naturally extended his hands towards Liu Hao, who extended his hands out subconsciously, while thinking about what he should say to sour Tao Xuan’s good mood. He didn’t want to be thought of as sa fool.

At this moment, a loud noise suddenly came from the practice room. Something heavy had fallen to the ground. Tao Xuan turned around to look and his expression immediately changed.

"What’s going on? Please be more careful. Is everyone okay? Is the dropped item broken? It’s still early. There’s no need to be in a rush. Slowly does it." Tao Xuan said, while walking over to check what had happened. Liu Hao’s hand was still extended. In the end, he still looked like a fool.

After Tao Xuan handled the accident, would he still come back and shake his hand? No one knew, but Liu Hao didn’t have the face to continue waiting there with his hand extended. His expression pale, he said "Let’s go" and turned around to leave.

Liu Hao and He Ming walked over to the elevator and were unexpectedly blocked by two security guards.

"Vice-captain Liu and Little He." The two security guards politely greeted, but the next few words that came out of one of the security guard’s mouth infuriated them: "Manager Cui instructed us to accompany you two out."

"What’s that supposed to mean? Do you think we’d steal from the Club or bring explosives with us or something? Would you like to search us before leaving?" The two had endured a lot these past days. How could they have any patience? Liu Hao had even been cold-shouldered just earlier. This time, he finally blew up and roared loudly.

"You misunderstand." The security guard hastily said, "We’re bringing you through the side door. There’s a lot of people at the main entrance. You might not be able to get out, especially since you two are very popular in the Club!"

The two listened to his explanation and suddenly understood. However, the reason they weren’t permitted to leave through the main entrance wasn’t only because of that single reason. The main entrance was surrounded by a huge crowd of the team’s fans. If the two wanted to leave, it indeed wouldn’t be easy. Under normal circumstances, the two would definitely ask to go through the side door. But today wasn’t normal! The two really wanted to walk through the front entrance, patiently give signatures to their fans, and tell them of their departure. The fans were here to welcome Xiao Shiqin, but the two wanted to make these fans to send them off.

The Club still hadn’t announced the details of the transfer. Were they waiting for some reason? If the two leaked the information early, the Club’s plan be affected.

As a result, the Club arranged two security guards to send them off through the side door. Protecting them was certainly a justifiable reason, but that wasn’t the main reason. The Club knew that if they walked through the crowd, the atmosphere would change. It was better to take precautions and keep an eye on them!

"Ha ha. That’s not a problem. It’s not like we’ve never experienced how passionate our fans are. We can take it. Don’t worry about it." Liu Hao spoke coldly.

"It’s better if you listen to us! Otherwise, it’ll make things difficult for everybody!" The security guard urged.

"Difficult? What’s so difficult about it? This is our own matter. Could it be that if we don’t listen, you’ll tie us up and throw us out?" Liu Hao continued. If the two were forced out of the side entrance, it could certainly turn into a scandal.

"Of course not. If you two insist, then please go ahead!" The security guards let them through the elevator.

Chapter 715: You’re in Luck

Liu Hao and He Ming stepped into the elevator and headed down.

Liu Hao had come to a decision. The more the Club didn’t want him to do something, the more he definitely needed to do it. He didn’t dare disclose the matter of kicking Ye Qiu out and then being kicked out of the Club as a result, but ruining Xiao Shiqin’s welcome day could still be done. As the vice captain of the team, he was quite popular among Excellent Era’s fans. He believed that if news came out that he had been traded away, Excellent Era would certainly receive backlash from their fans.

The elevator soon reached the first floor. Liu Hao held his head up and puffed his chest out. Right when he was about to arrive at the exit, he was blocked by security guards once again.　

"You can’t go this way." This time, the security guard was much stiffer. He didn’t greet the two pro players and instead wore a grave expression on his face.

"And why not? I just want to leave through this way." Liu Hao didn’t care and positioned himself in such a way that he could force his way out.

This security guard was much tougher than the two security guards on the floor above. He blocked Liu Hao: "Sorry. Someone important is coming today. In order to prevent any accidents, no one is allowed to exit this way. Please go through the side exit."

No one.

Liu Hao was surprised by these word. He suddenly understood why the security guards above weren’t concerned. Arrangements had already been made on the first floor.

The two words "no one" didn’t allow for any form of objection. If Liu Hao tried to force his way through, the Club would be in the right: no one is permitted to go through. You’re no exception. If you try to force your way out, we have the right to stop you. This security guard was a huge guy. Don’t look at how Liu Hao and He Ming were two people. As pro players who spent all day playing games, their bodies weren’t exactly extremely fit. If the security guard stood in front of the door, they might not even be able to push him aside.

As for the excuse of preventing any accidents, Liu Hao knew arguing was pointless. If the security guard insisted on such an excuse, what could he do?

Helpless, Liu Hao could only grind his teeth and leave through the side exit with He Ming. When he exited through the side door, he saw security guards guarding the path to the main entrance. He knew that the two of them really would be departing from the Club sullenly.

Just because we had to leave through the side door doesn’t mean that there aren’t other ways!

Liu Hao was furious! Once they exited from the side door, there would be a road. Excellent Era couldn’t block off a public road, right? I’ll put in some effort and circle around then.

When Liu Hao stepped out from the side door, he didn’t call for a taxi and instead started walking towards the main entrance. He Ming immediately understood Liu Hao’s intention. He wasn’t as angry as Liu Hao was though and endured it.

"Let’s not?" He Ming urged Liu Hao.

"You don’t have to, but I can’t." Liu Hao’s anger had reached the heavens. He didn’t stop and continued to head towards the main entrance with large strides.

He Ming had a sense of comradery with Liu Hao. Seeing that Liu Hao refused to budge on this matter, he sighed and followed behind.

More and more people were gathering around the main entrance. The fans holding up banners had clearly come prepared. Some had simply passed by and saw the crowd. Who knew if they were actually fans of Glory or Excellent Era. The media received the news and sent reporters to take pictures. As for whether or not Excellent Era had invited them over or not, no one really knew. The cameramen only added to the excitement. Liu Hao angrily stomped over. Seeing that there were even cameras, he didn’t feel happy, but rather somewhat discouraged.

If he walked out from the main entrance like a star, he wouldn’t be afraid of any interviews, but now that he had circled around from the side entrance, his intentions would clearly come through in front of the cameras. When he walked closer, Liu Hao saw the reporter with the camera and felt even worse.

He recognized this reporter. The reporter could be considered to be employed by Excellent Era. He would always stand by Excellent Era’s side and never report anything bad about Excellent Era. He would only say good things. If this kind of reporter had come, Liu Hao was certain that his action of circling around to the main entrance would be written a great deal about. His little scheme would be dirtied by the reporter.

He might be able to ruin the atmosphere of the crowd, but from a long-term perspective, the bad press would certainly hurt him more in the end.

Liu Hao had originally been on the north side of the sidewalk. After surveying the situation, he quickly crossed the road without anyone noticing. He Ming didn’t understand why, but seeing how Liu Hao had suddenly changed his mind, he immediately followed after him.

After crossing the street, Liu Hao continued to walk towards the main entrance. He hadn’t given up yet! When he was across the street from the entrance, he didn’t directly walk into the crowd. He thought he could cover up his intentions by doing things this way. He wanted to avoid the crowd, but be "coincidentally seen by fans".

But being "coincidentally seen by fans" wasn’t easy! The street in front of Club Excellent Era’s main entrance was quite a big one. Even with the relationship between fans and pro players, the distance was a bit far.

Come on!

Liu Hao encouraged the fans. After entering their range, he slowed down his footsteps, hoping to give the fans more time to catch sight of him. After all, he only had one chance. Once he walked past them, it wasn’t like he could just go around and around until someone noticed him, no?

Unfortunately, the fans let Liu Hao down. After slowly walking past the crowd, no one noticed him. He really had been treated as some random passerby.

Liu Hao felt disappointed. Without any other options, he could only look back and see the crowd get smaller and smaller. He was quite sorrowful too. At this moment, he suddenly heard a voice in front of him: "Liu Hao?"

F*ck me! Right when he was at the end of the line, a glimmer of hope appeared! A burst of excitement filled Liu Hao’s heart. Who would have thought that someone would recognize him?

Liu Hao excitedly turned his head around, hoping this fan would hurry up and shout loudly to call people over from the crowd. That would be too perfect.

When he turned around to look at this fan clearly, Liu Hao’s bright eyes instantly dimmed. His mood became even darker than it had just been.

This person wasn’t a fan. Wasn’t that Ye Qiu?

The one person that Liu Hao didn’t want to see the most just happened to be Ye Qiu. When Ye Qiu retired, he had clapped his hands with joy. Seven months later, it was his turn to be kicked out from Excellent Era. Wouldn’t Ye Qiu laugh at him to death?

Liu Hao was conflicted, but he didn’t want to appear weak in front of Ye Qiu. If he clearly saw him but pretended that he didn’t see him, wouldn’t that make him seem afraid? Thus, Liu Hao brushed his emotion aside and greeted him.

"Morning!" Liu Hao gave a common greeting. He felt like such a greeting would best show his current stance.

"Morning to you too." Ye Xiu said.　

"The Club has something urgent going on. It’s not good to oversleep! I don’t have as much free time as you." Liu Hao said as he looked at the crowd of fans. He was feeling quite annoyed, but he still needed to make Ye Xiu feel bad.

"Hm? What does that have to do with you?" Ye Xiu said.

"How does that not have anything to do with me? I’m Excellent Era’s vice captain. I have to welcome such a skilled player into Excellent Era." Liu Hao said coldly.

"You’re willing to give up everything and even be put up for trade?" Ye Xiu said.　

"Of course." Liu Hao heard "give up everything". That was naturally a very good thing, so he had replied with an "of course", but when he thought about what he said, he realized…...

"How did you know?" Liu Hao couldn’t hold his lofty facade together anymore. Not getting flustered was already quite good.

"How could I not know?" Ye Xiu smiled.

"Su Mucheng told you!" Liu Hao suddenly realized. With Su Mucheng in Excellent Era, how could Ye Qiu not know what was happening? He felt so stupid. He actually wanted to show off in front of him, so he wouldn’t be laughed at, but now he had become an even bigger joke. Liu Hao really wanted to slam his head against a wall.

"It seems like you’re not happy with it? You weren’t prepared to leave Excellent Era?" Ye Xiu said.　

Liu Hao had been jabbed at his sore spot again. He had planned on leaving Excellent Era, but after hearing that Xiao Shiqin and his Life Extinguisher were coming to Excellent Era, his confidence in Excellent Era had been renewed. Who would have thought that he would become a bargaining chip. If he had been traded into a top team, he would have been fine with it, but Team Thunderclap... without Xiao Shiqin, how bad would the team be in the Alliance?

In front of Ye Qiu, Liu Hao refused to admit defeat. Everything he had done in Excellent Era stemmed from his enmity with Ye Qiu. No matter the situation, Liu Hao could always find something to hold onto against him: "I just happened to be unlucky, but I’m still doing better off than you. Next season, I’ll still be playing in the Pro Alliance. And you?" Liu Hao continued to challenge him.

"Unlucky? I don’t think so. I think you got lucky." Ye Xiu smiled.

"What do you mean?" Liu Hao didn’t understand.

"If you stayed in Excellent Era, then let alone this season, don’t even think about playing next season. Excellent Era has to go through the Revival Tournament, but unfortunately, they’ll have to face us." Ye Xiu said.

"True." Tang Rou had come over to see what was going on and nodded her head.

"You really do think too highly of yourself!" Liu Hao coldly sneered, "I really do want to see who will lose, but if you both take each other down, that’d be even better."

"Then I’m afraid you’ll be disappointed." Ye Xiu laughed.

"Humph, bye." Liu Hao turned around and was about to leave with He Ming, when he saw two people coming over. One had long hair, while the other had a thuggish face and a cigarette in his mouth. The two had slippers on, shuffling their way over. Liu Hao moved to the side to let them pass. These guys shouldn’t be messed with.

When the two passed by them, a "Yi?" suddenly came out. The guy with the cigarette backed up and looked at Liu Hao: "Aren’t you that guy?"

"Who?" The other person with long hair backed up and asked.

"That guy from Team Excellent Era!" The guy with the cigarette thought hard.

"That guy?" The other one seemed to only know how to ask questions.

"Right, Liu Gao!" The cigarette guy suddenly shouted.

"D*mn... are you stupid? His given name is pronounced Hao. We don’t know each other! Steamed Bun, hurry up and get away from him." Ye Xiu said.

"Yes, sir!" The guy with long hair immediately distanced himself. Whether it was Liu Gao or Liu Hao, he had no idea what was going on.

Chapter 716: Xiao Shiqin’s Arrival

Did these people come here specifically to humiliate me? Liu Hao had been called "Liu Gao" by Wei Chen, and Ye Qiu had mercilessly exposed it, but logically speaking, that shouldn’t have been the case. He just happened to be passing by this way. How could Ye Qiu have arranged this encounter beforehand?

Thinking of this, Liu Hao felt that it wouldn’t be right to flare up, when he heard the person next to him mutter: "Oh? It’s Hao? Not Gao?"

That person’s tone of voice made it sound like the name Liu Hao itself was a mistake; Liu Gao should be the correct name. The contempt in his voice made Liu Hao furious. He was just about to say something, when he heard Ye Xiu say: "Old Wei, don’t annoy him. He has to catch the Route 9 Bus!"

"Oh?" Wei Chen turned his head to look at him. Sure enough, a Route 9 Bus was slowly pulling up to the stop. He didn’t feel embarrassed at getting someone’s name wrong. He even patted Liu Hao’s shoulders as if they were good friends: "The bus is here. You’d better hurry!"

Route 9 Bus…...

Liu Hao felt like he had been humiliated again. The Route 9 Bus was indeed one way to get to the airport, but did he need to use such an economical method? Did they think he didn’t have the money to ride a taxi?

Wei Chen swaggered away. Liu Hao didn’t look at the incoming Route 9 Bus. He stood straight up and started waving to hail a taxi. Not long afterwards, a taxi pulled over. When he looked back at Happy Internet Cafe, he realized that they had already left. He didn’t know if they had seen him hail a taxi or not…...

"Hey, are you going or not!" The taxi driver interrupted Liu Hao’s thoughts. He sat in the taxi and left this damned place.

At Happy Internet Cafe, when they saw Liu Hao turn around and hail a taxi, they entered the Internet Cafe, but they didn’t stop to watch him. It was tiring, standing by the entrance the entire time. After going inside and finding a good angle, they could simply sit down and watch from the comfort of the internet cafe. Wei Chen followed along everyone else to here. He grabbed a wooden stool and sat down, gazing at the crowd and saying: "Is that idiot coming?"

One of Glory’s Four Master Tacticians was about to transfer to Excellent Era and become a formidable opponent for Happy in the Challenger League, so Wei Chen referred to him as an "idiot". However, Wei Chen wasn’t alone. Choosing to transfer to a relegated team like Excellent Era and needing to wait a year before joining the Pro Alliance again was certainly a controversial decision. Wei Chen wasn’t the only one who regarded him as an idiot. Wei Chen’s view was only because of his own position. Others actually thought he was being stupid.

"Tsk tsk, what a welcoming. He really is popular." Wei Chen sighed. Even though he had been Team Blue Rain’s former captain and could be considered an influential figure, he had never experienced such a grand event. At that time, the Alliance had only just been created. There weren’t nearly as many fans as there were now, let alone such passion. Now that he had decided to return to the pro scene, he couldn’t help but sigh as he compared the past with the present.

"Okay, let’s not be concerned about them. We still have other things to do. The new week has just begun!" Ye Xiu got up and headed upstairs. The results from last week’s wild boss hunting had been quite good. The various big guilds had their cake stolen away though and definitely wouldn’t stand still. What would they do today?

In the practice room on the second floor, they all logged on. Loulan Slash and the other three guild leaders were already online and waiting for him to log on. Last week, Ye Xiu hid himself using Enlightened Lord, but the results weren’t that good. He didn’t have a guild tag on his head, and yet he had still been noticed in the large-scale battles. After a few fights, he was already exposed. Enlightened Lord suddenly became the priority target of everyone.

For the few times that Enlightened Lord had successfully been killed, the guilds discovered that killing him didn’t have the desired effect! Was this Enlightened Lord really Ye Qiu? This was the real problem!

At this moment, some people thought: Ye Qiu doesn’t only have one account. It’s too naive to only target Enlightened Lord. After he dies, he just switches to a second account. Do we really have the ability to kill them all off one after the other without getting wiped out by our opponents?

In the end, apart from cursing out "Too despicable, too evil." What could the guilds do? They could only deal with the character, but not the person behind the character. The person, not the character, was the truly scary one.

Seeing these results, everyone stopped rushing to kill him as soon as he came out. If they killed him, he could just switch accounts. It would only make things worse too, because it would mess up their own formations. They might as well just go with the flow. If they encountered an opportunity, they would kill him. If they didn’t, they would regard him as their primary target and run into a dead end.

Ye Xiu logged onto Enlightened Lord. As soon as he came online, the four guild leaders messaged him. Four wild bosses had spawned in the Heavenly Domain between last night and now. The alliance failed to get any without Ye Xiu’s leadership . This was actually the alliance’s greatest weakness: their reliance on Ye Xiu. Without Ye Xiu to lead them, their competitive strength drastically decreased. Ye Xiu was irreplaceable. As a result, they couldn’t be competitive 24/7 like the Club guilds and could only be competitive for about two thirds of the time. Yet even in this kind of situation, they were still able to get 33 out of 74 wild bosses. These results were extremely terrifying. How could the various big guilds not be fearful?

"Call me if there’s any news." Ye Xiu replied to them. This was how snatching wild bosses worked. If there were no bosses, the rest of the time was for themselves.

Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Little Cold Hands were following the training program that Ye Xiu created for them. As for Ye Xiu, his work wasn’t limited to just the game. The two million RMB worth of materials had gradually been paid over the course of this week. Samsara wasn’t trying to drag the matter out, rather Ye Xiu hadn’t been prepared to receive them until now. They needed enough accounts to store all the materials. It was two million RMB worth of materials! How could the storages of a few accounts be enough? The storages of all of the accounts they had on hand were completely filled to the brim. Ye Xiu was using most of his free time to figure out how he should utilize these materials.

The Clubs had their own logistics departments. The pro players didn’t need to worry about researching how to create equipment. However, as a player from an older generation, Ye Xiu wasn’t like the young pro players who only knew how to play the game. In the early years, pro players had multiple responsibilities. They had to compete, manage the in-game guilds, and even research how to create self-made equipment to improve their own team’s strength. Even though the Clubs created their own logistics department to deal with these matters later on, it didn’t mean that their experience was wasted! They just didn’t put in as much energy or time as they had before. It was because of this that Team Samsara’s Tong Lin directly joined Samsara’s logistics department after retiring as a pro player. The dual guns used by Cloud Piercer, Wildfire and Shattered Frost, were mostly his work. Tong Lin’s contribution to the title Great Gunner couldn’t be understated.

　

At Happy, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Wei Chen’s Windward Formation both had Silver weapons. Steamed Bun and Tang Rou still needed one though. They might not need to worry too much about regular opponents in the Challenger League, but facing Excellent Era, a bunch of Orange equipment wasn’t going to cut it. Silver equipment was a must. Ye Xiu had to develop numerous Silver pieces of equipment for these characters. He needed time to organize everything.

Everyone in the practice room was busy doing their own thing. There was no news from Loulan Slash or the other guild leaders. At around ten o’clock, a sudden clamor from outside their window interrupted the silence. The noise was almost ear-piercingly loud. Everyone in the room jumped up out of their chairs in surprise. After staring blankly for a bit, they realized what had happened.

Even the windows were shaking from the noise. " XIAO SHIQIN! XIAO SHIQIN! XIAO SHIQIN!"

Xiao Shiqin had finally arrived.

None of the five players in the room pretended to be calm. They got up and went to the window to look outside. Compared to earlier that morning, there were who knew how many people at Excellent Era’s main entrance. Even a part of the road had been blocked off by the crowd. Fortunately, this road wasn’t a particularly busy one. It was strangely spacious too, so it didn’t actually cause any traffic.

The crowd surrounded a van stopped by the road. Ye Xiu recognized it. The van was a Ford E350 that Excellent Era rarely used. This time, it was being used to pick up Xiao Shiqin, which showed how much Excellent Era truly valued this All Star player.

The van didn’t directly go into the Club. Instead, it stopped right outside of the front entrance. Of course, before the fans could crowd in front of it, the security guards had quickly created a pathway. Excellent Era was well prepared for Xiao Shiqin’s arrival. They lacked the necessary manpower, so they even hired outside security to help.

Amidst the shouting from the fans, Xiao Shiqin finally stepped out of the car. As soon as his foot hit the ground, cheers instantly erupted, causing the electronic alarms of quite a few cars along the side of the road to go off. For a moment, the alarms added to the noise made by the fans.

Excellent Era hadn’t anticipated this would happen and it ruined the mood a bit, but from this, Xiao Shiqin’s popularity could be seen. Many fans heard the alarms go off and yelled even harder to suppress the noise created by the alarms.

Xiao Shiqin jumped with fright from the noise. A small team like Team Thunderclap couldn’t compare to the popularity of a famous team like Team Excellent Era. Along the way to the Club, the employees who received him said that there were many fans waiting for him to arrive. Xiao Shiqi didn’t think too much of it, but when he got off the car, he was stunned by the scene in front of him.

Xiao Shiqin truly felt like he had made a significant leap in his career.

Even though Excellent Era had been relegated, while Thunderclap was still fighting in the pro scene, from the amount of noise created just from his welcome, Xiao Shiqin could already feel that Thunderclap didn’t have such power. If Excellent Era was still in the Pro Alliance and stayed as a formidable competitor, what would the fans be like then?

Xiao Shiqin suddenly wanted to see this scene very much and he knew that the reason he came here was to make that scene a reality.

Once Xiao Shiqin finished thinking about what he wanted to say, he began speaking to the fans.

Chapter 717: Some Happy Some Worried

Club Excellent Era gathered the fans, the media, and had even reserved a car to pick Xiao Shiqin up from the airport. How could they just let Xiao Shiqin simply get off the car, walk through the main entrance, and end the event like that?

Inside, the Club had prepared a stage out in the open in order to officially announce Xiao Shiqin’s addition to Excellent Era. Liu Hao and He Ming being blocked from going through the main entrance wasn’t necessarily aimed towards them. Random people couldn’t just freely move around in such a carefully arranged area. Of course, two pro players being considered as random was a bit of a stretch.

On the path opened up by security, Xiao Shiqin greeted all of his new fans left and right, while walking towards Excellent Era’s main entrance. Even though he came from a smaller team, he was still an All Star player. Xiao Shiqin could cope with this kind of environment.

Right when Xiao Shiqin reached the main entrance, he suddenly stopped, staring at the team emblem hanging above the gate. The weather was good today. The ten o’clock sunlight reflected off the team emblem.

Once he stepped through this door, he would be walking on a new path in his career. Xiao Shiqin never doubted his feelings for Team Thunderclap, but like every other pro player, he had great ambitions. Unfortunately, Team Thunderclap couldn’t achieve what he wanted. Both sides understood and parted on good terms.

A new team. A new path. Xiao Shiqin needed to succeed to show that he hadn’t given up on Team Thunderclap for no reason.

Amid the cheers from the fans, Xiao Shiqin finally stepped through Club Excellent Era’s main entrance. The cheers reached their peak, drowning out the car alarms. On the second floor of Happy Internet Cafe, both Chen Guo and Wei Chen had unhappy expressions.

"How noisy." Chen Guo grumbled. She had gone from an admirer to a detractor. If she and Ye Xiu had never met, she would definitely be at the front of that crowd. Boss Chen had quite a reputation among the Excellent Era fans in the area, especially the ones who frequented Happy Internet Cafe. Those people regarded her highly as a leading figure among fans.

"He’s even enjoying it!" Wei Chen’s attack was mainly aimed at Xiao Shiqin. He had a bad impression of that "idiot" from the very beginning: "Let’s see if you can still smile next season!" Even though he said that, Wei Chen was feeling a bit weak in his heart. Team Excellent Era was truly a formidable opponent. It would arrogant and ignorant for anyone to think that they could guarantee a win facing Team Excellent Era. Even the new champions, Team Samsara, wouldn't dare be so confident facing Excellent Era’s new roster.

After Xiao Shiqin entered through the main entrance, the Club did not stop the fans from pouring in. The press conference was completely open to the public.

The media was already prepared. On stage, the owner of Excellent Era, Tao Xuan, personally came out. Next to him was the manager Cui Li and behind him were Team Excellent Era’s pro players.

Sun Xiang, Su Mucheng, Guo Yang, Shen Jian, Zhang Jiaxin, Wang Ze, Fang Fengran, and two new players scouted from the training camp: Zeng Shenghe, Meng Yongming.

Apart from the pro players, the director of the development department and the director of the public relations department stood in a rather inconspicuous corner.

All of the important figures in Excellent Era came out for Xiao Shiqin’s welcoming. On one hand, it was to show how much they valued him. On the other hand, it was a good opportunity to show the media and fans Excellent Era’s lineup and image for next season.

The pro players naturally received cheers from the crowd. Not all of them were shouting Xiao Shiqin’s name anymore. Some began to yell out their favorite player’s name. However, the fans quickly noticed that their vice-captain Liu Hao and He Ming were missing.

Everyone had come to this event, yet these two were missing. It let the media and fans realize something.

On stage, Excellent Era’s owner Tao Xuan personally made the opening statement, welcoming Xiao Shiqin to Team Excellent Era. Afterwards, the two shook hands. The fans still gave face despite their doubts and the cheers reached another peak.

Next, it was Xiao Shiqin’s turn to speak. Xiao Shiqin knew this would happen, so he was prepared.

"I’m still very sad about leaving Team Thunderclap...." Xiao Shiqin started, but he didn’t talk too much about his feelings for Team Thunderclap. After all, this was Excellent Era’s venue. Everyone around him was a supporter of Excellent Era. Talking too much about Thunderclap wouldn’t be appropriate. After saying a few words about Thunderclap, XIao Shiqin immediately began talking about Excellent Era. He didn’t compare the two teams. He mainly emphasized how he thought highly of Excellent Era’s future, which was exactly what the higher ups of Excellent Era wanted to hear. Inviting Xiao Shiqin to join was to prove this point to the fans. Xiao Shiqin’s words further strengthened it. Excellent Era was extremely satisfied with how Xiao Shiqin stuck to his principles.

"I hope that along with my teammates and all of you, we’ll be able to walk through this low point together and restore our former glory as the three-time champions!"

Xiao Shiqin ended his speech under the thunderous applause. An experienced team captain like Xiao Shiqin naturally knew what to say at the right moment.

Practically all team captains in the Alliance possessed this trait, but Tao Xuan was feeling a bit emotional as if he had never seen someone like that before. After all, everything had exceptions. Team captains who weren’t like this had appeared in the Alliance. There were only two extreme cases though. One was Zhou Zekai. He spoke through his playing on stage. Off stage, he pretty much didn’t say anything. The other case was Excellent Era’s former captain, Ye Qiu, who Tao Xuan had forced out. Ye Qiu was even worse than Zhou Zekai. He wouldn’t even show up to press conferences. At first, it didn’t matter too much. But as the Alliance grew day after day, this sort of behavior from a team captain was difficult to bear. Excellent Era had put in who knew how much effort to let the media and fans finally accept such a figurehead as the team’s captain.

Ye Qiu was finally gone. Now there was Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin to fill in the gaps in Tao Xuan’s heart. He almost wanted to cry…..

After the speeches ended, Excellent Era finally announced the details of Xiao Shiqin’s transfer. They had used Liu Hao and He Ming to trade.

On paper, trading Liu Hao, He Ming, and their two characters for Xiao Shiqin alone and his Life Extinguisher was a bit of a loss. However, this trade had other implications, which weren’t convenient to tell the public. And after seeing the life brought back to Excellent Era from Xiao Shiqn’s arrival, this trade couldn’t be seen just by what was on paper.

There were a lot of tricky issues that needed to be mentioned with this trade though. For example, would trading players instead of purchasing the transfer be met with resistance from the players? Did Excellent Era not want to spend the money because they were worried about the Challenger League? However, Excellent Era had put in great efforts to deal with the media. In the press conference afterwards, all of the reporters invited would show restraint. Both parties knew exactly what would be asked and what wouldn’t be asked, so nothing troublesome came up for Excellent Era. Everything went harmoniously. Regarding the transfer, Excellent Era said things like "we respect the choices of our players and we hope that they do well in Team Thunderclap".

That morning, Excellent Era immersed themselves in joy. Under their careful operation, nothing unexpected happened. While some were happy, others were worried. Apart from Liu Hao and He Ming, at Club Tiny Herb, there were was one person packing his belongings and getting ready to leave.

In Qiao Yifan’s room, Gao Yingjie quietly watched him pack his bags. Perhaps he should help him, but he didn’t want to help him. If he packed slower, Qiao Yifan would at least be able to stay for that much longer.

Gao Yingjie truly didn’t want his good friend to leave, but the decision had already been made.

Pro player contracts in the Alliance typically started on July 1st and ended on June 30th of some other year. As a result, there were always players whose contracts had expired on June 30th. If the Club wanted the player to stay, the Club would always extend the contract before the end date. This year, on June 30th, Qiao Yifan’s contract would expire. Unfortunately, it wasn’t yet June 30th and the Club had already notified him that he wasn’t a part of Team Tiny Herb’s future plans. Once the contract expired, he could search for another path forward.

Search for another path?

Qiao Yifan smiled bitterly. He had never come out on stage in an official match for even a single second. A player like him was usually called "the team member who was closest to a water dispenser". Yes, his value in the team was perhaps as useful as serving tea to the other team members.

He wasn’t a part of Team Tiny Herb’s future plans, but what team would want a water dispenser like him their future plans?

The future of a championship team?

What a joke. With Gao Yingjie’s existence, all of the spotlight shined onto him. Qiao Yifan’s contract wasn’t renewed, which was proof that he didn’t belong in a championship team. Perhaps in the past, he might have been, but that notion had quickly been wiped away. For a player like him, it wasn’t a question of whether a team could find a use for him, but rather if they would even notice him. At least, when June 30th came, Qiao Yifan still hadn’t received any offers from another team.

His status wasn’t enough for someone to want to pay him to join. He could offer his services for free, wait foolishly for something to happen, or leave the pro scene. What other options did he have?

"Yifan… what do you plan to do?" Gao Yingjie was worried about what choice Qiao Yifan would make. He knew about his good friend’s current situation. With his current position in Tiny Herb, if he insisted, maybe he could rudely and unreasonably demand that Qiao Yifan stay, but Gao Yingjie wasn’t someone who did that sort of thing. He could only respect the Club’s decision, while worrying for his friend’s future. He didn’t know what he could do.

Me?" Qiao Yifan smiled. He didn’t seem to be too distressed.

"I’m going to go pay a visit to a certain Internet Cafe." Qiao Yifan said.

Chapter 718: The Golden Generation

"Internet Cafe?" Gao Yingjie was puzzled at Qiao Yifan’s reply. He even thought he had heard wrong. When Qiao Yifan confirmed it with a nod of his head, Gao Yingjie noticed that he had finished packing his belongings.

Qiao Yifan only had one suitcase, stuffed with his clothing. The other things had been provided by the Club. New players didn’t have the qualifications to request anything. In comparison, many famous players bought their own residences. The Club provided them with a room, but it was used more as a rest stop. However, since pro players often moved around quite a bit, they would one day move to a different city, so not all players bought their own homes.

"Where did you say you were going?" Gao Yingjie still had his doubts towards Qiao Yifan’s reply.

"I’m going to a place, so I can continue practicing and improving." Qiao Yifan smiled, "Don’t worry. I’ll come back."

"Oh..."

"But I’m afraid that when we meet again, we won’t be teammates. It’s too bad that we never got the chance to play alongside each other in a match." Qiao Yifan said.

"That’s okay. We’ll always be friends!" Gao Yingie said.

"You’re right." Qiao Yifan smiled.

"I’ll send you off?"

"Sure."

The two youths walked out of the Club together. After exiting through the main gate, one of them got on a car, while the other stayed. They waved goodbye and from then on, the two would walk different paths.

City H, Club Excellent Era.

The welcome ceremony for Xiao Shiqin went on for the entire morning. It ended at around noon.

The fans left, filled with hope and excitement, while Xiao Shiqin’s understanding of the Club Excellent Era had only just begun. He met with the pro players and the employees of the different departments, which took up the afternoon. Excellent Era was very content with Xiao Shiqin. Xiao Shiqin found no issues receiving such courtesy either.

Dinner that day was nothing out of the ordinary. There were just more people than usual. Tao Xuan personally attended it too. However, at this moment, the main character was no longer Xiao Shiqin. Sun Xiang had transferred last winter, arriving half a year before Xiao Shiqin. He was also someone who Tao Xuan valued greatly and couldn’t be treated coldly just because of Xiao Shiqin’s arrival. In Tao Xuan’s heart, Sun Xiang was the true core and ace player of the team.

At dinnertime, Tao Xuan sat between these two, chatting cheerfully with them. The other team members couldn’t help but be envious. In reality, Team Excellent Era wasn’t so harmonious or stable. They were a relegated team, after all. With so many players in the team, how could they not have any plans for themselves? Some were willing to bet on Team Excellent Era’s future, while others weren’t. However, they didn’t need to make their decision on July 1st. The transfer window opened between July 1st and August 31st. During these two months, there was time for them to survey the situation first.

Especially for the players in the main roster. Who didn’t want to have a few offers? Relegated teams were often shopped around by the other teams as if they were supermarkets. However, most relegated teams were crappy, so the supermarket goods were of limited quality. Excellent Era was different though! Excellent Era’s relegation could be considered a miracle. No one ever doubted the skill level of Team Excellent Era’s players. When Excellent Era was officially relegated, who knew how many Clubs contacted Excellent Era or their players.

Inviting Xiao Shiqin to join the team was not only to appease the fans and give them confidence in Excellent Era’s future, but also to tell the other Clubs: Excellent Era isn’t finished yet. Don’t think of us as a supermarket. In fact, we’re only growing stronger! Did you see? We were even able to grab an All Star player like Xiao Shiqin despite being relegated!

Inside the team, Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin needed to be won over. As for everyone else, preparations had been made. Xiao Shiqin’s addition to the team could be used as an opportunity too. However, you cannot get fat with only one mouthful. There was an order that needed to be followed. Work had to be completed step by step. Right now, winning over Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin was most important.

Tao Xuan chatted with these two core members, while also being mindful of the other players in the team. From time to time, he would say a few things to everyone and even talk with a few one on one. He didn’t leave anyone completely out.

However, there was one person who was difficult to deal with.

Su Mucheng.

These days, even though Su Mucheng participated in everything the Club required, her heart wasn’t there. When Tao Xuan talked to her for a bit, her only replies were "Oh", "Mm", "Ah".

"Ha ha. Why are you like Zhou Zekai all of a sudden, Mucheng?" Tao Xuan joked. Everyone laughed at the joke that their boss made. As for how Su Mucheng would react, everyone had their own thoughts. Only Xiao Shiqin was a bit puzzled. He and Su Mucheng weren’t strangers. Both of them had joined the competitive scene in season four. The rookies from that year were considered as the Alliance’s golden generation because a huge number of the rookies from that season ended up becoming All Star players.

Apart from Su Mucheng and Xiao Shiqin, there was Team Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou, Team Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian, Team Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie, Team Misty Rain’s Chu Yunxiu, Team Void’s Li Xuan, Team Royal Style’s Tian Sen, and Team Tiny Herb’s Li Yibo. All of them were now famed All Star players and all of them started in season four. In addition, all of them immediately became core members of their respective teams. Zhang Xinjie even helped Han Wenqing end Team Excellent Era’s consecutive championship victories, becoming the first rookie in Glory history to win the championships as a part of the main roster.

The golden generation was not just in name.

These players even created their own chat group called "The Golden Generation". They weren’t really being arrogant. It was named in a joking manner. In reality, the rookies each year always created their own group to talk to each other. That year, they just happened to call it "The Golden Generation". The other difference was that the majority of rookies had difficulty standing out. However, their golden generation immediately came out as talents in the main roster. That topic wasn’t as prominent for them.

They happily chatted together in the group chat, so their relationships with each other were naturally quite good. There were two female players in their group too, and Su Mucheng was an extremely pretty one at that. When they were bored, they would tease her. They didn’t act any differently from normal people. The players from the golden generation were on good terms with each other. Xiao Shiqin and Su Mucheng could be considered as friends. When he came to Excellent Era, he thought of how apart from Yuwen Zhou and Huang Shaotian, no one else from the golden generation was on the same team together. Now, he would be with one through his transfer to Excellent Era. But when he saw how Su Mucheng didn’t seem to have her heart here, he felt a bit puzzled.

With his understanding of Su Mucheng, he didn’t think she was acting this way because of him. After seeing Su Mucheng reply with simple ahs and ohs to Tao Xuan, he could see that Su Mucheng might have some conflict with the team. It seemed like there really were internal issues in the team. And with the problem being on Su Mucheng, Xiao Shiqin immediately thought of the rumors related to Ye Qiu’s retirement.

Just when he was about to get up and talk to her, Tao Xuan’s attention switched to him and Sun Xiang: "I’ll bring you guys to a place in a bit."

"Ah?" Xiao Shiqin was surprised: "Where?"

"It’s very close." Tao Xuan laughed.

Xiao Shiqin glanced at Sun Xiang. Sun Xiang shrugged his shoulders, indicating that he didn’t know.

"Let’s eat, let’s eat." Tao Xuan smiled as he said to everyone. In reality, he was quite angry at Su Mucheng.

Truthfully, he originally didn’t plan on keeping Su Mucheng. He wasn’t worried about not getting a good price for her. However, Su Mucheng herself refused. It wasn’t possible for another Club to purchase a player without the player’s approval. As for a player trade, Su Mucheng only had a year left in her contract, making it a big obstacle. No one was willing to trade a valuable player, who could leave the next year. So even though Excellent Era could trade players, it would be hard to negotiate any good deals with Su Mucheng’s situation. And the problem was that Su Mucheng refused to extend her contract with Excellent Era. She also refused to be bought or traded to another Club. All of this clearly indicated that she planned on leaving on her own once the contract expired.

Tao Xuan was depressed at this issue! Such a valuable player couldn’t even be sold for money. Even worse, for a player like Su Mucheng with incredible business value, the sponsors required her to appear on stage a certain number of times or else their sponsorship money would be reduced. But for the current Excellent Era? They were relegated….. The Challenger League matches didn’t count. The amount of money that Su Mucheng brought through sponsorships would certainly be significantly reduced. The sponsors wouldn’t be happy either! But there was nothing they could do. He hadn’t expected Excellent Era to have been relegated. It was a big miscalculation on his part!

Such a profitable player would only remain for the Challenger League. After the team returned to the Alliance, she would just wag her tail at them and leave. It didn’t fit in with Tao Xuan’s plan at all. There was nothing he could do though. He couldn’t sell her even if he wanted to, but leaving her in the team was a problem too. Su Mucheng made it even worse by pretending to be like Zhou Zekai and keeping silent. Tao Xuan was at wit’s end. He knew very well that Su Mucheng was just waiting for the contract to expire. Afterwards, she would go look for Ye Qiu. Who knew if Ye Qiu had told her to make this move!

Ye Qiu!

Tao Xuan was about to go and pay a visit to their former team captain. He was bringing these two new core members of Excellent Era along with him too. He really wanted to see just how confident Ye Qiu would be, when facing them.

Chapter 719: A Visit

In the practice room of the second floor of Happy Internet Cafe, the people there continued to play the game as usual, but the mood in the room was somewhat downcast. Excellent Era’s grand welcoming for Xiao Shiqin angered Chen Guo and Wei Chen. On the other hand, Ye Xiu wasn’t as emotional as the other two. Steamed Bun had no idea who Xiao Shiqin was and Tang Rou wasn’t afraid of anyone. Xiao Shiqin’s arrival didn’t bother these three at all.

The reason that these three weren’t happy was because their boss hunt didn’t go as well as they had planned.

The problem wasn’t them, but rather that their opponents were a lot stronger than before.

Especially Tyrannical Ambition. After a few exchanges, Ye Xiu was certain that Tyrannical Ambition had an absolute expert on their side. On Tyrannical Ambition’s side, there was a single heavily guarded Cleric. Ye Xiu immediately knew that Zhang Xinjie had personally come out to the game.

Both Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie were skilled in tactics. Although they mainly specialized in five versus five team battles, in large scale battles, their impact on the battlefield was far greater than someone like Zhao Yuzhe, who could kill a few more players than the others at best. With Zhang Xinjie’s help, Tyrannical Ambition’s fighting strength practically doubled. Their elites were already widely reputed as powerful. As a result, Tyrannical Ambition immediately won themselves a huge advantage in the competition for bosses. Even though Ye Xiu didn’t lose to Zhang Xinjie in tactics, their troop’s fighting strength lost to Tyrannical Ambition’s by quite a huge margin.

Their numbers advantage wasn’t actually much of an advantage. A top guild like Tyrannical Ambition only sent out two elite groups, but that didn’t mean their side only had two elite groups. Which of their branch guilds didn’t have their own elite groups? The only reason that the guilds sent out two groups was so that they didn’t waste too many people’s time. At the same time, they didn’t want every wild boss fight to become a world war. The big guilds didn’t want that. The small guilds even less so. In fact, they might not even have the resources to sustain such fighting. Thus, Ye Xiu and the alliance didn’t want to fight by overwhelming the opponents with a sea of people. It was better to follow the unwritten rules like everyone else.

But today’s results ended pitifully for the alliance. Tyrannical Ambition was the strongest guild, but the other guilds either found an alliance or had come to an agreement. The competition for bosses instantly became complicated. Six bosses had spawned today, but Ye Xiu and the alliance failed to get a single one. How could he be feeling good? Loulan Slash and the other allied guild leaders also sighed. Even though Ye Xiu had given them a warning before by letting them know that this week would be the most difficult, no one expected such a disparity compared to last week, not even Ye Xiu. It was unpredictable that even Zhang Xinjie had personally came.

Zhang Xinjie coming to the game wasn’t likely at the request of the Club guilds. This action could be considered as made by the Club as a whole. It seemed like Tyrannical Ambition was about to make a huge move. During the summer break, the Club even had their vice-captain come out. This move showed just how much the Club valued the upcoming season. Zhang Xinjie had been with Team Tyranny today too. It didn’t look like he was helping out just for fun.

Loulan Slash and the others were still distressed by today’s bosses. Ye Xiu was thinking deeper though.

"What do we do?" They asked Ye Xiu.

"Zhang Xinjie isn’t that hard to deal with." Ye Xiu said.

"What?" Their eyes lit up, but then again, if he wasn’t hard to deal with, then why didn’t they win even a single boss today? Of those six bosses, Tyrannical Ambition actually got three of them. Three in one day! That was an exceptional harvest. They were only a single guild. They didn’t need to split their harvest with four or five others.

"He follows his sleep schedule very strictly. We’ll just have to be more active when he’s sleeping." Ye Xiu said.

"Ah?" The four guild leaders hadn’t thought that dealing with Zhang Xinjie would involve something outside the game.

"This is the most economical and simplest method." Ye Xiu said.

"Oh, that’s true. It’s very reliable." Yue Ziqin said.

Zhang Xinjie was like Ye Xiu. There was no point in killing his character. What mattered was the person controlling the character. However, Zhang Xinjie’s strict self-discipline was famous in Glory. For Ye Xiu and these guild leaders, changing their sleep schedule was something they often did, but for Zhang Xinjie, that would make headlines for gaming news. Simply avoiding Zhang Xinjie would certainly be an effective strategy.

"But we’ll only be able to play for a third of the day. If he plays like this everyday, we’ll lose out on quite a lot." Yue Ziqin said.

"We’ll think of something else for the other two thirds of the day! We were caught unprepared today. If we have a better understanding of them, we might not lose." Ye Xiu said. He glanced at Wei Chen. He could finally employ the mole in Samsara. How could he use Samsara’s elite troops to his advantage?

Ye Xiu thought to himself, when suddenly, someone knocked on their practice room’s door.

"Who is it?" Chen Guo called out.

An employee from Happy Internet Cafe pushed the door open a bit and said: "Boss, someone’s asking for you."

"Who? Tell them to come over." Chen Guo said.

"Okay." The employee didn’t say who it was. He closed the door and left.

"I’ll go take a look." Chen Guo told the employee to have them come over themselves, but she still got up. However, just when she got up, the door was pushed open again and the employee stood to the side: "They’re here."

The people in the practice room raised their heads to see who it was. Some felt like the people outside seemed familiar, while some felt like they should recognize them. The only ones who completely recognized them were Chen Guo and Ye Xiu.

"Hm? Is this your practice room? Not bad!" The first person to come in laughed. Tao Xuan, Excellent Era’s owner. A powerful owner of a huge Club praising Happy Internet Cafe’s small practice room felt insincere. It almost sounded like he was ridiculing them.

To the left of him was the young and arrogant Sun Xiang. To the right was Xiao Shiqin. Because Tao Xuan had kept it a mystery on the way here, Xiao Shiqin was even more surprised and serious than Ye Xiu and Chen Guo. He wrinkled his brow and pushed his glasses up. He was quite nearsighted and didn’t feel confident in his eyeglasses. After adjusting his glasses and squinting, he finally confirmed: "Senior Ye Qiu?"

Yes, in front of Ye Xiu, the golden generation was still several generations younger than someone from the first generation.

Chen Guo was already feeling upset upon seeing Tao Xuan and Sun Xiang. She was about to shout "Who let you in?" However, XIao Shiqin’s tone of voice was very polite, so Chen Guo didn’t shout in the end. Ye Xiu got up and greeted Xiao Shiqin: "Oh, Little Xiao’s here. Sit anywhere you’d like!"

As for the other two, Ye Xiu gestured towards the sofa in the practice room and said "Let’s sit there."

"Oh, Xiao Shiqin. I was about to say you looked a bit familiar." Wei Chen stood up at this moment.

"You are?" Xiao Shiqin asked. The other side spoke very casually as if they were close, but Xiao Shiqin didn’t seem to recognize him at all.

"Wei Chen." Wei Chen introduced himself.

"Team Blue Rain’s former captain?" Xiao Shiqin immediately recalled.

"Ha ha, that’s right. That’s me." Wei Chen was quite happy that Xiao Shiqin immediately knew who he was. He felt as if he were famous. In reality, he was just lucky to run into Xiao Shiqin. As a master tactician, Xiao Shiqin might not have even interacted with Wei Chen before, but he still had that information in his head. In comparison, a normal, younger player…..

"Wei Chen. Who’s that?"

See, there’s a younger person right there. Sun Xiang had never heard of Wei Chen’s name before. Sun Xiang repeated it in his head, but still couldn’t come up with anything, so he asked.

"Of course you don’t know. At that time, you were still playing around with your little JJ!"

Sun Xiang instantly turned red. He was no stranger to trash talk, but it was his first time hearing such a straightforward and vulgar insult. In particular, after Wei Chen finished speaking, he turned his head to look at Sun Xiang. Who knew what he was imagining in his head?

"What did you say!" Sun Xiang’s counterattack was quite terrible.

Tao Xuan was also surprised! He had met Wei Chen before. It had been many years since though, so he hadn’t recognized him. After the introduction, he immediately remembered and was surprised that he was with Ye Qiu. By the time he reacted, the two sides had already started butting heads. Sun Xiang’s response made even Tao Xuan extremely disappointed. However, Sun Xiang was still a young player, after all. He couldn’t compare to those older fellows. Not every player had this kind of talent like Huang Shaotian.

"Ha ha, so it’s captain Wei Chen. I apologize for not recognizing you sooner. We’ve met before, right?" Tao Xuan hastily said to cover up Sun Xiang’s terrible response. Tao Xuan wanted to show Ye Qiu their strength, but Ye Qiu hadn’t even said anything yet and Wei Chen shut Sun Xiang down.

"Who are you?" Wei Chen asked. It was hard to say if he was sincere or not. Only he would know.

"Tao Xuan." Tao Xuan introduced himself.

"Oh, Excellent Era’s owner?"

"Correct." Tao Xuan nodded his head.

"When is Excellent Era disbanding?" Wei Chen asked.

"Why would we disband?" Tao Xuan was still smiling. He wouldn’t be so childish as to be furious at such words.

"You’ve already been relegated. Why wouldn’t you disband?" Wei Chen said. Before Tao Xuan could reply, he said to Xiao Shiqin: "Little Xiao, right? You seem like a good person, but why are your so stupid? Excellent Era’s already sinking and yet you jump on board. Are you thinking that the world’s not ending soon enough?"

Xiao Shiqin heard Wei Chen’s taunt, but only smiled in response. He knew that Wei Chen was just trash talking. He wouldn’t try and explain his reasoning to him, so he just smiled. He was more concerned about why the boss brought him and Sun Xiang here.

"Getting relegated isn’t the end of the world. Speaking of which, you retired many years ago. Aren’t you also struggling?" Tao Xuan had some skill. He guessed Wei Chen’s intentions and countered.

"My struggle spells disaster for you! To think Excellent Era would fall by my hands. Ye Qiu, you’d better not stop me when the time comes!" Wei Chen said.

Ye Xiu finally had a chance to speak. He laughed: "I hope we come across Excellent Era someday."

Chapter 720: The Drunkard’s Heart Isn’t in the Cup

Wei Chen’s trash talk was rather straightforward. Sun Xiang had stomped the ground in anger, but Tao Xuan and Xiao Shiqin didn’t have much of a reaction. However, Ye Xiu’s words cut deeper into their hearts. Even Xiao Shiqin started to sweat.

I hope we come across Excellent Era someday.

It sounded like a reasonable statement, but who would ever think a championship team like Excellent Era would be eliminated by some random players in the Challenger League? Ye Xiu was telling Tao Xuan not to be so confident, but there really shouldn’t be any reason for Excellent Era not to be confident. Their team was simply too heaven-defying when placed in the Challenger League.

No one but Tao Xuan himself would know what he was feeling towards these words, but he clearly heard the implied ridicule. He replied: "Ha ha! How come it sounds like these words are more appropriate for you? How’s it going? How’s your preparation for the Challenger League going? Are the people sitting here your teammates?"

It was all clear now.

Xiao Shiqin finally understood.

Even a blind person could see that Ye Qiu and Excellent Era had some sort of conflict with each other. The two sides evidently didn’t part on good terms like he and Team Thunderclap had. After Ye Qiu announced his retirement, it seems like he wanted to create his own team and return to the Pro Alliance. Things happened to play out like a drama and Excellent Era actually ended up relegated. The two sides unexpectedly became enemies in the Challenger League.

It was obvious why Tao Xuan brought them over to pay Ye Qiu a visit.

For them, it could be considered a demonstration of their strength. For the other side, it would put them under greater pressure. At the same time, it was a warning to Xiao Shiqin that their run in the Challenger League wouldn’t be easy. With an opponent like Ye Qiu hiding in their midst, they couldn’t relax.

Yes, they couldn’t relax.

How could Xiao Shiqin dare to underestimate a God like Ye Qiu? He began playing Glory precisely during Team Excellent Era’s dominance in the Alliance under Ye Qiu’s lead. When he became a pro player, Team Excellent Era had just become three-time champions and Ye Qiu’s fame was at its peak.

Ye Qiu’s influence on their generation of players was incomparably deep. How many of them grew up studying Ye Qiu’s playstyle? Underestimate Ye Qiu? Maybe players from the newer generation like Sun Xiang might, but for Xiao Shiqin, he didn’t dare to even think of it.

Our opponent is Ye Qiu…...

Xiao Shiqin understood what Tao Xuan wanted to tell him. He wasn’t a person who gossiped much and didn’t have too much interest in understanding the grudges between Ye Qiu and Excellent Era. As opponents, Ye Qiu wasn’t a stranger to him. He grew up watching Ye Qiu play in the Alliance. After becoming a pro player, he had fought against him many times before. At that time, he had been looking for ways to defeat Team Excellent Era. Now, he had become a member of Team Excellent Era, and his number one opponent was unexpectedly Team Excellent Era’s former captain, Ye Qiu. In any case, they could not lose this fight. There was no leeway in the Challenger League.

"What exactly are you guys here for?" Seeing Tao Xuan acting all delighted, Chen Guo felt like she needed to show that she existed.

"Nothing really." Tao Xuan smiled, "I just wanted to bring our captain and vice-captain to pay a visit to their senior and see if any advice could be given to them."

"Advice?" Tang Rou became excited, "How about a spar?"

"Huh?" Tao Xuan was a bit surprised. He took a look at her. That was just something he had said! He had no intentions of bringing these two All Stars to challenge anyone. They didn’t even have their account cards on them!

"Who’s going first?" Tang Rou was already eager to give it a try.

"They’re not going up together?" Steamed Bun asked.

"That’s not good, right?" Tang Rou hesitated.

Sun Xiang couldn’t help but want to give it a go, but Xiao Shiqin was calm. He spoke first: "There’s no need for us to spar. We’ll see each other again on stage sooner or later. We’re simply here to say hi to our senior."

"That’s right." Tao Xuan laughed. He didn’t mind Xiao Shiqin taking matters into his own hands. Team Excellent Era currently needed someone who could take the initiative and make firm decisions. Although Team Excellent Era appointed Sun Xiang as team captain and Xiao Shiqin as vice-captain,Tao Xuan was certain that the person calling the shots would certainly be Xiao Shiqin.

Sun Xiang didn’t have much desire to bear the responsibilities of a team captain, but he liked the title of team captain. As a result, Tao Xuan didn’t bother making trouble by switching his position to something else. Xiao Shiqin’s position as vice-captain was enough to lead the team. Tao Xuan believed that an experienced player like Xiao Shiqin would be able to understand his intentions and perform his duties appropriately.

Just like now, he was very satisfied with how Xiao Shiqin stood out and gave his reply. On the other hand, Sun Xiang’s eagerness only made him sigh: he really is young. This type of willingness to fight was meaningless to them. What were Sun Xiang’s and Xiao Shiqin’s statuses? Against those random people that Ye Qiu had found from who knew where, of course they should win. If they happened to lose, that would be a huge loss of face. It would also increase the other side’s morale and confidence.

Sun Xiang didn’t consider this sort of lose-lose situation. He saw that the other side wanted to challenge him, so he wanted to beat them. That was it.

Xiao Shiqin clearly thought of the consequences and stopped it from happening. He simply restricted the situation to only talking.

Tang Rou saw that there was no fight to be had. Her enthusiasm waned and she went back to focusing on the game. She knew why the other side came, but she had no place in their talks, so she didn’t bother with it.

However, the way she didn’t put Sun Xiang or Xiao Shiqin in her eyes attracted their attention. Truthfully, when Team Excellent Era had been relegated and Ye Qiu was confirmed to be their opponents, Tao Xuan had been anticipating this moment for awhile.

He began paying attention to any information on Ye Qiu. He gathered any conjectures in front of him, such as what pro-level experts he had on his side.

These were just conjectures though. Tao Xuan didn’t want to be bogged down by conjectures and not facts. He wanted to use this opportunity to give them a greeting, while probing out Ye Qiu’s team to see what type of people he had. He wanted to know the background of these various experts. If there really were so many Glory experts, how could they all have been dug out by Ye Qiu? If so, those Club workers, whose job was to pay attention to any potential talents, were too useless, no?

When he walked through the door, he saw Wei Chen. Then, he saw the classes used by Tang Rou and Steamed Bun from their screens.

Battle Mage, Brawler.

These two classes completely matched the reports given by their guild, Excellent Dynasty. Tao Xuan felt like his trip here wasn’t a waste. He had a much clearer grasp of Ye Qiu’s strength now. However, seeing that there were 12 computers in the practice room... was it supposed to be one for each player? It was already quite late, so it would be very normal if not all of them were still playing in the practice room.

Thinking of this, Tao Xuan felt like he may have been a bit hasty. It was currently vacation time and it was late at night. Not all of Ye Qiu’s team might have shown up! If he directly asked, it would be too obvious. The other side could simply lie. Right now, the biggest advantage that Ye Qiu possessed was that Excellent Era had no knowledge of his team. Even though Excellent Era had Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin as their core, Sun Xiang was using One Autumn Leaf, which Ye Qiu couldn’t be any more familiar with. Xiao Shiqin was no stranger to Ye Qiu either.

I need to find other opportunities to scout him out!

All of these thoughts sounded complicated, but Tao Xuan tidied them up in an instant. Just when he was about to say something, there was another knock on the practice room door. The same employee stuck his head in and said: "Boss, there’s someone looking for you again!"

"Who is it this time?" Chen Guo wasn’t in a good mood. Excellent Era had brought two All Star level players to show off their strength. How could she be happy?

"He says his name is Qiao Yifan." The employee said.

"Oh?" Chen Guo turned to look at Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu immediately took note of the name.

"So Yifan’s already here!" Ye Xiu headed towards the door.

"Who is it?" Steamed Bun asked.

"One Inch Ash." Tang Rou knew.

"OH! That fellow! I’m going to go too then." Steamed Bun jumped up.

"Me too." Tang Rou got up as well.

"How interesting." Wei Chen also had a deep impression of the Ghostblade and also headed out of the door with everyone else.

"Little Li, could you take care of the guests?" Ye Xiu told the employee to attend to the three guests in the room. Everyone else had already walked out in a line. Only Tao Xuan, Xiao Shiqin, and Sun Xiang were thrown aside in the practice room. The person accompanying them would be Happy Internet Cafe’s Little Li.

Little Li clearly wasn’t sure how to handle this situation. Unfortunately, he had been abandoned by the others already. He looked at the three in front of him at a loss of what to do. In the end, he squeezed out a few words: "Would any you like some water?"

"No need. Thanks." Xiao Shiqin replied.

At this moment, Tao Xuan was so angry, no words could come out of his mouth. How disrespectful! This was unadorned disdain for them. Excellent Era’s owner, captain, and vice-captain had just been thrown aside in a practice room just like that. Ye Qiu left an employee here to attend to them and then everyone just ran over to meet some random punk. Who was this person? Was he more important than them?

"Qiao Yifan….. That name sounds quite familiar?" Xiao Shiqin muttered.

"Really?" Tao Xuan was surprised. He felt like this person’s background shouldn’t be small, but after thinking about it for awhile, he couldn’t think of anything.

Sun Xiang remembered though: "Isn’t he the one that lost to Li Xuan in the All Stars Rookie Challenge?" Sun Xiang had participated in the Rookie Challenge, and had been quite depressed at the results. The painful experience deepened his impression of the event, so he even remembered a no-name like Qiao Yifan.

"Right, it’s him." Xiao Shiqin hadn’t been wrong when he said that the name sounded familiar. If Qiao Yifan wasn’t so invisible, he would have thought of it awhile ago: "He’s from Team Tiny Herb. Even though he has never gone out on stage, he’s an officially registered member of Team Tiny Herb."

Chapter 721: Hi

"Team Tiny Herb!" Tao Xuan’s expression darkened. Just this name alone was enough for him to take things more seriously.

Team Tiny Herb had a somewhat strong start, but weak finish in this past season. They were the season seven champions and entered the new season at a high. In the beginning, Team Tiny Herb didn’t let down their fans and led the regular season in first place. Unfortunately, in the second half of the regular season, they were passed by Team Blue Rain and Team Samsara, ending the season with third place.

A team’s placing in the regular season didn’t determine who would be the championship winners. Once a team reached the playoffs, no team would slack off. As the defending champions, many thought Team Tiny Herb’s chances at winning were quite high, but although Team Tiny Herb smoothly entered the semifinals, they ended up under Team Samsara’s feet as their stepping stone. Team Samsara beating top teams like Team Tiny Herb and Team Blue Rain one after the other only made their championship victory that much more glorious.

"Tiny Herb? Who is this Qiao Yifan?" Tao Xuan turned to ask Xiao Shiqin.

"That..." Xiao Shiqin felt a bit embarrassed. Qiao Yifan was truly too invisible. How could an outsider know such information on someone who had never played in an official match? Xiao Shiqin could only say what he knew: "He has never participated in an official match before, so there isn’t much information on him. From what I know, he uses an Assassin, but the only time he’s ever appeared on stage was in the All Star Rookie Challenge. However, at that time, he used a Ghostblade. He challenged Li Xuan and the outcome….."

The outcome was a tragic sight, but Xiao Shiqin was kind person. Even though Qiao Yifan wasn’t in front of him listening, he still tried to find the appropriate words to soften the harsh truth.

Tao Xuan had some impression of this year’s All Stars. It was a once a year event after all.

That Ghostblade who lost to Li Xuan? Tao Xuan hadn’t bothered to remember that kid’s name because there was nothing noteworthy about that kid’s performance. How many remember the loser?

Xiao Shiqin’s words still let Tao Xuan know that this Qiao Yifan’s official class was an Assassin, but in the Challenger League, he played a Ghostblade. Could he have been hiding his strength and simply playing in the Rookie Challenge for fun?

Tao Xuan started to become a bit uneasy. He paced about the room and even opened the door to look outside, but he didn’t see Ye Qiu’s group returning. If they planned on welcoming Qiao Yifan here, they should have come up by now. The first floor wasn’t that far away? It seems like they don’t want us to see him?

"Let’s go." As a result, Tao Xuan quickly made his decision. Just like how they barged in, he decided to go down and see what they were up to.

"Ah? You’re going to leave? You’re not going to wait for my boss to come back? Are you sure you don’t want any water?" Little Li saw that the three were getting ready to leave, so he quickly called after them.

"No thanks. We have something we need to do, so we’ll get going." Tao Xuan didn’t need to go so far as to take his anger out on an Internet Cafe employee. After politely responding, he and the other two left the practice room. When they exited the room, the three quickly put their sunglasses on and started walking quickly and carefully.

It didn’t matter much for Tao Xuan, but Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin were like sheep in a tiger’s den coming to an Internet Cafe. If they didn’t disguise themselves a bit, the fans would quickly nab them like wolves.

Happy Internet Cafe. This is the right place…..

Qiao Yifan came directly to their door. Of course, he had told Ye Xiu beforehand. If not, he wouldn’t have known the Internet Cafe’s location or name. After knowing that he wouldn’t be staying with Team Tiny Herb and that he didn’t have any offers from any other Club teams, Qiao Yifan decided to seek shelter under Ye Qiu’s wing, who had been of great assistance to him. He would be fine even if Ye Qiu only wanted him as an apprentice. Coming from a championship team, he had been quite proud in the beginning, but after a year, there wasn’t much left of it.

Ye Xiu obviously didn’t reject Qiao Yifan and also told him their plans for the future. After listening to it, Qiao Yifan happily accepted. He wanted to learn and improve, and it couldn’t be any better if he could also have the chance at becoming a pro player again.

While Qiao Yifan waited in front of the Happy Internet Cafe’s reception desk, he was still feeling uneasy. However, he soon heard the employee go upstairs to send the message. A bunch of footsteps soon followed. It seemed like quite a few people were coming down.

"Is it them?" Qiao Yifan thought to himself. His gaze had already shifted to look in that direction. He soon saw one, two, three, four, five people come over. Qiao Yifan recognized Ye Qiu among them.

"Senior." Qiao Yifan immediately went up to meet them and gave a respectful greeting.

"Ha ha, not bad, little kid! You’re very polite!" One of them reached out his hands and gave his shoulders a heavy pat. This person was seemingly a middle-aged guy with a gruff face. Qiao Yifan leapt up in fright. Did I get the wrong person? I don’t think I did?

Qiao Yifan wasn’t sure what to say, when he heard the person who he thought was senior: "Ha, he can be considered your senior too. Wei Chen. Have you heard of him?"

Qiao Yifan had never heard of him.

If he were a Warlock player or someone from Team Blue Rain and understood the team’s history, perhaps he would have heard of the name Wei Chen before, but his current knowledge was the same as Sun Xiang’s. He didn’t recognize this name at all. However, Sun Xiang dared to say "Who’s that?" Qiao Yifan didn’t have that sort of arrogance and hastily said a "Hi senior" to Wei Chen.

"Ha ha ha, good, good. You’ve got a good future ahead of you, little kid!" Wei Chen patted Qiao Yifan again. He didn’t seem to mind that Qiao Yifan had no idea who he was.

"Steamed Bun, Soft Mist. You’ve played in the game together." Ye Xiu introduced Steamed Bun and Tang Rou. Steamed Bun laughed loudly as his greeting. Tang Rou didn’t lack manners and greeted him politely. She had a good impression of Qiao Yifan.

"This is our boss." Ye Xiu introduced Chen Guo last. Chen Guo was actually at a loss of what to do facing such a proper introduction. In the end, she treated him like they were family and said: "So you’ve arrived? I’ve already arranged living quarters for you. Later, Old Wei and Steamed Bun can bring you over."

"Thank you, thank you." Qiao Yifan hastily replied.

Just when they were getting acquainted with each other, noise could be heard from the stairs again. Tao Xuan’s group grew impatient from waiting and went downstairs. The three wore big sunglasses as if they were from the Matrix.

Even though everyone recognized the famous pro players, they mostly saw them on the screen, so it wasn’t as easy to identify them in real life. Thus, sunglasses were usually good enough as a disguise. However, Qiao Yifan was different. Although he might be just a "water dispenser", he still went around with the team everywhere and would encounter anyone Team Tiny Herb encountered. These three walked directly towards their group, giving Qiao Yifan plenty of time to recognize them. At first, he felt that these three faces looked quite familiar. At a second glance, he began to identify them. At a third glance, he cried out all of a sudden: "Senior Xiao Shiqin? Senior Sun Xiang? Hi….."

Qiao Yifan was so polite! Sun Xiang had only registered a year before him and Qiao Yifan already considered him a senior. After crying out their names, he walked forward weakly and greeted them.

He may not have spoken very loudly, but he hadn’t spoken very quietly either. Quite a few people nearby had heard it. Numerous customers lifted up their heads to check. Now that they were deliberately looking for these two pro players, the sunglass facade collapsed like paper. Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin were quickly recognized by Glory fans.

"HOLY SH*T! IT’S SUN XIANG! IT’S XIAO SHIQIN!!" Someone shouted loudly. Many had already leapt up from their chairs and dashed over. Such a large commotion immediately startled even more people. It was as if a brick had been thrown into a pond. Waves of people began crashing around inside the Internet Cafe.

Not everyone at an Internet Cafe played Glory, and not everyone who played Glory was so passionate about chasing after stars. Happy Internet Cafe existed before Glory existed. When the Glory Alliance was established, it just happened to be located across the street from Club Excellent Era. Chen Guo paid a lot of attention in caring for Glory and Excellent Era fans. Happy Internet Cafe could be considered a gathering place for Excellent Era’s fans.

With Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin having been exposed, the passion from the surrounding fans was practically the same as when Excellent Era played in their home stadium. A huge number of customers left their seats and quickly walked over to watch.

"Not good!"

Tao Xuan, Xiao Shiqin, and Sun Xiang weren’t the only ones crying this out in their hearts. Ye Xiu’s group also felt the same! Fortunately, they were still at the front desk. The door was very close, so they rapidly scurried away. Tao Xuan’s group reacted too slowly. Then again, the fans weren’t going to hurt them. If they ran away, it might hurt their feelings too much and result in a bad reaction. During their short moment of hesitation, the three were surrounded in an instant. Not long afterwards, a pair of sunglasses flew off and was kicked around by the crowd. One of the lenses even fell off. In the end, it was thrown at Ye Xiu’s feet.

"What a pity." Tang Rou picked up the sunglasses, "They’re Ray Bans too. They’re ruined now."

"It’s okay if the sunglasses are ruined. They’re not going to get ruined, right?" Steamed Bun asked.

"Should we go over to Club Excellent Era and call their security over?" Ye Xiu wondered.

"I….. I….." Qiao Yifan was nervous. He felt like he had invited disaster onto them.

"I knew you had a bright future ahead of you!" Wei Chen praised.

"It’s such a mess. No one’s going to try and use this chance to not pay their bill, right?" Chen Guo was also worried.

Chapter 722: Previously Invisible

After the sunglasses flew out, one person frantically struggled out of the crowd. His clothes were crooked now and his hair had become disheveled. Once he stumbled his way through, he got up and heard a concerned voice from in front of him: "Boss Xuan, you okay?"

Tao Xuan looked up. The person asking was his competitor, Happy Internet Cafe’s owner and Ye Qiu’s supporter, Chen Guo. It was a pity that Chen Guo couldn’t keep up her act. She wasn’t a natural at taunting people like Ye Xiu was. When she asked if he was alright, her eyebrows were raised in delight, letting Tao Xuan know: she wasn’t really concerned about him, but rather laughing at him.

Even though Tao Xuan was the owner of Excellent Era and the senior, who provided the wages for his pro players, the fans didn’t care much about him. After Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin were recognized, they were immediately swarmed. Tao Xuan wasn’t as well known, so despite wearing sunglasses as well, the fans took a few glances at him and acted like he didn’t exist after determining that he wasn’t a pro player. The two pro players were being asked left and right with requests for signatures and photos. As for Tao Xuan, he had been squeezed out as if he were an obstacle.

Tao Xuan didn’t have the physique fitting for a security guard. He couldn’t protect those two. In the end, he was forced out like that pair of sunglasses.

Tao Xuan felt gloomy! The pro players receiving love and respect from their fans shouldn’t be a bad thing, right? However, his opponents were laughing at them. Tao Xuan really wanted to shout that Ye Qiu was here too. He was certain that there would be a similar effect, but why should he split Excellent Era’s fans? In truth, Tao Xuan didn’t want to regard Ye Qiu as his opponent. He knew how much Excellent Era fans cared for Ye Qiu. If the two became enemies, the fans would be split, so Ye Qiu quietly retiring was for the best, but Ye Qiu refused to go out quietly and started creating his own team. Tao Xuan wanted to minimize the damage the other side could bring to Excellent Era. How could he push Ye Qiu towards the fans?

Tao Xuan didn’t bother arguing with them. With a dark expression on his face, he tidied up his clothing and ran back to the Club. Not long afterwards, helpers arrived at Happy Internet Cafe. They weren’t going to force the two away. It would be too disrespectful to the fans. The fans should at least surround the pro players in an orderly fashion though. What if an accident happened and the crowd started to run amok?

When the helpers came, they brought a megaphone. After a few shouts, the crowd calmed down a bit and the scene gradually turned into a fan meet and greet for the pro players. Chen Guo walked over, laughing: "Boss Xuan, Happy Internet Cafe is my place. Don’t you think you should be paying to host an event here?"

"Is that so? It seems to me that bringing my pro players over here will help your business quite a bit. I think you should be the one paying me fees for their appearance." Tao Xuan said.

"Did I ask for them to come over?" Chen Guo asked back.

"Then if you don’t want us to use your venue, then disperse the crowd!" Tao Xuan said.

In truth, neither of them cared about paying fees! The two were simply venting their anger on each other. In any case, the one to lose out today was Tao Xuan’s side. What he just said wasn’t false. Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin appearing at Happy Internet Cafe would certainly be a boon to Happy Internet Cafe’s business.

Ordinarily, with the status of these two pro players, Happy Internet Cafe didn’t have enough influence to invite them over. In business, it wasn’t all about earning profits from advertising fees! While celebrities made the advertised products more popular through their own fame, celebrities also relied on the product to make themselves more well known. Happy Internet Cafe wasn’t a chain brand that everyone in the country recognized. Its fame couldn’t compare to an All Star player. The two sides weren’t on the same playing field. For today’s events, if news spread, Excellent Era would explain it as the two pro players coming out for their own private matters and then inadvertently being recognized. If it became described as a business move, Happy Internet Cafe would profit greatly from it. It would lower the value of these two pro players as well.

In any case, Happy Internet Cafe could only gain from this occurrence. When Chen Guo bickered with Tao Xuan, she didn’t care about who won or lost in the end. Ye Xiu and Wei Chen chatted on the side, not caring about the situation. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had joined the crowd. Qiao Yifan was still terrified after letting a storm loose from a slip of the tongue.

Excellent Era’s helpers arrived and organized the crowd into a more orderly fashion. After the fans calmed down, they would try and get the pro players out. If not, once the news started to spread, more and more fans would show up. If things went badly, the media would even come over and so on.

As a result, after satisfying all of the requests for signatures and pictures, the Excellent Era employees explained the situation to the fans, while slowly evacuating Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin.

Although the fans were sad, the pro players had indeed stayed for some time, showing their sincerity and interacting with them. When Excellent Era’s group left Happy Internet Cafe, they quickly escaped to Club Excellent Era. Tao Xuan didn’t come over and say a few departing words to them.

That Qiao Yifan left him an impression though.

His "Senior Xiao Shiqin? Senior Sun Xiang? Hi" had caused them quite the trouble. In addition, it even helped advertise for Happy Internet Cafe. That guy wasn’t a good person!

Tao Xuan didn’t think that he had been prompted to do so because it wasn’t necessary! Those other five could have shouted their names at any time and caused them trouble, but they didn’t do so. It was only that newcomer Qiao Yifan who said their names when he saw them. His actions were too despicable and shameless.

This person was still just a child too! They had to be wary of him!

Tao Xuan took his time to investigate his enemies. Qiao Yifan had been noticed by him. While they were under pressure, that guy set off a calamity with a nervous appearance. His acting skills were truly superb.

Qiao Yifan. I’ll remember you!

After Tao Xuan returned to the Club, the first thing he did was make a phone call. Finding out information about a player, who was part of a team in the Alliance, wasn’t difficult at all. He directly called Team Tiny Herb’s owner.

As owners, their relationship with each other was very subtle. This type of situation was similar to the politics between in-game guilds. When they needed to fight, they would be at each other’s throats. When they were sitting idle, they would chat with each other.

"Qiao Yifan?" Tiny Herb’s owner was very surprised at hearing Tao Xuan ask for this name in particular.

He knew this name because even though Qiao Yifan was a nobody, deciding not to renew his contract required his approval. It had only been three or four days since, so he still hadn’t forgotten about Qiao Yifan. When he saw that Excellent Era’s Tao Xuan was personally calling to ask about him, he immediately began to wonder whether their team had let some sort of talent go.

What was Team Excellent Era? Despite having been relegated, Team Excellent Era could still attract an All Star player like Xiao Shiqin. They weren’t some team that could be shopped around like a supermarket after being relegated. They didn’t need some free agent player that had been abandoned by another team.

"Qiao Yifan….. Ah, that player..." Tiny Herb’s boss wanted to act as if he wasn’t sure, but he discovered that he really didn’t know much about this player. A few days ago, Tiny Herb’s manager came over to talk about this matter a bit, but he hadn’t cared too much. An unfamiliar player meant that the player wasn’t very important one. As a result, he didn’t ask too much about him. If every decision had to be personally made by the boss, the Club wouldn’t need so many different departments!

It was just that when he heard Excellent Era’s boss unexpectedly ask for this particular player, he started to have some thoughts.

"Boss Xuan, I actually don’t know much about this Qiao Yifan. I’ll go ask around and when I find some more information on him, I’ll tell you." Tiny Herb’s boss finally replied.

After hanging up the phone, Tiny Herb’s boss immediately called Tiny Herb’s manager. When the manager heard the question, he was also very surprised. His decision for Qiao Yifan hadn’t been made on the spur of the moment though. He had even asked for captain Wang Jiexi’s opinion. For a championship team like Team Tiny Herb, a player like Qiao Yifan wouldn’t be of much use. Whether it was signing a stronger player or raising a new rookie, it would be more worth it than funnelling resources into Qiao Yifan.

Since his boss was asking him, the manager didn’t dare to delay and naturally informed of what he knew. He didn’t forget to say that the decision hadn’t been made solely by him. He had also asked for Wang Jiexi’s opinion.

The team captain didn’t have any decision-making authority, but his opinions were of great importance. When the manager made these kinds of decisions, he mostly did what the team captain recommended. In some sense, it was the team captain who decided whether a player should stay and whether the team needed a new player. Tiny Herb’s manager shifted the responsibility to Wang Jiexi to explain to his boss: this was a decision that the team captain had proposed!

This was a matter that he had talked about with the boss just a few days ago. After being suddenly asked to explain, the boss must have some doubts! The manager was certain. As he explained, he thought of what Qiao Yifan might have done to make the boss suddenly ask about him.

No matter how hard Tiny Herb’s manager tried, he wouldn’t be able to think of Qiao Yifan seeing Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin and giving them a polite greeting. It was because of what that resulted in, which caused such a huge misunderstanding.

Tiny Herb didn’t have a clue about any of this. Tao Xuan didn’t know it was a misunderstanding. He thought that Qiao Yifan was a threat and immediately called Tiny Herb to ask, but in the eyes of Tiny herb, a powerful owner like Tao Xuan had personally come to ask about a nobody. Could they have made a mistake?

Qiao Yifan.

An hour earlier, Qiao Yifan had been a nobody, but because of this small accident, he had suddenly drawn the attention of two strong teams. If Qiao Yifan knew about it, he probably wouldn’t know whether to laugh or cry. When all is said and done though, this mess stemmed from the pressure that Ye Xiu had put on Excellent Era.

Chapter 723: Upgrades in the Later Stages

At Excellent Era, Tao Xuan pondered over the “threat” that Qiao Yifan posed.　

At Tiny Herb, because of Tao Xuan’s phone call, Tiny Herb’s boss gave a call to Wang Jiexi after asking the manager. Wang Jiexi had gone home during the season’s break. He was also very surprised to suddenly get a call from his boss, urgently asking about Qiao Yifan.

After hearing Wang Jiexi’s explanation for his decision, Tiny Herb’s boss finally felt at ease. Wang Jiexi didn’t deny Qiao Yifan’s potential. It was more of an issue with how he fit into the team. Team Tiny Herb aimed for the championships. Every single player on the team needed to do their bit to reach this goal. However, it didn’t require Qiao Yifan’s addition. Team Tiny Herb didn’t need someone who wouldn’t make a difference whether he was there or not. It was impossible to say how he much he would grow in the future, but Team Tiny Herb couldn’t give him the necessary time to grow. Leaving him on the team wouldn’t benefit either side.

When their conversation ended, Tiny Herb’s boss immediately called Tao Xuan back, telling him that Qiao Yifan was not a bad player. Team Excellent Era should consider him.

These were more or less just polite words. Usually, teams would say that about the players, who left the team, were very good, or very skilled. In return, the players would usually say that they felt it was too bad that they had to leave the team, but if that were the case, why did they even split in the first place? It indicated that despite being good players, there was an even better replacement or option. Just because the player felt regretful for leaving the team didn’t mean that the player wouldn’t feel regret for joining another.

How could Tao Xuan not hear the implications from these words? That was all Tiny Herb’s boss said though. After all, they were still competitors. It wasn’t like Tiny Herb’s boss would be so devoted as to conduct thorough research on whether Excellent Era needed such a player.

“Thank you, Boss Yu. We should grab lunch sometime.” After saying some polite words, Tao Xuan hung up. The call hadn’t given him as much information as he had wanted. He had already realized that he had been somewhat impulsive. If he really wanted to know information on a player, it would be more appropriate to have the other employees deal with it. A powerful owner like him ran over to ask Tiny Herb about a tossed-out player. It was as if…… he was picking up another person’s trash?

As for what exactly was up with Qiao Yifan, he would have his employees under him find other channels to find out. This was the decision that Tao Xuan made in the end.

At Happy Internet Cafe, Ye Xiu wouldn’t know that Qiao Yifan’s words would cause such a ruckus between the owners of the two teams. Even after the crowd had been dispersed, Qiao Yifan was still somewhat in a panicked state! Then, he was dragged away for a welcoming dinner. Afterwards, he followed Wei Chen and Steamed Bun to his living place as if nothing unusual had happened today.

The next morning, when everyone came together at the practice room, Ye Xiu told Qiao Yifan the details of their team’s situation, as well as their current work. Needing to face Excellent Era in the Challenger League didn’t scare Qiao Yifan though because he already knew! He knew Ye Xiu would be participating in the Challenger League. Excellent Era had been relegated too, so Qiao Yifan had already put two and two together long ago.

“I’ll definitely try my best.” Qiao Yifan had a cautious personality. He didn’t say anything like “We must beat Excellent Era!” He only dared to guarantee that he would do his best.

“Okay, as long as you understand. Let’s start playing! Old Wei is currently a spy and is Samsara’s second elite group leader.” Ye Xiu said.

“Wow!” Qiao Yifan gasped in astonishment. He obviously understood how guilds operated. The second elite group leader was certainly a core member position, no? It was extremely difficult for a spy to get to such a high position.

Wei Chen wasn’t about to explain that he was just being used for labor because of his skill. He waved his hands and said: “You flatter me.”

“Little Qiao, you’ll mainly be playing with us. When you have nothing to do, you’ll practice on your own. When I call for you, we’ll gather together and snatch wild bosses.” Ye Xiu said.

“Understood.”

Soon afterwards, Ye Xiu threw a bomb at Wei Chen: “Old Wei, when I was organizing our materials, I discovered that there are enough materials for you to upgrade your Death’s Hand.”

“Is that so….” Wei Chen replied. He was somewhat puzzled for a moment. In today’s game environment, creating a Silver equipment on one’s own was extremely difficult. Silver equipment required uncommon materials, but uncommon materials were monopolized by the Club guilds. It had taken Wei Chen a year to upgrade Death’s Hand to Level 60. Who knew how many coincidences and lucky encounters he had been given in order to achieve that. After becoming one of the competitors for wild bosses and getting good results, they were able to gather enough materials to upgrade his Silver weapon in just a few days.

“Are you sure there aren’t any issues with your blueprint to upgrade it to Level 65?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I…. can’t guarantee it.” For someone as shameless as Wei Chen to hesitate, it could be seen just how difficult of a step this was. Not having an accurate blueprint was the main reason for the waste of materials. During the process of adjusting the blueprint, batch after batch of uncommon materials would be used. It was a bottomless pit.

“I looked over your blueprint and it didn’t seem like there were any big issues.” Ye Xiu said. The value of a talent in this area could be seen here. A talent would be able to ascertain an accurate and reliable blueprint with minimal experimentation by relying on his or her own experience and understanding of the game. In comparison to someone who didn’t have a clue, how many materials would be wasted by praying on luck alone? No matter how much money or materials you had, it wouldn’t be enough.

“I also can’t find anything wrong with it.” Wei Chen said. He had been by himself before and didn’t have the resources to afford such a loss, so who knew how many he had gone over the blueprint. He wouldn’t ignore any little thing he thought of. This was the best he could do in theory. If there were any problems, the issues would need to be discovered through experimentation. In other words, they had to find the problems through failure. Thinking of this, Wei Chen couldn’t help but hesitate.

“How about we give it a try?” Ye Xiu said.

“Let’s try?” Wei Chen also said.

“You do it or I do it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“F*ck, I’m doing it myself!” Wei Chen ground his teeth, “Give me the materials.”

“Alright.” Ye Xiu prepared the materials needed. Upgrading Death’s Hand to Level 65 didn’t completely require only uncommon materials. The rest could be found from the two million yuan worth of materials from Samsara. If there weren’t any problems with a Silver equipment blueprint, there wasn’t much pressure. For example, for teams like Samsara or Excellent Era, if Cloud Piercer’s Wildfire or One Autumn Leaf’s Evil Annihilation broke, the respective teams could easily create another one in a matter of minutes. It was because there were no errors in their blueprint. The losses in material didn’t need to be considered at all.

After Ye Xiu prepared the necessary materials, Wei Chen logged onto his Windward Formation. Death’s Hand was in his inventory. He didn’t dare to bring it with him for his spy account. Firstly, it was too eye-catching. Secondly, what if it dropped when he died? Even if his Level 60 blueprint was perfect, he would still care about such a loss. Materials weren’t easy to get, after all.

The two met up in game and completed the trade. On Wei Chen’s side, Death’s Hand and the materials were put into the equipment editor. Windward Formation went to the Arena, a safe zone, before opening it up.

When he turned his head to look around, Ye Xiu, Chen Guo, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Qiao Yifan had all gathered around him to watch. Everyone knew that this was an important matter. How could they not want to see the result?

“Ptui!” Wei Chen spat in his hands and rubbed them around to pray for good luck. He clicked on Death’s Hand and started to slowly disassemble it.

Next, he needed to replace the old parts with the newly crafted parts and assemble it back together. Some of the parts could be directly formed through the equipment editor, while others needed to be hand-crafted by Wei Chen. Ye Xiu had seen his blueprint, so he knew of the details. Wei Chen noticed the differences between the materials used in the new one and the original and adjusted the parts accordingly. The new parts wouldn’t have a mold already, so Wei Chen would need to create his own. He had to cut, slice, and grind away. The equipment editor was like a virtual lathe.

Ye Xiu hadn’t used any of these functions yet for his Thousand Chance Umbrella, but he would need to sooner or later. When Su Muqiu designed the weapon, Glory’s level cap was 50. Now it was level 70. The biggest change wasn’t the level difference, but the new high-end realm: the Heavenly Domain.

Starting from Level 55, the materials from the Heavenly Domain dominated everything else. Even though normal servers also had Level 55 to Level 70 wild bosses, no less rare than those in the Heavenly Domain, those bosses weren’t on the same level as those in the Heavenly Domain. It was like the difference between Level 70 equipment from a normal server and one from the Heavenly Domain. How could Silver equipment created from materials from the normal servers compare with one created from materials from the Heavenly Domain?

Top-tier Silver equipment required uncommon materials from the Heavenly Domain. Normal server uncommon materials could be used, but from Level 55 onwards, they could only be considered inferior substitutes.

Until Level 50, Silver equipment followed the same path, but the road afterwards was an entirely different matter. The materials from the Heavenly Domain were even more rare and complicated. The same mold couldn’t continuously be used for Heavenly Domain materials. As a result, a lot of parts required slight adjustments according to the materials used. Wei Chen’s blueprint for Death’s Hand considered this aspect. Ye Xiu’s Thousand Chance Umbrella would face the same issue to continue and upgrade it. Ye Xiu was currently in the middle of researching how to do it. It was impossible for Su Muqiu to leave any resources behind for him. When Su Muqiu passed away, the Heavenly Domain hadn’t even existed yet…...

Chapter 724: Perfect Upgrade

Apart from Wei Chen, everyone else had left their computers. They stood behind Wei Chen, quietly watching.

The practice room just looked like a room on the second floor that had been created by linking several private rooms together. In reality, Chen Guo had put a lot of effort into its renovation. The practice room was well-soundproofed. After closing the door and the windows, practically no noise could be heard from outside. Surrounded by people watching him, Wei Chen carefully worked on his Death’s Hand in silence.

The first part was finished!

Wei Chen wiped his forehead. He wasn’t actually so nervous that there was sweat, but he wiped it subconsciously as a way to loosen up. Only then did he notice the people standing behind him. It could be seen just how focused he had been before.

“Not bad. You’re off to a good start.” Ye Xiu praised, after Wei Chen completed one part of the weapon.

“Shut up. Who needs you to say that? I say you guys go and do whatever you were doing before. Don’t watch.” Wei Chen yelled.

“This is to give you an excuse if you make a mistake. When you mess up, you can say that it was because were were bothering you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Pah! Can’t you ever say anything nice? Hurry up and go outside to smoke or something. The air in this room is bad with you here.” Wei Chen cursed.

Ye Xiu laughed, but he didn’t go outside and smoke. He just told everyone to go back to their seats. Wei Chen didn’t insist on getting Ye Xiu to leave. After seeing everyone leave, he immediately began working on the next part. Even though everyone else returned to their seats, they would occasionally glance at Wei Chen from time to time.

Four parts.

Ye Xiu had looked at Wei Chen’s blueprint for Death’s Hand. The upgrade from level 60 to 65 had four parts, which all required materials from the Heavenly Domain. Three level 65 materials and one level 60 material. Because he knew about the blueprint, when they split wild boss drops, he had naturally prioritized these materials.

After Wei Chen finished one part, he would immediately work on the next part. Finally, Wei Chen wiped his forehead for the fourth time. Ye Xiu knew that he must have been able to successfully complete all four parts. Wei Chen wasn’t the type of person, who wouldn’t utter a peep if he were to fail. He was the type of person, who would curse out loud for at least five minutes!

“You’re done?” Ye Xiu asked.

“The crucial ones are done.” Wei Chen nodded his head.

The crucial ones were those four parts, which required Heavenly Domain materials. The rest of the materials weren’t nearly as precious and didn’t require him to hand-craft them. He could simply use his original template and have the equipment editor craft it for him, so there was no pressure after he completed the important parts. Soon afterwards, the rest of the parts were created and now he just needed to reassemble the weapon again. He couldn’t make any mistakes in this step, but it didn’t require as much precision as creating those four parts. As a pro player with good microing, he shouldn’t be making any mistakes on this step either way.

As a result, under Ye Xiu’s lead, everyone went over to watch again. This time, Wei Chen didn’t stop them. He shouldn’t be making any mistakes in this step.

The individual parts were quickly pieced together by Wei Chen.

“Done!” After Wei Chen put the last part in place, he heaved a sigh of relief and clicked “Confirm”. While the equipment editor saved the changes, the new form of Death’s Hand appeared on the screen. It was a black magic staff around 1.3 meters tall. The tip of the staff was a skeleton hand with its palm open. As it revolved on the screen, it looked like it was about to grab something. The entire staff looked like two skeleton arms linked together.

After the changes were saved, Wei Chen immediately closed the equipment editor and returned to the game. He clicked on Windward Formation’s inventory and saw Death’s Hand quietly sitting there. Wei Chen sucked in a breath of air and turned to look at Ye Xiu. He had done thorough research on the blueprint beforehand, so he didn’t think that the weapon would fail to form after putting the pieces together. Whether or not the weapon was finished would depend on the stats!

If the stats were all around better than the stats at level 60, it would be considered a success. If only a portion of the stats increased, or if some of the stats changed, he would need to see which stats failed to increase, or which stats changed and figure out how to fix those problems. If the stats didn’t change at all or even decreased, it would be a complete failure.

The research teams of the Clubs conducted research with a strong foundation of related knowledge. They would never create equipment by blindly testing their luck. As a result, they would never fail or create trash. It just depended on whether the piece of equipment had been upgraded to its maximum potential. If it did not, they would continuously adjust and test it until it did. Materials would rapidly be consumed in this process.

Team Happy didn’t have the resources to achieve perfect results yet. In truth, if Death’s Hand only had a few flaws, it would still be used. They would perfect it in the future if their circumstances permitted it.

“How is it?” Chen Guo was starting to get anxious. Wei Chen decisively exited the equipment editor and opened his character’s inventory, but his mouse still hadn’t clicked on the weapon yet. Chen Guo didn’t know how to create her own equipment, but she would still know if it had failed or not. It wasn’t like she had never tried to make her own before.

Wei Chen finally clicked on Death’s Hand and the stat window immediately appeared.

Death’s Hand - Level 65.

Weight: 3 kg

Durability: 30

Attack Speed: 2

Physical Attack: 591

Magic Attack: 837

Intelligence +55

Darkness Affinity + 25

Darkness Resistance +25

Critical Strike Chance + 12%

Cast Speed + 12

Cast Range +3

“SUCCESS!!” Wei Chen roared. He slammed his fists on the table. The monitor trembled. All of the stats had increased. It was a huge success. The only numbers that didn’t change were the ones for weight, durability, and attack speed. However, none of those affected a Warlock’s fighting ability. The upgrade wouldn’t focus on those aspects at all. Everything else had improved and all of them reached Wei Chen’s expectations. There were unexpected improvements too. At Level 60, the cast range increase had only been +2. Originally, it shouldn’t have increased until its Level 70 form, but now, it had reached this step ahead of time. Wei Chen couldn’t be any happier.

“F*ck. It’s a success on the first try! On the first try!!!” Wei Chen laughed. He looked so excited that he might try and grab the weapon from the screen to play with it.

While everyone was excited, Chen Guo was somewhat disappointed: “That’s it?”

“What else did you expect?” Wei Chen asked.

“You’re not going to give it a try and see if it won’t break?” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu laughed: “That’s indeed the case for the Thousand Chance Umbrella because some of the transformations might not have been successful. In that case, the Thousand Chance Umbrella wouldn’t be complete yet, but for his staff, what else is there to see besides the stats?”

“Oh, that’s what you were talking about. You scared me to death…..” Wei Chen wiped away some sweat this time. Chen Guo’s sudden words made him think that his Death’s Hand might have some flaws that he hadn’t noticed in his excitement.

“Then it really is a success! That’s great!” Chen Guo became excited too.

“I’ll go find someone to test it out on.” Wei Chen wanted to hurry and try out his new weapon. His Windward Formation just happened to be in the Arena, so he clicked on 1v1 and automatically entered a room with an opponent.

The two sides began fighting. Everyone was still there watching. They wanted to see the might of the newly upgraded Silver weapon, but in reality, with Wei Chen’s skill, he didn’t need a Silver weapon to beat a normal player. Even if his opponent had the Silver weapon, he would still easily beat him into the ground. He was really just showing off. The poor opponent became Wei Chen’s test dummy. He kited around utilizing the +3 cast range, got closer to show his 12% increase in cast speed, and checked the effects of the +25 to Darkness Affinity. Then, he checked his critical strike chance.

Unfortunately, his opponent didn’t have any darkness attribute skills, otherwise, Wei Chen would have let his Windward Formation take some damage to see the effects of the +25 to Darkness Resistance.

“Ha, another critical strike. Awesome!”

“Haha, this senior’s cast range is longer than you think, you weak chicken.”

Wei Chen chattered on excitedly. Ye Xiu had gone back to his seat long ago. Ye Xiu couldn’t help but sigh: “So shameless! You really are shameless…..”

Although it’s said that the Heavenly Domain had no noobs, all normal players were noobs to them. Wei Chen bullied his opponent happily with his Silver weapon. Ye Xiu couldn’t watch any further. He was busy organizing the materials too. The noise from Wei Chen was headache-inducing.

“Can you quiet down! It’s not like you’ve never used a Silver weapon in your life. How disgraceful!” Ye Xiu couldn’t help but say.

“One more time. It’ll be my last one, okay?” Wei Chen replied, while choosing another room.

“AH! He’s the same class as me! Hurry up and come watch me bully him!” Wei Chen didn’t find it shameful to bully a normal player. He was even proud of it and wanted others to share the joy with him!

Ye Xiu gave up and turned his head to ask Qiao Yifan: “Little Qiao, how’s that account?”

“My account has practically never touched a quest before!” Qiao Yifan was excited. Ye Xiu had given the skill point guide to him for One Inch Ash to use. His One Inch Ash had pretty much been power leveled by someone else. Power levelers seeked efficiency. When leeching off of a higher-leveled account, it was much faster to kill monsters than run quests. It was very dull and repetitive though. That didn’t matter for power levelers though. When killing monsters, the character would also get gold, materials, and equipment. For them, it was much more worth it than completing quests. As a result, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was lucky to be power leveled most of the time. Nearly all of the quests in the skill point guide hadn’t been cleared yet. Thus, with this guide on hand, his skill points soared.

Chapter 725: Two Bosses Spawned Simultaneously

Once Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash entered the Heavenly Domain, power leveling became even faster. Speaking of which, in the Heavenly Domain, “power leveling” didn’t really exist because players usually always beat the Heavenly Domain Challenge at Level 70. The only exception was when the level cap was raised.

When Qiao Yifan left Tiny Herb, he took his One Inch Ash back from the power leveler. One Inch Ash was now a Level 70 Ghostblade. Of course, the power leveler only cared about leveling. Clearing stat point and skill point quests required additional fees. Qiao Yifan paid those fees, so his One Inch Ash had the stats and skill points of an average character.

“So there’s a guide like that!” Qiao Yifan couldn’t help but be surprised, because he had come from a championship team. The things he had witnessed were on the higher end. Yet, even in Team Tiny Herb, their most powerful character, Vaccaria, only had 4855 skill points.

“It’s just so-so.” Qiao Yifan even dared to use these words to describe the God-level character Vaccaria. Because he could already predict that his little Ghostblade One Inch Ash, which had been sent over by an invisible player to be power leveled, would certainly have over 4900 skill points once he finished all of these quests.

My One Inch Ash will be better than Vaccaria?

It was just one aspect, but Qiao Yifan had never imagined it could ever happen. However, it was about to right in front of his eyes. Qiao Yifan couldn’t control his excitement. Vaccaria had always been a peak existence in Team Tiny Herb. To think he would be able to surpass it…...

Qiao Yifan suddenly stopped the current quest at hand. The next part had fairly strict requirements. Qiao Yifan didn’t want to mess up.

Ye Xiu continued to organize the materials. At the same time, he also pondered over how he would continue upgrading the Thousand Chance Umbrella. The foundation had already been established. The following steps required an even greater understanding of Glory. Ye Xiu had accumulated eight more years of experience than Su Muqiu. For this work, even Su Muqiu wouldn’t be able to do better than Ye Xiu.

For the Level 55 Thousand Chance Umbrella, Ye Xiu was currently planning on using six uncommon materials. It required even more resources than the Level 65 Death’s Hand, which only required four uncommon materials. Although uncommon materials were important, the choice of materials couldn’t be ignored either. The end result depended on how well each part worked with each other. From this perspective, the importance of dungeon materials and uncommon materials was the same. However, dungeon materials were a lot easier to get, while uncommon materials were extremely difficult. As a result, uncommon materials seemed much more important. It was because of uncommon materials that kept Silver equipment from flooding the market.

“How are things? Can the Thousand Chance Umbrella also be upgraded?” Chen Guo saw Ye Xiu looking through the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s blueprints and went over to ask.

“I still want to take a closer look at the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s blueprint.” Ye Xiu said. After all, he hadn’t spent years researching his weapon like Wei Chen had. It had only been seven months since he had left Excellent Era and started using Lord Grim and the Thousand Chance Umbrella. He had constantly been thinking about how to upgrade the umbrella past Level 50, but he had only started to take action starting from when he reached Level 50. Ye Xiu hoped things could turn out like Wei Chen’s weapon, where the theory was bulletproof, but required actual implementation to discover any issues.

“Are there enough materials?” Chen Guo asked.

“Normal materials aren’t a problem. We’re still lacking in uncommon materials though.” Ye Xiu said.

The blueprint might not be finished, but Ye Xiu would still take a look at what materials he might need when splitting loot dropped by wild bosses. The six materials required for the upgrade would all be Level 55. These types of low-leveled bosses weren’t valued as much by the top guilds, so the alliance’s success rate would be a lot higher. Their alliance was formed midway through last week though and they couldn’t stay on 24/7. It was hard to avoid missing a wild boss that Ye Xiu needed and he really did miss one.

Ye Xiu really wanted this wild boss and it still hadn’t spawned yet this week. However, from the looks of how things were going, Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie was very determined. He even showed up for Level 55 wild boss fights. If their team’s vice-captain personally took the lead, Tyrannical Ambition didn’t dare to hold back. Did Tyranny urgently require materials for some sort of Silver weapon? Ye Xiu guessed.

The morning passed. Ye Xiu still hadn’t received any messages from Loulan Slash or the other guild leaders. No news of any bosses spawning came that entire Tuesday morning.

“God…..” The four guild leaders said to him, “Not a single boss has showed up this entire morning. Shouldn’t we all go to sleep now? And then when we wake up at night, we’ll play while Zhang Xinjie isn’t on?”

Ye Xiu was the one who had told them this plan, but he never said when they should start it. Weren’t they still on right now? They had waited all morning, but no boss had spawned. They were still thinking about wild bosses, so they went over to ask Ye Xiu.

“Don’t be in such a hurry, you guys.” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.”It’s only been a day. Zhang Xinjie’s been with us from start to finish, but who knows if he’ll come today? Let’s confirm it before calling it quits! After all, it’s more convenient for us to work during the day, no? We have more people to work with during the day too.”

“That’s true.” The guild leaders nodded their heads. Even though the guild had a bunch of players, who played as if it were their jobs, relying on these players all the time wasn’t realistic. They often required the assistance of more players, especially for large-scale battles like wild boss hunts. They could look for these full-time like players, but it wasn’t like these kinds of players covered every corner of the Heavenly Domain! In particular, when looking for bosses, they needed to rely on every player in the guild. The guild wasn’t asking much. While you’re playing, if you see a wild boss around or if there are any unusual movements from other guilds, just notify us. Thus, it was much easier if there were more people online. More people also meant more competition, but everything had their pros and cons.

“Then let’s keep going into the afternoon?” Radiant’s White Stream suggested.

“Let’s keep going.” The others agreed.

They had opened up a QQ group. It was convenient to talk about things there. In the game, they each had their own guilds, so it wasn’t easy to get together in the same chat. Ye Xiu often switched accounts too.

In the afternoon, when everyone returned to the game, it was as if the wild bosses couldn’t endure it anymore and suddenly spawned. Two of them spawned too. Both Heavenly Justice and Parade received the news.

Level 55 wild boss, Red Ribbon Janna.

Level 65 wild boss, Green Magic Disciple Amofu.

It wasn’t impossible for two or even three bosses to spawn at the same time. If the two bosses were Level 70, then it would be difficult for them to choose because both were of equal importance. The current situation was more welcome though. The Level 55 boss didn’t require any elite troops. The boss could be given to their other groups, while the elite groups competed for the higher level boss. Fighting two at once also saved time.

However, the situation wasn’t so good for the alliance. They didn’t have the strength to fight on two fronts. God Ye Qiu couldn’t be at two places simultaneously. Making a decision was easier though: choose the more important one. The four guild leaders prepared to head over, when Ye Xiu suddenly said: “Let’s go to Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite?”

“Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite?” The four guild leaders stopped for a second, when they heard the name because that was the name of the Level 55 area. It was the location of Red Ribbon Janna. They were going to give up on the big fish and go for the smaller one?

“That’s fine too.” Conquering Cloud’s Yue Ziqin felt like he understood Ye Xiu’s intentions and said: “We didn’t really get any bosses yesterday, so we should start off the day well.” He thought Ye Xiu wanted to boost their morale, so he spoke up.

“Oh oh.” The other three immediately understood.

When Ye Xiu said: “Everyone, let’s work hard! Red Ribbon Janna has something I need!”

“What?” The four guild leaders felt dizzy. Was that the real reason why he was giving up on the Level 65 Magic Disciple for the Level 55 Red Ribbon? It was just because he needed something from it and not because of something deeper like boosting their morale?

There was no point arguing at this point. The four guild leaders grabbed their troops and led their troops over to Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite.

Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite was a Taoist location and an ostentatious little place. The symbol of a red cloud hung above the main entrance. In the middle, a black “武” looked as if it were about to fly out like a dragon. Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite was a Level 55 leveling area. The dungeon, Scarlet Cloud Ancient Altar, ended the lives of who knew how many heroes. However, the level cap was now level 70. Scarlet Cloud Ancient Altar had long since become empty. The occasional players that came were here for the Level 55-57 NPCs. The former most difficult boss, Red Ribbon Janna, was now a boss the big guilds were too lazy to send their elite groups to.

A group of players passed underneath Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite. Above their names was the guild tag: Blue Brook Guild.

At the very front of the group were two Blade Masters. One was one of the famous Five Great Experts of Blue Brook Guild: Blue Bridge Spring Snow. The other was someone that others wouldn’t recognize. However, everyone in the group knew that he was a kid, who Team Blue Rain had told to come over. It seemed like he had just come out from Team Blue Rain’s recent training camp. His name was Lu Hanwen. His character: Blade Master Flowing Clouds.

Chapter 726: Team Blue Rain’s New Talent

“Ah! So this is Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite?” Lu Hanwen’s voice revealed his youth. He was definitely a kid. pitch of his voice still possessed the innocence of childhood. He was even younger than Gao Yingjie and Qiao Yifan.

“Yeah, this is Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite.” Blue River said as he controlled Blue Bridge Spring Snow. He wasn’t surprised at Lu Yuwen’s amazement. Lu Yuwen was only fourteen years old. How long could he have been playing Glory for? Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite’s era of splendor took place when the Heavenly Domain had just been released. Even Blue River hadn’t been a part of the first wave. By the time Lu Yuwen started playing Glory, Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite had already become an outdated leveling area. No one came to the Heavenly Domain at Level 50 to level up, except for that guy, of course.

Thinking of that God, Blue River couldn’t help but look at the Blade Master, Flowing Cloud, next to him. This character was the kid’s, not the guild’s. Lu Yuwen came running over, saying that the team had told him to come over and that he was from the training camp. Blue River obviously understood the implications. Lu Yuwen was probably someone who Team Blue Rain considered as their future star. A Blade Master….. Could the team be raising the successor to Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain?

But Huang Shaotian was still at his peak, right now. Wasn’t it too early to look for a successor? Then again, Lu Yuwen was still very young. Maybe the team planned on raising him for a few years? Team Blue Rain indeed had this kind of tradition. If there was someone with talent from the training camp, they wouldn’t hesitate to add him to the team.

“Wow! It’s so beautiful! Every single room has a symbol of a red cloud!” Lu Yuwen clearly didn’t have as many thoughts as Blue River did. As soon as they stepped into Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite, he ran around all of a sudden like he was here to tour around the place.

‘Hey, slow down!” Blue River shouted. He and the troops chased after him. After just a few steps, they alarmed quite a few monsters. Even though Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite looked like a small city, it was still a leveling area and not an actual city. Every NPC was hostile and would actively seek to attack players. These were only level 50 or so monsters though, so they were easily beaten. Alarming a few monsters wouldn’t be an issue.

At this moment, Blue River suddenly noticed that no matter where Lu Yuwen’s Flowing Cloud went, not even a single monster would be alarmed.

“Is it coincidence? Or is it…….” Blue River thought. He naturally began paying more attention to Flowing Cloud’s movements. Soon afterwards, he saw Flowing Cloud zig zag left and right swiftly and then continue running forward as if nothing had happened.

This is…...

Blue River looked around. Sure enough, there was a monster on either side, wandering about. When Flowing Cloud zig zagged, he threaded his way through the gap between their aggro radii.

Yes, that should be what he did…...

Blue River could only guess because he couldn’t clearly distinguish the aggro ranges of those two monsters.

But from looking at Flowing Cloud, Blue River could ascertain that Lu Yuwen had purposely avoided their aggro range.

Avoiding the aggro range of a monster wasn’t difficult, but Lu Yuwen did it so swiftly. Only someone with a good eye to judge the situation and precise control over one’s character could take the path that Flowing Cloud had just taken. For example, if Blue River wanted to avoid those two monsters, he would have needed to wait for the two monsters to be a little farther apart before rushing through the gap between their aggro radius.

But Lu Yuwen? He accurately managed to determine the gap between their aggro radii and moved through the tiny gap. It was definitely a move that surpassed a normal player’s capabilities.

It was unnecessary to dodge these monsters though. With their strength, these monsters could be killed with just a few hits. There was no need to waste so much effort with such precise microing, but what about for Lu Yuwen? It looked like the kid didn’t think of it as anything troublesome. He continued to use this sort of excessively high-end technique to avoid all the weak monsters.

“This kid really is skilled!” Blue River couldn’t help but say his thoughts to a teammate.

“What do you mean?” As expected, the others didn’t even notice because of their difference in skill level. Those who came to kill a Level 55 wild boss were just hastily gathered troops. The elites had gone over to fight the Level 65 one.

“Just watch him more carefully and you’ll know.” Blue River said.

“D*mn!”

Just when Blue River finished speaking, several players cried out in astonishment. Blue River turned around to look, but didn’t see anything unusual, so he asked: “What is it? What is it?”

“So fast!” Someone next to Blue River said.

“Who?”

“That kid. He killed off that monster in an instant. How many skills did he use?” The person replying asked himself.

Who knew when Lu Yuwen had suddenly become excited, but he suddenly found a monster to kill, causing the Blue Brook Guild players to cry out in surprise. Blue River knew that although these players weren’t elites, they were still sent out to compete for a wild boss. They wouldn’t be much worse than the elite players and could still be considered as top players within the Heavenly Domain. For them to be so astonished, Lu Yuwen must have showed some terrifying skill.

“How incredible!”

“Will he be a part of Team Blue Rain next season?”

“He’s a Blade Master. Could it be……”

They guessed all sorts of things. Blue River was filled with curiosity and expectations for this kid.

“Let’s hurry! We can watch more carefully when we fight the boss.” Blue River urged everyone to hasten their pace. He was also impatient to see this scene.

In the end, they failed to catch up to Lu Yuwen’s Flowing Cloud. That guy charged forward without stopping to take a break. Blue River checked his coordinates. He wasn’t running around randomly. He was heading towards where the boss had spawned. It was just that he quickly lost them. Soon afterwards, they saw a message from Flowing Cloud: “Everyone, hurry up! I’m already here!”

“We’re coming.” Blue River replied. Everyone advanced forward hastily until they arrived inside the flower garden of Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite. Flowing Cloud was hopping around the rock garden.

“This kid just can’t stay still, can he?” Blue River had accompanied him the entire way, so he had a small grasp of Lu Yuwen’s personality now. Lu Yuwen was the type of person, who just couldn’t sit still.

“Ah! You’re here! Hurry, he’s here! I saw her!” Flowing Cloud jumped and shouted, when he saw Blue Brook Guild.

“Careful!” Blue River saw a figure hidden in the rock garden. A bright light flashed and a bullet headed towards Flowing Cloud.

Bang!”

Everyone saw the bullet fly out from the gun, drawing an arc through the air.

It missed!

Flowing Cloud was able to dodge the sudden attack at such a close range. Blue River didn’t dare to say it was because of his warning. He felt like he had yelled it out right as the gunshot rang. He reckoned that the sound from the gunshot was louder than his warning from Lu Yuwen’s perspective. Typing out a warning didn’t need to be said. Blue River couldn’t type that fast.

Lu Yuwen dodged it on his own.

The bullet whizzed by. While in mid-air, Flowing Cloud slashed down at the half hidden figure.

Falling Phoenix Slash!

Too many people could throw out this skill, but Lu Yuwen performed the move as he was doing a 180 degree spin in midair. It looked the same as a Berserker doing a reverse Collapsing Mountain. The advantages of doing it in such a way could clearly be seen: the angle was lower, so the attack would be more thorough.

A sword light flashed and Flowing Cloud descended. He was soon together with that figure behind the rock garden. Blue River and everyone else hurried over. It hadn’t even been ten seconds yet, when Flowing Cloud hopped back onto the rock garden and shouted at them: “Hurry up! I already killed him……”

It had only been ten seconds…...

Even though Blue River knew Flowing Cloud had an exceptional set of equipment, the guild had provided him with a full set of Orange equipment, killing a same-level opponent in ten seconds couldn’t be done just through advantage in equipment though. His hand speed must be extremely fast too.

‘I got a gun. Does anyone want it?” Seeing that everyone had arrived, Flowing Cloud waved his hand and threw the weapon on the ground. It was the gun that had just dropped from the gunner.

Blue River had Blue Bridge Spring Snow walk over. He picked up the gun to take a look. It was a Level 70 Purple weapon Shining Rifle. The slow attack speed was the gun’s flaw, but it was a Purple weapon from a hundred player dungeon raid. Just from this gun alone, the person shouldn’t have been too weak. Even so, he had been destroyed by Lu Yuwen in just ten seconds.

This kid was terrifyingly talented!

Thinking of how Lu Yuwen was only fourteen years old and would be raised by the team for several more years, Blue River couldn’t help but feel excited for Team Blue Rain’s future.

“What guild was that player from?” Blue River didn’t forget to ask who attacked them.

“Parade.” Lu Yuwen replied.

“No way?” Blue River was astonished. Everyone knew which guilds comprised of the four guild alliance. Parade was one of them. If someone from Parade had hidden himself here, didn’t it meant that the alliance was going to come fight for the level 55 wild boss? Did they not receive news of the Level 65 boss spawning? Blue River felt like since the alliance depended on Ye Qiu, they had no way of fighting two fronts at once. If they had to choose between a Level 55 and a Level 65 boss, of course they would go for the Level 65 one. So why did they choose the Level 55 one?

“I’m sure that he was from Parade. What is it?” Lu Yuwen could the surprise from Blue River.

“If it’s them, then we have a very troublesome opponent.” Blue River said.

“Who?” Lu Yuwen asked.

“Ye Qiu!” Blue River said.

“Ah! He really is troublesome!” Lu Yuwen suddenly gasped.

“Oh, you also know about him?”

“Yeah! The Captain and Huang Shaotian said Ye Qiu was the most troublesome opponent they’ve ever faced.” Lu Yuwen said.

Chapter 727: Ambushed

Ye Xiu’s group was almost at Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite, but midway through, Parade’s guild leader, Martial Awareness, received a report that the player ahead, who had discovered the boss, had been killed.

The scouts in the Level 55 areas were actually oftentimes the more trustworthy part-time players, because Level 55 areas usually didn’t have any players, so they naturally wouldn’t receive any kind of information. The dead player at Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite was someone Martial Awareness knew of. This player’s skill and equipment weren’t bad. He was just one person though. If the other guilds noticed him, of course he would die. As a result, Martial Awareness didn’t think too much of his death. The sacrificed player knew the risks involved, so Martial Awareness didn’t say any consoling words. Instead, he immediately asked: “Which guild arrived first?”

“Blue Brook Guild.”

“Oh, Blue Brook Guild. That’s fine.” Martial Awareness let out a sigh of relief. They were only worried about Tyrannical Ambition. If it was just Blue Brook Guild, they shouldn’t run into much trouble with God Ye Qiu leading the group.

The other side soon replied: “Blue Brook Guild has an expert on their side!!”

“Expert? How skilled is he?” Martial Awareness snorted disdainfully. With God Ye Qiu watching over their battle, let alone an in-game expert, even a normal pro player wouldn’t be an issue. Last week, Team Howling Heights had the Best Rookie, but didn’t he get swept away by God Ye Qiu?

“In any case, I was still trying to figure out what was going on when I died. It probably took him around ten seconds to kill me. He made his move so quickly.” The scout replied in an instant, as if he wanted to show that his hand speed was nothing to scoff at.

“Ten seconds!” Marital Awareness immediately refocused when he heard that number. For a normal player, let alone an actual human opponent, most probably wouldn’t be able to even beat a sandbag in ten seconds. This “expert” truly wasn’t simple.

Martial Awareness immediately told Ye Xiu and the other three guild leaders.

“Ten seconds!” Sure enough, everyone was shocked by this number.

“What class?” Ye Xiu finally asked.

“Uh……” Martial Awareness didn’t know, so he hastily asked the scout.

“Blade Master.” Martial Awareness soon replied.

“Could it be Huang Shaotian?” White Stream blurted out. A Blue Brook Guild Blade Master killing someone in ten seconds. It would be strange if they didn’t think of Huang Shaotian.

“He says it probably isn’t.” Martial Awareness had clearly asked the scout beforehand.

“How does he know?” White Stream asked.

“Because when that guy attacked, he was silent the entire time.” Martial Awareness said.

“Oh…..” Everyone reacted instantly. White Stream nodded his head: “Then it probably wasn’t him.”　　

“Was it an ambush?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No…..” Martial Awareness replied, “It was my guy who ambushed the Blade Master, but the Blade Master dodged it and fought back……”

“The Blade Master’s name?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Flowing Cloud.” Martial Awareness said.

Loulan Slash immediately flipped through his archives. Online documents were very convenient. He CTRL-F’ed Flowing Cloud and returned to the game in five seconds: “I don’t have any information on him. What about you guys?”

The other guild leaders did the same thing. They all replied in the same manner: “No idea. Never heard of him.”

“He was able to kill an expert from the Heavenly Domain within ten seconds. He must be a pro-level player, but if it’s Blue Rain, who else could it be but Huang Shaotian?” Ye Xiu couldn’t think of anything.

“Let’s hurry. We can’t lose the boss.” Yue Ziqin said. They only had one scout at Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite, and he just died. If Blue Brook Guild started attacking the boss without any other guilds interfering, they could lure the boss to who knows where.

“We should hurry.” Ye Xiu said. During this discussion, they were still moving forward. They soon reached the entrance to Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite. After passing through the gate with the word “武” on top of the scarlet cloud insignia, they ran to the boss’s last known location. It would take time for Blue Brook Guild to lure the boss away. In the best case scenario, another guild will have started fighting with Blue Brook Guild.

“It’s just up ahead. Everyone, hurry!” Martial Awareness called out. The information came from his guild, so he remembered the coordinates the best. As they approached, a wooden on their group’s right side suddenly splintered. A person, bent like a small shrimp, flew out the window. While in the air, he straightened his body and a sword light slashed towards them.

The group suddenly went into an uproar. None of them expected an ambush. Speaking of which, they were usually the ones who did the ambushing.

The sword light came swiftly. It could be seen just how fast this ambusher was. The players directly in the path of it were in a fluster, stumbling to the left and right. The sword light passed by them and a small gap now appeared in the formerly compact troop formation.

The ambusher dropped down from the small window. He wasn’t done attacking yet. He raised his sword and countless shadows suddenly leaped out.

Formless Phantom Blade!

This ambusher was able to complete such a complicated high-level move in such a short amount of time. He executed the skill as soon as he touched the ground. Sword light covered the ground. This high-level skill didn’t wasn’t targeting a specific person, but rather the small gap in their troop formation. The troops still hadn’t recovered from seeing the ambusher immediately use a high-level skill, when the sword light struck them. A spurt of blood flew out from everyone. Formless Phantom Blade’s final attack was sent out. The strong blow away effect knocked back one player, who sent the entire line of players behind him crashing to the ground.

Fast. Too fast. It was so fast that they weren’t able to keep up.

Using Formless Phantom Blade in a group of enemies wasn’t a wise move. The high-level skill had little starting lag and was a fierce attack, but the long ending lag was an issue. After the Blow Away effect ended, the Blade Master sheathed his sword. He looked quite cool, actually. But to the players right now, it made them feel disgusted.

Because they were stunned by the sudden ambush, Formless Phantom Blade was a success. By the time everyone recovered, the Blade Master could move again. The Blade Master jumped lightly. He just barely left the ground before immediately landing with a Falling Silver Blade. The shockwave dispersed outwards and the circle of players nearby crashed to the ground. The Blade Master then utilized a Triple Slash to chase after the players who had been sent flying by Formless Phantom Blade’s final attack. Those players were just about to get up, when they were knocked to the ground again with a light tap.

The four guild alliance troops were split in two by just a single person. Many of them suddenly felt like they woke up from a dream. When they looked around left and right, they saw that apart from that attack, it was completely silent. The ambush had been done by just one person?

Flowing Cloud.

This Blade Master was Lu Yuwen’s Flowing Cloud. Ye Xiu and the others, who were at the very front of the troops, looked back and immediately identified him. They also saw how he had split apart their troops. This person was very frightening.

“Ignore him. Keep advancing. Clerics, keep up the healing.” Ye Xiu ordered.

“Ah?” The four guild leaders were surprised. This little guy was brave enough to ambush all of them by himself. No matter how skilled he was, he wouldn’t survive if they all attacked. They thought that they should teach this arrogant guy a lesson, but God Ye Qiu unexpectedly gave a different order. Was even God Ye Qiu scared of him?

The four guild leaders may have a lot of thoughts, but they still followed Ye Xiu’s instructions. The troops were in an uproar, when they heard the order, but they also complied. Ye Xiu said to the four guild leaders: “You guys keep going. I’ll go provide support to the rear.”

“Oh?”

“Little Hands, come with me.” Ye Xiu didn’t explain himself to the four guild leaders. He called for Little Cold Hands.

Little Cold Hands didn’t say anything and followed behind Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord to the rear. After Lu Yuwen’s Flowing Cloud split apart the troops, he didn’t stop to take a break and attacked the left side. But it was as if the troops couldn’t see him and just continued forward. Only the Clerics were doing something by healing the injured players.

Lu Yuwen was also surprised. He attacked once, twice, thrice, but everyone just ignored him. These troops seemed to only care about running forward. It was as if his attacks were like scratches from low level monsters. However, Flowing Cloud wasn’t lacking in damage. He had a full set of Orange equipment. In the game, he was most definitely at the top. Every single one of his attacks made the Clerics suck in a cold breath. Even so, everyone was able to endure the attacks without any signs of fighting back.

Because the four guild leaders had given them clear orders: “Ignore him and continue forward. Clerics, heal the injured.”

“Why aren’t you guys fighting back?” Lu Yuwen finally asked in bewilderment. Everyone was astonished by his voice. This person was clearly still a little kid!

At this moment, someone replied to him: “Because we have more important things to attend to.”

Lu Yuwen located the source of the words. Two Clerics were walking towards him. Blue River had informed him that Enlightened Lord was one of God Ye Qiu’s alternate accounts.

“Senior Ye Qiu?” Lu Yuwen asked.

“That’s me. Who are you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“My name is Lu Yuwen.” Lu Yuwen introduced himself rather loudly.

“Lu Yuwen?” Ye Xiu was sure that he had never heard of this name before. He was clearly a new player that Team Blue Rain was raising. He was probably from the training camp, so the public wouldn’t know of him.

Team Blue Rain has found quite a talented player! Ye Xiu sighed. Lu Yuwen’s Flowing Cloud suddenly charged towards him.

“Eight shadows!!!”

Chapter 728: Really Troublesome

Shadow Steps. Eight shadows!　

In the finals, Huang Shaotian used seven shadows and that already made the crowd go wild. In the entire alliance, the only Blade Master, who could use more than seven shadows, was Team Tiny Herb’s Blade Master, Liu Xiaobie. But even though Liu Xiaobie could reach the required hand speed, his control over the shadows wasn’t too good. He could never find a balance between his hand speed and control. It was a huge problem that prevented him from improving it even further. If he tried more shadows, the other side would instantly be able to distinguish between the real from the fake, rendering the skill meaningless.

Lu Yuwen could reach eight shadows. Just this number alone was enough to scare everyone foolish because this was the highest number of Shadow Steps that anyone had accomplished in Glory. No one had ever achieved eight complete shadows.

Ye Xiu was also surprised at first, but after looking at it more carefully, he could tell that although Lu Yuwen could produce eight shadows, his control wasn’t very good, just like Liu Xiaobie. Of those eight shadows, Ye Xiu could identify four of them as fake with just a glance. Compared to Huang Shaotian’s seven perfect shadows, Lu Yuwen’s eight shadows was far from being as effective.

However, this was from the perspective of an experienced expert like Ye Xiu. Let alone normal players, even pro players, those who weren’t familiar with Shadow Steps would be frightened by Lu Yuwen’s eight shadows. More importantly, Lu Yuwen was still young. His high-pitched childish voice stuck out loud and clear. How old was he? 13? 14? After a few years of practice, once he better control, he might just be able to produce eight perfect shadows.

Although this level of Shadow Steps might make the others cry out in fear, for Ye Xiu, it was far from being anything noteworthy. Ye Xiu could instantly see through four out of the eight shadows. It would have been more effective for Lu Yuwen to produce five perfect shadows!

Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord stepped to the side. The onlookers watched as he crashed into a shadow. If that was a real one, wouldn’t he just be killing himself?

Ye Xiu ignored everyone’s bewilderment. He had naturally devised a plan already. While Enlightened Lord stepped to the side, the cross in his hands lit up. Cleric skills would come out whenever the cross flashed with light. Clerics were mainly healers, but Clerics had better offensive capabilities than Paladins. They had a few attacking moves that could be used.

Hypnosis, Sacred Fire, Holy Commandment LIght.

Three skills used consecutively.

Hypnosis inflicted Sleep onto the target.

Sacred Fire was a 5 second DoT and a 3 second silence.

Holy Commandment Light immersed the target in light, causing the target to take 30% more damage from all attacks. It lasted six seconds.

These three skills were naturally used on those four indistinguishable shadows. The shadows of Shadow Steps were virtual images. Anything tangible would pierce through one on contact. However, Enlightened Lord’s equipment wasn’t very good, meaning his stats were on the low side. All three skills required cast times. Without any casting speed buffs from equipment, using all three skills before Flowing Cloud reached him wasn’t possible. Fortunately, Ye Xiu wasn’t alone. He brought Little Cold Hands with him.

Little Cold Hands had good perception. Distinguishing between real and fake was his forte. He couldn’t compare to Ye Xiu though and instantly see through four shadows, but during the time it took Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord to step sideways, Little Cold Hands identified three as fake. He was still lacking in comparison to Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu could instantly see through four, while Little Cold Hands only saw through three after taking some time.

He didn’t need anyone to tell him what to do next though. Little Cold Hand immediately raised his cross and began casting. However, he took more time than Ye Xiu to find the fake shadows. His control over his character wasn’t as good as Ye Xiu either. By the time he was about to do something, he was only able to cast a single spell. Little Cold Hands also had better equipment than Enlightened Lord. Although he might not be able to move his hands as fast, his character casted faster. In the end, Little Cold Hands cast a Sacred Fire, while Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord cast a Hypnosis and a Holy Commandment Light.

Lu Yuwen had been too hurried, which meant that retreating was more difficult. After the enemy skills arrived, he wasn’t able to switch out of the shadow in time. The enemies targeted their skills at troublesome locations. Ye Xiu didn’t need to be said. As for Little Cold Hands, this was his strength.

Of the three shadows, Hypnosis passed right through one of the shadows. Another shadow wasn’t set on fire after stepping on Sacred Fire. The third one began to glow brightly under Holy Commandment Light.

That one was without a doubt the real body. Little Cold Hands hastily retreated, but he was still nicked by the enemy sword. Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord crashed into one of the shadow under the cries of the surrounding onlookers. When Holy Commandment Light glowed around Flowing Cloud’s real body, Flowing Cloud was able to cut Little Cold Hands, but by the time his sword reached Enlightened Lord, it was too late. Lu Yuwen’s intentions of directly killing Enlightened Lord had been seen through. There were even players jumping out to protect Enlightened Lord now.

Holy Commandment Light was a persistent effect spell. The light produced by the spell still covered his body from head to toe. There might be real or fake shadows in Shadow Steps, but the fake shadows wouldn’t disappear. Thus, when facing Shadow Steps, if the shadows criss crossed with each other and switched places, the opponent might lose track. This was the true value behind Shadow Steps. The real body might have been identified, but as long as you weren’t caught, you could rely on other methods to cover it up.

This was exactly what Lu Yuwen did. His eight shadows suddenly gathered together and then scattered. He thought he would be able to cause the enemies to lose track of his real body, but when he looked at his screen, light surrounded his body. Ye Xiu had accounted for Lu Yuwen trying to confuse them.

“To think you could even see through that. You really are amazing!!” Lu Yuwen exclaimed. He wasn’t dispirited though. Shadow Steps may have been seen through, but he didn’t cancel the skill. The eight shadows still headed towards Enlightened Lord.

Two Knights protected him. With Holy Commandment Light as a guide, the two Knights knew very well which shadow was the real one. One of the Knights charged forward. Flowing Cloud stepped to the side and that Knight passed right by him like a train. The second Knight learned from the other Knight’s mistake. He didn’t leave his spot and attack. Then, he heard Ye Xiu shout: “Provoke!”

The Knight wasn’t going to ignore God Ye Qiu’s instruction. He used Provoke, and Flowing Clouds immediately headed towards him. Lu Yuwen saw the Knight lift his hands and predicted that he would be Provoked. The eight shadows suddenly gathered together, providing cover for him. The Knight swiped his mouse back and forth, but the other shadows were making it difficult for him to click on the real one!

Provoke didn’t have any special requirements. The user just had to click on the target and it would hit 100% of the time. But against a pro player, this sort of disgusting problem came up: he couldn’t click on the target. In Glory, whether it was attacks or skills, the player had to point in the desired direction and then click to release the skill. It wasn’t like other games, where the game did the aiming for you and all you had to do was press the right key.

Glory was widely known for its complex game mechanics. Every attack required the player to guide. As a result, just clicking on a target to use the skill might not be easy as it sounded. Using the other fake shadows to block the real one from being clicked on was one way. Moving around like a fly also made it difficult for the opponent to predict his movements. An experienced player could figure out when you were about to use your skill based on your movements. If you knew when the opponent would click, if you moved at the same time, wouldn’t you cause the opponent to miss? If the opponent missed, the skill would go on cooldown. In this case, the Knight’s Provoke would miss.

The Knight was facing a bunch of shadows. Provoke being used on a fake shadow was no different from it being used on the air.

At this moment, he heard God Ye Qiu remind him: “Roar!”

Right, Roar!

The Knight hastily clicked randomly to release Provoke. Even if he canceled it, it would go on cooldown, so it didn’t matter either way. When he clicked, it missed Flowing Cloud’s real body, but the Knight quickly followed with Roar.

This skill was even easier. As long as the target was in its range, it would hit. Tricks couldn’t be used to dodge it. The instant the Knight roared, Flowing Cloud immediately turned around and his sword headed towards the Knight.

But Knights specialized in defense. Even more so, he had many Clerics healing him. Of course he wouldn’t be afraid of a single sword. He lifted his shield and blocked it.

The moment the sword struck the Knight, a heal was also cast on the Knight. After the attack, Flowing Cloud removed the taunt on him. When he turned around, Enlightened Lord had already retreated a good distance away.

“You really are troublesome!” Lu Yuwen pulled himself together and got ready to chase, but before he could even move two steps, another Roar came. That Knight was a self-made genius. He didn’t need Ye Xiu to remind him. He activated Knight’s Spirit and all his skills went off cooldown. He used a Sacrificial Roar. The range was even larger. Flowing Cloud had no way of avoiding it and could only go back to attack. That Knight was waiting for the attack though.

The other players looked at the scene. Isn’t he under our control now? Should we go over and kill him off? But Ye Xiu directly reminded everyone: “Ignore him. We need to hurry.” Enlightened Lord was already prepared to cast Heal on that Knight.

Chapter 729: High Level Confrontation

Lu Hanwen was helpless. It wasn’t like there was no counterplay to Knight taunting skills, but Blade Masters had no such method. Lu Hanwen could only quietly watch as his Flowing Cloud dashed towards that Knight. The Knight couldn’t avoid the attack, but he was able to disrupt the enemy’s rhythm. Taunt skills were quite useful in PvP.

Roar wasn’t a skill limited by time. The target had to hit the target once to dispel Roar’s effects. This Knight was quite smart. After roaring, he immediately ran in the other direction. He clearly wanted to delay Lu Hanwen from doing anything for as much time as possible. Lu Hanwen obviously knew what Roar did. Since he had no ways of dispelling the effects on his own, he actively chased after the Knight. He used Triple Slash to close the distance and his sword flew towards the fleeing Knight.

The Knight ran, while turning his head back from time to time. But when he turned around, how come Flowing Cloud wasn’t heading towards him?

The onlookers saw things more clearly. Flowing Cloud closed the distance with Triple Slash and the tip of his sword slashed upwards. No one could tell if the attack hit or not, but Flowing Cloud had already turned around and left.

If he turned his head to leave, then his attack clearly hit. But the Knight, who had been hit by the attack, didn’t even notice it. He was still looking back foolishly. How light was that attack? That kid really didn’t want to waste any time.

Flowing Cloud headed towards Enlightened Lord again, but before he could even take three steps, Flowing Cloud turned around again and went back.

"Ah ah ah ah ah, who is it this time!!" Lu Hanwen cried. This time, Flowing Cloud had been Provoked. That Knight from before didn’t have any taunt skills off cooldown yet, but there were plenty of Knights among the alliance troops to take his place…..

Provoke’s duration was based on time and not by an attack. This time, Lu Hanwen's Flowing Cloud didn’t charge towards the provoker as decisively. Instead, he made sure Flowing Cloud didn’t rush out too much. As he moved around, he hacked wildly at the hurrying players, but they all ignored him.

A lone individual’s strength compared to a group of players could be seen here. No matter how skilled Lu Hanwen might be or how powerful his equipment was, facing such a huge army, if the army chose to ignore you, there was nothing you could do about it.

The troops finally realized why Ye Xiu ordered them to completely ignore Lu Hanwen.

If they tried to kill Flowing Cloud, they might have more numbers, but they might not be able to catch himt. Instead, they might even be lead around by the nose. But if they completely ignored him and treated him as a pesty fly who constantly tickled them, the fly would never be able to kill them, so they could still endure it. They practically played the game for a living, yet they didn’t have as much in-game experience as a pro God? But they soon felt at ease. They might be familiar with the game, but they had never encountered such a high level expert before, so they obviously had no idea how to deal with one. For this type of battle, someone who was familiar with both the game and the pro scene like God Ye Qiu was more suited to lead.

Lu Hanwen was certainly in a pitiful position. The alliance troops continued to hurry over, but Flowing Cloud? The Knights were all lined up to deal with him. After one Provoke ended, another Provoke would come. After one Roar ended, another Roar came. Once their skills went on cooldown, boom, Knight’s Spirit activated and their skills would refresh. And the cycle continued….. Every Knight could taunt him four times. And how many Knights were there in the four guild alliance’s troops? Lu Hanwen was stuck in an infinite loop. Flowing Cloud ran around and jumped abou left and right, hacking and slashing, but all it led to was the other side laughing out loud.

After understanding the reason why, the players no longer thought of him as annoying, rather they found it hilarious messing around with him.

Lu Hanwen constantly shouted" Ah ah ah!!" in anger, but what could he do? It had nothing to do with him not being good enough. Blade Masters just didn’t have any way of dealing with taunt skills. Ye Xiu and Little Cold Hands were personally supporting everyone too. Every time Lu Hanwen happened to grasp an opportunity, Ye Xiu and Little Cold Hands always found some way to take it away.

Lu Hanwen was tossed about back and forth. In the end, he failed to delay them for very long. The alliance troops soon reached the battlefield. Blue Brook Guild hadn’t been able to move the boss anywhere because they had enemies!

Samsara and Seaside had arrived as well. The three sides were fighting with each other and for the boss. Blue Brook Guild arrived first though. Their guild was stronger too, so the boss was currently in their grasp. However, trying to move the boss away, while facing two enemy guilds wasn’t very likely. In addition, most guilds wouldn’t think of moving a level 55 boss anyways. They killed the boss quickly. The hardest part was the PvP. If they could just hurry and kill the boss off, there wouldn’t be any problems. There was no need to go into a you live or I die situation with the other guilds.

The battle for the boss was fairly normal. Blue River was very worried about Ye Qiu’s group though. After Lu Hanwen heard about his worries, he volunteered to delay them and win Blue Brook Guild some time. Blue River thought about it. Lu Hanwen was very skilled. Even though he was alone, he should be able to give them some trouble. Even if the other side killed him, it should take them quite a bit of time to do so. If they could be delayed, they had a much higher chance of snatching the boss!

As a result, Lu Hanwen was sent out. His ambush was indeed sharp and incisive, but he failed to accomplish his goal. The enemy troops completely ignored him and continued to hurry over. Lu Hanwen knew why he had come here, but he couldn’t do anything! Being controlled by such a disgusting method was quite sad.

Blue River immediately noticed the alliance troops arriving. His heart thumped.

That was quick! Did Lu Hanwen fail? Blue River thought to himself. He soon saw Lu Hanwen Flowing Cloud though. He was in the middle of the enemy troops being tossed around by a bunch of Knights like a dog.

Blue River immediately understood. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was being completely controlled through this method! Thinking of how the little kid had been played around with like a toy, Blue River wanted to apologize.

I was too careless! How could I underestimate Ye Xiu! Lu Hanwen is still just a child and I pushed him into a bunch of bullies. I sent a sheep to a tiger’s den!

Seeing how pitiful of a situation Flowing Cloud was in, Blue River hastily dispatched people to rescue him.

A few classes had skills, which could negate the effects of Provoke and Roar. For example, Knights had Immoveable Mountain, Qi Masters had Calm and Composed, which nullified taunts.

Blue River was about to go personally rescue him, but when the alliance troops arrived at the battlefield, they suddenly scattered. He no longer knew Flowing Cloud’s location. Before he could find him again, another guild had arrived: Tyrannical Ambition.

No guild would ever give up on a wild boss, but Ye Xiu was left speechless, when he saw the Cleric leading Tyrannical Ambition’s troops.

"Are you serious, Zhang Xinjie? You’re leading the troops for the Level 55 wild boss? Can’t you give us poor people a way out?" Ye Xiu shouted at them.

Misty Mountains.

This Cleric on Tyrannical Ambition’s side wore a full set of top in-game equipment too. After fighting all day yesterday, all of the guild learned of the news. This Cleric was Team Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie. How else could Tyrannical Ambition have been so dominant yesterday?

When Ye Xiu shouted at Tyrannical Ambition, Blue River also noticed them. He immediately wanted to run away. F*cking hell. Two bosses spawn at the same time and both Gods run over for the level 55 one. Are you serious? Both of you want the easy pickings? Instead of going for the harder level 65 boss, you all ran to fight with our reserve troops??

Blue River turned his head to look at his troops. Their side only consisted of reserve troops. Not just Blue Brook Guild. Samsara and Seaside weren’t using their elite troops either. Blue River was an elite player. He often met with the other guild elites, so he was very familiar with them.

Zhang Xinjie’s Misty Mountains led the way. When he looked at the enemy troops, he saw Enlightened Lord. He was also surprised, when Ye Xiu shouted at him.

"There’s something I need from here." Zhang Xinjie’s reason was the same as Ye Xiu’s.

"Hm? You need something from here? Is Old Han switching equipment?" Ye Xiu guessed. Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite’s Red Ribbon Janna mainly used Grappler skills, but the boss also knew a few Striker skills. Although the materials that dropped from a boss didn’t necessarily depend on the boss’s class, they often were. Just because Zhang Xinjie needed something from Red Ribbon Janna, it didn’t mean that Team Tyranny wanted to create new Striker equipment, but since Zhang Xinjie was personally leading the troops, Ye Xiu was obviously thinking higher. Team Tyranny’s Striker, Desert Dust, was their most powerful character.

"Team secret." Zhang Xinjie didn’t tell Ye Xiu. As he spoke, he already gave orders to his troops. Tyrannical Ambition didn’t bring their elite troops either. Zhang Xinjie clearly thought that they wouldn’t encounter anyone too troublesome for a level 55 boss, so it should be more than enough if he led the troops. But when he saw Ye Xiu unexpectedly there, he felt his head ache a bit.

Yesterday, the alliance wasn’t able to beat Tyrannical Ambition in any of the fights. But that wasn’t because of Zhang Xinjie alone. Ye Xiu wasn’t any worse than him in leading. As a result, the deciding factor was Tyrannical Ambition’s overall greater strength. However, he didn’t bring Tyrannical Ambition’s elite troops with him, while the other side brought their core forces. Tyrannical Ambition had no advantage right now.

Blue Brook Guild, Samsara, and Seaside were in an even more awkward situation... they were still attacking the boss, while Tyrannical Ambition and the alliance argued with each other as if they didn’t exist. But with Ye Qiu and Zhang Xinjie there, so what if they were being ignored? How could they object? They were currently fighting the boss though. Wouldn’t it be a bit too shameful to suddenly flee?

Chapter 730: Blue River’s Suicide Squad

Blue Brook Guild, Samsara, and Seaside were in an awkward situation. It seemed pointless to fight. One of the two Gods was going to take the boss, but retreating felt shameful! Even though you could say, oh, we came across two Gods, just fleeing at the sight of them was too cowardly, no? If word spread around, it could easily turn into one team being afraid of the other team. That wasn’t acceptable.

As a result, although the three guilds felt uneasy, they had no choice but to continue fighting foolishly. Even if they knew that they had no chance, they still had to follow the proper steps. Being a Club guild came with its own problems!

Meanwhile, Tyrannical Ambition and the alliance stood opposite from each other. The atmosphere was quite heavy, but neither side moved. The respective group chats on both sides were filled with messages though. Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie were currently arranging their troops. From a communication perspective, Tyrannical Ambition had the clear advantage. Zhang Xinjie could use the guild chat to give everyone orders.

It was more troublesome for Ye Xiu’s side though. The four guilds each had their own troops. He had to type his instructions into the QQ chat group and then have the guild leaders pass down the orders to their respective troops.

The first to move was Tyrannical Ambition.

The Tyrannical Ambition troops split into two. One half moved into a defensive formation like a wall, blocking off Ye Xiu’s side from the battlefield. The other half directly joined the chaotic boss fight and started contesting with the other three guilds.

The first to make a move may have the initiative, but it also revealed their strategy. The last to make a move could come up with a more direct countermeasure. Of course, as one of the four Master Tacticians, Zhang Xinjie accounted for it. Tyrannical Ambition acted swiftly, not wanting to give the other side enough time to respond. Although the defensive side formed a wall, they didn’t just stand there and wait. They pressed towards Ye Xiu’s side as if wanting to push them out of the battle.

The other side had to respond to an attack from the front. Zhang Xinjie hoped Ye Xiu would directly contend with them and crash into the wall. Zhang Xinjie didn’t think that they would be able to completely block the enemy troops, but he only needed time. It was only a Level 55 boss. With their level advantage, they would kill it very fast.

It had to be said that Blue River’s initial plan was no different from Zhang Xinjie’s. However, he overestimated the influence an individual could make on the battlefield and tried to let Lu Hanwen stall the enemy troops. However, the following events proved that in front of a well-organized group, an individual’s strength was too insignificant to matter.

How were things going for Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud? Not many were paying attention to him at this moment. Even Blue River, who had originally been leading the rescue team, ran back dejectedly to fight the boss after seeing those two forces collide.

"How is it going, Little Lu?" Blue River could only message Lu Hanwen to let the other know that he hadn’t been forgotten.

"Ye Qiu really is a difficult opponent. Not only did he see through the flaw in my Shadow Steps, he even used Knight taunt skills to put a collar on me!!!" Lu Hanwen liked to use exclamation marks, making it sound like he was always excited.

The words "put a collar on me" made Blue River sweat. This little kid really had a way with words. What kind of person are you regarding yourself as?

"Can you still hold on?" Blue River asked.

"They don’t seem to want to spend the time to kill me!" Lu Hanwen replied.

"Yeah, they’ve got a formidable opponent." Blue River said.

"Who?" Lu Hanwen asked.

"Zhang Xinjie. Tyrannical Ambition’s vice-captain." Blue River replied.

"Ah! The one who’s a Master Tactician like Ye Qiu and Xiao Shiqin! That Zhang Xinjie!!!" Lu Hanwen exclaimed.

"That’s him."

"I should go watch and learn from them!!"

"What are you doing right now?" Blue River was a bit depressed. Lu Hanwen didn’t seem very busy. He was chatting quite happily.

"There’s no point doing anything. It depends on what they want to do!" Lu Hanwen finally expressed his helplessness. He clearly felt powerless in his current situation.

"Don’t worry. I’ll think of some way to rescue you." Blue River said. He circled around with his small rescue squad. With those two Gods competing, was there any point trying to fight for the boss? None at all! Blue River felt like if he could stop those two Gods with his troops, he would be qualified to take over Yu Wenzhou’s shotcalling position in Team Blue Rain.

Blue River clearly knew his own capabilities. Although he didn’t say it out loud, he had already given up on the boss. But he wasn’t the type to do things half-heartedly. If Lu Hanwen wasn’t deep within enemy ranks, he would still definitely be trying his hardest leading his troops. But that wasn’t the case, so Blue River just send a suicide squad into the the enemy ranks. As for the fight with the other guilds, he had someone else take over.

When that someone else heard about the arrangement, he nearly pissed himself. If he didn’t know about Blue Bridge Spring Snow’s kindly reputation, he would have thought that Blue Bridge was leaving everyone here to sacrifice themselves, so he could run away safely. Facing Zhang Xinjie and Ye Qiu was too heavy of a responsibility!

"Try your best." Blue River was quite serious, "We’re going to go rescue Little Lu."

Blue River led his suicide squad away. Meanwhile, the two forces were already clashing with each other. All sorts of skills and players being blown away flew around everywhere. The two Master Tacticians lived up to their name. Blue River doubted that he could grasp the mind games being played, so he simply watched as if it were a movie. At the same time, he circled around to the back with his suicide squad and found a rooftop to jump onto. The squad leaped up and then lay on their bellies, crawling until they got to the edges of the rooftop to look down covertly.

How terrible!

Lu Hanwen was having a hard time. Ye Xiu’s group as fighting against Tyrannical Ambition. The Knights were the defensive core of the troops. How could they not be used? As a result, they didn’t have the manpower to keep Lu Hanwen under control. But leaving a skilled expert like Lu Hanwen alone was the same as lighting their own home’s backyard on fire. They had to kill him off.

Being restricted by taunts, Lu Hanwen was truly struggling to survive. It was only because his skill level was much higher than a normal player’s that he was still alive. A normal player would have died many times over by now. Even so, Flowing Cloud was just barely hanging on by a thread.

"Buff him!!" Blue River hastily ordered. A Knight and a Qi Master rushed forward immediately.

"Protect!" Blue River ordered. He led the way and jumped down from the rooftop with a Falling Light Blade. The other squad members occupied the high ground and released their long-ranged attacks. The Knight and Qi Master also leaped down. The Knight used a Heroic Leap, while the Qi Master used Slipstream. Along with Blue River and the other squad members, they began fighting fiercely.

These ten players came out of nowhere. They really did surprise the alliance players. However, over here, hundred player groups were the unit of measurement. Ten players weren’t anything to be frightened of, unless these ten were all pro players. That wasn’t possible though. The entire Team Blue Rain being dispatched for a Level 55 wild boss? A commemoration for the level 55 era would be more believable!

"Ah! Leader!!!" The kid had good eyes. The sudden ambush surprised everyone, including Lu Hanwen. But once he looked at them, he noticed Blue Bridge Sprint Snow among them, who descended with a Falling Light Blade. Unfortunately, the Falling Light Blade didn’t hit anyone. The surrounding players had all scattered away to avoid it.

"Leader, you used your Falling Light Blade waaayy too early!!" Lu Hanwen criticized Blue River.

"Shut up!" Blue River blushed. He had to admit though. He really had used his skill too early. But that was to show off their strength, right?

"Buff!" Blue River roared.

"Understood!" The Knight and the Qi Master had been brought over by Blue River to get Lu Hanwen out of his predicament. Just one was enough actually. If their buffs overlapped, it wouldn’t extend the duration or anything. Blue River still brought two over for insurance.

Heroic Leap and Slipstream both had slight AoE effects, so the surrounding enemies dodged the attacks, giving the two players time to cast their buffs onto Flowing Cloud.

Immovable Mountain.

Calm and Composed.

When these two skills were used, a Knight from the four guild alliance used a Roar, affecting the entire suicide squad, except for Flowing Cloud.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had one of the two buffs, so he wouldn’t be affected by taunts.

"You go first!" Blue River shouted.

"Then what about you guys!" Lu Hanwen said.

"We’ll come back from the revival point!" Blue River said the truth and expressed how they might not be able to escape. But at the same time, he reminded Lu Hanwen: this is a game. If we die, we can just come back. Don’t be like a hero from a drama and insist on dying with everyone else. We’re too old for that sort of thing.

"Don’t jump to conclusions. Buff me and I’ll bring you guys out! Why’d you bring so few people!" Lu Hanwen didn’t leave Blue River and the others. His words sounded quite heroic, making Blue River feel a bit ashamed. He came here thinking he would die. Had he been thinking too negatively?

Headwind Strike!

Flowing Cloud’s sword began to glow to open a path for these ten players. The ten players were affected by Roar, so they all pounced on that Knight. Before reaching the Knight, they were already attacking. If their attacks hit, Roar would disappear. These ten were experienced players. They had already reached this step. How could they let the Knight go so easily? The ten surrounded him. He brought it upon himself. Even if they couldn’t kill him, they could put more pressure on the healers and waste their healing skills.

"Go!"

Blue River and the other nine players were still beating up that Knight, when they heard Lu Hanwen’s shout. They turned their heads. D*mn! In such a short amount of time, there were already quite a few players in front of Flowing Cloud, who were swaying unsteadily. How many skills had he used?

Afterwards, he used Shadow Steps. This was the suicide squad’s first time seeing it. They gasped in shock: "Eight shadows?"

There was no Ye Xiu here. These eight shadows were like eight real shadows to those normal players. The enemies were in a panic. One of the enemy Knights was about to use Roar, but the Knight in the suicide squad activated Knight’s Spirit and re-applied Immovable Mountain on Lu Hanwen. Roar wasn’t going to work. Flowing Cloud forced open a path. The ten players followed behind him. The Knights, who still wanted to taunt them, didn’t have any methods left. There weren’t many Knights remaining here.

"We got out! Ha ha!" Lu Hanwen quickly rushed out. Blue River was ecstatic as well. But at this moment, he received a message from the substitute group leader: "We can’t hold on! The boss has been snatched away!"

Their enemies weren’t any slower…...

Chapter 731 - The Intention Isn’t to Break Through

Blue Brook Guild’s second group leader was in a state of agony. He didn’t know who he should express it to. Blue River told him that it was good enough if he tried his best, and he had resolved to do as he had been told. In the end, he felt like before he could even try his best, Tyrannical Ambition swarmed Scarlet Ribbon Janna and snatched her away. That sort of feeling, where he had the power yet couldn’t use it, made him feel miserable.

Tyrannical Ambition had split into numerous small teams to carry away the boss. They forced their way into the battlefield, instantly cutting apart Blue Brook Guild’s troops into several sections. The second group leader hastily gave an order, but before the message could even be passed down, the players fighting the boss reported: the main tank has been killed. The boss is being forcefully pushed away.

Being forcefully pushed away meant that the boss’s aggro wasn’t actually on anyone in Tyrannical Ambition. Rather, Tyrannical Ambition blocked the boss from moving towards its target. The boss couldn’t just only lock in on a target and refuse to attack anyone else. In order to close in on its target, the boss would try to get rid of any obstructions. In this case, the obstruction was Tyrannical Ambition, who had wedged their way between the boss and its target.

Obstructing the boss in this way could generate aggro as well. In addition, Tyrannical Ambition was attacking, while Blue Brook Guild was unable to reach the boss, slowly swaying the boss’s aggro from Blue Brook Guild to Tyrannical Ambition. If this situation continued, Tyrannical Ambition would successfully steal away the boss.

The second group leader obviously understood the situation. He immediately ordered his troops to clash with Tyrannical Ambition. However, Tyrannical Ambition’s layer up layer defense prevented them from closing in on the boss. What made the second group leader even angrier was that Samsara and Seaside seemed to have given up on the boss. They fought half-heartedly, not at all with the same energy as Blue Brook Guild.

All in all, their situation was different from Blue Brook Guild’s. Blue Brook Guild had the advantage up until now. The more Blue Brook Guild fought Tyrannical Ambition to a deadlock, the better of a chance they would have to steal the boss. After all, Tyrannical Ambition couldn’t focus all of their attention on the boss. They split their forces into two to deal with another powerful enemy on the other side.

As for Samsara and Seaside? They had been on the disadvantage against Blue Brook Guild previously. Rushing over and burning up all of their energy wouldn’t improve their situation much. Their efforts might even help Blue Brook Guild, who was in the lead. A deadlock would obviously be advantageous to the one in the lead. They wouldn’t gain much from helping.

If there was no thing to gain, why bother? Why not just keep faking it? If Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition continued to injure each other, who knew if an opportunity would appear. However, after seeing Tyrannical Ambition swiftly take the initiative, the two guilds no longer had any hope for Blue Brook Guild. But what if the alliance broke through Tyrannical Ambition’s defense and threw the battlefield into disorder?

“Fourth group charge! Everyone else, look for an opening!”

“2 o’clock! Gather towards the 2 o’clock direction!”

“Ai, too slow……”

Ye Xiu observed the field and adjusted accordingly, but passing down orders through twists and turns illustrated a problem: by the time the troops started carrying out the orders, the other side already finished fixing it. The alliance was unable to break through the opening in one go. They still slowly nibbled away at the enemy defenses, but it was progressing too slowly. At this rate, by the time they broke through, Tyrannical Ambition would have gained enough of an insurmountable lead. With Zhang Xinjie commanding Tyrannical Ambition, forcefully pushing the boss away or annihilating Tyrannical Ambition along with the boss was too difficult.

“Steamed Bun, Little Tang, Little Qiao, Little Hands, Loulan Slash, Little Bei, Ocean, Night Tide, Thousand Leaves, come with me!” Ye Xiu saw that this wasn’t an issue that could be solved in a short amount of time, so he picked out an elite team and prepared to breakthrough the enemy defenses using a small but powerful team. Of the nine people picked out, four were from Happy, while five were the main core of Heavenly Justice’s team.

“What about me!” Chen Guo had come with them to the boss. Ye Xiu had picked out a bunch of people, but she wasn’t one of them. It made her angry.

“Uh…... a team can only have ten people maximum…..” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo wanted to cry. She was the boss, yet no face was given to her.

“Don’t you have too many Clerics!” Chen Guo noticed. Of the ten, Ye Xiu, Little Cold Hands, and Heavenly Justice’s Thousand Falling Leaves were all clerics. There were times when three healers when needed, albeit rare. Chen Guo didn’t care though. She wanted a spot.

“You can just come along with us.” Ye Xiu said.

Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord quickly formed a team with the other nine players. After gathering together, Chen Guo pitifully followed along like an outsider. She waited for instructions, but she didn’t hear Ye Xiu say anything. When she turned to look, he was actually typing.

“How am I supposed to see it if you type!” Chen Guo got angry. Ye Xiu was giving instructions to the team through the team chat. Chen Guo wasn’t a part of the team though, so she couldn’t see any of the messages.

“Okay, so it’s like that. Everyone, get ready. Chasing Haze, follow us.” Ye Xiu immediately shouted. Chen Guo wanted to cry again. Ye Xiu said a few words to appease her anger. How could that be considered as giving her any face?

“Everyone else, pay attention to our movements and coordinate with us.” Ye Xiu said in the QQ group chat and then began leading the team.

“Chasing Haze, Satellite Beam!” Ye Xiu gave Chen Guo a task. Chen Guo didn’t know whether this was a consolation prize or not. In any case, she carried out her given task. A brilliant Satellite Beam descended from the skies, directly towards Tyrannical Ambition. Tyrannical Ambition refused to budge though. The healers simply had more work to do. The sacred light matched the strength of the Satellite Beam, quickly rendering it null. The other side had more players. Clerics were also one of Tyrannical Ambition’s two best classes. A single Satellite Beam wouldn’t do much.

“Forward!” But the team charged forward nonetheless. The one at the front was Tang Rou’s Battle Mage. Her Dragon Breaks the Ranks sent three flying. Tyrant’s Destruction and Falling Flower Palm sent several more away as well. However, soon afterwards, three Sacred Fires surrounded Tang Rou’s Battle Mage in a triangle, trapping her inside. The long-ranged mages fired a barrage of spells. The gunners focused their fire. They made every effort to kill this reckless lone wolf.

Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire!

Crimson Storm!

Ocean Ahead and Loulan Slash timed their attacks perfectly alongside Tang Rou’s attacks. Lightning and fire covered the ground. Blood aura boiled about. Yet Tyrannical Ambition stood strong. They just couldn’t see Tang Rou’s Battle Mage anymore.

“Keep up her health!!”

Ye Xiu personally led the healing. The three Clerics focused their heals onto Tang Rou’s Battle Mage. At the same time, everyone rushed into the enemy ranks. From the very beginning, every one of them carried an automatic heal over time buff.

“Holy Commandment!” Ye Xiu shouted again. The three cast Holy Commandment. Ye Xiu had told them where to cast the spell beforehand. Their Holy Commandments landed on the enemy troops ahead. Despite being inside Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire’s spell range, the three players immersed in the sacred light glowed brightly.

After being hit by the skill, the three became the focus of everyone’s attacks. The three obviously understood this reasoning and hastily retreated, but a Dragon Breaks the Ranks welcomed them. Tang Rou wasn’t the only Battle Mage in the team. Little Bei was there too.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Tyrant’s Destruction, Falling Flower Palm swept the field clean. A common combo like this was something an aspiring pro player like Little Bei could easily do. His usage was even better than Tang Rou’s too. Many Tyrannical Ambition players were once again sent tumbling. Night Tide and Steamed Bun rushed out. They didn’t attack towards a specific direction, but rather revolved around the team, protecting them. The team was now deep in enemy territory. The next person to attack was Qiao Yifan. One Inch Ash set up an Ice Formation, instantly freezing several Tyrannical Ambition players. The team quickly wiped the frozen blocks away. The ten players along with Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze stood together, fending off enemy attacks around them, while slowly advancing forward using Qiao Yifan’s ghost formations.

The assault began with Tang Rou’s initial attack, but the one to lead the way was Qiao Yifan’s Ghostblade. The pressure was huge for the three Clerics though. Deep in enemy territory, the melee attacks weren’t too difficult to deal with, but the long-range attacks, especially the AoE ones, were difficult to avoid. They all depended on the healing from the three Clerics to survive. The mana costs for the Clerics were immense, but support soon came from behind. The alliance troops attacked the two sides along the path set by the team. If Tyrannical Ambition was only concerned with Ye Xiu’s small team, Ye Xiu would be happy. Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses would fall even faster in that case.

Unfortunately, Zhang Xinjie wouldn’t make such a low leveled mistake. His troops continued to prioritize the large-scale assault, which reduced the pressure on the ten-man team, allowing them to quickly advance. Zhang Xinjie’s defensive formation had a fair amount of depth to it, but by not prioritizing the small team, the small team easily broke through.

“D*mn, we’ve been ignored!” Ye Xiu wasn’t happy about breaking through the defensive lines. He sighed instead because he knew they were let through. Getting the team through wasn’t his intent. He hoped that their team would put pressure on Tyrannical Ambition and disrupt the enemy’s flow. Zhang Xinjie saw through it though. He still focused on the overall situation. A ten-man team? Letting them through was fine. A ten-man team stealing away the boss under Zhang Xinjie’s eyes was at all possible.

Chapter 732 - A God’s Way of Fighting

After breaking through the blockade, Ye Xiu had Enlightened Lord look back. Tyrannical Ambition’s defense was just as complete as before. Zhang Xinjie handled their ten-man team the same way he had dealt with Blue Brook Guild’s Lu Hanwen. Ignoring the threat was the best way to deal with it. Trying to deal with it only made it worse.

Ye Xiu was helpless. Had he made the decision too hastily?

When Ye Xiu looked ahead, the boss had been trapped by Tyrannical Ambition. The aggro still wasn’t stable, but seeing Blue Brook Guild’s helplessness, Tyrannical Ambition thoroughly stabilizing the boss’s aggro was simply a matter of time.

“Let’s go!” Ye Xiu called out to his teammates. Enlightened Lord rushed towards the boss.

“To steal the boss?” Loulan Slash and the others asked.

“That’s a bit too difficult, but we can at least give them some trouble.” Ye Xiu said.

“Alright. We’ll just do as you say!” Loulan Slash said.

“Where’s Zhang Xinjie?” Ye Xiu surveyed the surroundings, but he didn’t see any signs of Zhang Xinjie’s current character, Misty Mountains. Although the value he brought to the table was more than just what a character could bring, being too conspicuous would still certainly make him a target. It was better to stay low. It was something Ye Xiu also did.

“Let’s go from here!” Unable to find Zhang Xinjie, Ye Xiu found an opening.

“Forward!”

For this charge, they directly flocked over without the same sort of coordination as before. One Inch Ash threw down a ghost formation. The eleven gathered inside, sending out their skills or coordinating or acting at opportunities. They fought as they pleased. Ye Xiu’s only instruction was to attack whoever was attacking the boss.

For example, when they fought against Howling Heights for the boss, eliminating the Knight, who had the boss’s aggro, was obviously the best way to disrupt the enemy. However, facing Zhang Xinjie, Ye Xiu couldn’t find a big enough opening to do so. They could only keep working at it.

The eleven naturally closed in on the long-ranged classes surrounding the boss first. They were the most convenient targets for them. Tyrannical Ambition quickly formed countermeasures. The long-ranged classes shrunk away and switched places with the melee classes, who fended them off.

“Stick closely!” Ye Xiu instructed.

Qiao Yifan placed his ghost formations tightly. The eleven chased after the long-ranged classes and continued bullying them. However, the enemy gunners threw grenades together and the enemy mages erected Fire Walls. They were clearly being directed by someone. In an instant, Ye Xiu’s team was separated from Tyrannical Ambition.

“Turn right!” Ye Xiu ordered again.

A shotcaller needed to make swift decisions and quickly adjust depending on the situations.

They continued to follow their original strategy of attacking anyone who was fighting the boss. Strategy gave a general direction. Tactics were the details. Tactics needed to be constantly adjusted. This was where the value of a shotcaller could be displayed. Having a shotcaller who couldn’t adapt was the same as having none at all.

“Second group leader, break through there!”

The person telling the second group leader where to go wasn’t his own ally, but the name of an enemy player. Ye Xiu had targeted a Tyrannical Ambition player called Second Group Leader. This player wasn’t actually a priority target. Ye Xiu was using him as an indicator for the general direction. A Holy Commandment soon fell. Steamed Bun’s Brawler rushed over the fastest and initiated with a Strangle. Holy Commandment increased damage from all sources by 30%. Strangle dealt 150% of his physical attack. With another wave of attacks following, how could this Second Group Leader survive?

Even worse, the people who killed him didn’t care about him. He was just an indicator for where Ye Xiu’s team would move to. Killing him was simply because he was a convenient target for tactical purposes.

Tyrannical Ambition switched out their melee classes to defend. The enemies quickly moved.

“Cut off their rear. Have four teams gather at the 10 o’clock direction to confront them. Long-ranged classes cover the field. Push them towards Blue Brook Guild’s side.” Zhang Xinjie was watching Ye Xiu’s team closely! He gave command after command. It was his main work right now.

“Long-ranged classes, attack. Hurry! Rush forward and break through!”

Zhang Xinjie ordered four teams to meet Ye Xiu’s team, but such a gathering couldn’t be done in an instant. Ye Xiu also gave a command swiftly. Seeing the other side’s intentions, he decided to forcefully break through while the other side’s formation wasn’t complete yet. In this confrontation, Ye Xiu’s team had fewer people, so it was more agile. Their battle strength could be displayed without restraint.

Before Tyrannical Ambition’s four teams could reach 60% of what Zhang Xinjie hoped, the eleven charged over. Chasing Haze began firing a barrage of bullets. Ocean Ahead covered the team with spells. One Inch Ash paved a path with his ghost formations. The two Battle Mages once again became the spearpoint. Loulan Slash rampaged. Steamed Bun’s Brawler and Night Tide’s Grappler didn’t have good AoE attacks, so they specifically looked for any openings. If they saw a player, who was at a loss for what to do, they immediately went over to bully him.

With this sudden and violent attack, how could the four teams finish assembling? The eleven instantly broke through. The four teams were at a loss for a moment. They obviously knew why Zhang Xinjie wanted them to gather together, but they failed to do so, so should still continue gathering together?

“Two teams move left and converge. Long-ranged classes go in and cover the gap. Chase after them with your long-ranged attacks.” Zhang Xinjie felt sorry that it didn’t works, but it was never realistic to expect something to happen for sure. His troops were temporary ones, so their ability to carry out his orders was limited. If he had Tyrannical Ambition’s elite troops, perhaps it might have worked.

It was just a maybe though.

No one could guarantee something would happen in a battle.

“Knights, chain three Provokes and lead the boss in the 7 o’clock direction. Everyone else follow after the boss.” Zhang Xinjie said.

When the boss moved, the entire battlefield slowly shifted. Ye Xiu’s team stayed in the same place, but their relative location to the boss was changing. Ye Xiu turned around to check the overall situation. Zhang Xinjie wanted to throw them into Blue Brook Guild. Along with the long-ranged classes pressuring them, he wanted them to clash with Blue Brook Guild.

Ye Xiu wasn’t going to fall for it.

“Charge! Continue charging forward!”

It was a simple order. He was banking on their team’s far superior strength. Tyrannical Ambition had to guard the boss and block Blue Brook Guild. There was no way for them to concentrate their forces onto them. In this situation, Zhang Xinjie being able to distance the boss from Ye Xiu’s team was worthy of being called a God.

“This isn’t good!” Ye Xiu surmised. Even though their team was unstoppable, they were still unable to close in on the boss. Zhang Xinjie utilized his numbers advantage, minimizing the damage their team could bring.

“We have to break in.” Ye Xiu decided.He knew Tyrannical Ambition’s core defense would be like an iron wall, but they had no choice. They needed to tear through the iron wall. If they didn’t, there would be no more opportunities.

“Tofu Pudding Cake, kill!”

Tofu Pudding Cake was another unfortunate player to be named. Ye Xiu saw him and picked him. The eleven charged. Tofu Pudding Cake died and his corpse marked the team’s new path.

“This time, we’ll be relying on you and Little Bei.” Ye Xiu told Loulan Slash. Opening up a path fit Tang Rou the best, but Tang Rou’s current equipment wasn’t doing enough. Poor equipment meant low damage. No matter how hard she tried, there were things she couldn’t do. Their following plan required power and force.

If it were One Autumn Leaf…...

Ye Xiu couldn’t help but think. If he had One Autumn Leaf, he might have been able to open a path earlier.

“Relax. Leave it to me!” Loulan Slash replied. As a guild leader and team captain, Loulan Slash knew when to take responsibility. It wouldn’t be right to have Ye Xiu give him a task only for him to say “I can’t do it. Let someone else do it.”

“Little Tang, you follow after them. Steamed Bun and Night Tide act as support. Chasing Haze and Ocean Ahead protect them. Everyone else knows what to do, right? Okay, let’s go!” Ye Xiu arranged their formation and they put their plan into motion. He wanted to make an abrupt move to fluster Zhang Xinjie.

“So he really did decide to charge, huh.”

Ye Xiu’s tactics truly made it difficult for Zhang Xinjie to contend against. His troops were constantly rushing about, but he had figured out Ye Xiu’s general intent long ago. Someone as cautious as him had already made preparations for this stage before it was necessary.

“Too bad! His team’s DPS isn’t high enough!” Zhang Xinjie had noticed their team’s brave charge and had noticed this unfortunate problem. Heavenly Justice’s five players had top-tier equipment, but the others were underwhelming.

“If your equipment is lacking, you can make up for it with your skill. If you were a damage dealer, even with poor equipment, it might have been enough. But too bad! You’re using a Cleric. Despite your support, it isn’t enough!” Zhang Xinjie was completely calm now. No one was more familiar with Clerics than him. The support skills weren’t enough to be a deciding factor. According to the enemy team’s coordination, Zhang Xinjie had made adjustments to their defense. He believed that there were no holes. The ten-man team wouldn’t be able to break through. After a while, the team might even be surrounded and eventually be killed alongside the boss.

“Not good…..” Their initial assault went well, but Ye Xiu soon noticed the enemy’s swift response. The enemy defense soon became difficult to penetrate. Seeing the enemies ahead, none of the ideas that Ye Xiu thought up of would work. They couldn’t tear through the iron wall. The reason was heartbreaking: their DPS wasn’t high enough.

“Prepare to retreat.”

“Prepare to surround them.”

The two Gods gave their respective orders simultaneously. Who knew at this moment, someone from outside rushed over: “Ah! There’s an opening here! I’m in!!!!”

Chapter 733: More Damage

Not everyone recognized this voice, but everyone immediately realized who it had come from because the pitch it had was very particular.　

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud, with Blue Brook Guild’s tag above his name, shouted while slaughtering his way through the crowd like a whirlwind. He was following the very path that Ye Xiu’s team had torn open. How could the remaining leftovers stop Lu Hanwen? All they saw was a flash of light and Flowing Cloud was already amongst them.　

"Kid! You’ve got a bright future ahead of you! Keep charging forward!" Ye Xiu saw this unexpected arrival and his spirits instantly rose. Skill? Lu Hanwen had it! Damage! Flowing Cloud wore a full set of Orange equipment, top-tier in the game. Their team was lacking damage, but the addition of this kid would certainly fix that problem.　

"What? You guys are in here too?" Lu Hanwen looked in astonishment at Enlightened Lord’s group.　　

"We’ve been here for awhile now. You’re late! Hurry! We need to seize this opportunity." Ye Xiu shouted. He was afraid that Lu Hanwen wouldn’t be able to control himself and would furiously attack them on sight. Not only would he be not helping them, he would spell disaster for their little team.

Reality gratified him. This fourteen year old kid didn’t act impulsively. He calmly asked: "I heard the enemy commander is Senior Zhang Xinjie."　

"Yes." Ye Xiu said.

"Then I can’t be careless this time!" Lu Hanwen said. His Flowing Cloud rushed forward. During this time, he activated Shadow Steps. His character flickered and split into one, two, three, four, five, six shadows.　　

Lu Hanwen only released six shadows, but this time, none of them could instantly be distinguished. These six shadows were perfectly created.

"What a little demon!" Ye Xiu was amazed, not because Lu Hanwen could control six perfect shadows, but because of his temperament.

Lu Hanwen didn’t employ eight shadows like he had before and instead only used six, indicating that he was well aware of the flaws in his technique. Thus, after confirming that his opponent was God Zhang Xinjie, he switched from eight shadows to six. When he fought against Ye Xiu, he realized that his eight shadows was no better than four in front of a God.

This hyperactive kid was actually very serious and calm when it came to battle.

With all six shadows being indistinguishable, Tyrannical Ambition could only test each one out one by one, but under Lu Hanwen’s incredible control, these six shadows crossed over each other mystifyingly. Those that had been found out were switched around until they were hidden again, making it even more difficult for Tyrannical Ambition to identify the fakes. Flowing Cloud neared, but Tyrannical Ambition’s players didn’t know where to defend. Six shadows but only one was real. It was too difficult to guess!

"Who is this person!" When Zhang Xinjie saw Flowing Cloud, who had Blue Brook Guild’s tag above his name, he didn’t pay too much attention to him. He thought that Flowing Cloud was just some random player, who had gotten lost in the midst of battle. He thought Tyrannical Ambition would quickly dispose of him, but by the time he saw Flowing Cloud go along the path set by Ye Qiu’s team and the six perfect shadows, Zhang Xinjie realized: an unexpected variable had intruded.　

"Third from the left!!"

Lu Hanwen’s shadows crossed over each other rapidly like a blur to everyone else, but for a God like Zhang Xinjie with practiced eyes and experience, he was able to identify the real one. Zhang Xinjie wasn’t certain, but he needed to pick out one. Tyrannical Ambition couldn’t cover all six.　　

Third from the left was actually correct.

But by the time he shouted at the warning and Tyrannical Ambition’s players counted, Flowing Cloud had already arrived. His sword danced and Tyrannical Ambition’s formation started to crumble.

"Charge!" Ye Xiu wasn’t going to let this opportunity slide. He gave the order and the small team started attacking.

"Nice synergy!" Lu Hanwen shouted.

"Join our team so you can receive heals!" Ye Xiu decisively split the team. They originally had eleven players, only one extra from the limit. As a result, Ye Xiu set up two teams and moved the positions around before throwing an invite to Lu Hanwen.

"Okay!" Lu Hanwen was straightforward and accepted. As soon as he entered the team, Ye Xiu cast a heal on him.

"Your heal sucks!" Lu Hanwen saw his health barely go move and shouted. He had been trained with a pro team, so his eyes weren’t ordinary. The amount of healing that a character with trash equipment could do naturally seemed like nothing to Lu Hanwen.

"Kid, you talk too much!" Loulan Slash wasn’t happy. That little punk was talking to God Ye Qiu. How could he say that his healing sucked?

"It’s not a problem that skill can fix, but rather his equipment!" Lu Hanwen spoke the truth.

"Stop chatting. Are your pretending that this is easy?" Ye Xiu said. Although they had broken through, they were still within Tyrannical Ambition’s core forces. This was just the first step. Next, they needed to stir up trouble. They couldn’t be careless!

"Where’s Zhang Xinjie?" Lu Hanwen asked.

"His character’s called Misty Mountains. If you see him, don’t be nice." Ye Xiu sold Zhang Xinjie out in an instant.

"Kill that Knight!" Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was the first to break into the core. He headed straight for the Knight which held the boss’s aggro. He swiftly slashed down a few times. The Knight tried to block, but he wasn’t Lu Hanwen’s opponent. However, his body constantly glowed with white light. Despite Lu Hanwen’s fierce attacks, the Knight’s health refused to budge, even with the boss attacking him.

"An expert’s healing him!" Lu Hanwen shouted.

"Who would have thought? Didn’t I say Zhang Xinjie was here?" Ye Xiu replied sarcastically.

"Where is he?" Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud looked around.

"Don’t bother looking for him. Attack the boss!" Ye Xiu suddenly said.

"Boss?" Lu Hanwen didn’t understand the reason behind his order. He clearly didn’t have unconditional respect for Ye Qiu either.

"I just looked at a guide..."

"Cough..." Loulan Slash couldn’t help but cough. They were in such an intense predicament, yet God Ye Qiu was giving them an order based off a guide that he had just skimmed through. Despite God Ye Qiu always being reliable, it still felt wrong.

"I checked the conditions for making this boss get enraged. You can do it. Enrage him!" Ye Xiu finished his words.

"How do I do it?" Lu Hanwen asked.

"Damage. Deal as much damage as possible." Ye Xiu said. Then, he called out to others: "Protect him. Little Qiao, Sword Formation. Thousand Leaves, Holy Commandment."

Everyone did their assigned tasks. Thousand Falling Leaves cast a Holy Commandment. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash lay down a Sword Formation. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud acted at this moment. Double Stab, Rising Dragon Slash, Sky Strike, Falling Phoenix Slash, Headwind Strike... Skill after skill rolled forth, each hit tearing blood from Red Ribbon Janna’s character model. The storm of attacks made it impossible for the boss to ignore his existence. The boss turned around and grabbed at Flowing Cloud. Red Ribbon Janna was a Grappler with terrifying grabs.　

"Dodge one unit farther. The boss has an extended grab range!" Ye Xiu immediately reminded. A young player like Lu Hanwen might have never encountered this Level 55 Heavenly Domain boss before.

"It truly deserves to be a boss!" Lu Hanwen replied. Sure enough, Flowing Cloud dodged farther than before. Red Ribbon Janna missed and then swiped. Lu Hanwen reacted quickly. Flowing Cloud crouched and rolled back to his previous location. He started attacking furiously again.

Ye Xiu knew Lu Hanwen was more than skilled enough to handle the boss, so he wasn’t worried. He turned around, checking the surroundings.

"Attack that Blade Master! Knights, pull him away by force." Zhang Xinjie saw Flowing Cloud’s movements. After a moment of surprise, he realized the reason and immediately passed down an order.

Pulling away by force told the Knights to use their taunt skills to pull him away. However, Lu Hanwen had been toyed with by this tactic all day and was very wary of it. As soon as he saw the Knights begin move, his character immediately dashed about unpredictably to prevent them from clicking on him.

At this moment, Ye Xiu suddenly shouted: "Move left two units."

Lu Hanwen didn’t know why, but he still listened to the shout, when he heard a Roar. He had been hit! A Knight had successfully cast Roar on him.

"I’ve been hit by Roar!" Lu Hanwen was furious.

"It was intentional!" Ye Xiu replied.　

Lu Hanwen regained his calm and looked around in delight. He had been taunted, but so had the boss. Both of them were headed in the same direction, meaning that the two couldn’t be separated for now. Ye Xiu told him to move two units to the left, so Flowing Cloud and the boss would both be in range.

Tyrannical Ambition’s Knights had to adjust again. Ye Xiu shouted again: "It’s about to be Enraged. Let’s scatter. Little Lu, you’re on your own!"

"What! Where’s your sense of brotherhood?" Lu Hanwen jumped up and down in anger.

"Yeah! Don’t forget that we’re still enemies!" Ye Xiu said. Their team rushed out. Lu Hanwen just happened to reach the boss’s Enraged conditions. Red Ribbon Janna waved his arms and roared. His upper garment tore apart.

"At least tell me what his Enraged skills are!!!" Lu Hanwen had no idea what this Level 55 wild boss did.

"No time. Baidu it yourself!" Ye Xiu replied. His team fled swiftly. Tyrannical Ambition’s players were hastily pulling away under Zhang Xinjie’s orders as well. Lu Hanwen looked at the situation and knew that running far away from the boss was what he should probably be doing, so he hastily ran as well, but he had been the one to Enrage the boss. The boss’ attention was focused entirely on him. Red Ribbon Janna leapt high into the air with both fists clenched, smashing straight for Flowing Cloud.

Level 55 wild boss, Red Ribbon Janna Enraged skill: Earthquake Mountain Sway.

Chapter 734: Triggering An Enraged Boss

Red Ribbon Janna’s ripped upper garment fluttered in the wind. He crashed to the ground with the force of 30,000 catties. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud rolled backwards to dodge the fists, but Red Ribbon Janna wasn’t going to stop just because he missed once. His fists slammed into the ground.

A huge explosion boomed like thunder. Everyone in Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite watched as their screens shook from the shaking caused by the impact. Those within 30 units of Red Ribbon Janna’s attack experienced it to a vastly different extent. The quake threw them into the air.

"Earthquake Mountain Sway! An Enraged attack? The boss has already hit red? That fast?" Blue River immediately understood what was happening when he felt the trembles. He was astonished. It hadn’t been long since the boss battle had begun. Despite having a level advantage over the level 55 wild boss, the boss still shouldn’t be dying so fast.

While he was in awe, he saw numerous players bounce into the air along with countless rocks. Earthquake Mountain Sway wasn’t finished yet though. Red Ribbon Janna roared. He struck out with both of his arms and suddenly spun 360 degrees. The surrounding air within 30 units of him began to churn. A tornado began forming with him as the eye of the storm. The rocks and players in the surrounding area were swept away by the tornado, unable to resist.

Red Ribbon Janna once again raised his arms and slammed the ground. A boom erupted from where he had struck and the rocks within the tornado disintegrated. As for the players flying inside? They also disappeared.

A level 55 wild boss might be 15 levels lower than the players, but a powerful Enraged move was still more than enough to instantly kill. During the level 55 era, Red Ribbon Janna had been the most difficult boss to kill. After using Earthquake Mountain Sway, all those within 30 units were instantly killed. Nothing had changed compared to the past.

Tyrannical Ambition had originally formed a prison for the boss, but their formation had already been broken apart, either from dying or avoiding the attack. As for Red Ribbon Janna’s aggro? Once he finished his Enraged attack, he headed towards Blue Brook Guild.

Blue River wasn’t going to let this opportunity slip. He hastily called his Knights to receive the boss, while searching for Flowing Cloud.

No signs.

Blue River looked around, but soon received a message from Lu Hanwen, who cried: "I died."

"Were you hit by that attack?" Blue River sighed. Even an expert wouldn’t be able to escape if he were hit by that attack.

"I got duped by Ye Qiu!" Lu Hanwen said.

"What?" Blue River was startled.

"I was the one who triggered the boss’s Enraged mode!" Lu Hanwen said.

"Oh…. no wonder…." Blue River had been with the guild the entire time. He was also one of the guild’s core experts, so he had a good understanding of dungeon and wild bosses. He knew very well what the conditions were to trigger a famous boss like Red Ribbon Janna to become Enraged. One way for it to happen was if an individual’s DPS was excessively high. A melee class like a Blade Master would need to be very close to the boss in order to deal that much damage, so it wasn’t difficult to imagine why he wasn’t able to escape the tornado’s range.

"Don’t worry. You didn’t die for nothing. Triggering the boss’s Enraged mode has benefited us greatly." Blue River said.

"Tyrannical Ambition’s forces have all scattered, right?" Lu Hanwen said.

"Of course, but apart from that, Enraging a boss generates a lot of aggro. With this, our lead has become very stable. If we defend well enough, we’ll be able to take down this boss." Blue River was excited. Stealing a way a boss from two Gods would be a huge honor, but a part of that victory was because of having an expert on their side. A pro player was truly extraordinary.

"That’s good!" Lu Hanwen was happy, hearing Blue River’s words, but soon afterwards, Lu Hanwen suddenly thought of something and sent a crying emoji to Blue River.

"What?" Blue River was puzzled.

"When the boss was Enraged, I wasn’t in Blue Brook Guild’s group, but Ye Qiu’s team. He told me to join, so he could heal me!" Lu Hanwen said.

"F*CK! THAT SWINDLER!!!" Blue River was furious. Triggering Enrage generated an enormous amount of aggro. However, the boss’s follow-up Enraged attack was extremely strong. It was too difficult to deal with. The nearby players couldn’t survive it. Very few used such a method to generate aggro. It was good for Ye Qiu though. He cheated a Blue Brook Guild player and had him trigger the Enrage.

Ye Qiu’s team was was the one to do it, but the person to die was their own and the aggro generated wouldn’t belong to them either.

Blue River looked around. He couldn’t stay calm. He wanted to immediately find Ye Qiu and whack him a hundred eighty times. It was too, too, too, too, too despicable of him.

Blue River wanted to vent his anger, but the boss still needed to be dealt with! Tyrannical Ambition had been thrown into disarray by Red Ribbon Janna’s attack. Blue Brook Guild received the boss smoothly though. Blue River immediately ordered his troops to defends the boss. Tyrannical Ambition was still reorganizing themselves, when Ye Xiu led his team to once again cause chaos.

"Charge charge charge! Charge towards the boss! Kill whoever is attacking the boss!"

Their strategy hadn’t changed, but their assault was more tyrannical than before. Blue Brook Guild didn’t have a God like Zhang Xinjie commanding. Ye Xiu led his team and clashed head-on. Blue Brook Guild was thrown into chaos not longer afterwards. Blue River had originally wanted to whack Enlightened Lord a hundred and eighty times. Instead, Ye Xiu’s team charged straight into their troops and made a mess of things.

Tyrannical Ambition hastily reorganized to try and snatch the boss once more, but the defensive line holding back the four guild alliance crumbled.

Yue Ziqin, White Stream, and Martial Awareness led the four guild troops into battle for the boss.

"Over here!" Ye Xiu had told them where to go awhile ago. He called over the majority to convene.

The four guild alliance’s troops suddenly poured in like a tide with frightening momentum. Zhang Xinjie was quite calm though. Although the situation had already surpassed what he could have predicted, he didn’t think that Ye Qiu held any sort of advantage.

"Don’t rush. The boss’s aggro is still mainly with us and Blue Brook Guild. They started too late. It won’t be easy for them to steal away the boss!"

Zhang Xinjie raised the morale of his troops and once again began going for the boss. This time, it was Ye Xiu’s turn to return the favor though. Ye Xiu didn’t just tell team one or team two to go. He directly called for "Conquering Cloud and Parade" to form a great wall, blocking Tyrannical Ambition from going over.

"Don’t worry. We can go slowly. They started late. If we attack steadily, they’ll only be able to help us in the end." Zhang Xinjie had their troops attack Conquering Clouds and Parade wave after wave, shaking their defenses.

In comparison, Blue Brook Guild was in an extremely miserable state. Blue River had initially been telling Lu Hanwen that they would drag the battle on to stabilize their lead, but Ye Xiu’s elite team tore through their troops like a bullet, disrupting their formation. The injuries weren’t large, but their troops had been thrown entirely into disarray. They wanted to chase after and kill the small team too. All of their troops were on back side.

Be passive on the defense and active on the offense.

Blue River failed to do what Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie were trying to do. Heavenly Justice and Radiant swarmed the disorganized Blue Brook Guild troops, immediately making the Blue Brook Guild players to feel like it was every man for himself. Everywhere they looked seemed to be someone from a different guild. It was like all of their allies had died.

The boss was still in Blue Brook Guild’s hands, but when these two guilds arrived, they started slaughtering everything around them. The elite team sliced their way through and dissected the Knights. Heavenly Justice’s Knights began to get Red Ribbon Janna’s attention. Ye Xiu had given precise orders for this specific Knight team to come out. This was because Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had been a part of this team when he Enraged the boss. The boss’s aggro was on Flowing Cloud. Once he died, the aggro wouldn’t completely transfer to the team, but the amount of aggro generated by Enraging the boss could be said to be a small amount of capital, yet large profits.

Apart from these guilds, Samsara and Seaside were still there. After seeing Red Ribbon Janna become Enraged, they suddenly wanted to try fishing, but once they saw the four guild alliance charge in, the two went silent and became cheerleaders.

"Strikers, Ferocious Tiger Flurry! Push forward!"

Team 2, 3 left. Team 4,5 right."

"Fewer on the rear. Watch their tail."

"Pull back! 2 o’clock, charge!"

Zhang Xinjie calmly commanded the troops. Bit by bit, they broke through the wall and returned to the battlefield. Zhang Xinjie checked the time and was quite satisfied. Ye Qiu wouldn’t be able to snatch the boss in just this amount of time. Perhaps Blue Brook Guild’s hold on the boss might have lessened, giving Tyrannical Ambition a stronger hold.

But once the troops broke through and Zhang Xinjie checked the situation, he couldn’t help but be surprised. Ye Qiu’s troops had trapped the boss. That wasn’t anything surprising. What was surprising was that the boss’s aggro was clearly on the four guild alliance’s troops. How did they stabilize the aggro so quickly? Even Tyrannical Ambition wasn’t able to do it! Stealing away the boss’s aggro will be more difficult now too, because that Blue Brook Guild kid Enraged the boss and generated a huge amount of aggro, but how could they have taken away the aggro from Blue Brook Guild so quickly then? Is everyone in Blue Brook Guild dead?

Enraged the boss? Wait…..

Zhang Xinjie suddenly realized something.

The reason that the four guilds could gain an aggro advantage so fast could only be because they were the ones to receive the aggro generated by Enraging the boss.

Chapter 735: He’s Back

This isn’t good!

Zhang Xinjie immediately thought, when he realized what had happened.

Taking the boss away from Blue Brook Guild and taking away the boss from Ye Qiu’s troops were two completely different concepts. Ye Qiu’s defensive formation wouldn’t be in any way lacking compared to Zhang Xinjie’s. Zhang Xinjie’s defensive formation was broken through in the end, but he didn’t have the same resources that Ye Qiu had, when he did so.

For example, that small elite team! Zhang Xinjie saw their performance. Let alone inside Tyrannical Ambition’s reserve troops, even their elite troops didn’t have such skilled players. There was also that Blade Master, who Enraged the boss. That Blade Master’s skill astonished Zhang Xinjie.

Zhang Xinjie saw through that Blade Master’s intentions at that time, but he had no way of stopping him. This was because of that Blade Master’s individual skill.

Zhang Xinjie currently didn’t have a small elite team. Without oppressive experts, he had no way of opening up the enemy defenses nor could he Enrage the boss.

Wait for the boss to automatically become Enraged?

Red Ribbon Janna’s Enrage was truly terrifying. Even with warning, the player must escape thirty units away from the boss to survive. But once the boss automatically became Enraged, it would be nearly impossible to turn the tides because that meant the boss had less than 10% health left. It was practically impossible to snatch back the boss’s aggro before the boss died. The only way would be to annihilate the leading team. Ye Xiu was commanding the leading team. How could he let that happen so easily?

Zhang Xinjie wasn’t hopeful, but he still tried his best. He didn’t dare act slowly like before. Tyrannical Ambition split into numerous smaller teams and attacked repeatedly. However, the ones who didn’t budge were the four guild alliance’s troops. Ye Xiu constantly filled in any openings.

Time passed minute by minute, second by second. Tyrannical Ambition’s efforts weren’t without results. They chased after the boss closely and their long-ranged classes could already reach the boss. Thus, they attacked the boss as well as enemy players. However, it seemed as if this was as far as they could advance. Ye Xiu was trying to pull the boss away. The two sides clashed, utilizing various tactics. As for Samsara, Seaside, and Blue Brook Guild, these three guilds were practically the same as air. Their players had drowned amid the other two side’s troops and scattered into bits and pieces.

They couldn’t find any allies nor could they coordinate in any way. It was every man for himself to survive. Kill the boss? Noone in Blue Brook Guild was thinking about that at the moment!

Blue River could be considered as skilled among normal players. He was still alive. After all, Blue Brook Guild wasn’t the main target.

Their circumstances were unsalvageable. Name after name turned gray on the group list. Blue River had already told everyone to retreat.

Each player could only rely on himself to retreat though. No one had the energy to help anyone else.

Blue River still wanted to find Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord and whack him a few times. This could only remain a thought though. Not only was it difficult to find any particular character in this huge battle, even if he did, did he have the capability to actually hit Enlightened Lord?

Probably not….. Blue River thought with sorrow. For now, he just hoped he could hurry up and leave!

Blue River charged forward, when someone from the side rushed in.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had returned!

Scarlet Cloud Taoist Rite and the closest main city weren’t far apart. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud revived and came back. His stats weren’t complete and he may have lost a piece of equipment, but his battle spirit was as high as ever.

That Blade Master danced nimbly with his sword like a sprinkling rain. Blue River quickly noticed him.

"Is that you, Little Lu?" Blue River was surprised and hastily messaged him.

"I’m here for revenge!" Lu Hanwen replied. His sword didn’t stop.

Blue River’s spirit suddenly rose again. Little Lu had such willpower. I should go help him! With this in mind, he moved towards the direction of that brilliant swordplay.

His path of carnage over to Flowing Cloud’s side didn’t seem very heroic. He wasn’t as graceful nor as unstoppable as Lu Hanwen.

"Wow! Leader! What a coincidence!" Lu Hanwen noticed Blue River and exclaimed in surprise.

"What coincidence!" Blue River didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. I came looking for you, okay? He said, while throwing an invite to Flowing Cloud. He also checked his group. There were originally a hundred, now only 42 remained. The others weren’t gone because they left the group, rather they automatically left after dying.

"Where’s Ye Qiu!" Lu Hanwen asked Blue River after joining the group.

Blue River hadn’t been paying attention before, but since Lu Hanwen asked, he should find out. Immediately afterwards, he asked the group: "Does anyone here see Enlightened Lord?"

Everyone in the group was running away with their tails wagging behind, but they could still take a glance around them. Soon, someone actually responded and sent a set of coordinates, indicating Enlightened Lord’s current position. This player could only express helplessly: that’s the case for now, but trying to stay around or get closer is too difficult.

The 42 players still alive had survived by running into gaps. They would hurry and run to where there was a blank space. Directly killing anyone in their way was something only Lu Hanwen had the ability to do. Blue River had to put in a lot of effort to reach Lu Hanwen.

"Does anyone want to come with me?" Lu Hanwen asked in the group chat in high spirits.

"That’s a bit difficult….."

"Give it a try! Maybe you’ll survive."

"Too far. Good luck!"

Everyone replied in Blue Brook Guild, but Lu Hanwen was just randomly asking. There wasn’t any actual purpose to his words. His Flowing Cloud turned directions directly towards the reported coordinates. Blue River followed behind, feeling the pressure lessen. Lu Hanwen was opening the path over. He just needed to not go astray.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud soon reached the previous coordinates, but he didn’t see Enlightened Lord. It wasn’t like Ye Xiu was just sitting there the entire time.

After asking again in the group chat, this time, no one knew. Blue Brook Guild’s numbers had fallen to 36. Another six had died.

"Look around!" Lu Hanwen pursued justice with no second thoughts. He went around in a circle, but didn’t see him.

"How about I go and Enrage the boss?" Lu Hanwen discussed with Blue River.

"Alright!" Blue River didn’t mind. With so few numbers left, he knew that Blue Brook Guild had no hopes at snatching the boss back, so it didn’t matter what happened. The two The two safely raised their shit sticks. The boss wouldn’t end up in their hands, but the two leading guilds weren’t going to take it so easily.

"Charge!" Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud charged. The boss was quite easy to see. Just like how Flowing Cloud’s sword was like a propellor blade, the boss had powerful moves too. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud stabbed forth like a dagger. The defense that Tyrannical Ambition had been trying to break through was being done by him alone!

This obviously didn’t mean Lu Hanwen was equivalent to that many of Tyrannical Ambition’s troops. The main reason was because the direction he was advancing towards wasn’t given much attention. The four guild alliance put most of their attention onto Tyrannical Ambition.

However, now that Flowing Cloud had gotten this far, it would be unwise if they didn’t start taking notice.

"The kid’s come back. He’s quite spirited. It seems like he wants to Enrage the boss again?" Ye Xiu also saw Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud and figured out his intentions. He immediately ordered his troops to stop him. As a result, breaking through became more difficult for Lu Hanwen. The reason was actually the same as when Ye Xiu’s small team tried to get through Zhang Xinjie’s defenses: his damage wasn’t enough.

No matter how skilled Lu Hanwen was or how incredible his equipment was, a single person’s damage output would never be able to compare to a team’s. Ye Xiu’s small team had broken through due to their combined efforts. Right now, a lone individual trying to tear through an iron wall would only feel powerless.

"Hm? Ye Qiu!!!" Through a small crack in the defense, Lu Hanwen saw Enlightened Lord in the midst of battle. It wasn’t like he could break through the defense anyways, so he turned around and immediately dashed towards Enlightened Lord.

"Hm? He’s coming towards me?" Ye Xiu soon noticed. Flowing Cloud was the most noticeable character apart from the boss.

"I’M HERE FOR REVENGE!!!!" Lu Hanwen rampaged his way through quickly. His sword glinted and arced towards Enlightened Lord.

Ye Xiu immediately had Enlightened Lord turn to dodge the attack. Lu Hanwen reacted fast. Flowing Cloud’s second attack followed afterwards. It was only now did Blue River’s Blue Bridge Spring Snow begin his first attack.

"Hm? You’re leading again?" Ye Xiu saw Blue River.

Blue River was depressed! It seems like his team looked really weak in Ye Qiu’s eyes. Ye Qiu failed to even notice who had been leading. In any case, they were easily defeated.

"You’re too shameless. To think you’d trick Little Lu." Blue River angrily rebuked.

"That’s not completely correct. At that time, if no one healed him, he wouldn’t have been able to Enrage the boss. I say, is this the tactic you came up with? Have one person charge around violently? The first time, he tried to ambush alone, fine. But to think he didn’t learn his lesson and tried again. Don’t you have any sense of teamwork? You can’t do everything in Glory again." Ye Xiu said.

Blue River couldn’t help but pause. What the heck? Why does it seem like I’m wrong? But what normal player could keep up with Lu Hanwen’s pace? Lu Hanwen charging straight through wasn’t my idea anyways. Is it my mistake or is it because I gave him too much free reign? But try and order around a pro-level player? Blue River started to sweat. Ye Xiu seemed to know what he was thinking though: "Even if he’s a pro player, he has to obey orders no matter what team he’s in and try his hardest with everyone together!"

Chapter 736: Human Bomb

Ye Xiu’s words stumped Blue River. He remembered in the beginning, when he only just met Lord Grim in the tenth server. At that time, he hadn’t known Ye Qiu’s identity as a God and had dungeoned with him. How did Ye Qiu act when they played together? Blue River recalled. Lord Grim’s skill astonished them, of course, but no matter how high of a skill level he played at, he never failed to coordinate with the rest of them. It was only because of that that Blue Brook Guild’s five-man team could instantly achieve such a dominating dungeon record. That record hadn’t been set because they had an incredible expert, who soloed his way through, but rather his existence improved the strength of the entire team.

Blue River contemplated. Lu Hanwen expressed his approval towards Ye Xiu’s words though: "That’s very reasonable, senior!"

"Of course." When Ye Xiu said these words, who would have thought that he had been forced to roll on the ground due to the pressure exerted by Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud.

But Lu Hanwen was only able to keep it up for a short amount of time. Ye Xiu’s Enlightened Lord wasn’t standing alone. Many others had already begun protecting him.

None of them were elite players though, so fighting against Lu Hanwen didn’t end well for them. Of the three who arrived, two were sent flying from a blow away skill, while the other was hit up into the air. Lu Hanwen whacked him and the poor player shot towards Enlightened Lord like a cannonball.

Ye Xiu used that moment of interruption to retreat, while fulfilling his duty as a healer. However, three normal players and a healer wasn’t going to be enough to beat Lu Hanwen. These normal players couldn’t stop Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud at all. They were knocked aside after a few hits as if they didn’t exist.

"AoE attacks!" Enlightened Lord had many long-ranged classes around him. They clearly weren’t suitable to directly contest against Lu Hanwen’s Blade Master. Ye Xiu shouted and these long-ranged classes used their AoE skills. Lu Hanwen responded with Shadow Steps, instantly forming six of them. Even Ye Xiu couldn’t figure out which was fake. The others wouldn’t be any better. They randomly guessed and launched their AoE skill. Who cares if it was real or fake. Just fire more attacks.

The attacks covered the ground. In the end, Shadow Steps could only make it so that the attacks were more spread out, so Flowing Cloud wouldn’t immediately die. But with this barrage, Ye Xiu was able to identify the real shadow. Although all six were heading towards Enlightened Lord, it was very obvious which was the real one. When Flowing Cloud rushed out, Enlightened Lord cast a Holy Commandment. It didn’t hit, but it gave everyone a general direction. AoE attacks didn’t need to be aimed with high precision.

"See, this is the power of teamwork!" Ye Xiu said and another wave of explosions came. Who knew how many players attacked in that direction. Lu Hanwen tried his best to escape, but unfortunately, it wasn’t enough. Only a portion of the skills hit, but it was enough to kill Flowing Cloud.

Enlightened Lord walked over to pick up Flowing Cloud’s equipment. He looked around: "What about that other one?"

That other one was Blue River’s Blue Bridge Spring Snow. Even Lu Hanwen wasn’t able to survive the bombardment, let alone Blue River. His Blue Bridge Spring Snow had died before Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had died.

"The annoyances have been eliminated! Keep fighting the boss!"

Everyone returned to Red Ribbon Janna. Tyrannical Ambition was also fighting hard to increase their aggro. Zhang Xinjie looked at Red Ribbon Janna’s health and felt like the two sides weren’t too far apart. Right now, Ye Qiu had the advantage. They had control of the boss, so they were building up aggro fast. However, Tyrannical Ambition had a solid foundation. If they continued to deal damage and maintain their aggro, they might not surpass the enemy side, but they wouldn’t be too far behind. When Red Ribbon Janna dropped below 10% health and became Enraged, his attack would reset the battlefield. Perhaps he might be able to turn the situation around before the boss died.

Zhang Xinjie instructed his troops, while beginning to make arrangements for their final stand. Red Ribbon Janna’s health rapidly fell. Finally, it was only a sliver away from dropping to red health. The compact forces surrounding him were starting to loosen up. The nearby players prepared to retreat. They were only waiting for the order now.

"Disperse!" Ye Xiu finally gave the order. The players centered around Red Ribbon Janna immediately dashed away. Tyrannical Ambition wouldn’t try and get closer at this moment. They also retreated to a safe distance away. They stood on the very edge of the safe zone. This was Zhang Xinjie’s plan. Tyrannical Ambition had been on the outside the entire time. If they lined up here, they could try and prevent the other side from retreating.

It really did work. One of the opposing Knights rushed towards them, when he saw Tyrannical Ambition’s brick wall. They weren’t going to let him go through. If he wasn’t killed by them, he would be killed by the boss. But at this moment, Zhang Xinjie suddenly realized something.

"Not good!" The careful Zhang Xinjie rarely said these types of words, but he did this time.

"Kill that Knight!!" Zhang Xinjie shouted urgently. Right now, he regretted that he was using a Cleric. If he were using a damage dealing class, he would have hurried over to kill that Knight.

Just when Zhang Xinjie pointed it out, that Knight turned around, extended his arms, and made an insulting gesture at Red Ribbon Janna.

Provoke!

Everyone understood now. The other side was truly too despicable. Having this Knight bring over Red Ribbon Janna was the same as bringing over a human bomb.　

This Knight had clearly been prepared. After using Provoke, he activated Knight’s Spirit and followed with a Heroic Leap straight into Tyrannical Ambition’s troops. Normal players couldn’t react to such a speedy switch. While they fumbled around looking for the Knight’s location, Red Ribbon Janna was rushing over. Bosses never moved slowly either.

"Knights, force him away!" At this moment, Zhang Xinjie could only make a suicidal attempt. It would work in theory, but in practice? The skill level of a normal player wasn’t enough to deal with this type of emergency situation. When the Knights attempted to rush out and sacrifice themselves, the four guild alliance began bursting Red Ribbon Janna, instantly dropping the boss’s health to below 10%. It became Enraged and started its powerful attack. Tyrannical Ambition didn’t have time to dodge. Red Ribbon Janna smashed downwards with his two hands. Countless players flew into the air and whirled around until they were smashed into smithereens…..

Zhang Xinjie’s Misty Mountain didn’t die, but he knew it was all over. They suffered too many losses and no longer had the power to contest with the four guilds.

After the attack ended and the ground was littered with scars, Zhang Xinjie looked at Enlightened Lord, who stood in a conspicuous place. Enlightened Lord looked towards Zhang Xinjie’s directions and lifted his arms. He seemed to be waving his hands. The waving was done by the player and didn’t have any combat purpose to it.

"Thanks, Vice Captain Zhang! Tell Old Han I said hi!" Ye Xiu yelled.

Since the conclusion was set, Zhang Xinjie recollected himself and replied: "You’re welcome."

Soon afterwards, Tyrannical Ambition dispersed. They didn’t try again or take revenge. Tyrannical Ambition officially gave up on Red Ribbon Janna.

After becoming Enraged due to falling below 10% health, the boss’s stats would be permanently increased. There would also be a random chance of it using the tornado attack again. However, if there was no warning for the players, it would be too difficult. Apart from meeting certain conditions to trigger the boss’s Enrage, enough warning was given for the tornado attacks so that the players could avoid it. Without any disturbances, the four guild alliance killed the boss with ease. Once the items dropped, everyone let out a sigh of relief.

They thought that choosing the level 55 boss, when two bosses spawned simultaneously, would be an easy victory. Who would have thought their most troublesome opponent, Zhang Xinjie, would run over. Luckily, they won this time. It wasn’t an easy one though. Each of the four guilds had heavy casualties.

"God, which one do you want? Take a look." Loulan Slash didn’t forget about this. The reason they came for the level 55 boss was because Ye Xiu needed something. After picking up everything and listing it out in the group chat, they gave Ye Xiu first pick.

"Then I won’t be polite." Ye Xiu only had one item he really needed. He already saw it among the list of drops, so he picked it out.

The other guild leaders paid attention. Iron Floating Phosphorous. It wasn’t anything particularly special. It was just one of the numerous rare materials out there, so they wouldn’t argue over it. Ye Xiu took the item. Afterwards, they started from the beginning and split the drops accordingly.

After splitting the drops, they withdrew their troops and started discussing this boss battle with each other.

"Why does it seem like Zhang Xinjie plans on coming over for materials every day?" Loulan Slash said.

"It looks like we really do need to play the time difference game. In the future, we’re all going to need to switch up our sleep schedules!" Yue Ziqin said.

"Ah, we have no choice! Luckily, it’ll only be for two months." Martial Awareness said. Zhang Xinjie was a pro player, after all. Once the Pro Alliance started, he wouldn’t have time to play the game.

"God, what do you say?" Loulan Slash asked Ye Xiu. When he looked around, Enlightened Lord had disappeared to who knows where.

Then, when he checked his friends list, Enlightened Lord had already logged of. Lord Grim, which he hadn’t seen in a long time, logged on. Ye Xiu finally had all the materials to upgrade the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella to Level 55. This upgrade had been completely thought up of by Ye Xiu. He had not experimented with it. It only existed in theory similar to Death’s Hand. Although Ye Xiu had gone through all of the details he could think of, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s complexity couldn’t compare to Death’s Hand. Whether or not it would succeed was something Ye Xiu had no grasp of.

Chapter 737: Finding Enemy Intelligence

Ye Xiu traded the materials obtained from Red Ribbon Janna to Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze. Then, he logged onto Lord Grim, hid in the Arena, organized the materials needed for the umbrella’s upgrade, and conducted one last inspection to check for anything he might have missed.

Ye Xiu had done this who knew how many times, but he never appeared impatient. He opened up the equipment editor, looked at the blueprints of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and the gathered materials, slowly studying each step.

Chen Guo carried all of the important materials. Although she followed along everyone else, she couldn’t help but feel nervous. She would often check her surroundings to see if there were any nearby hostilities. When she returned to the city, she immediately headed towards the Arena and found Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. It was only when she finally traded the materials on her did she let out a sigh of relief.

Right when she traded the materials, a knock could be heard on the practice room door. Chen Guo stood up and opened the door. An employee stood outside: "Boss, there are people looking for you."

Chen Guo had already noticed the two standing behind her and went "Ah!"

Su Mucheng and Xiao Shiqin were unexpectedly standing there.

"Come on in! Come on in!" Chen Guo obviously knew how risky it was for these two stars to come into her Internet Cafe. Didn’t a disaster just happen last night? Today, the two came in with disguises, but if someone looked at them for awhile, they would still be exposed. Chen Guo hurriedly urged Su Mucheng into the room. She was about to rush outside and call out "Xiao Shiqin", but in the end, she decided not to. Last night, Xiao Shiqin had left her a good impression. If it was Sun Xiang who had come instead, Chen Guo probably would have shouted out his name.

"You’re here?" Ye Xiu lifted his head and glanced at her. He didn’t seem surprised at her visit.

"This time, I’m completely on vacation!" Su Mucheng said.

"Hm? Little Xiao is here too." Ye Xiu noticed Xiao Shiqin and felt somewhat surprised.

"I don’t have anything to do, so I came to look around." Xiao Shiqin said.

"After joining a new team, instead of hurrying to unite the team, you immediately come over to scout for enemy intelligence. How dedicated of you." Ye Xiu remarked.

"Ahem….." Xiao Shiqin coughed in embarrassment. He had come over to visit partially for this reason. Ye Xiu’s team would be a formidable opponent for Excellent Era in the Challenger League. However, he had zero knowledge about their enemies. Xiao Shiqin couldn’t help but feel uneasy. He always liked to form his strategies based around his opponents. It was easier to find information in the Alliance. Even if he had never fought against an opposing team before, that team would certainly have records facing other teams. Happy was a newly formed team though. How could there be any records on them?

He planned on strolling over to Happy, when he bumped into Su Mucheng. In the beginning, neither of them said what they were planning on doing. They just walked around together, when they noticed that that they seemed to be heading towards the same destination. The two looked at each other incredulously and that was how they ended up arriving here together.

"Everyone in the team has gone on vacation. Even if I tried to unite the team, there’s no one to unite!" Xiao Shiqin replied to the first half of Ye XIu’s words. He wasn’t wrong. After Excellent Era held the welcoming ceremony for Xiao Shiqin, everyone went on break. The players left early today either back to their homes or to travel around on vacation. Xiao Shiqin didn’t plan on staying in the Club for the summer, but he had just joined the new team, after all. It wouldn’t be too late to go on vacation after he spent a few days getting used to the environment.

As for whether or not he was here to scout out enemy intelligence, Xiao Shiqin didn’t say because that really was his reason for coming. An explanation would just be an excuse, so he might as well just leave at that!

"Everyone, don’t talk to him. Be careful not to leak out any information." Ye Xiu grinned.

"Senior, you’re too blunt." Xiao Shiqin coughed again.

"What are you up to?" Su Mucheng was still a member of Excellent Era, but she didn’t feel like an enemy at all. She went up to Ye Xiu and looked to see what he was doing.

Xiao Shiqin also wanted to go over and look, but he knew that he and Su Mucheng were different. After spending yesterday understanding Ye Qiu’s situation, Xiao Shiqin didn’t need to ask to know that Su Mucheng would most likely leave Excellent Era after fulfilling her contract this season. It seems like Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian would once again be the only duo from the golden generation after the Challenger League was over.

"The Level 55 upgrade for the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Would you like to watch?" Ye Xiu answered Su Mucheng, while calling out to Xiao Shiqin: "Little Xiao, come and sit. I’m upgrading my Silver weapon."

Silver weapon!

Xiao Shiqin raised his eyebrows. Yesterday night, Tao Xuan told him information about Ye Qiu’s situation, and the transforming Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was no secret.

"Oh, that Silver weapon? I’ve heard of it." Xiao Shiqin replied. He was already thinking in his head: apart from that Silver weapon, what other weapons does Happy have?

Right now, Excellent Era’s greatest advantage over Happy was their characters. A newly formed team wouldn’t be able to catch up to their level in a short amount of time. However, this newly formed team had God Ye Qiu in it. He had started playing professionally since the very start of the Alliance and had seen everything there is to see in Glory. It wouldn’t be unusual if he had some knowledge of how to create Silver equipment. Tao Xuan had personally told him that he wouldn’t be surprised if Ye Qiu could create One Autumn Leaf’s set of Silver equipment.

Ye Qiu had used One Autumn Leaf for his entire professional career. One Autumn Leaf’s relationships with Ye Qiu went even farther back than its relationships with Excellent Era. Team Happy just happened to have a Battle Mage too. Tao Xuan didn’t need to explain the implications.

Xiao Shiqin wanted to see if anyone else in the team had a Silver weapon. Of course, he didn’t count on Ye Qiu answering that question direction, but there might perhaps be hints.

But in the end, all he got was: yeah, that one.

That wasn’t the answer Xiao Shiqin was looking for because he already knew that!

Xiao Shiqin didn’t plan on watching Ye Qiu. The details of Ye Qiu’s Silver weapon was certainly a secret. Letting him take a look was already giving him face. Going over to watch the process was too impolite. The other side would certainly kick him out. In an official Club, the research department had a sign saying "Unsolicited visitors are not welcome". He wouldn’t even be allowed in the room.

Xiao Shiqin wouldn’t actually listen to Ye Qiu’s words and take a seat! He wasn’t here to wait for the other side to tell him anything. He couldn’t hope for Ye Qiu to tell him: Little Xiao! Our characters are like this and like this. These are our Silver equipment. Go back and figure out how to deal with us!

Xiao Shiqin walked around like he had nothing to do. There were three people in front of him, playing the game: Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, Qiao Yifan.

Xiao Shiqin glanced at their screens. He might not actually be able to see anything, but he could maybe see their reactions?

Sure enough, there was a reaction! Xiao Shiqin glanced around. The person he walked past turned his head and looked at him. That person leaned forward as if he wanted to jump into the screen, blocking Xiao Shiqin’s line of sight.

"What are you looking at!" Steamed Bun asked accusingly.

"I….. I wasn’t looking at anything! I’m just walking around." Xiao Shiqin was startled. He thought the other side would react, but he didn’t think he would make such a big reaction.

"What secret could this Brawler be hiding?" Xiao Shiqin thought to himself. At the same time, he moved back in embarrassment.

What could that Steamed Bun be hiding?

Not just Xiao Shiqin, but even Chen Guo was thinking of this question! If there was actually anything that couldn’t be seen, she would have blocked Xiao Shiqin before he got there or she might have simply blocked the door, not allowing any visitors. But they didn’t have any secrets to hide, so Chen Guo didn’t mind. Ye Xiu had just said a few teasing words. As for telling Xiao Shiqin about his Silver weapon, Ye Xiu was reminding him: don’t come over here.

Xiao Shiqin understood. He didn’t follow Su Mucheng. He had only taken a few steps though and Steamed Bun reacted in such a way. Everyone was puzzled just like Xiao Shiqin.

Steamed Bun continued to glare at Xiao Shiqin, making Xiao Shiqin feel like he couldn’t just blindly look around. As a result, Xiao Shiqin listened to Ye Xiu and sat down on the sofa.

With Ye Qiu in the team, the Battle Mage’s equipment wouldn’t be an issue. But this Brawler might really be hiding something. That Wei Chen was Team Blue Rain’s former captain and the original owner of Swoksaar. As a result, Wei Chen might have a similar relationship with Swoksaar like Ye Qiu’s relationship with One Autumn Leaf. Silver equipment for Warlock might not be an issue either.

And Su Mucheng. Tao Xuan had already put it plainly. If they couldn’t keep Su Mucheng, Dancing Rain would most likely be brought away as well and join Team Happy.

Wait... it would still be a year before Su Mucheng would be joining Team Happy. And by that time, the results would be out. Either Excellent Era or Happy would remain. Su Mucheng could not be a part of Team Happy during the Challenger League. He had thought too far ahead.

And the last one…...

Xiao Shiqin’s gaze fell on Qiao Yifan. Tao Xuan had attached a lot of importance to this youth. Xiao Shiqin had tried to understand this youth too. From the public statements, Qiao Yifan had been registered to Team Tiny Herb last season as an Assassin! But at All Stars, he had used a Ghostblade to challenge Li Xuan. And from what he saw just before, Qiao Yifan was clearly playing on a Ghostblade.

What’s going on? Xiao Shiqin found a hint. Could Ye Qiu have won over Qiao Yifan a long time ago and persuaded him to switch from an Assassin to a Ghostblade? Could Ye Qiu already have Ghostblade equipment prepared as well? At this moment, he suddenly saw Qiao Yifan get up and walk towards him.

Chapter 738: Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, Upgrade Complete!

Xiao Shiqin was puzzled. Qiao Yifan was someone even his boss, Tao Xuan, worried about. Right now, he was walking over. What... could he be up to?

Xiao Shiqin didn’t look anywhere else. He fixed his gaze on Qiao Yifan, who walked over to a water dispenser and poured out a cup of water. Afterwards, he returned and placed the cup in front of Xiao Shiqin on the small coffee table: "Senior, have a cup of water..." Then, he went back to his seat.

Uh….. Xiao Shiqin pondered over what just happened for the next five minutes. He didn’t think Qiao Yifan had any hidden motives behind his action. There shouldn’t be any issues?

After he snapped out of his daze, he was about to say something, when he suddenly realized that the entire room had fallen eerily silent. The small bit of noise that could be heard came from a single direction: Ye Xiu’s seat.

Was he working on his Silver weapon?

Xiao Shiqin subconsciously wanted to take a look. His butt left the seat before he realized that getting up wasn’t right, so he quietly sat back down. He followed everyone else and didn’t utter a word, maintaining the silence.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was currently in the process of being upgraded…..

First, let’s not talk about the complexity of the parts. Just the amount of rare materials needed exceeded that of a normal Silver weapon. These excess materials weren’t used to increase the weapon’s stats, but rather the various transformations. In order for these transformations to function smoothly, the complexity of each part was naturally higher. Normal weapons needed to only maintain a single form. No other weapon was like the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, which required numerous moveable parts. Even moveable parts such as those inside guns weren’t as troublesome as those in the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Once everyone knew that Ye Xiu was upgrading the umbrella, the practice room became even more quiet than when Wei Chen had upgraded his Death’s Hand.

Xiao Shiqin couldn’t just run over to Ye Xiu’s side to watch, so he sat on the sofa, but there wasn’t much he could see. Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Qiao Yifan had their backs facing him, covering their screens up. Wei Chen, Ye Xiu, and Chen Guo had their computers covered even more. He couldn’t even see their faces. The only thing he could see was Su Mucheng’s expression.

But Su Mucheng? She was just focused on Ye Xiu’s screen. He couldn’t discern any information from her face.

Xiao Shiqin felt a bit impatient.

If he said anything, he was afraid that he might mess up the upgrade process. They had let him in and didn’t obstruct him in any way. It was very polite of them. If he intentionally made a ruckus, Xiao Shiqin felt it would be too wrong of him. He wasn’t the type of person who could do that.

But just sitting here doing nothing! He wasn’t friends with any of them and couldn’t experience their anxiousness or hopes, so he stayed careful and cautious. He really felt somewhat uncomfortable.

However, Xiao Shiqin was still a kind and honest person. Even though he felt uncomfortable, he endured it. Happy’s practice room was silent for an entire hour. When he saw Su Mucheng suddenly relax her eyebrows and then stand up, Xiao Shiqin felt like they should be done…..

Xiao Shiqin only said it in his heart. On the other hand, Chen Guo directly spoke: "Done?"

"Mm..." Ye Xiu replied. It was done. The parts had been assembled together, but was it a success? Ye Xiu excited the equipment editor and returned to the game.

Lord Grim. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella sat in his inventory.

The mouse hovered over it and the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s stats could be seen.

Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Level 55.

Attack Speed: 5

Weight: 2.3 kg

Durability: 23

Physical Attack: 592

Magic Attack: 592

Vitality + 13

Strength +13

Intelligence +13

Spirit +13

The stats ended there. Wei Chen and Chen Guo had stretched their necks to look. After looking at the stats for a good while, Chen Guo carefully asked: "Is it a success?"

From the base physical attack, magic attack, and four stat increases, the umbrella had clearly been upgraded. But Chen Guo knew that when the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella upgraded from level 45 to level 50, there was a significant increase. The original blank weapon with just attack numbers, suddenly increased the other four stats at level 50. Who knew if there might be other bonuses for the level 55 upgrade? However, only the original stat lines increased. Was that a success?

"It’s not bad for now." Ye Xiu replied.

The check-up on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella didn’t stop here though.

Lord Grim exited the Arena to a place, where he could freely move around. He equipped the umbrella and transformed it to its spear form.

Ye Xiu quickly looked over it and then changed the umbrella’s form again.

Change change change change change.

Ye Xiu changed the umbrella to each of its six forms. When it transformed one last time, Ye Xiu’s tense expression finally relaxed.

"It’s a success." Ye Xiu said.

"Sweet!" Chen Guo slammed the table.

"It’s just a level 55 upgrade, so there’s not much to it." Ye Xiu smiled.

"But you said that you had no reference materials for the level 55 upgrade and you needed to figure out the upgrade process completely on your own. That makes the procedure risky! Is it not sweet for it to succeed on your first try?" Chen Guo said.

"If the next upgrade processes succeeded like this one, that would be sweet." Ye Xiu said. Of course, he was happy about the umbrella successfully being upgraded to level 55, but Ye Xiu knew well that it was just another step taken. The equipment needed to be upgraded to level 70. If it failed before then, everything would be for naught.

After all, it was still just at level 55, right now.

Wei Chen’s Death’s Hand was level 65. Compared to his other equipment, the level was enough to be useable. A level 65 Silver weapon could compare to a level 70 Orange weapon. In the Glory Alliance, many teams didn’t have complete sets of Silver equipment and used Orange equipment as placeholders.

However, it was a bit different for weapons because a character’s attack stats mainly depended on the weapon. The increase in strength brought from a better weapon was the highest compared to other pieces of equipment. It was by a lot too. As a result, good weapons were always the most expensive in the game. Pro teams always prioritized creating Silver weapons first.

Of all the equipment used, even in the pro scene, most of it was Orange. However, very very few still used Orange weapons, apart from a few exceptions, where the Silver weapons weren’t as good as a similar Orange weapon. For example, Loulan Slash’s Swordpoint wasn’t something that could survive in the pro scene.

A level 65 Silver weapon was still more valuable than an Orange weapon. After all, a Silver weapon was fit to the player’s style. But because practically everyone in the pro scene carried a level 70 Silver weapon, if you brought a level 65 Silver weapon to compete, no matter how good the stat increases were, it wouldn’t be able to compare, overall.

Other Silver equipment could be used at level 65 because many characters in the pro scene still wore inferior Orange equipment. A level 65 Silver weapon would put you at a disadvantage in the pro scene though.

The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s upgrade to level 55 let Ye Xiu relax. But he was mostly excited about how he didn’t need to waste any more materials or time on this step. In terms of value, a level 55 Silver weapon was far from enough. Level 60, 65, and 70 was still awaiting for him!

Ye Xiu had obviously pondered over these stages, but his plan wasn’t mature yet. He didn’t have the necessary materials either, so those weren’t as urgent. After succeeding, Ye Xiu logged out of Lord Grim and slumped into his chair to rest. The equipment editor had exhausted him. It was even more tiring than his confrontation versus Zhang Xinjie because everything needed to be done with careful precision.

On the sofa, Xiao Shiqin heard about the success. When he saw Ye Xiu relax, he stood up and smiled: "You succeeded? Congratulations!!"

"You heard it! It’s only a level 55 upgrade. It isn’t anything worth getting excited about." Ye Xiu said.

"Everything has to be done step by step. You don’t become fat in a single bite." Xiao Shiqin said.

"True!" Ye Xiu thought about it. Then, he stood up and headed over to Xiao Shiqin, so he could properly receive his guest. He started off saying a bunch of rubbish, expressing his concern: "Are you getting used to Excellent Era?"

"I just arrived. I’m still adapting." Xiao Shiqin smiled.

"Do you need my help? Ask away!" Ye Xiu said.

"Senior, you’re too polite. Everything’s going well." Xiao Shiqin said.

"Do you have any confidence facing us in the Challenger League?" Ye Xiu asked.

"..." Xiao Shiqin was a bit speechless. Yes, he was an All Star and a former team captain. He was still at a loss towards Ye Xiu’s question.

Because to anyone else, asking whether or not you had confidence was something the one with the higher status said to the one with the lower status. In terms of his individual status in the Alliance compared to Ye Qiu’s, Xiao Shiqin being considered the one with the lower status wasn’t an issue. But this was comparing two teams! How could Team Happy be the one with the higher status compared to Excellent Era?

However, Ye Xiu clearly asked Xiao Shiqin in this way, rendering Xiao Shiqin speechless.

"Uh….. yeah….." Xiao Shiqin finally answered awkwardly. "Yeah…." could be understood as "Actually, no. But I have to say yes." It could also be understood as "Of course." In any case, it was a half-hearted response.

"If you lose to use, it’ll be a tragedy for sure. What are you going to do? You didn’t plan on coming to Excellent Era to play in the Challenger League, right?" Ye Xiu asked.

Psychological warfare! Ye Qiu was trying to put him under pressure!

Xiao Shiqin understood very clearly, but he couldn’t help but feel a bit panicked at being asked this question so directly. When he finalized the contract with Excellent Era, Excellent Era had already been relegated, so the contact was only a year long. This point hadn’t been publicly announced. It was naturally a preventive measure if Excellent Era failed to return to the Alliance. Xiao Shiqin couldn’t say this though! If he replied in this way, it would appear as if he had no confidence in their victory. How troublesome!

Chapter 739: Give Us a Hand

Xiao Shiqin knew that his visit today had been a bit rash. Very few would barge directly into an enemy team’s practice room to look for information on them.

But just because few did it this way didn’t necessarily mean that others didn’t want to do it. In truth, it simply wasn’t possible. If it were actually possible to infiltrate an enemy team’s practice room discretely and see how the team was practicing, especially before a match, the information gained would be extraordinarily valuable.

Unfortunately, no Club guild would allow such things to happen. Casually letting anyone into the practice room and openly divulging information wasn’t logical. Normally, if an outside team were allowed into another team’s practice room, it would be a social activity set up by both Clubs. It would be completely unrelated to scouting for information.

For Team Happy, Xiao Shiqin successfully obtained information through this method though. He was mostly taking advantage of Team Happy being newly created. A newly created team obviously wouldn’t have many regulations set up yet! Xiao Shiqin reckoned that if he just came over, they wouldn’t be able to stop him. It went just as he predicted.

However, after arriving, he saw that the the enemy players just seemed to be playing the game. He didn’t see any sort of systematic training routine going on. Xiao Shiqin obviously knew that it was too early to expect to see how they would fight against Excellent Era. He mainly wanted to know more about Team Happy’s strength, whether it be information on their characters or their players.

He wasn’t going to get any information by just sitting there and waiting for them to tell him. He had to make deductions based on any tiny hints revealed. Xiao Shiqin felt like he did a fairly good job. Based on Steamed Bun’s reaction, Team Happy must have quite a powerful Brawler. As for the others, there were clear signs that they weren’t ordinary.

But just knowing that Team Happy wasn’t merely at an in-game team level wasn’t enough. Xiao Shiqin needed to know more, but he didn’t have any good methods right now. Maybe he should go to the game and start probing them? Don’t look at how Xiao Shiqin just seemed to be sitting there. He was constantly thinking. When Ye Xiu walked over to chat with him, he knew that he wouldn’t be getting any information out of him. Instead, he fell into a psychological trap…...

As a former team captain and ace player, Xiao Shiqin wouldn’t panic so easily. He quickly collected himself: "In any case, I’ll still be doing my best."

"Mm, that’s a good attitude to have." Ye Xiu appeared as if he were lecturing a rookie and not an experienced team captain and All Star player. Xiao Shiqin could only give a forced smile in response.

Just when he was about to say something else, Chen Guo suddenly shouted: "Something’s come up!"

"What is it?"

"Another boss has spawned!" Chen Guo said.

"Ah! So fast!"

Ye Xiu immediately ran over. His Lord Grim wasn’t logged into the game at the moment! This time, Heavenly Justice had discovered a boss. Loulan Slash couldn’t find Ye Xiu in the game, so he shouted at him in the chat group. Ye Xiu wasn’t in front of his computer though, so how could he see the message? As a result, Loulan Slash looked for Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze to get Ye Xiu’s attention.

"What boss?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Level 70. Red Mage Mierworr." Loulan Slash brightened at Ye Xiu’s reply.

"Gather! Gather!" Ye Xiu called. If there was a boss, of course they needed to go kill it. At the same time, he tilted his head towards Wei Chen: "Did you guys receive the new?"

"Of course." Wei Chen’s expression was grave. He turned his head back to look at Ye Xiu: "We’re going to be needing this one."

Ye Xiu shot a glance: "I can hear the excitement in your heart!"

"Don’t hold back!" Wei Chen said.

Ye Xiu knew why Wei Chen was so excited. Wei Chen had already come up with a clear blueprint for his weapon’s upgrade, all the way to level 70. As a result, Ye Xiu paid attention to any materials needed for Death’s Hand when they split boss drops.

Death’s Hand required five level 70 rare materials. Ye Xiu had already obtained three last week. As for the remaining two, both dropped from Red Mage Mierworr. A boss wouldn’t only drop a single material. If they got Red Mage Mierwoor, there would be a high probability of gathering both remaining materials for Death’s Hand.

As for the other materials, the two million yuan worth of materials from Samsara covered it. At that time, the upgrade process for Death’s Hand had already been formed, so there was no way Ye Xiu wouldn’t have accounted for any required materials.

Wei Chen had worked for so many years to upgrade his Death’s Hand to level 60. Now he had the chance to finally upgrade it to level 70 and fulfill his long-cherished wish. How could he not be excited?

"If the situation allows, maybe you can provide us with some help." Ye Xiu said.

"As if you need to say that." Wei Chen replied. This was his value in being a spy. When commanding Samsara’s second elite group, he could employ tactics to secretly help Ye Xiu snatch the boss.

"I’ll think of some way to deal with Zhang Xinjie!" Wei Chen was prepared to go all out for his Death’s Hand. He obviously knew who their most troublesome opponent would be today. Yesterday, Wei Chen had secretly helped Ye Xiu’s side, but it still didn’t go smoothly against Zhang Xinjie. After all, there were a lot of competing guilds. All of them were trying to stop each other. Wei Chen couldn’t be too conspicuous. As the saying goes: water flowing out in a trickle takes a long time to exhaust. He was willing to throw it out the window for his Death’s Hand though.

"Don’t lose your head." Ye Xiu logged onto Enlightened Lord. Then, he turned to look at Xiao Shiqin: "Little Xiao, it’s not like you’ve got anything else to do. Come. Why not give us a hand!"

How casual! How natural! It made him feel bad to refuse.

But how could Xiao Shiqin accept so easily?

He could obviously tell what Ye Xiu was going to do. They were going to go boss hunting again. Killing bosses was for materials and materials were used for creating Silver equipment. Help the other side create Silver equipment and beat Excellent Era in the Challenger League?

If Xiao Shiqin helped them out here, wouldn’t he be working against his own interests?

How could Ye Xiu not understand something so obvious? Of course, he wouldn’t, but he seemed to not know what was at stake. It was as if he were talking casually to a good friend. His words came out naturally as if it were a "Hey, I’m moving some stuff. Come help me out."

How many guests could refuse such a request?

Xiao Shiqin was conflicted!

They didn’t slam the door in his face or treat him like an evil enemy. That made him rejoice, but now he regretted it. The other side was now asking for his help. If he helped, he would be biting his own hand. If he didn’t, he would appear rude and unscrupulous. They were letting you play in their practice room despite your identity, but you only cared about your own interests!

To put it plainly, Xiao Shiqin was let in out of kindness. Now they wanted you to return it, but they wanted you to do something very wrong. It would make anyone feel troubled.

Xiao Shiqin felt a bit at a loss facing this request. He looked around and saw everyone waiting for his response. He suddenly thought of something.

Helping the other side in their battle was a good opportunity to see their strength! Even if he helped them take down the boss, it was still just a boss. How could that be a deciding factor? Through this way, he would be able to obtain a lot of information on each of Team Happy’s members.

Thinking of this, Xiao Shiqin nodded his head. As for whether he was agreeing for enemy intelligence or because it was difficult to refuse, Xiao Shiqin admitted: it was both. It was two birds with one stone! As for gathering intelligence, while intentionally messing up their boss hunt, Xiao Shiqin had no intention of doing so. He wasn’t so despicable. If he didn’t want to help them, he would have outright refused from the beginning. He wouldn’t pretend to agree and then deliberately make a mess.

"Boss, give him a Mechanic account." Ye Xiu saw him agree and called out for Chen Guo.

Chen Guo took out a stack of cards from a drawer and gave one to Xiao Shiqin. At the same time, she said warily: "This account has a lot of materials inside the storehouse. You won’t take any, right?"

Xiao Shiqin didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. Wasn’t her suspicions a bit rude?! What was his identity? How could he do something so despicable, but the other’s suspicion was very straightforward. Xiao Shiqin responded with an "I won’t", and Chen Guo handed the card over to him.

"Can I use any of these computers?" Xiao Shiqin asked.

"Mm, anyone that you like!"

Happy’s practice room had twelve computers with every three grouped together. Wei Chen, Ye Xiu, and Chen Guo were one group. Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Qiao Yifan in another. There were six empty computers. Xiao Shiqin picked a random one and turned it on.

Then, he heard Su Mucheng say joyfully: "Then shouldn’t I also play?"

Xiao Shiqin’s eyeglasses almost fell off. He felt like he was the one setting the example. He came out to help and then Su Mucheng followed after grandiosely.

Xiao Shiqin hadn’t thought of that, but he had already agreed. It didn’t matter anyways. He rolled his eyes at her, telling her how cunning she was.

Su Mucheng had said those words for Xiao Shiqin to hear. She was naturally looking at him too! She didn’t mind Xiao Shiqin’s eye roll and sat down delightedly ---- Chen Guo gave her seat to Su Mucheng. She found another Launcher account and switched computers.

Xiao Shiqin logged into the game and saw this Mechanic’s equipment. How terrible! When he checked the guild info and felt even more miserable. There weren’t many in the guild in the first place. Right now, besides him, there were a total of seven. Lord Grim wasn’t one of these seven. Then, he saw someone called Let There Be Light: "Come to Sarke City."

Xiao Shiqin skimmed over the member list. This Let There Be Light was a Battle Mage, probably Ye Qiu. He replied "Oh" and then started controlling his poor Mechanic over. How many years had it been since he had used such a garbage character? Xiao Shiqin’s mind started to wander off.

The four guild alliance had gathered at Sarke City. The four guilds were already there. Xiao Shiqin’s Mechanic teleported over and saw Let There Be Light, who called him over.

"I’ll lead two guilds. He’ll lead the other two." Ye Xiu said to the four guild leaders.

The four guild leaders glanced at the lousy Mechanic. They clearly felt a bit unconvinced at Ye Xiu’s arrangements. "And just who is this person?" The four guild leaders practically asked at the same time.

"Xiao Shiqin." Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 740: First Come First Serve

If they were not in their team studio, the four guild masters were most likely in their own homes. No matter what, an online game was rarely played outside. However, as of that moment, all four of them felt as if the wind had drowned out Ye Xiu’s words.

"WHO?" The four asked again in disbelief.

"Xiao Shiqin." Ye Xiu emphasized clearly again.

The four all quieted down immediately.

"Hello…" Xiao Shiqin greeted them helplessly. He knew clearly that the guild masters were the equivalent of a department head in the club. The four in front of him were all core members of their respective clubs. Allowing them to know that he was helping Ye Qiu steal bosses in the game was the same as telling these clubs and their teams about it. Within no time, the entire community would probably know as well.

Xiao Shiqin was a bit worried, but he had to admit, revealing his identity was the fastest way for others to accept him as a commander. This acceptance was very important for good teamwork. No matter how Ye Qiu explained how incredible he was, the others would still doubt, hesitate, and try to test him.

As of now, people were simply speechless at Xiao Shiqin’s name because this was an identity that everybody knew of. The only one doubtful was White Stream, who said with a trembling voice, "Is he THAT Xiao Shiqin?"

"Yep. That’s the one." Ye Xiu confirmed.

"Ay! Hello, hello. What brings you here?" White Stream finally started greeting him frantically. At the same time, the other three had just snapped back to reality and hurried over to offer their own greetings as well.

"Alright. Let’s stop wasting time. Radiant and Parde, would you follow Xiao Shiqin?" Ye Xiu spoke up.

"Sure, sure. No problem!" White Stream and Martial Awareness answered hurriedly. Their second-rate teams weren’t in the spotlight, nor were they low to the ground. Therefore, they weren’t too popular and didn’t have any feuds with other teams. Unlike Tyrannical Amibition’s players, whose mood deteriorated at the mention of Ye Qiu’s name, these players did not harbor such strong feelings towards anyone. The members of their own teams were unquestionably their favorite. As for the other God level players in the league, that was completely up to personal preference. There were no feelings behind it that were associated with their supported teams.

Xiao Shiqin was quite popular.. None of the four guild masters seemed to dislike him. They were all asking around and being friendly with him.

Loulan Slash even sighed regretfully, "If we knew God Xiao would transfer teams, we Heavenly Justice would have welcomed you no matter the cost."

Loulan Slash was more than just a guild leader. He was also the captain and the owner of the club. To be honest, the significance of his identity was an entire level higher than both Ye Xiu and Xiao Shiqin. After he threw out such a weighty comment, Yue Ziqin, White Stream, and Martial Awareness were all at a lost of words.

"Ha. Looks like Heavenly Justice is doing well." Xiao Shiqin steered the topic away calmly.

People from the guilds were slowly gathering. Ye Xiu led two guilds and put the other two under Xiao Shiqin. As they traveled towards their destination, Xiao Shiqin picked out the members of Team Happy. Regretfully, these people wouldn’t be joining his troops, so he wouldn’t have a chance to evaluate their strengths closely.

Despite having matched all of the members to their characters, there was one person that Xiao Shiqin could not find anywhere. In the end, he could not hold in his own curiosity anymore and asked, "Um, Wei Chen… He doesn’t seem to be here yet?"

"Yeah." Ye Xiu answered.

That’s it? Xiao Shiqin scratched his head, Would saying one more word kill you? Wei Chen was a pro player, but by the time Xiao Shiqin joined the Alliance, he had long since retired. When he was learning about Team Blue Rain, Xiao Shiqin learned about this founding team leader. However, since he was no longer an opponent he had to face, Xiao Shiqin did not spend much time studying this retired person. Does he want to re-enter the pro scene after so many years.

Xiao Shiqin counted: he had being away for six years. If he wanted come back, then what had he being doing in the past six years? If he were coming back now, then how powerful was he?

The thing Xiao Shiqin cared the most about was still the strength of Team Happy.

Not long after everyone left Sarke City, they arrived at the nearby Midnight Inn.

No matter how big the Inn was, it could not be big enough to be a leveling ground by itself. It was just a landmark building in the area. This time, Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr had just respawned here.

Midnight Inn was getting more lively as more people were arriving to fight for the boss. The small place was packed with players from various guilds, as well as those who did not belong to any big guilds.

The clubs saw fighting over wild bosses as their main job, but that didn’t mean other regular players weren’t interested in these boss fights. As of this moment, there were a number of level 70 players who had gathered into a random team, hoping to take down the boss for themselves. Unfortunately, after a few futile struggles, they all eventually died. Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr left without even sparing a glance at the numerous corpses around. He made it seem as if the bloodshed were as insignificant as raising his hand.

"F*ck. Everytime! There are alway idiots." Salty Not Sweet complained. He was a player in one of the four branch guilds of Tyrannical Ambition. He was not some elite member, nor was he a star player. He had just happened to bump into Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr’s respawn when he had been roaming around the leveling area, going about his own business.

Wild boss fights were the troubles of the elites. However, reporting boss respawns were the responsibility of every guild member. When he reported it to the management level of the guild, he quickly got a reply from the highest command, Wandering Shockwave: Keep watching. Report any changes immediately.

Salty Not Sweet had been quite excited.

A wild boss fight would be a battle of the highest level in the guilds. Despite being weak, to still be able to participate in such a way was still something worth rejoicing over for a fan. The players who provide the information would be rewarded by the guild with contribution points later.

Salty Not Sweet carried out his mission carefully. He roamed around while avoiding the boss and keeping track of the nearby players. Unluckily, a random team decided to challenge the boss first, but ended up getting pulverized. To make the matters worse, these players almost got the scouts like him involved. He watched a player from Misty Castle die from a single Shadow Arrow from Mirworr just because he had reacted one second too slow.

"Wild bosses are truly terrifying." Salty Not Sweet sighed. Although he was a member of a a major guild, he had not witnessed the true powers of a wild boss before.

"A team just got wiped along with a player from Misty Castle." While marveling at the powers of a boss, Salty Not Sweet did not forget his mission and reported the newly confirmed information.

"The troops from the guild will arrive soon."

Salty Not Sweet’s eyes lit up in delight: This boss must belong to Tyrannical Ambition now, right?

He was not disappointed after seeing the troops from Tyrannical Ambition arrive shortly afterward. Not only did he see the guild leader, Wandering Shockwave, who he would have no chance of meeting normally, he even got called over and got to speak with the guild leader. This special honor would have Salty Not Sweet all excited normally, but today, his attention was not on the guild leader. There was a Cleric standing quietly besides him: Misty Mountains.

Tyrannical Ambition was never short of Clerics, or Cleric experts. However, the one in front of him right now was a Cleric who stood at the pinnacle of Glory, not just Tyrannical Ambition or the Heavenly Domain. He was the vice captain of Tyranny: Zhang Xinjie.

All secrets would be revealed eventually. On top of that, Zhang Xinjie leading the troops in a wild boss fight was not some kind of secretive plan that needed to be hidden from everyone else. When every other guild knew that Zhang Xinjie had come himself, what reason did Tyrannical Ambition have to not know it as well? Just by staring at this godly cleric in Glory, Salty Not Sweet’s excitement drowned out the words of Wandering Shockwave. He was just thinking about how regretful it was for Zhang XinJie to use this account. If it had being his usual account, it would have been even cooler.

In the end, Salty Not Sweet mustered up the courage to speak to Zhang Xinjie’s Misty Mountains: "Hi Captain Zhang." He intentionally dropped off the "vice" part, when calling the team’s vice captain, directly promoting him one rank. This was a common approach often seen in society, but Zhang Xinjie replied seriously: "Hi. It should be vice-captain."　

"Uh….." Salty Not Sweet didn’t know what to say in response.

Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader and Wandering Peak’s user, Jiang You, laughed amusingly. He had been talking to Salty Not Sweet. Right when he turned his head to look somewhere else, Salty Not Sweet went over to greet Zhang Xinjie. Jiang You appeared as if he wasn’t being respected, but the reason for the disrespect was because of Zhang Xinjie. What could he say? He understood a fan’s adoration of an idol too.

"Ahem... Blue Brook Guild has arrived." Jiang You received news of other players coming.

"What about Ye Qiu?" Zhang Xinjie asked. He clearly only worried about Ye Qiu’s forces. As for Blue Brook Guild, he had encountered an extremely sharp kid in the previous battle, who he even suspected was Huang Shaotian in the beginning. But after watching this kid more carefully, he knew the kid was not. Huang Shaotian didn’t like to charge forward and strike head-on nor would he be so quiet. Lu Hanwen might not be considered as too quiet, but he was compared to Huang Shaotian. Even against Huang Shaotian, Zhang Xinjie still wouldn’t be as concerned over Blue Brook Guild as he would be over Ye Qiu’s side. Yu Wenzhou was a different matter. In wild boss hunts, hundred player groups were the units in battle. The scale of the battle surpassed a professional match by several tens in magnitude. The value of a God adept in tactics far surpassed that of a single blade.

"They’ve also begun moving. It’s just a matter of time at this point." Jiang You answered.

"What other guilds?"

"Samsara, Misty Rain, Howling Heights." The reports in Jiang You’s hands had information on these three guilds.

"Okay, let’s begin. We’ll first ascertain our advantage." Zhang Xinjie didn’t delay any further. In a battle between tacticians like him and Ye Qiu, advantages were gained little by little. Arriving early was one type of advantage. Zhang Xinjie didn’t want to let this advantage slip through and wait for another opportunity in the future.

Advantages needed to be accumulated. Acting a second early won them one second of an advantage. Tyrannical Ambition quickly moved to surround Red Mage Mirrwor.

Chapter 741: Assault from Two Paths

Tyrannical Ambition’s chief Knight charged forward and the battle for the boss officially began. Zhang Xinjie had personally arranged everyone’s position. The boss itself was secondary. The primary battle would be against the other competing guilds, especially Ye Qiu’s forces, which were of the utmost priority.　

The first opponent that Zhang Xinjie would meet wouldn’t his most troublesome foe, Ye Qiu, but rather Blue Brook Guild.

Changing Spring, Blue Bridge Spring Snow, Ice of Dawn, Chilling Nightfall, and Flying Brushstroke. All of Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts had come out for this battle. Important battles such as competitions for level 70 wild bosses were naturally the highest stage for these in-game experts to stand on.

However, the star of Blue Brook Guild wasn’t any of these five today.

Flowing Cloud.

Zhang Xinjie noticed this Blade Master. In their struggle for Red Ribbon Janna, the one to Enrage the boss and turn the tides was actually this fellow.

But rather than turning the tides in Blue Brook Guild’s favor, he created an opportunity for Ye Qiu. He was most definitely one of those sh*t sticks whose job was to stir sh*t up.

This fellow’s individual skill was certainly outstanding though. Zhang Xinjie couldn’t help but regard him as a ticking time bomb. That time, there had only been one small crack in their defense and that little ghost happened to find it. By the time they tried to respond, it was already too late. It wasn’t Zhang Xinjie being too slow to react, but rather Tyrannical Ambition was unable to carry out his orders quickly enough. No matter how outstanding a commander was, if his subordinates couldn’t carry out his instructions, it was difficult to be effective.

This time, he wouldn’t allow this little punk burrow into an opening.

When Flowing Cloud appeared, Zhang Xinjie took notice. In his eyes, he was perhaps the only threat that Blue Brook Guild posed to him.

"Group one, team four, team five. Group two, team four, team five. Prepare to engage with Blue Brook Guild!" Zhang Xinjie ordered. Tyrannical Ambition took the initiative to strike. Both team fours had been positioned towards Blue Brook Guild’s direction according to previous intelligence, so attacking Blue Brook Guild was very convenient for them. Everyone had come here with confidence in their skill and it didn’t seem like they would need to do much thinking.

Blue Brook Guild didn’t seem to be certain about what they planning on doing, when Tyrannical Ambition suddenly attacked.

"Ah! They’re coming!" Lu Hanwen cried out in astonishment. Flowing Cloud unsheathed his sword.

Zhang Xinjie headed Tyrannical Ambition. Changing Spring obviously knew about this piece of information, but it wasn’t like he could just give up on such an important battle. No matter how difficult the battle would be, he could only face the challenge head on. Changing Spring started taking notice. If Zhang Xinjie continued to support Tyrannical Ambition in this way, he might need to ask the Club for help. There was no hope of him beating Zhang Xinjie. If he could topple Zhang Xinjie, he would be leading the pro team, not just the guild.

"Long-ranged, attack. Melee, push. Even push." Changing Spring only typed six words. His dislike for typing really made those under him curse silently. If a new person joined them, they probably wouldn’t understand his instructions. However, everyone here was a part of the elite group. They understood Changing Spring’s short instructions very well. In this way, Blue Brook Guild’s elite group would be more efficient in battle because the commander didn’t need to spend as much time typing out his orders.　

Blue Brook Guild’s forces pushed forward. Flowing Cloud led the troops. His dazzling swordplay sliced apart Tyrannical Ambition’s forces.　

However, when he looked ahead, Lu Hanwen noticed several Knights facing him.

"Not good!!" Lu Hanwen could feel an ominous premonition creeping up in his mind. It had only been two hours ago that a bunch of Knights had toyed with him. His Flowing Cloud still hadn’t recovered all of its lost experience. His stats were still red!

Lu Hanwen immediately maintained his distance from those Knights, but it was too late. An enemy Knight activated Knight’s Spirit and used Roar. Its range was sufficient to reach Flowing Cloud. Flowing Cloud turned around and charged towards the Knight.

He didn’t learn his lesson well enough. He had been too rash!　

Lu Hanwen scolded himself, while hastily calling out for help: "Situation!"

"What situation?" Changing Spring was puzzled at the message. Blue River, who had fought with Lu Hanwen not long before, seemed to have telepathic powers and shouted: "Not good! Hurry up and find a Knight and Qi Master! He must have been Roared away."

Blue River wasn’t wrong, but their rescue arrangements came too slowly. Under Zhang Xinjie’s personal command, these Tyrannical Ambition Knights worked together to bring Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud farther and farther away. Lu Hanwen was helpless. He could still use a technique like Shadow Steps while taunted, but it wouldn’t help him in any way. Roar forced his real body to move.

The rescue that Lu Hanwen had hoped for never came. Zhang Xinjie had made prior preparations and stopped any attempts at a rescue. Afterwards, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was quickly killed. This was the difference between this time’s experience and last time’s experience. Last time, he had been restricted to walking along with them. This time, he was immediately killed at the fastest speed possible. More enemies meant more danger, especially with a God leading them.　

Two minutes after the two guilds clashed, Blue Brook Guild’s strongest player fell.　

"I charged forward too quickly..." Lu Hanwen had Flowing Cloud revive in the city and typed an ashamed emoji in the guild chat, as if to explain what had happened.

"No worries!" Changing Spring replied. He even added an exclamation mark!　

"Yes! I’m on my way back!" Lu Hanwen shouted.

Changing Spring laughed bitterly. By the time Lu Hanwen came back, what would Blue Brook Guild’s situation be like? Would they already be beaten into a sorry state? It was too difficult to expect his players to have the confidence to face a God.

Changing Spring continued to lead his troops. Under the cover of their long-ranged attackers, Blue Brook Guild slowly advanced. Tyrannical Ambition was being pushed back. It seemed like their defense wasn’t able to hold on. It looked as if Blue Brook Guild’s forward push was going smoothly.　

Unfortunately, everything was a facade. Just when Blue Brook Guild was thinking their push was going well, Tyrannical Ambition suddenly countered with a powerful rebound like a compressed spring. Once they were pushed to their limit, they suddenly shot forward.　　

The tide-like counterattack turned Blue Brook Guild stupid. None of their troops had made any sort of preparation for such a strong rebound, whether that was in tactics or mentally.　

If Blue Brook Guild had advanced four coordinates, after this counterattack, Tyrannical Ambition repelled them six coordinates back.　　

Casualties? Dropped equipment?　

Their losses couldn’t be totalled at this moment, but they wouldn’t be small. Changing Spring sighed. He wasn’t sighing at Blue Brook Guild losing morale. Facing Zhang Xinjie and the elite troops that he led, he wasn’t surprised that such losses would be the result.

At this moment, the two guilds both received new information: Heavenly Justice, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade were closing in.　

If this were before, no one would have cared about these four guilds, but now, when they heard the names of these four guilds, no one could avoid their heads going numb.　

Zhang Xinjie immediately inquired for any information. No guild dared to underestimate them.

The reports indicated that the four guilds had split into two. Heavenly Justice and Conquering Clouds along one path. Radiant and Parade along another. The two paths would converge towards Midnight Tavern.

"Split into two groups….." Zhang Xinjie thought to himself. Afterwards, he asked: "Which path did Ye Qiu take?"　

"We haven’t seen Enlightened Lord."　

That was the answer given. It hid a hint. The person only said that he hadn’t seen Enlightened Lord, but not that Ye Qiu wasn’t there. Ye Qiu could switch accounts. Everyone knew he could do this, because they always made it their priority to kill him…...

"He doesn’t want us to know where their main defenses are." Zhang Xinjie said, "But he must be on one side."

Zhang Xinjie quickly deployed troops and made arrangements according to the paths those four guilds took. He didn’t put an emphasis on either side though. He arranged several flexible teams. These teams could attack the boss to gain some contribution towards winning the boss’ aggro . A gap was reserved between the two sides. When things became dire, these flexible teams could quickly turn around and patch up any holes.

"There’s no need to be too worried about either side." After Zhang Xinjie made arrangements, he examined the entire battlefield carefully and felt very satisfied. As for Blue Brook Guild, once they received the news, they made a strategic withdrawal. Blue Brook Guild didn’t have the confidence to directly confront either of the two Gods. Their only chance was to watch these two tigers battle and see if there were any opening they could take advantage of.　

"They’re here!"　　

Jiang You received another report and passed it on to Zhang Xinjie. Everyone could already see the two armies coming from two directions.　

"Prepare to clash. Don’t be polite. The faster we can determine where Ye Qiu is located, the faster we can formulate countermeasures." Zhang Xinjie said.　

"Samsara has almost arrived too." Jiang You said.

"Okay, understood." Zhang Xinjie nodded his head. No matter how small, he would take everything into consideration. It was his style of doing things.

However, everything that had happened so far was within his expectations.　

What if something unexpected occurred?

Heavenly Justice, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, Parade. The four guild alliance troops soon arrived. They made a few slight adjustments and directly threw themselves into the fray.

"Block them!" Zhang Xinjie ordered. The two sides clashed.

"We’re in danger on this side!!" The troops on the right side reported first. Zhang Xinjie smiled and waved his hands: "Flexible teams, assist the right side."

The flexible teams stopped attacking the boss and began PKing. According to their previous arrangements, they immediately shifted to assist the right side.

Zhang Xinjie’s smile persisted for only a second, when the left side reported: "Danger! Danger!!!"

"What happened?" Zhang Xinjie was startled.

"An expert!! Expert!!!!" The players on the left side cried.

Chapter 742: Left Path, Right Path

"Expert?" Zhang Xinjie was surprised. The enemy troops did have a few fairly skilled elite players, but Zhang Xinjie had factored them into his calculations when he arranged his troops. His progressively decreasing defensive formation shouldn’t be so easily routed by just a few elite players.

The right path was being led by Ye Qiu. Having a difficult time holding off the enemy troops on that side would be understandable, but what expert on the left side could instantly break through their defenses?

Zhang Xinjie had originally planned on going to the right side to personally confront Ye Qiu. After a short moment of hesitation, he led his Misty Mountains to the left path.

The defenses on the left path had already fallen apart. Zhang Xinjie took in everything within his line of sight and then quickly looked around. His gaze moved in a certain direction.

Zhang Xinjie felt a bit dazed.

Was this the game or the Alliance?

Was he dreaming? What was today’s date?

Zhang Xinjie actually checked the date: the year, the month, and the day. He ascertained that his eyes hadn’t gone astray. Today wasn’t the date of a professional match. Even if it were, the scene in front of him shouldn’t feel so familiar.

The two characters in front of him had unfamiliar names and different equipment, but their two figures matched up with the image in Zhang Xinjie’s mind.

One Autumn Leaf.

Dancing Rain.

Glory’s Best Pair. Despite not winning the Glory Championships, these two always won this award without any competition. Other teams also had their own duos. These duos might be outstanding, but they were all completely outclassed in front of this duo. Every time the selection for the Best Pair came up, a few might be able to obtain a few votes, but it was never even a contest. The closest competitor was Team Void’s Ghostblade Duo, Li Xuan and Wu Yuce, but their total votes never exceeded half of the votes that Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng received. And they were already the "closest".

Zhang Xinjie’s impression of this duo might be deeper than any other player.

Because Team Excellent Era was Team Tyranny’s rival. In the first three years of the Glory Alliance, the two teams faced each other in the finals all three times. The season two finals had been the most competitive.

Unfortunately, Team Tyranny lost all three times and Team Excellent Era had the last laugh for three years in a row.

Team Excellent Era’s three consecutive championship victories was the darkest part of Team Tyranny’s history.

Zhang Xinjie came to Team Tyranny in season four. He quickly accepted Team Tyranny’s motto: Advance bravely. Beat Excellent Era and defeat Ye Qiu.

That year, they finally did it. In the season four finals, Team Tyranny beat Excellent Era. Zhang Xinjie had definitely been one of the main reasons for their victory. That year, a new player also came to Excellent Era. She and Zhang Xinjie both became a part of the so-called golden generation. Her name was Su Mucheng. A girl, and very beautiful one too. In the male dominated Glory scene, she was certainly a welcome sight.

What made everyone’s eyes light up even more was that this beautiful girl wasn’t just a flower vase. The synergy between her and Excellent Era’s God Ye Qiu was as if the two shared the same mind. Team Tyranny may have won the championships, but the Best Pair was awarded indisputably to these two.

As for Team Tyranny, although Zhang Xinjie and their ace player, Han Wenqing, coordinated well with each other, Clerics played a support role on the team, limiting their scenes shown together. As a result, it appeared as if they had fewer moments of brilliance.

For the next three years, Zhang Xinjie saw these two win the Best Pair award again and again. Team Excellent Era was Team Tyranny’s rival. Even though neither of them appeared in the finals again since that season, the sparks between them never lessened.

Who could have a deeper impression of this Excellent Era duo than Zhang Xinjie? Not even Han Wenqing did. After all, Han Wenqing had fought against Ye Qiu alone during the first three finals. Even after Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng paired together, Han Wenqing still attached more importance on Ye Qiu.

Ever since Zhang Xinjie had entered the Alliance, the foe he worked hardest to defeat was these two. Losing to them was even worse than losing ten other matches for Team Tyranny.

He had an extremely deep impression of them. Zhang Xinjie didn’t know how long he had spent studying these two. As a result, although it may have just been a glance, he felt a sense of familiarity. In the blink of an eye, One Autumn Leaf and Dancing Rain appeared in his mind. He soon cleared his mind and saw that this Battle Mage was called Let There Be Light, while the Launcher was called Chasing Haze.

Chasing Haze.

As Ye Qiu had begun to receive all sorts of attention, this name came up frequently from the big guilds. There had been a lot of debate over who actually played this Launcher. However, her relationship with Ye Qiu wasn’t shallow. This was the one point everyone agreed on.

Who was she?

Zhang Xinjie had always suspected.

He soon got his answer ten seconds later.

Su Mucheng. The person playing was definitely Su Mucheng.

And that Let There Be Light must be Ye Qiu.

Ten seconds was more than enough to make a definite conclusion. Don’t forget that these two had won Best Pair four years in a row and that they beat their closest competitor by enormous margins. If they weren’t so unique and unmatched, how else could they have won the award year after year?

Their coordination together couldn’t be replicated.

Even though One Autumn Leaf was still a part of Excellent Era and the one behind the character, Sun Xiang, was also a top-tier God, there was zero synergy between him and Su Mucheng.　

In these ten seconds, Zhang Xinjie was certain that these two were Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng. There was no mistake.

The Battle Mage charged forward while the Launcher provided support. The coordination between these two was the same as ever. No matter how bad Excellent Era’s records may be, these two had never changed. Even though Ye Qiu had left the pro scene for seven months now, when the two appeared together on the battlefield again, Zhang Xinjie felt like nothing had changed. This was why he checked the data. 　

"Flex team, to the left!" Zhang Xinjie decisively ordered.

If Ye Qiu was on this side with Su Mucheng assisting him, this side should be where he should emphasize all his defenses towards. What was going on with the right side though? Maybe Ye Qiu had guessed what he might set up, so he had formulated a counter for it. Did he want to use the brief advantage seized to decide the entire battle?

However, there was still time to adjust.

Zhang Xinjie was confident. He had come with Tyrannical Ambition’s elite troops this time. Their coordination and strength were better than the temporary team that he had come with last time. When he switched which side the flex teams would support, he had explained his actions to the right side. He believed that these in-game players wouldn’t make any huge mistakes.

"Pull back." Zhang Xinjie ordered.

Even though he found which side he should prioritize, he couldn’t just ignore the right side! To what extent had Ye Qiu planned ahead? Zhang Xinjie couldn’t wait to see. He decided that both sides should pull back, so he could get a better picture of the situation and command both sides at the same time.

"Clerics, focus. Knights, forward. Use Provoke and Roar to CC Let There Be Light and Chasing Haze. Troops, go between these two and attack. Try and split them up. Focus your attacks on Chasing Haze for now. Qi Masters, use Cloud Grasping Fist whenever you find an opportunity." Zhang Xinjie gave a string of orders, completely towards these two. He had to admit that this Best Pair was scary, but Zhang Xinjie was sure that he could deal with this pair, which he understood well. If it wasn’t for the enemy side having a lot of troops as well, Zhang Xinjie wouldn’t feel like this Best Pair would be a threat.

"Right side, continue pulling back a bit more. Flex team one, team two provide assistance on this side. Disrupt their attacks from the side." Zhang Xinjie paid attention to the left side, while also taking note of the right side.

Flex team one and two faithfully completed his instructions and struck from the side. The effects were outstanding. A tear instantly formed in the enemy troops. It looked as if they would break. The two team leaders were excited. They planned on penetrating deeper and completely splitting apart their troops. Zhang Xinjie saw the positions of their troops after being split apart and suddenly felt his heart leap.

"Team one, team two, retreat! Don’t go any farther!!" Zhang Xinjie hastily shouted.

But he was too late. The two team leaders impatiently charged in. When they received Zhang Xinjie’s warning, they didn’t dare to hesitate and immediately retreated, but the other side’s ruptured formation suddenly snapped back like a pair of scissors, pincering them. The players, who had been scattered, returned to attack, giving the two teams a difficult time.

Fortunately, Zhang Xinjie’s warning had put them into a retreat already. If they had gone any deeper, they would have certainly been wiped out. Even so, team two lost six players and team one was was practically destroyed.

"How did things turn out like this?" Zhang Xinjie was astonished.

His move to attack from the side had been a decision based on the current situation of the battle. No matter how great Ye Qiu might be, there was no way he could have predicted so precisely that this battle would turn out this way. The other side had clearly lured them in deep. That was a very fast and directed reaction. It wasn’t something an in-game player could easily accomplish.

A normal player might be able to react based on the current circumstances, but such a quick countermeasure and such adept awareness was something only a professional player possessed.

At this moment, Zhang Xinjie saw a Mechanic on the right side. His equipment might be poor, but he was very skilled. Anyone with some skill could instantly tell him apart from the rest of the troops. This person wasn’t only attacking. He would fight and then stop to move a few steps from time to time. The places, where he moved to, were places, where he could see the battlefield.

"Mechanic... It can’t be?" Zhang Xinjie suddenly felt his head begin to hurt.

Chapter 743: Complete Defense

Xiao Shiqin!

Zhang Xinjie instantly thought of this name.

But why would he be with Ye Qiu? Zhang Xinjie felt a bit dizzy. No one could have anticipated this.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t want to believe his suspicion, but as he continued to watch the Mechanic and command his troops on this side, he couldn’t help but become more certain.

His countermeasures were being casually dissolved by the other side. Their defenses were being scattered.

Xiao Shiqin wasn’t better than Zhang Xinjie, but Zhang Xinjie had prioritized his defenses towards the left path, where Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng were located.

Zhang Xinjie now understood why the enemy split their troops. The enemy wasn’t trying to play any tricks. Both paths were solid and required his full attention to answer to. However, he was either emphasizing the defenses on the left path and not taking care of the right path, or emphasizing the defenses on the right path and not taking care of the left path.

"Retreat. Everyone on the left and right sides, retreat." Zhang Xinjie could only retreat. He needed to be able to see both sides at the same time. Ye Qiu and Xiao Shiqin weren’t opponents that he could contend against by running back and forth between the left and right side.

As his troops withdrew, he had the team attacking the boss move away, so the enemy troops would move in a desired direction. By moving everyone together to the same place, he could give out orders to his troops in one go.

The situation was stabilized.

Zhang Xinjie let out a short sigh of relief. He wasn’t glad that his commands were on point, but rather that the troops being led weren’t just temporary troops. Tyrannical Ambition’s elite troops were superior to the four guild alliance’s troops. Relying on this advantage, Zhang Xinjie temporarily stabilized the situation. However, this didn’t mean the situation was in his favor.

In reality, Tyrannical Ambition was in a terrible spot. Zhang Xinjie’s original plans had been completely disrupted. The rearranging of his troops was proof of that.

"They actually stopped us?" Xiao Shiqin was very surprised. The enemy guild seemed to know exactly when to retreat and when to advance. Wasn’t their enemy commander a bit too skilled? Could it be…..

"Who’s leading Tyrannical Ambition?" Xiao Shiqin couldn’t help but ask.

"Zhang Xinjie, who else?" Ye Xiu replied.

Xiao Shiqin suddenly felt dizzy.

He had been busy these past few days dealing with his transfer to the Club and team’s circumstances. How could he know that there was such a storm taking place in the game? Tyrannical Ambition actually sent Zhang Xinjie out to personally take command. No wonder Ye Qiu wanted him to help out. If he didn’t help, Tyrannical Ambition wouldn’t be easy for Ye Qiu to deal with.

Who was Xiao Shiqin? After a few exchanges, he had a good estimate of both side’s strengths. In terms of strategy and tactics, both sides were equally matched, but in terms of average strength, Tyrannical Ambition’s elite troops were clearly a step higher than the four guild alliance’s. The reason why Tyrannical Ambition couldn’t respond, when they attacked from the left and right paths, was because Zhang Xinjie had purposefully been drawn to protect the side that Ye Qiu was on, so he hadn’t placed as much importance on the other side. Zhang Xinjie had probably realized it now though. He adjusted his troops and retreated promptly. Neither side would be able to win an advantage in just a short amount of time.

Their side had two Gods leading. By dividing up the work, their tactics would be more detailed and meticulous. However, Tyrannical Ambition’s troops were stronger than theirs. By using this advantage, Zhang Xinjie would be capable of holding them off.

If the two fought head to head, Xiao Shiqin felt like they would eventually win because he knew that he and Ye Qiu wouldn’t have their troops directly clash with the stronger Tyrannical Ambition. They would certainly utilize their greater flexibility in terms of tactics to force Zhang Xinjie into dire straits.

However, this problem was that this wasn’t a PK to the death. Both sides came for the boss. As long as Zhang Xinjie could maintain the current situation and kill the boss, victory would be decided.

Xiao Shiqin quickly saw through what Zhang Xinjie had intended by having Tyrannical Ambition retreat.

Everyone would be on the defense. Their goal was to stall for time.

Xiao Shiqin felt like winning would truly be difficult. Xiao Shiqin had a deep understanding of defensive tactics. He had come from a middle of the pack team, so he rarely took the initiative against stronger teams. Defend and counterattack. Strike only after the enemy has struck. These were the methods that Xiao Shiqin had relied on for so many years. However, he knew very well that the reason he employed these tactics was because his team’s circumstances forced him to. Zhang Xinjie was truly talented at defensive tactics. Perhaps it had to do with his personality. However, what made things conflicting was that Team Tyranny pursued fierce assaults and emphasized a strong offense. Attacking was the best defense. These words couldn’t suit Team Tyranny any better. As a result, Zhang Xinjie’s greatest strength was never fully utilized.

Even so, Zhang Xinjie’s talent for defensive tactics never faded. Xiao Shiqin looked at Zhang Xinjie’s defensive formation and immediately felt troubled.

It wasn’t like he had no confidence in winning. After all, he had God Ye Qiu on his side too. He worried that by the time they managed to break through Zhang Xinjie’s defenses, the boss might already be dead.

Tsk! How should he go about doing this!

Studying tactics was Xiao Shiqin’s specialty. He had relied on tactics to obtain victory these past few years. He immediately began thinking of possible countermeasures. After about two seconds, he suddenly realized that something wasn’t right.

Why did he need to try so hard?

His goal was to observe Ye Qiu’s team and measure each player’s skill level. Why was he so concerned about winning the boss? As long as he didn’t command his assigned troops too poorly, it would be fine. Figuring out a countermeasure should be left for Ye Qiu to mull over. Why was he overthinking things?

Xiao Shiqin reminded himself fiercely. Afterwards, he searched for Steamed Bun. At the same time, he realized that Zhang Xinjie had put himself an advantageous situation. Splitting their troops into two made it difficult for him to observe Ye Qiu’s people. However, Tyrannical Ambition grouped together and moved everyone to one place making it convenient for him to obtain more information.

Right, obtain information!

Xiao Shiqin confirmed his point of view. Zhang Xinjie had created a good opportunity for him to obtain information! His defenses distributed every class into appropriate locations, so all angles could be covered. Some players were placed in fixed locations, while others constantly moved, providing assistance where needed.

Hm? That’s not right. That side has an opening. Hurry up and attack over there!

Ah, it’s been filled up. Zhang Xinjie was worthy of his reputation. The Tyrannical Ambition players over there probably weren’t paying too much attention to their positions and had made a slight mistake.

Hm? That side! Tyrannical Ambition retreated a bit too far. Their side could take advantage and push forward. They were a bit far though and might not make it in time. The troops on Ye Qiu’s side should go. They were closer.

Xiao Shiqin wanted to message Ye Qiu, but just when he typed out the words, he suddenly stopped and felt like crying.

What’s going on with me? Why am I still studying on how to break Zhang Xinjie’s defenses! His habit of looking at the enemy side’s tactics and forming his own tactics was like a conditioned reflex now.

Information. Pay attention to finding information.

Xiao Shiqin thought to himself as he noticed Ye Qiu order two teams to move. Ye Qiu’s Let There Be Light led the way towards the location, where Tyrannical Ambition had pulled back slightly too far.

They were a bit too far too…. Zhang Xinjie has probably noticed it by now?

Sure enough!

Xiao Shiqin watched that side attentively. The opening was suddenly patched up. Zhang Xinjie clearly hadn’t been trying to set up a trap. After all, despite being elite troops, those elite players were still far from being at a professional level. Even more so, tactics required practice to carry out. Zhang Xinjie arranged his troops, taking these normal player’s skill levels into consideration. However, it was still extremely hard to avoid mistakes. Zhang Xinjie could correct these mistakes though. Two openings appeared, but were quickly fixed.

The situation went just as Xiao Shiqin predicted. Both sides were in a deadlock. Although their side held the initiative, Zhang Xinjie had intentionally put his side on the defensive in order to stall for more time.

Xiao Shiqin glanced at Ye Qiu’s expression. Ye Qiu didn’t seem to be worried at all though. "Could he have some way of breaking through? How come I can’t see any?" Xiao Shiqin, who put it as his priority to collect enemy information, accidentally started to think about tactics again.　

On Tyrannical Ambition’s side, Zhang Xinjie was quite satisfied with the current situation. Jiang You reported to him at this moment: Samsara’s elite troops have arrived.

"Mm, got it." Zhang Xinjie nodded his head. Another guild joining the struggle for the boss was within his expectations and he had already prepared for it. This wouldn’t break their deadlock.

Samsara had naturally sent out their two elite groups. Their team had become the new champions and shone boundlessly. However, their guild couldn’t match their team’s achievements. Disappointment filled the guild. The guild leader Three Paths Six Realms had trouble upkeeping his honor.

He called over the second elite group leader to his side. This person hadn’t been a part of the guild for very long and couldn’t be a core member of the guild yet. However, this person was skilled and a very talented commander. Unfortunately, Ye Qiu and Zhang Xinjie were their opponents. Three Paths Six Realms really wanted to cry. He was pretty much trying to give medicine to a dead horse at this point.

This second group leader saw the current situation and said excitedly to Three Paths Six Realms: "Those two guilds are fighting fiercely. This is our chance!"

"Oh? What do you mean?" Three Paths Six Realms asked humbly. Don’t look at how this person had been promoted to the second group leader position. The two weren’t familiar, when discussing serious matters.

"Tyrannical Ambition is completely on the defensive. They are clearly struggling to stand up to the other side’s pressure. If we suddenly attack, we’ll instantly break through. Then, we can surround the boss and move the boss away, while attacking it. Those two sides seem to have exhausted their strength already. Even a God leading them won’t be enough."

"It can’t be as easy as you say though, can it?" Three Realms Six Paths said.

"If we don’t try, how will we know?" The second group leader appeared extremely confident.

Chapter 744: Three Opponents

Samsara’s second elite group leader was of course, Wei Chen. After he said those words, everyone in Samsara raised their eyebrows. Who were their opponents? Zhang Xinjie and Ye Qiu, two of Glory’s Master Tacticians. Even so, he dared to boast about his ability to command in front of them! Not only did no one in Samsara feel confident, they also started to doubt Wei Chen. Quite a few players didn’t give him any face and typed a sweating face emoji into the team chat. Wei Chen may be the second elite group leader, but his position in Samsara wasn’t actually that high, especially among the elites. Anyone with talent would be used to their full ability, but a becoming a true elite required loyalty and trust. A newcomer couldn’t gain trust in such a short amount of time.

Their doubt towards Wei Chen made him feel gloomy.

Everyone felt like he was just speaking big words. However, Wei Chen didn’t think so. Not only did he did not think that his words were ridiculous, he thought he had a seventy percent chance of turning them into a reality.

　

If we don’t try, how will we know?

Wei Chen even thought that he had been more on the modest side. Who was he? He saw the opposing sides and instantly analyzed the situation and the stakes involved. If Samsara helped Ye Xiu’s side, breaking through Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses wouldn’t be a problem at all.

After Tyrannical Ambition set up defenses against Ye Xiu’s four guild alliance, they had also made sufficient preparations for any following guilds. That was only the case for normal players though. In Wei Chen’s eyes, the amount of strength dedicated to defend against other guilds was nothing to look at.

In fact, Wei Chen was one hundred percent sure of being able to break through Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses. However, if he appeared so certain, Samsara probably wouldn’t believe him. After all, in their eyes, their opponents were way too powerful. Wei Chen had already held back in his speech, yet who would have thought that Samsara still wouldn’t believe him? There weren’t too many boos, but many disapproved. Their attitudes could be seen above their heads. Weren’t they overreacting?

I really am too skilled to be a spy!

Wei Chen sighed. He might as well continue with his "overconfident" attitude: "What? You don’t believe me? Zhang Xinjie and Ye Qiu are evenly matched in tactics. However, Tyrannical Ambition’s overall strength is greater than the four guild alliance’s. In a one on one battle, Tyrannical Ambition doesn’t need to be on the defensive. Something unexpected must have come up for Tyrannical Ambition to be on their back foot. Right now is the perfect time to fish in troubled waters! If you guys insist on waiting for one side to beat the other before acting... don’t blame me for being too blunt! Whether Zhang Xinjie or Ye Qiu wins, without an evenly matched opponent restricting the other, how will we manage to beat them?"

Wei Chen was reasonable. It didn’t sound like he was being brainlessly overconfident. Everyone fell silent. No one randomly complained.

"If we’re going to act, then we must do it before it’s too late! Tyrannical Ambition isn’t trying to beat Ye Qiu’s side right now. Zhang Xinjie is only trying to stall for time, so they can kill the boss before their defense gets broken through. The more we watch from the sidelines, the happier he will be. We’re actually a bit late already. If we wait any longer, how are we going to generate enough aggro to steal the boss?" Wei Chen followed.

In the end, Samsara’s guild leader, Three Realms Six Paths couldn’t hold back anymore. They weren’t here to watch a movie. Their goal was the boss. At this moment, Wei Chen added: "We’re a championship team’s guild. Don’t you guys have any pride?"

These words struck Three Realms Six Path’s wound. Guild Samsara’s recent achievements were quite shameful for a championship team’s guild. Three Realms Six Paths couldn’t calmly continue pondering. They were already here. Dawdling around was truly a bit disgraceful.

"I’ll lead group one. Sky will lead group two. Everyone, get ready!" Three Realms Six Paths ordered. Wei Chen’s spy Warlock was called Sky Trip. Three Realms was letting Wei Chen command or telling the second elite group to listen to Wei Chen.

"I’ll lead the second group to tear open Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses. Your first group will trap the boss and lead it away." Wei Chen said.

"Okay!" Three Realms Six Paths agreed. A boss’ aggro was generated group by group, not by guild. As a result, between the first and second group, only one group could hold the aggro. Leaving the aggro with his group put him more at ease.

"Samsara, our team is the championship team. Show some spirit! Everyone, advance!" Three Realms Six Paths roared and Samsara charged forward.

"Samsara’s coming." Jiang You had been hoping that Samsara would be like Blue Brook Guild and keep watching foolishly, but not long after arriving, they charged over murderously. He hastily reminded Zhang Xinjie, so he wouldn’t forget.

"I see them." Zhang Xinjie replied plainly. The current situation, as well as the progress on the boss, was going very well. Just Samsara alone wouldn’t be enough to tip the balance. However, he couldn’t completely ignore them either.

Zhang Xinjie turned his gaze towards Samsara and adjusted his troops slightly. Against Ye Qiu and Xiao Shiqin, two troublesome opponents, he couldn’t spend too much time dealing with Samsara.

Just when he finished making his arrangements and started shifting his attention back to the two Gods, he suddenly discovered that Samsara’s incoming group quickly adjusted their offensive formation and direction in response.

Zhang Xinjie was startled, but the two groups had already began to clash.

A huge cloud of magic undulations formed, instantly enveloping countless figures. Samsara had strong Spellblades, similar to how Tyrannical Ambition had strong Clerics. However, their strongest class was probably still their Sharpshooters. Their Sharpshooters were more outstanding than the featured classes of other guilds. It was simply because of Zhou Zekai’s insane popularity. His influence not only increased the popularity of Sharpshooters in Samsara, but the popularity of Sharpshooters in all of Glory.

Glory was a very balanced game, but that didn’t mean the class distribution was completely balanced. The existence of the Pro Alliance affected players the most. An outstanding player made many players incorrectly think "This class must be very strong."

During Excellent Era’s period of dominance, there was a saying in Glory: there are as many dogs as there are Battle Mages. Nowadays, Zhou Zekai’s popularity increased the number of Sharpshooters in Glory. The players, who became Sharpshooters because of Zhou Zekai, were often fans of Zhou Zekai and Samsara. The most outstanding among the numerous Sharpshooters appeared in Samsara. There were already too many Sharpshooters in Samsara. Anymore and many of the guild’s activities would start to get affected. More players meant more experts. The strength of Samsara’s Sharpshooters were indisputable. As a result, in their confrontation with Tyrannical Ambition, Samsara’s offense came quickly and furiously.

Sharpshooters attacked in the first wave. Spellblades attacked in the second wave. Although Tyrannical Ambition counterattacked, they clearly suffered the larger loss. Afterwards, Samsara’s melee classes charged forward. They randomly walked in a circle and didn’t even attack before retreating.

"Don’t move!!" Zhang Xinjie saw his players subconsciously step forward to chase. If they chased, their formation would crumble. However, if they didn’t chase and traded blows with their long-ranged classes, they would be on the losing end. They couldn’t rely on their Clerics to carry them. If it were a one on one, it would work, but right now, Tyrannical Ambition could only deploy a limited amount of resources to each side. Not only did they need to defend against two powers, they also needed to deal with the wild boss!

"Hm! How patient!" Wei Chen saw that Tyrannical Ambition’s members didn’t chase. After a moment of surprise, he followed up with a message to Three Realms Six Paths: "Guild leader, provide us with some cover. Have your mid-ranged and long-ranged classes coordinate with us."

"Okay." Three Realms Six Paths replied.　

As a result, another wave of attacks from Samsara pressured Zhang Xinjie even more.

"Move the boss away in the six o’clock direction. Everyone press towards this side." Zhang Xinjie quickly ordered. If the other side wouldn’t come over, he could only have his own troops go over.

"Move move move to the left." Wei Chen immediately commanded. Samsara began to shift horizontally.

Zhang Xinjie was once again surprised at the turn of events. If he wanted to respond, his team would need to move in addition to rotate. However, his defenses for each side were arranged differently. Moving and rotating was too difficult for so many people. Many would certainly make mistakes in trying to maintain the formation, while moving. One too many mistakes and his opponents would instantly find an opportunity to break through. After all, his opponents were Ye Qiu and Xiao Shiqin.

No! There was one more!

Who was the person leading Samsara?

Zhang Xinjie didn’t regard Samsara’s tactics as mere coincidences. He was more willing to regard Samsara’s movements as intentional and began to create countermeasures accordingly.

But if this enemy commander was making these decisions intentionally, this commander was truly quite skilled. Baiting the enemy into making a mistake and then seizing that opportunity…...

Zhang Xinjie suddenly felt his heart go cold.

Baiting the enemy into a mistake and seizing that opportunity was the style that Team Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou was most proficient in! It was this style, which created Glory’s greatest opportunist, Huang Shaotian. What was going on today? The other three Master Tacticians had allied together to teach him a lesson?

Zhang Xinjie felt dizzy. He started looking for any conspicuous Warlocks among Samsara’s troops, but when he looked at all the guild tags above their heads, he suddenly felt like something wasn’t right.

Wasn’t Blue Brook Guild over there? Yu Wenzhou ran over to help Samsara? Did he finish eating and have nothing left to do?

Could it be... Yu Wenzhou was using the strength of another to do his dirty work? He would first borrow Samsara’s strength to break through Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses?

The more Zhang Xinjie thought about it, the more convoluted his thoughts became…...

Chapter 745: The Difference in Treatment

Zhang Xinjie hadn’t finished dealing with the opponents before him, when he began pondering over what to do with Blue Brook Guild. No matter how capable he may be, he truly didn’t have the ability to cope with every side simultaneously. Let alone Blue Brook Guild, when he shifted his attention towards Samsara’s movements, he no longer commanded the Tyrannical Ambition players behind him, resulting in them being unable to hold their own against the assault led by Ye Qiu and Xiao Shiqin.

Zhang Xinjie was unable to personally check Blue Brook Guild’s movements, so he gave the task to Jiang You. Following afterwards, he immediately turned around to organize the troops behind him.

Jiang You suddenly felt terrified when he heard that Blue Brook Guild might attack as well. Even he could tell that their formation was whirling around rapidly. After Samsara attacked, their complete and sturdy formation immediately started to fall apart, especially when Samsara started shifting to the side. Samsara began attacking their sides, while their defenses were unable to keep up. Even worse, Zhang Xinjie needed to urgently deal with Ye Qiu’s troops at the same time.

Jiang You’s face dripped with sweat as he took over Zhang Xinjie’s position to lead this side. As the guild leader, he naturally had some skill of his own. He had a good understanding of Zhang Xinjie’s system.

Zhang Xinjie gave a few orders on that side and turned his head to organize this side.

"Not bad." Zhang Xinjie approved of Jiang You’s actions. He gave a few more detailed orders and then turned back around again to contend against Ye Qiu’s side.

How long can this last? Jiang You felt even more worried, seeing Zhang Xinjie’s hurrying about. However, no matter how anxious he was, he couldn’t think of any way to break out. Despite Zhang Xinjie’s desperate efforts, he still failed to regain control of the situation. If he didn’t respond, it would be over. If he responded, perhaps there might be a chance.

Unfortunately, Zhang Xinjie’s predictions played out as expected. The group tried to force a complex adjustment and, sure enough, numerous players made mistakes. The defensive formation quickly fell into disorder and could no longer resist against the enemy’s assault.

It was too early to give up though. For Zhang Xinjie, this was just a loss for this stage in the battle. A professional match would go through several ups and downs. There weren’t many situations where a single tactic would thwart the enemy completely. This situation was similar to a basketball match. It constantly went back and forth. The two teams would constantly switch tactics, finding a way to stabilize the situation or turn the situation around.

In Zhang Xinjie’s eyes, the opening move of the match had gone quite well. The unexpected appearance of Xiao Shiqin forced him to go on the defensive. After Zhang Xinjie switched tactics, he steadied the situation. However, Samsara appeared, completely messing everything up. It was still too early to say that Tyrannical Ambition had lost though.

If the boss’s aggro was converted to numbers, Tyrannical Ambition was leading by quite a bit! However, in the next stage, the other side would probably be able to close the gap.

"Retreat in the 4 o’clock position. Leave the boss on the edge." Zhang Xinjie gave a new order. This time, Zhang Xinjie wanted to divert the enemy’s attention. Everyone was here for the boss, not to wipe the other side out. Weren’t the two enemies charging at them because they wanted to surround the boss? Now that Tyrannical Ambition withdrew and left the boss behind, what else would those two enemies do?

After resisting for a long time, Tyrannical Ambition finally pulled back to the mountainside to let the tigers fight.　

He gave Samsara a choice as well. Samsara clearly knew that they could break through Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses, so they did so, but now? The leaders of the two enemy sides would see that Tyrannical Ambition was letting them fight each other, but what else could they do? Let the boss sit there and not take it? Ally together and annihilate Tyrannical Ambition?

The latter choice sounded good, but it was unlikely to happen because of their relationships with each other and their frequent fights for bosses.

It went just as Zhang Xinjie predicted. The boss was left at the edges and the two sides set their eyes on the boss instead. After breaking apart Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses, the two sides sent a group towards the boss.

Fight! Let me have a good look at how you two fight each other.　

Zhang Xinjie relaxed and spent some more time paying attention to Blue Brook Guild. It looked like Blue Brook Guild still didn’t plan on making a move yet. For now, Samsara’s enemy commander was still a mystery. That previous strategic decision conformed with Yu Wenzhou’s expertise, but making a conclusion based off of a single move was too hasty. After all, such a tactic wasn’t impossible to replicate as the synergy of the Best Duo.

But even if Samsara’s enemy commander wasn’t Yu Wenzhou, he was certainly an expert. On Samsara’s side, vice-captain Jiang Botao was quite accomplished in tactics. That was something that he was completely capable of doing.

Under Zhang Xinjie’s eyes, the two sides clashed with the boss at their intersection.

Such a chaotic fight between so many made it difficult for even Zhang Xinjie to see every detail clearly. Moreover, he quickly discovered that he didn’t need to analyze the situation because Samsara had already lost. Samsara clearly had better elite troops and an outstanding commander, but when the two sides clashed, Heavenly Justice quickly swarmed the boss away. Samsara tried their hardest to snatch it back, but all of their efforts seemed meaningless. The other side easily neutralized all attacks and the boss was moved farther and farther away.

"Why is it like this?" Zhang Xinjie was having a hard time understanding. Samsara appeared way too weak in that moment. Where was the Samsara that thoroughly thwarted his defenses? How come they suddenly turned into jello when facing Ye Qiu’s troops. Why was there a huge difference in treatment? Could Samsara’s performance previously have been coincidental?

Zhang Xinjie felt gloomy at this point. They couldn’t keep waiting any longer. Tyrannical Ambition needed to attack at full force. Their current situation was different from before. Whichever side held the boss would be attacked on both sides. The pressure from two enemy sides, which Tyrannical Ambition had to resist before, would now shift over to Ye Qiu’s alliance.

Tyrannical Ambition chased after them, but were blocked by Radiant and Parade shortly after. After fighting for awhile, Zhang Xinjie already knew that Xiao Shiqin was commanding. For a moment, he felt his head hurt. Xiao Shiqin was a defense-oriented tactician. Breaking through his defenses wouldn’t be an easy feat.

What about Samsara? We can help each other!

Zhang Xinjie looked for them and saw Samsara rushing over. Xiao Shiqin’s troops didn’t seem to be planning on blocking Samsara. Why would Samsara waste time here then? They happily chased after the boss.

For a moment, Zhang Xinjie felt like he believed in his guess. He was afraid that he had truly made a mistake. Samsara didn’t actually have any expert commander on their side. Perhaps the sudden appearance of Su Mucheng or Xiao Shiqin caused his mind to lean towards such thoughts. He had been wary because of Samsara’s flexible tactics, when in reality, there was actually nothing to be afraid. As a result, he had misunderstood, but Ye Qiu hadn’t. That was why he let Samsara go because he believed that he could hold the boss while resisting Samsara’s attacks.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t know whether to laugh or cry at the reversal of circumstances. Ye Qiu and Xiao Shiqin had decided on the same strategy as his initial one. The alliance didn’t care about a decisive victory over him. Xiao Shiqin focused on leading the defense. As long as he could stall for enough time, Ye Qiu’s side would be able to finish off the boss.

Although he could see through the other side’s intentions, Zhang Xinjie didn’t dare to completely forego their defense and pour everything into attacking because his opponent was Xiao Shiqin, who only cared about dragging out the battle. Xiao Shiqin didn’t need to care about doing anything else. However, Xiao Shiqin didn’t tend to be solely on defense. He was most adept at defending before counterattacking. Zhang Xinjie couldn’t neglect to take precautions, especially against Xiao Shiqin.

Behind the confrontation between Zhang Xinjie and Xiao Shiqin, Ye Qiu led the other two guilds to defend against Samsara’s attacks, while dealing with the boss.

Ye Qiu was at the forefront. His Let There Be Light and Su Mucheng’s Chasing Haze created the spearhead of their team’s attacks.

Yes, they were completely on the offensive. They didn’t bother defending and attacked instead. Their troops were slightly weaker than Samsara’s, but their troops also had pro-level players, specifically the Best Pair.

Samsara couldn’t hold on. Samsara’s guild leader, Three Realms Six Paths, was blaming himself deeply. Wei Chen consoled him on the side: "Don’t take it to heart. This is just like a pro match. No one can ever be sure of the final outcome."

Three Realms Six Paths sighed: "You broke apart Tyrannical Ambition’s defenses and created an opportunity for us, but I wasn’t able to grasp it firmly enough and let Heavenly Justice take it away. It was my mistake."

"Look clearly. Ye Qiu must be leading that side. That Battle Mage called Let There Be Light! That one with the disgusting name! Yes, that’s him. I’m sure everyone will understand." Wei Chen said.

"Yes, that’s definitely him, and that Launcher. Could it be..." Three Realms Six Paths stared.

"If it really is her, then there is no need to feel ashamed at all. How are we supposed to contend against a f*cking God? One day, maybe one of our champion players will come over and then we’ll see who’s arrogant." Wei Chen sounded indignant.

Just when they said this, the two leaders were fleeing with their tails behind their backs! They weren’t able to defend against such fierce attacks! The several players leading the assault were simply too powerful, especially that Battle Mage and Launcher duo. Three Realms Six Paths felt like they were definitely Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng.

"How do we do this?" Three Realms Six Paths felt hopeless. He didn’t realize that the person next to him wasn’t putting in any effort at all.

Chapter 746: Punish You Out of Battle

"It looks like... Samsara is unable to hold on..." Of course Tyrannical Ambition would pay attention to Samsara’s situation. In the end, Jiang You carefully worded his report because, under the usual reasoning, Samsara should be on the offensive, while Heavenly Justice and Conquering Clouds would be suppressed. However, Samsara was the side labeled as being unable to hold on. For the side on the offense to be "unable to hold on", Jiang You could only think of the word pathetic to describe them.

"Sigh...." Zhang Xinjie sighed deeply. If he had known that Samsara’s tactic was a false alarm, if he had been a bit more courageous and ignored their movements, they would still be in an advantageous situation. Samsara probably wouldn’t have actually gotten anything done with their move. He had been too cautious and messed up his own troops!

It was too late to regret though. Xiao Shiqin and his two guilds weren’t opponents for Zhang Xinjie and Tyrannical Ambition. In terms of pure strength, Xiao Shiqin’s side would not be able to contest against Tyrannical Ambition, but stalling for time was a completely different matter for these tacticians.

With Samsara broken apart, Xiao Shiqin immediately pulled back, clearly to coordinate with Ye Qiu’s two guilds. If that happened, Tyrannical Ambition would have an even harder time shattering the stalemate.

Samsara’s guild leader, Three Realms Six Paths, noticed this scene. He immediately halted and looked backwards. He suddenly spoke: "Right now, Tyrannical Ambition is pushing their way over there. When the two sides are in a deadlock, perhaps there might be an opportunity for us to join?"

"That’ll depend on the circumstances." Wei Chen reacted instantly: "If that kind of situation from before is replicated, of course we can, but if the pressure put on by Tyrannical Ambition isn’t strong enough, giving their opponents energy to spare, we might not be able to gain the advantage."

"You’re right." Three Realms Six Paths nodded his head.

"We’ll see!" Wei Chen spoke in a serious tone.

His analysis was correct, but he didn’t give Three Realms a complete picture. The four guild alliance had Ye Qiu and Xiao Shiqin, two Master Tacticians, to deal with Zhang Xinjie. They didn’t need to pull back and shrink into a defensive ball like Zhang Xinjie had needed to do before. The two tacticians were enough to keep Tyrannical Ambition’s troops busy. The alliance also had two powerful attackers, Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng.

Three Realms Six Paths anxiously waited for an opportunity to appear. Wei Chen’s thoughts wandered elsewhere. He was already lusting for his level 70 Death’s Hand. A long-desired wish of his was on the verge of being fulfilled. Wei Chen was starting to get emotional.

"Hurry up and kill the boss!!!"

Wei Chen couldn’t bear it anymore. He took of his headphones and urged Ye Qiu to pick up the pace.

"What are you getting impatient for? It’s just a matter of time." Ye Xiu’s confidence put Wei Chen’s heart at ease. He was still determined to give him a helping hand. He didn’t bother listening to Three Realms Six Path’s observations. He needed to guard against any unexpected occurrences. If there were, he could still remind Ye Xiu, even if it wasn’t convenient for him to stop it from happening.

Wei Chen’s Warlock, Sky Travel, began to turn. Wei Chen was being wary of any surrounding movements.

Blue Brook Guild had arrived quite early, but Tyrannical Ambition had forced them into a submissive state. It seemed like they were beginning to move again.

"Be careful of Blue Brook Guild." Wei Chen immediately warned Ye Xiu.

Right when Wei Chen finished warning Ye Xiu, Blue Brook Guild acted. Blue Brook Guild had suffered fairly heavy losses from Tyrannical Ambition’s previous attacks, but now the dead had revived and they had rallied together. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had once again returned to their troops.

Since they had been waiting and watching the entire time, they clearly still had a plan. Now that everyone was ready and the two sides were in a deadlock, they immediately made their move. Blue Brook Guild could rely on Lu Hanwen as a blade. Lu Hanwen didn’t dare to act rashly anymore. Flowing Cloud carefully followed the troops to meet the enemies. Several support classes accompanied him. As soon as he started moving, countless buffs were placed on him. At this instant, who knew how many times stronger Flowing Cloud had become as he bravely charged forward.

"I’M HERE!!!" Lu Hanwen shouted.

"Blue Brook Guild’s sh*t stick is back." Loulan Slash reported helplessly.

Ye Xiu had listened to Wei Chen’s warning, so he was already paying attention to Blue Brook Guild! When he saw the countless buffs on top of Flowing Cloud, he couldn’t help but smile: "He’s been buffed quite a lot!"

"You keep holding on." Ye Xiu told Xiao Shiqin. He and Su Mucheng turned towards Blue Brook Guild and headed over.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had already slaughtered his way to the front like a general showing off his might. Su Mucheng took aim. A beam of light exploded from Chasing Haze’s cannon. Lu Hanwen reacted quickly. His character flipped over the beam of light, dodging it. The instant Flowing Cloud landed, a spear emanating magic undulations stabbed towards his body, instantly piercing his body.

A dazzling magic explosion erupted. Flowing Cloud was blasted into the air as he yelled: "Who is it!!!"

"The most troublesome one." Ye Xiu grinned.

"F*ck, stop playing around. Hurry up and get rid of Blue Brook Guild." Wei Chen went over and roared. Afterwards, he sat back down, put on his headphones, and said in a serious tone: "Don’t be rash. We have to wait and see whether Blue Brook Guild will give them enough trouble or not! We’re not any weaker than Blue Brook Guild, but what happened when they fought against Tyrannical Ambition?"

"Just one might not be enough, but with Blue Brook Guild and us, that’ll make three. Three guilds together might be enough to force open an opportunity." Three Realms Six Paths wasn’t muddle-headed. His clear-headed thinking worried Wei Chen. He obviously knew that if three guilds fought against the alliance, it was hard to say how the situation might turn out. Why else did he urge Ye Xiu to hurry up and get rid of Blue Brook Guild?

"If three guilds work together, we might able to disrupt the balance, but will we be the ones to benefit?" Wei Chen continued to try and stop Three Realms Six Paths from acting.

"Under normal circumstances, this is still a good opportunity, but with those two Gods fighting it out evenly matched, I feel like if we act too hastily, we’ll only be helping Tyrannical Ambition." Wei Chen slowly said. He wasn’t speaking slowly to show his careful thinking, but to stall for more time.

Three Realms Six Paths didn’t say anything and carefully pondered. Wei Chen hastily racked his brains to search for more excuses. Tricking the person in front of him wouldn’t work. Three Realms Six Paths was the guild leader of a large club. He was probably more experienced in the game and boss hunts than even Wei Chen was. His greatest flaw was experience dealing with Gods, so Wei Chen felt like exaggerating the strength of a God would work.

"Think of before. Why did we fail to get the boss? Because when we broke through their defenses, Tyrannical Ambition shrunk back, intentionally throwing the boss in front of Ye Qiu and us. They wanted us to compete against Ye Qiu. How could we be Ye Qiu’s opponents? These Gods are too crafty. The current situation is still the same. If we join the fray, even if we break apart Ye Qiu’s defenses, Ye Qiu would probably be as crafty as Zhang Xinjie and throw the boss in front of us. I feel like this isn’t an opportunity for us." Wei Chen continued to analyze.

"Then what do you think we should do?" Three Realms Six Paths asked.

"Wait and see the situation more clearly." Wei Chen said solemnly.

"Sigh….." Three Realms Six Paths sighed. Wei Chen wasn’t speaking nonsense. Three Realms Six Paths felt that it was reasonable enough. If they pushed Ye Qiu away, they had to fight against Zhang Xinjie. If they pushed away Zhang Xinjie, they had to fight Ye Qiu. Those two Gods could be half-dead and would still crush them easily.

Wei Chen saw that Three Realms Six Paths couldn’t come to a decision and finally let out a sigh of relief. He immediately checked the situation on Ye Xiu’s screen.

The situation was a carbon copy of the previous one. The only difference was that it was Blue Brook Guild instead of Samsara. Blue Brook Guild may have a powerful expert like Lu Hanwen, but a sharp blade without a good swordsman couldn’t be utilized to its full potential. Against a normal guild, it was a huge advantage, but against Gods like Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie, Lu Hanwen’s blows tickled.

This time, Ye Xiu personally fought him. By coordinating the troops to support him, even the buffed Flowing Cloud could only survive for a few short breaths before dying.

Flowing Cloud’s death dealt a huge blow to Blue Brook Guild’s morale. Their strongest expert kept dying instantly again and again. Not matter who they were up against, their expert just died with a flop. How were they supposed to battle against these Gods?

After fighting messily for awhile, Blue Brook Guild could’t find any opportunities. Their guild leader, Changing Spring was straightforward and simply typed "Retreat." Blue Brook Guild once again withdrew dejectedly.

"See!" Wei Chen saw this scene and immediately started discussing with Three Realms Six Paths: "Blue Brook Guild couldn’t hold on at all. They only started fighting for a bit and had to run away. They’re even worse than us."

"Sigh, it’s completely out of our control." Three Realms Six Paths empathized with Blue Brook Guild.

Ye Xiu didn’t go back to defend after forcing Blue Brook Guild to retreat. He directly led his team to attack Tyrannical Ambition from the side to counterattack in the passing.

Zhang Xinjie reacted quickly and immediately sent troops out to defend. However, as soon as his offense towards Xiao Shiqin weakened, Xiao Shiqin immediately seized the opportunity. He deserved to be reputed for defending before counterattacking. As if an attack had been brewing the entire time, it instantly burst forth. Xiao Shiqin’s change in tactics was as smooth and powerful as a river. He seemed to attack and defend at the same time, flustering Zhang Xinjie. The defense placed on the side failed to be of any use. Ye Xiu didn’t command his troops in this flank, but personally led the way as the main attacker. His Battle Mage tore through their ranks with Su Mucheng’s Launcher freely opened his left and right sides. This familiar scene once again appeared in Zhang Xinjie’s eyes, except it was all happening close to him as if they were in a match.

"You really are too troublesome! I’m going to need to punish you out of battle!" Ye Xiu swiped his mouse and Let There Be Light’s spear stabbed towards Misty Mountains.

Chapter 747: Huge Success

How familiar!　　

Zhang Xinjie thought to himself, as the spear close in on him.

The name Let There Be Light only sounded mighty. In reality, who knew how much of a difference there was in strength between it and One Autumn Leaf. Even so, Zhang Xinjie could see One Autumn Leaf’s style emanating from Let There Be Light, or perhaps that was simply a reflection of the player’s style.

Zhang Xinjie obviously didn’t find Let There Be Light familiar at all. When the spear came, he pushed down with his hand. Misty Mountain immediately rolled away, while calling for his nearby allies to shield him. Zhang Xinjie had no intention of fighting Ye Qiu’s Battle Mage with his Cleric, even if his Cleric had superior equipment compared to Ye Qiu’s Battle Mage.

The nearby Tyrannical Ambition players heard Zhang Xinjie’s call for help and immediately rushed over. They also knew that this Battle Mage was Ye Qiu. How could they dare to be careless? Although they clearly had the advantage in numbers, they were actually mostly on the defensive, but before they could gather together, a Satellite Beam descended from the sky. The pillar of light split into several smaller pillars and began to expand. Satellite Beam was being manually controlled by Su Mucheng to strike these nearby players. Several characters were enveloped by the light. They could barely protect themselves, so how would they have any time to block Ye Xiu?

Ye Xiu seemed to have already known that this would happen. Let There Be Light completely ignored these Tyrannical Ambition players and dashed between them. His Battle Mage thrust his spear towards Misty Mountains once more.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t think the assistance he called for wouldn’t be of any use. It was as if they weren’t even there. Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng hadn’t been secretly practicing right? How else could their synergy still be so perfect? His astonishment wouldn’t help him dodge this strike though. Let There Be Light struck Misty Mountains with a Circle Swing. He then shook his sleeves and sent out a Witch’s Shadow Cloak. Level 20 and below Mage skills could also be learned by Battle Mage. Let There Be Light had clearly added a point to this skill.

Shadow Cloak wasn’t used on Misty Mountains, but rather the several players struck by Satellite Beam. After wrapping them into a bundle, he followed it up with a Falling Flower Palm to sent them all flying away. When he turned back, Zhang Xinjie’s Misty Mountains had just gotten up. Let There Be Light stabbed at him once more.

A normal player definitely wouldn’t be able to dodge this strike, but Zhang Xinjie wasn’t a normal player. Even though he wasn’t using a combat class, how could a pro player not practice dodging basic moves like a simple spear thrust? 　

As the spear approached, Misty Mountains rolled to the side. Zhang Xinjie suddenly heard a bang. Smoke and fire erupted, and Misty Mountains was knocked back.

Su Mucheng! Su Mucheng again! A perfectly timed and coordinated attack rendered Zhang Xinjie’s predictions completely helpless. The Best Pair was a one plus one is greater than two existence. Fighting against the two of them alone was much too difficult.

Misty Mountains was naturally blown back into Let There Be Light’s spear and Ye Xiu’s attack…...

Zhang Xinjie was always skilled enough to survive on his own for awhile. However, he had to split his attention to lead Tyrannical Ambition’s troops, while facing the coordinated attacks from the Best Pair. It was equivalent to sacrificing himself. Zhang Xinjie tried his hardest to survive, while searching for reinforcements, but before anyone could rescue him, Tyrannical Ambition’s frontline collapsed. Xiao Shiqin’s agile counterattack, along with Ye Qiu’s sudden flank completely destroyed Tyrannical Ambition’s push.

Zhang Xinjie’s Misty Mountain hadn’t lost much health....

Zhang Xinjie instantly understood.

Ye Qiu’s attack towards him hadn’t been to kill him, but rather to distract him. Ye Qiu didn’t allow Zhang Xinjie to concentrate on commanding his troops. Instead, Tyrannical Ambition was thrown into disorder while trying to protect their God. And the result? The result was what had just happened. A complete collapse. Zhang Xinjie hadn’t been able to escape from their attacks either. Perhaps he could hurry and switch accounts in order to reorganize his troops.

Zhang Xinjie looked left and right. In Tyrannical Ambition’s game studio, there were several core elite members participating in this battle. Zhang Xinjie could switch places with any of them to break free from his predicament and return to leading his troops.

But would that work?

Zhang Xinjie glanced at their screens. The battlefield had already turned into chaos. They were practically fighting with no strategy and just joined the fray.

Zhang Xinjie sighed. He felt like switching accounts wouldn’t make that much of a difference at this point.

"Look, it’s a good thing that we didn’t join!" Wei Chen joyfully told Samsara’s guild leader, Three Realms Six Paths.

Blue Brook Guild joined and had been forced to retreat.

Shortly afterwards, Tyrannical Ambition was utterly defeated.

This scene seemed as if Samsara not joining was a wise decision, but Three Realms Six Paths kept feeling like something wasn’t right?

What wasn’t right? He couldn’t figure out what though, but the scene in front of him showed that despite having God Zhang Xinjie leading, Tyrannical Ambition’s elite forces were still defeated. It seemed as if there really had been no point in Samsara joining the battle.

Even if they had gone over carrying their pride as the champions, they would only be smearing their own name.

After routing Tyrannical Ambition, the four guild alliance quickly contracted and widened their defensive line. As for Tyrannical Ambition? After being defeated, they reorganized and left without a pause.

There were a few guilds left who tried to break through, not understanding the situation. All of them were met with bleeding heads. In the end, the system announced that Ye Xiu’s four guild alliance had killed Red Mage.

"D*MNIT!!" Wei Chen roared loudly. Samsara’s players quickly consoled him: "Forget about it. We were already expecting this to happen. Were you hoping for some sort of miracle?"

"Wouldn’t it have been nice if the server had suddenly gone down?" Wei Chen hatefully said. Glory’s servers hadn’t gone down for many years now. The game company maintained their servers exceptionally well!

Wei Chen grumbled and complained to Samsara’s players in game. Outside of the game, he was beaming with joy as he walked over to Ye Xiu’s screen. He was anxiously waiting to see what the boss had dropped.

Wild bosses dropped several different kinds of materials, but not all of them would drop. Wei Chen only needed two materials. It was possible that these two materials hadn’t dropped this week.

The boss belonged to Heavenly Justice. As Loulan Slash picked the items up from the ground, the materials were displayed in the group chat. Ye Xiu’s Let There Be Light belonged to this group, so he naturally saw all of the drops.

"Beautiful!!" Wei Chen suddenly shouted. One of the materials needed for Death’s Hand, Heart of Desire, had dropped.

One more!

Wei Chen waited anxiously for it to show up. At the same time, he estimated how many had been picked up and calculated the probability of it happening.

When the words "Loulan Slash picked up Red Mage’s Staff" appeared, Wei Chen suddenly couldn’t utter a word. His body completely relaxed and he slumped into his chair. He was silent for a good while.

Right afterwards, it was time to distribute the goods. Ye Xiu obviously requested these two materials. He looked back at Wei Chen, who wasn’t suspicious at all because he trusted that Ye Xiu wouldn’t fail at this stage.　　

"Are you going to do it now?" Ye Xiu asked Wei Chen.

"In a bit. I’m going to go out for a smoke first." Wei Chen stood up and quietly stepped out of the practice room.

Wei Chen wasn’t usually so well-mannered. He rarely went outside to smoke. With his shamelessness, standing by the window to smoke was already giving Chen Guo face. The current Wei Chen had succeeded at the final step. He had finally fulfilled a long-cherished wish of his.

In these past few years, who knew how many times he had dreamed of Death’s Hand being reaching its level 70 form, becoming the only weapon in the game that could rival a pro player’s Silver weapon.

Reality had been cruel though. Gathering the materials just by relying on his own strength was too difficult. After Ye Xiu had appeared, even the most difficult to obtain materials had been acquired.

What had Ye Xiu relied on? He didn’t have the backing of a strong guild. He mixed in with these guilds and succeeded.

When he reached the final step, Wei Chen suddenly thought of many things.

Why had he clung to this Silver weapon? Could it actually help him in the game? With just his skill alone, he didn’t need a Silver weapon to strut around in the game.

And would he sell this Silver weapon? Probably not.

After thinking about it, this Death’s Hand didn’t seem to mean anything to him, yet he had spent so much effort on it.

Was this love?

Pa!

Wei Chen felt disgusted at his own train of thought.　　

But no matter how disgusted he felt, he couldn’t help but admit that even if this wasn’t love, it comprised of his many years of unwillingness to leave the pro scene. He had funneled all of his unwillingness into this Silver weapon. This was different from creating the skill book guide. That had been done for its monetary value. He had never thought of earning money using his Death’s Hand though. It was a reminder of all the memories he had made during his career.

And he finally succeeded. More importantly, he was going to bring this weapon into the pro scene. At this moment, Wei Chen’s emotions could truly be described as fluctuating up and down. He had thought about his many years of perseverance and his struggle during his two years as a pro player. He thought about the two punks that came to the team at that time and were now Team Blue Rain’s stars.

This, this was all the past now.

What’s most important is that I'm back!

Chapter 748: Information Isn’t Easy to Get

Wei Chen’s mind was still wandering off, when someone knocked on the door to the practice room again. Xiao Shiqin moved fast and quickly walked out the door. Ye Xiu followed behind, while calling out to him: "Why are you in such a hurry to leave? Why not play a bit more?"

"No need. No need." Xiao Shiqin hastily declined, "I’ve got to go back. There’s a bunch of stuff in the team that I’ve still got to take care of. I’ve been out too long already, so it wouldn’t be good to stay any longer."

"It’s the holidays right now. What stuff could you have to do?" Wei Chen immediately interrupted: "Why not play a bit more?"

The expression on Xiao Shiqin’s face looked like a bittermelon: "I just arrived. There’s a lot of stuff in the team I need to understand!"

"Really?" Ye Xiu laughed.

Xiao Shiqin was gloomy! Normally, for his purpose in coming here, their polite request for him to stay longer was an opportunity that most wanted but would never obtain. Pushing the boat with the current by staying longer and observing their team more was usually a good thing, but was that the case now? While others would fight for such an opportunity, Xiao Shiqin braced himself and hastily tried to leave, especially when Ye Xiu laughed: "Really?" It made him feel like he had been completely seen through. He was certain that the other side had guessed his intentions for coming here, but if no one poked a hole through the window. Wouldn’t they have to continue pretending?

However, Xiao Shiqin didn’t feel good faking it. He wanted to hurry up and leave. If he didn’t leave now, another boss would soon spawn; should he help or not help?

Just when things had reached this step, Xiao Shiqin’s cellphone started ringing and vibrating. Xiao Shiqin was overjoyed! He quickly took out his cellphone, and indicated to Ye Xiu and Wei Chen that he needed to pick up the phone. Without saying anything more, he waved his hands wildly to say goodbye and immediately ran out, while asking "Hello hello hello?"

"Are you busy?" The person on the other side of the phone asked.

Xiao Shiqin had just gotten to the stairs and asked back: "Who is this?"

"It’s me. Zhang Xinjie."

Bang bang bang bang bang…...

Xiao Shiqin’s phone rolled down the stairs. Happy Internet Cafe’s stairs were fairly normal. They were built using wooden boards, so when his phone fell, it made a loud sound. In the blink of an eye, it fell to the bottom. The back cover and battery had flown out.

By the time Xiao Shiqin picked up all the scattered cellphone parts, the call had dropped. What else could Zhang Xinjie be calling him for? Of course it was to ask why he was helping Ye Qiu. According to common reasoning, if the two were participating in the Challenger League on different teams, shouldn’t they be opponents?

That wasn’t something easy to explain! Xiao Shiqin was conflicted. He couldn’t just tell Zhang Xinjie that he had shamelessly barged into their practice room to seek out enemy information, right?

During his moment of hesitation, Xiao Shiqin assembled his cellphone back together. The several cracks on his screen made his heart hurt. He tried turning on the cellphone. Luckily, it wasn’t broken. It could still power on. Right when, the cellphone startup screen ended, a call came. The name flashed and flashed. It was Zhang Xinjie again.

"Hello." Xiao Shiqin left the Internet Cafe, while picking up the call.

"What happened?" Zhang Xinjie asked.

"I dropped my cellphone onto the ground." Xiao Shiqin knew that Zhao Xinjie was probably asking about that.

"You were the one commanding Radiant and Parade, right?" The question finally came.

"That was me." Xiao Shiqin said.

"Why did you go that side?" Sure enough, Zhang Xinjie was very suspicious of Xiao Shiqin’s position.

"Sigh. We’ll be meeting in the Challenger League, no? I was trying to figure what their situation was like." In the end, Xiao Shiqin spoke the truth.

"Oh? How is it going on their side?" Zhang Xinjie asked.

"The majority are new players." Xiao Shiqin said. He hadn’t forgotten his purpose in coming there. While he commanded Radiant and Parade, he still gathered quite a bit of information. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were already quite skilled. To players in the game, these two were certainly top experts and not new players.

Indeed, for in-game players, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had already played for half a year. How could they still be considered new players? Games with too steep of a learning curve rarely thrived in the market!

But Xiao Shiqin was looking at them from a pro player’s perspective. From this perspective, playing Glory for seven months was still too short. Xiao Shiqin quickly saw numerous areas of the game that the two weren’t familiar with. Their newness to the game was a bit frightening, even if their mechanics were outstanding.

And that Qiao Yifan, who Tao Xuan had attached much importance to. Xiao Shiqin observed him several times and felt like although his placement of ghost formations were not bad, there was nothing particularly noteworthy. Maybe he wasn’t going all out because he was facing normal players?

Xiao Shiqin had carefully observed each person on Team Happy and these were the conclusions he more or less reached. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were fairly easy. He quickly saw through them. It was Qiao Yifan, who Xiao Shiqin had to repeatedly observe. In the end, he couldn’t make any definite verdicts. When Zhang Xinjie heard Xiao Shiqin say that they were mostly novices, he casually commented: "New players aren’t easy to grasp."

"Mm." Xiao Shiqin agreed. In fact, he didn’t continue staying in Happy’s practice room for this reason. If he could have found any more information on them, he wouldn’t mind helping them snatch another wild boss. But how could one or two wild bosses be any deadly threat to Excellent Era? Xiao Shiqin doubted it.

After observing the three player’s performances, Xiao Shiqin didn’t feel like there was any need to stay.

Xiao Shiqin understood why Zhang Xinjie said that new players were difficult to understand, especially Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. These two were the most difficult kinds of new players to grasp because not only were they new to the pro scene, but new to Glory as well. Such a degree of newness implied having a lot of room to grow. Everyone had different personalities and different levels of talent. Who knew how one would improve after so long. For new players, grasping their present strength was meaningless. It would require long-term shadowing of their growth to truly understand them. As for Qiao Yifan, his foundation in Glory was sturdy. He deserved to be a player from Team Tiny Herb. However, his performance also showed that he had a lot of room to grow or perhaps he was a master displaying a small part of his skill. In any case, Xiao Shiqin wouldn’t be able to get anything more out of him by staying.

"But it looks like Ye Qiu is doing quite well! His team has made you worried enough to personally pay them a visit." Zhang Xinjie said.

"It’s never bad to be careful! After all, he is Ye Qiu." Xiao Shiqin said.

"Yeah..." Zhang Xinjie added. The two then started chatting about other things before hanging up. Zhang Xinjie mainly called to figure out why Xiao Shiqin had been helping Ye Qiu. Once he knew that it was just a temporary alliance, he relaxed. If he needed to face these two Master Tacticians in future confrontations, Zhang Xinjie would need to completely redraw his plans.

After they got the information they wanted, the two hung up. Meanwhile, an atmosphere of nervousness could be felt in Happy’s practice room all, yet Wei Chen wasn’t there.

"Do you think it’ll be successful?" Chen Guo was playing, but her mind wasn’t there. She stared with fixed eyes at her screen, when she suddenly asked Ye Xiu.

"From what we’ve seen, there should be no reason for it to fail." Ye Xiu said.

"What if it fails?"

"Find the reason and fix it." Ye Xiu said.

"Ha ha." Steamed Bun suddenly laughed: "This is something even little kids know. You need that taught to you?"

Chen Guo nearly died from anger, but what could she do? Steamed Bun was right. Fix the mistake. Who didn’t know that?

After a long time, Chen Guo couldn’t sit still. She opened the practice room door and looked out. When she returned, she muttered: "Why isn’t he back yet?"

For the final and most nerve-wracking step, she gave him a private room to prevent anyone from bothering him. Everyone else was still in the practice room. The scene looked as if they were waiting for the news of a baby’s delivery.

Who knew how much time passed. Finally, someone knocked and pushed open the door.

Wei Chen held a cigarette in his mouth, his face completely smug. He didn’t attempt to hide his joy at the success, when he walked in.

For a moment, Chen Guo felt dizzy because she had the hardest time keeping his calm, so she kept overthinking. With her understanding of Wei Chen’s shamelessness, she thought he would certainly feign failure even if it was actually a success, to deliberately play with their emotions.Who would have thought that he would come back smiling. Although his smugness made her want to punch him in the face, Chen Guo couldn’t care about any of that right now.

"A success?" Chen Guo wanted confirmation.

"Hmph. Of course." Wei Chen looked down at everyone’s nervousness in disdain as if it had been an easy task. He seemed to have completely forgotten that he had been the one most nervous just awhile ago.

So this is where his shamelessness comes in! Chen Guo thought in despise. Afterwards, she saw Wei Chen swagger his way over, while puffing puffs of smoke. Chen Guo endured and didn’t say anything. Then, he saw him flick his hands and throw Windward Formation’s Warlock account card onto the table.

"Take a look!" Wei Chen said as if he were the boss.

Endure!!! Chen Guo quietly took the account card. She inserted the card and logged in. Ye Xiu also came over to look.

His character was still in the Arena. Who knew how many times he would bully a normal player after upgrading his weapon. Chen Guo looked back and glared at Wei Chen. She opened up his inventory and hovered over his weapon.

Death’s Hand - Level 70.

Weight: 3kg

Durability: 30

Attack Speed: 2

Physical Attack: 650

Magic Attack: 899

Intelligence +66

Darkness Affinity +30

Darkness Resistance +30

Magic Critical Strike +14%

Magic Cast Speed +14

Cast Range +4

Death’s Door Skill Level +1

All stats had increased. It couldn’t be anymore successful. There was also a +1 to a skill. After researching how to give Silver weapons a skill level up, it was found that all Silver weapons would level up a skill on its final upgrade.

"Death’s Door? How common!" Ye Xiu commented. Death’s Door was a Warlock’s strongest skill, so many would naturally use this precious skill level up for this skill.

Chapter 749: All Inclusive

"Hmph, you don’t understand sh*t!" Wei Chen regarded Ye Xiu’s comment with disdain. Everyone else raised their eyebrows. Calling Ye Xiu, Glory’s Encyclopedia, as not understanding sh*t was truly shameless!

"Powerful skills have long cooldowns and cast times. They have low coverage in a match." Ye Xiu said, using gaming jargon one after the other. Coverage pointed to how many times a skill could be used within a certain time period. Apart from passives and a few continuous actives with high coverage, the vast majority of skills depended on the cooldown, team tactics, and the player’s style. A high level skill like Death’s Door was just as Ye Xiu said. Its long cooldown alone determined its low coverage.

"Tch, coverage? What’s that? Efficiency is what’s important. Death’s Door is always cast to seize an opportunity. Do you know how many benefits an extra skill point into it can bring?" Wei Chen said.

"A real match might not leave you that kind of opportunity." Ye Xiu said.

"Opportunity is created." Wei Chen said.

"Tsk tsk." Ye Xiu turned his head to look at everyone else: "Look, this is a classic example of Team Blue Rain’s style."

Su Mucheng giggled. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were somewhat at a loss. Chen Guo wrinkled her eyebrows. Qiao Yifan was a bit puzzled at first, but he quickly understood.

Correct. This was a classic example of Team Blue Rain’s style. Their team captain, Yu Wenzhou, was skilled at using tactics to create opportunities. Huang Shaotian was skilled at seizing opportunities. And now, Team Blue Rain’s former team captain reflected this style, when adding a skill point bonus to his Silver weapon, pursuing a one hit one kill opportunity.

"Then what do you think a skill point should be added to?" Wei Chen asked.

"Have you ever considered learning a new mage skill? That way, you can create more variations in your play." Ye Xiu said.

"Oh, you mean like Teleport?" Wei Chen said. Teleport was a high level Elementalist skill. Battle Mages, Summoners, and Witches couldn’t learn this skill on their own, but a weapon’s skill point bonus could allow them to learn it. Of course, it could only stay at the lowest level. Teleport was a skill highly favored by mage classes. As a result, it was the first skill Wei Chen thought of. However, how could Wei Chen not have thought of something as commonly done as that? He shook his head in response: "I don’t think that suits me."

"Oh, if that’s the case. You win." Ye Xiu said.

"Bullsh*t. You think senior doesn’t understand?" Wei Chen scowled.

Since Silver equipment was created to fit the player, the player’s playstyle was obviously of the utmost importance. Blending in other people’s thoughts or imitating another weapon would still result in beautiful Silver equipment, but it was hard to say if the player could fully bring out its potential. Wei Chen clearly understood this concept. He didn’t admire this mainstream design and stuck to his own.

But soon afterwards, Wei Chen suddenly froze and let out an astonished expression. He stared at Ye Xiu: "Wait a second. Are you telling me that you can add a skill onto each of your Silver weapon’s transformations?

"Haha, what do you think?"

"F*ck! How stupid! How many transformations does your thing have?" Wei Chen cried out. Even Chen Guo and the others shivered at Wei Chen’s words. If a skill could be added to every transformation, not only could Ye Xiu’s unspecialized use all 120 pre-job advancement skills, but also a few high level skills. Although these high level skills would only be at level one, their might at level one far surpassed the might of low level skills with several points invested. Everyone already knew about the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s characteristic feature and power, but they didn’t know it was still hiding such an Easter egg. It could even let him learn several new skills.

"Before level 50, the umbrella could transform into a shield, a spear, a sword, a tachi, a rifle, a mechanic box, a magic staff, an Eastern-style staff, and a cane --- nine transformations. But after adding new Heavenly Domain materials at level 55, I’m still researching whether a new form can be added." Ye Xiu said.

"So you’re saying that your weapon can level up at least nine skills." Wei Chen said.

"So far."

"That’s... ridiculous..." For a moment, Wei Chen didn’t know what to say. He couldn’t describe his feelings with words. In this instant, he felt like his Death’s Hand was puny. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was all inclusive. What type of person could think of such an idea and actually create it?

"I’ll take my time!" Ye Xiu was quite calm.

"Research it well and have several hundred transformations. Wouldn’t you be able to learn all the skills then? That’s a true all-class unspecialized!" Wei Chen said.

"Are you dreaming?" Ye Xiu obviously regarded it as a joke. At that time, Su Muqiu had put in all his efforts to get the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella to possess nine transformations. His original design comprised six classes, but he was able to add in another three transformations. Additional transformations weren’t just for more skills. Different weapons of the same class had different characteristics. Every weapon had both physical and magic attack stats. For example, Death’s Hand was a staff. It had two hundred more points in magic attack than physical attack. It was clearly suited for mage classes. For Night Walker classes, the mage class would be a Warlock. Warlock skills mainly dealt magic damage, so a staff would obviously be more powerful. If he used dual swords, he could still use Warlock skills, but dual swords emphasized physical damage. His spells would be significantly less effective.

Not only did the many transformations of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella provide new skills, it also increased the strength of certain skills. When dealing physical damage, a physical weapon should be used. When dealing magic damage, a magic weapon should be used. That was Su Muqiu’s original intention for creating more transformations. However, his conditions back then were limited. In the end, he was only able to design three more transformations. Strictly speaking, only the spear and staff represented two Mage weapons with physical or magic emphases. Two of the other forms, the shield and mechanic box, weren’t even weapons.

Nowadays, the Heavenly Domain had more options for materials. Ye Xiu naturally began researching how to complete Su Muqiu’s original aspirations, which had been restricted by his circumstances. The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s evolution was still far from the end!

After taking a look at the completed Level 70 Death’s Hand, Ye Xiu and the others logged out of the game. Wei Chen took back his Windward Formation and began showing off his might in the Arena. When he saw everyone get up, he didn’t understand: "Where are you guys going?"　　

"Sleep. In the future, we’ll start work at night." Ye Xiu said.

Today was the second day of the new week. Zhang Xinjie once again ran to the game early in the morning to hunt bosses. Ye Xiu reckoned that this guy would be doing this the entire summer. He called out to Loulan Slash and the other guild leaders. They would start employing the time difference strategy. Those in the troops, who could freely arrange their time, went to sleep. They would start work once Zhang Xinjie went to bed at night. They would be able to avoid Zhang Xinjie for at least eight hours in this way.

"It’ll be two months at most. Sorry for troubling everyone!" Ye Xiu said.

"I’ve decided! I’ll be spending my vacation at Happy!" Su Mucheng declared.

"Great, great! Welcome, welcome." Chen Guo approved. She didn’t give Ye Xiu any time to say anything and welcomed her cordially.

At this moment, Zhang Xinjie was also reorganizing. Tyrannical Ambition had good results yesterday, but they suffered defeats one after the other today. The previous battle in particular frightened everyone. All Star players kept popping up. Fortunately, he confirmed with Xiao Shiqin that it was just by chance. In the end, for group battles, people like Xiao Shiqin worried Zhang Xinjie the most.

With knowledge that Xiao Shiqin wouldn’t appear again, Zhang Xinjie felt much more at ease. He didn’t need to do anything to placate the guild members. Failing to snatch the boss two times in a row was a common occurrence for any guild. It wouldn’t injure their morale in any way.

They were actually the ones concerned about vice captain Zhang!

A few of them had seen Zhang Xinjie make a phone call and noticed his calm expression return. They were secretly guessing if he was calling someone from the team to come over. That wasn’t the case though. After news of another boss spawning came, Zhang Xinjie gathered everyone together and set out like usual. He didn’t introduce any new person or plan.

However, this time, the boss hunt went smoothly. Zhang Xinjie’s most troublesome opponent, Ye Qiu and the four guild alliance, never appeared. It made Zhang Xinjie feel like there might some sort of hidden scheme being plotted, so he kept his vigilance up. However, Ye Qiu never came. Soon afterwards, he received a notification from the guild, reporting that most of Ye Qiu’s forces weren’t online, including the four guild leaders.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t understand at first, up until night came. Right when Zhang Xinjie was about to go to bed, reports came about movements from the four guild alliance. Zhang Xinjie stared blankly for a bit, but immediately felt at ease. The other side was putting knowledge of his private habits to use! Only someone like Ye Qiu, who understood Zhang Xinjie well, could accomplish it. Normal players might not be able to utilize such a method.

After clearing up the other side’s plans, Zhang Xinjie dismissed it with a laugh. He would rest, when he needed to rest, and log off, when he need to log off. He quite liked Ye Qiu’s plan. Ye Qiu found him troublesome and wanted to avoid him. He wanted to avoid Ye Qiu if possible too. The other side took the initiative to avoid him. Zhang Xinjie wasn’t going to chase after Ye Qiu and compete. There was only so much time in one day. Both needed to rest. A time difference was quite nice.

Chapter 750: For the Championships

When it was about time for Zhang Xinjie to go to bed, Ye Xiu and the others logged on. As a result, they ruled over the boss hunting that night. Their troops had never had such bountiful harvests from wild bosses before. Now they finally had a sweet taste of it. Thee alliance was currently in its honeymoon period. Everyone was in high spirits. Moreover, their day to day schedules being reversed would only last two months at most, so many were quite willing to adjust their biological clocks.

They would fight for the boss, when a boss appeared. If there was no boss, everyone was free to do whatever they wished to do. By the time the sun came up, a total of four bosses had spawned and all of them were won by the four guild alliance. Everyone split the materials joyfully and felt unwilling, when dawn broke.

"Let’s stay for a bit longer. In any case, that guy hasn’t come on yet. We can leave, when he appears." Loulan Slash said.

"I agree."

"Me too."

"Same."

The other three guild leaders expressed their approval. Ye Xiu saw their indomitable will, he could only nod his head and stop once Zhang Xinjie came on. In any case, he also knew how Zhang Xinjie lived like a robot. He went to bed at the exact same time every night and woke up at the exact same time every morning. When he would log on today would be the exact same time as when he logged on yesterday. Right now was still fine. It would be best if a boss would spawn just before he logged on.

"The boss spawns first. Zhang Xinjie spawns second. The boss spawns first. Zhang Xinjie spawns second."

Quite a few muttered these words repeatedly. It was hard to know whether to laugh or cry in response to their prayers. To their surprise, noon came and Zhang Xinjie had yet to appear.

After staying up all night, everyone was getting tired. But Zhang Xinjie still hadn’t spawned yet, so they weren’t willing to leave just yet. Ye Xiu felt that it was a bit strange. Why wasn’t he coming? Could he have seen through their intentions and wanted to deliberately give them trouble?

It didn’t seem like it.

Ye Xiu shook his head. This wasn’t Zhang Xinjie’s style. Perhaps he had some other business to take care of today? Or maybe today was his designated break day?

The first person to find out the truth was unexpectedly Chen Guo. Not in the game, but outside the game. Chen Guo had been browsing the Internet out of boredom and discovered a piece of news. Tyranny was holding a press conference right now to welcome a new player: Lin Jingyan.

"Lin Jingyan has gone to Tyranny!" Chen Guo was looking at the headlines on the official website for Glory news. She opened up the stream for Tyranny’s press conference. Therefore, this information wasn’t merely rumors. When she saw the news, she immediately told everyone.

"Lin Jingyan?" Ye Xiu and Wei Chen were surprised. Lin Jingyan was a rare pro player, who was still in the scene, yet had played against the both of them before.

Lin Jingyan joined the Glory Alliance in season two. He wasn’t like the Gods, who had become famous starting from their rookie years. Lin Jingyan was a player, who slowly made a name for himself step by step, until he became considered as Glory’s number one Brawler.

That was just the class he played though. Lin Jingyan himself was a meek person. He was always very polite towards anyone he met.

Unfortunately, nothing could stop the onslaught of age. As his condition fell, Lin Jinyan’s reputation as the number one Brawler was constantly challenged until this season, when the rising star from Team Hundred Blossoms, Tang Hao, challenged him at All Stars.

Lin Jingyan lost that match.

It was that battle, which lost him the title as the number one Brawler, even if he still held the strongest Brawler character, Three Hits. People were already discussing how Tang Hao would rise if Three Hits fell into his hands.

Rumors of Team Hundred Blossoms buying Three Hits never stopped. It was quite disrespectful to the person, who currently used the character. The competitive scene was merciless though. People wished to enjoy a new star than empathize with the departure of an old general.

When the playoffs came, Lin Jingyan’s days only became worse.

Team Wind Howl failed to enter the playoffs. As the team captain and ace player, Lin Jingyan couldn’t escape the blame. Team Wind Howl wasn’t a weak team. They had two All Star players and All Star characters as well as this season’s Best Rookie, Zhao Yuzhe. The other players on the team weren’t weak either. Their final results didn’t match up with their strength on paper.

Scorching mock and ridicule assaulted him, many of which were from Team Wind Howl’s fans. Even the fans felt like their team captain had held the team back. The more rational fans hoped Lin Jingyan would abdicate from his position and continue contributing to the team with his status as an old general. The more extreme fans described him as a malignant tumor. They vilified him wantonly through all sorts of means, telling him to beat it.

Lin Jingyan was put in a difficult position.

He didn’t want to leave. He felt like he could still fight on. He had played competitively for seven years, yet he had never been in a single finals. Although there were many other players like this, others were others. Lin Jingyan truly wasn’t willing.

Abdicate his position and continue persevering, not even part of the main roster? Lin Jingyan wasn’t unwilling. He only felt that it was a pity that the Club didn’t seem to have any intentions of doing so.

Whether it was in the Club or outside of the Club, the Club never gave a clear response towards his stance.

They neither supported nor opposed it.

Lin Jingyan had been in the competitive scene for seven years. He obviously knew what the Club was hinting at.

If the Club supported him, the Club would have announced their support a long time ago. Not saying anything didn’t mean the Club was still pondering over what to do or hesitating on the decision. In reality, the Club had already come to a decision. They just didn’t want to make things too hard on him. Lin Jingyan expressed his devotion to the team. If the Club coldly rejected him, it would hurt him and their fans.

The Club answered with silence to tactfully tell Lin Jingyan not to make any statements that would leave both sides in an awkward position.

Helpless, Lin Jingyan could only stay silent. It wasn’t a tactical decision. He just didn’t know what he could say. Retire? Or perhaps find a random small team to join?

Lin Jingyan had plenty of invitations, but his wish to continue fighting still held strong! He didn’t want to join those middle tier teams, who were there to read books to the princes. If that was the case, he would rather join a weak team, which needed to struggle to avoid relegations. He would at least have a clear-cut goal.

However, this was just a thought. Lin Jingyan truly didn’t want to have this type of goal. Or perhaps at this point, retiring was the best option.

Lin Jingyan was just about to make this decision, when an unexpected call threw his decision out the window.

"Come to our team! There’s a spot for you."

It was a very surprising invitation for Lin Jingyan.

Han Wenqing! Team Tyranny!

Lin Jingyan would have never expected that a top team would invite a declining player like him.

In Team Wind Howl, their goal was to join the playoffs and perhaps even win a match or two in the playoffs. But Team Tyranny? They were the Glory season four champions and a team, who always aimed to be the champions. Their team captain and ace player was also declining due to age, but their team’s goal had never changed.

This was a team, which never stepped backwards. If they wanted Lin Jingyan to come over, Lin Jingyan was certain that the team needed him for a good reason and not just to save him from a fire. After barely a minute since Han Wenqing had talked to him, Lin Jingyan had already come to a decision. He called Han Wenqing and stated: "I’ve decided to join Tyranny."

Team Wind Howl didn’t stop Lin Jingyan from leaving. They gave the go-ahead towards Tyranny’s quoted price. In the end, the All Star player and former number one Brawler, Lin Jingyan, was transferred to Team Tyranny for 1,000,000 RMB. If this was during his golden days, it would be completely unimaginable.

Team Wind Howl prepared a grand send-off ceremony for their old general, thanking him for his many years of contribution. The meek Lin Jingyan couldn’t bear any grudges towards his Club abandoning him. After shaking the hands of every one of the Club staff, the pro player, who had almost retired, once again set foot onto a path towards the championships. He took this step excitedly.

At Tyranny’s press conference, Lin Jingyan explicitly stated how he wasn’t there to live a nice retirement life at Tyranny. He was certain that he would be making a contribution to the team. When the team needed him, he would be ready to go to battle at any moment.

His words were quite tactful. Lin Jingyan implied: he didn’t care about his status in Team Tyranny. He was fine even as a substitute player. After all, with his status, it was easy to think of him as being a part of the main roster. Quite a few had already started to spread rumors just after the announcement. Many didn’t look highly upon Tyranny’s trade. They thought that a pro player like Lin Jingyan, who was at the end of his career, might argue about his position in the team and his opportunities to go on stage. If the team didn’t handle his requests well, there could be quite some conflict in the team. Lin Jingyan’s statement was naturally aimed towards these doubts.

Lin Jingyan wanted to dispel these suspicions, yet who would have thought that Tyranny would be the ones who countered his statement. Team Tyranny’s Han Wenqin gave a clear statement to the media: "Lin Jingyan will be an important part of Team Tyranny next season. The Club is currently creating a Brawler, just for him. Inviting Lin Jingyan to our team is only for one reason: for the championships."

His words held a completely different meaning compared to Lin Jingyan’s words. Lin Jingyan didn't mind though. Creating a character specifically for him as well as the team inviting him showed how much Tyranny valued him. Lin Jingyan’s uneasiness towards his acceptance of the invitation was now completely eliminated. From now on, he would be a part of Team Tyranny. Here, not just entering the playoffs, but he might even have a chance to be a champion!

Chapter 751: New Soldier Lin Jingyan

News of Lin Jingyan joining Team Tyranny didn’t explode like when Xiao Shiqin joined Team Excellent Era, but it still received widespread attention. After all, he was also an All Star player. Despite not doing well recently, his departure from the scene would still newsworthy. What’s more, Lin Jingyan’s transfer could hardly be considered a departure form the scene. Han Wenqin’s powerful and resonating statement at the press conference sparked the originally moderate amount of attention.

After the press conference, all sorts of discussions poured out. Just like before, some didn’t think highly of the transfer. Some felt like Team Tyranny must have some sort of plan in mind. Others surmised how the addition of Lin Jingyan would change Team Tyranny. After all, Team Tyranny didn’t have a Brawler right now. A change in classes meant a change in tactics.

After Ye Xiu and the others heard Chen Guo’s shout, they opened up their browser and searched for the newest information. Now they understood why Zhang Xinjie hadn’t appeared today.

With the arrival of a new member, the Club would usually host a welcoming party of some sort. Han Wenqing’s "creating a Brawler, just for him" very easily explained why Zhang Xinjie was busy in the game these past two days. He was most likely gathering materials for Lin Jingyan’s equipment.

"What are your thoughts on this transfer?" Wei Chen suddenly asked Ye Xiu.

"Very troublesome." Ye Xiu furrowed his eyebrows.

"Troublesome?" Wei Chen was surprised, "This has nothing to do with us for now, no? Could you already be thinking of what future opponents we might face?"

"You’re thinking too much. They’re already a competitor." Ye Xiu said.

"Already?"

"Zhang Xinjie is personally leading Tyranny’s troops to gather materials, most likely for Lin Jingyan’s Brawler. Lin Jingyan has also come. Do you think he’s the type of person, who would just watch while Zhang Xinjie worked hard to gather materials for him?" Ye Xiu said.

Not just Wei Chen, but everyone understood now.

Tyrannical Ambition with just Zhang Xinjie was troublesome enough already, but now an expert like Lin Jingyan would be joining too. It didn’t matter if his condition was deteriorating. With his experience and knowledge as an old general, his value in boss hunts far surpassed rookies like Zhao Yuzhe or Lu Hanwen.

"Does Lin Jingyan also have a strict sleep schedule?" Chen Guo hastily asked. They were using a time difference to avoid a conflict with Zhang Xinjie for the majority of the day, but if Lin Jingyan didn’t have that type of sleep schedule, he and Zhang Xinjie could rotate day and night shifts. They would be in a thorny situation then.

Even though Chen Guo asked this question, she didn’t think it was very likely. Zhang Xinjie’s work and rest schedule wasn’t the main reason for playing the time difference game. The main reason was Zhang Xinjie’s strict personality. For normal people like the individuals in Team Happy, completely changing their work and rest schedule for a boss was perfectly fine. If they could do that, how could Lin Jingyan not? Team Tyranny showed a great amount of respect for Lin Jingyan. It was time for him to return the favor.

Sure enough, Ye Xiu shook his head in response to Chen Guo’s question: "What’s the point?" A change in their sleep schedule only worked on Zhang Xinjie.

"It seems like we can only do things one step at a time." Wei Chen sighed.

Club Tyranny.

After the press conference, they held a welcome ceremony for Lin Jingyan. Captain Han Wenqing and vice captain Zhang Xinjie gave him a tour around the Club and then went to the equipment development department to show Lin Jingyan his new Brawler.

The character’s name was Dark Thunder, 4840 skill points and five Silver equipment. Lin Jingyan glanced at the stats of these Silver equipment and felt very satisfied. The missing equipment all had complete plans in place. The manager of the equipment development department personally explained these plans to Lin Jingyan.

This was another show of respect towards Lin Jingyan. After all, in front of the media, it was hard to say if their words were just for the public to hear. Lin Jingyan understood this logic well. Team Tyranny was afraid that he might think of this reasoning and still hold a few doubts. As a result, they intentionally made arrangements to put him at ease.

However, it seemed like the Club was thinking too much. When Lin Jingyan saw the Brawler created for him, he didn’t feel any weight come off of his mind. Instead, he checked if the Silver equipment suited him and then started discussing the future pieces of Silver equipment with the manager. No one had more of a right to speak about Brawlers than him. He was quickly engrossed with the character in order to improve the character’s strength and contribute what he could to the team.

Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie listened on the side. They looked each other in the eye, but didn’t interrupt and quietly left. The two knew that their arrangements to introduce the new environment and other team members to Lin Jingyan wouldn’t be necessary. An experienced player like Lin Jingyan would quickly adapt to a new environment, sparing them of much worry.

Lin Jingyan forgot about the time as he talked with the manager. After chatting for half an hour, he suddenly thought of Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie. When the looked around, the two were already gone. Just as he was puzzled, the manager took out some new material and pulled Lin Jingyan over for a discussion. Tyranny’s equipment development manager, Yang Chi, was a fanatic. He was the type of person, who didn’t the meaning of rest, when he started working. After chatting with Lin Jingyan for half an hour, he suddenly had flashes of insight in many areas. Lin Jingyan deserved to be called the number one Brawler. How could he let Lin Jingyan leave!

Lin Jingyan thought again. Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie left with saying goodbye to not bother him. They wanted him to get a better understanding of his equipment, so he happily accepted. Lin Jingyan just joined Tyranny and he was already working with the equipment development department.

In truth, this showed Club Tyranny’s boldness. In a more stingy Club, the equipment development department might hide their work. They might not even let their own players understand their equipment too in depth. After all, players weren’t permanent. One day, a player might leave to a different team or retire. What would happen if this player leaked out information? Even if a non-disclosure agreement was signed, it wasn’t a guarantee.

Lin Jingyan was already making himself busy. He wasn’t paying attention to any of the discussion about his transfer nor was he thinking about how his transfer might be a concern to Ye Xiu and the others in Team Happy.

Ye Xiu and the others hadn’t slept last night. It was already noon now and they were getting tired. Everyone carried a let’s worry about it later attitude and didn’t continue persevering. They all went to sleep.

At night, they woke up according to Zhang Xinjie’s sleep schedule. They called over Loulan Slash and the others to figure out what had happened, while they were asleep.

When they asked, they found out that Zhang Xinjie was back again in the afternoon.

"Did you see any particularly eye-catching Brawler?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That... we didn’t notice! Are you worried about Lin Jingyan joining?" The guild leaders responded quite well.

"Yeah! He just joined a new team and Tyranny said they were creating a character just for him. Zhang Xinjie’s recent activities might be related. Lin Jingyan might help out." Ye Xiu said.

"I’ll have my people pay more attention." Loulan Slash immediately said. The other three guild leaders had the same attitude. However, everyone’s mood turned heavy, when they thought of the possibility of another formidable opponent joining. Their boss hunting had so many ups and downs! They had never experienced anything like this before. However, suffering defeat battle after battle was something they could still endure.

That night, Ye Xiu thought of many things.　

When the first wild boss spawned that night, their troops quickly gathered together and they met with Tyrannical Ambition. Zhang Xinjie wouldn’t appear at this time, but what about Lin Jingyan?

Ye Xiu paid attention to any Brawlers in Tyrannical Ambition. He and Su Mucheng as well as other elite players clashed with Tyrannical Ambition’s elite troops. In the end, Tyrannical Ambition was thrown into chaos. Ye Xiu was now certain that Lin Jingyan wasn’t there. If not, with his skill level, despite not being a Master Tactician, his tactics wouldn’t be at a normal player’s level!

In the end, no Lin Jingyan appeared, but they had an unexpected harvest.

Deception!

That little punk suddenly appeared on the battlefield, clearly back at scrap picking. Ye Xiu saw him. How could he let him go free? He let go of everything at hand and led his elite troops to kill him. How skilled could Deception be? He couldn’t escape from an encirclement specifically designed for him. When he died, Ye Xiu suddenly thought of something: "Did I forget to tell him who I was?"

Everyone witnessed his death and had no idea what Deception had done to offend Ye Qiu.

"It’s fine. If we kill him a few more times, he’ll find out who I am sooner or later." Ye Xiu said in the end. Everyone continued to give a moment of silence for the dead Deception.

Lin Jingyan didn’t appear that night. Unfortunately, they encountered fewer bosses too. Only a single boss spawned that night, which made the all nighters feel like it wasn’t worth it. But what could they do? Boss spawns were completely random. At least they got the one boss. The other guilds, who stayed up all night, lost experience and equipment. Now that was not worth it!　　

The sun came up. After receiving notifications of Misty Mountains coming online, everyone immediately logged off to rest. They couldn’t completely avoid Zhang Xinjie, but when they did, they would at least be able to face off against a tired Zhang Xinjie, while they were still full of energy. Right now, everyone was tired from staying up all night. How could they fight against Zhang Xinjie, who just woke up from a full night’s rest?

The morning would be given to Zhang Xinjie! That was a tactic as well.

Chapter 752: Record Breaking Transfer

July 4th. Day four of the summer transfer window.

The members of Team Happy gathered together in the practice room, greeted each other, and logged in to the game. Many of them were thinking about how many bosses had spawned, while they had been asleep.

They had gone to bed fairly early today, so it was still the afternoon, when they woke up. Zhang Xinjie should still be playing. Even though they reversed their sleep schedules to dodge Zhang Xinjie for a good portion of time, it was still hard to completely avoid him. However, Ye Xiu’s side was full of energy right now, while Zhang Xinjie was tired. It would be much easier to deal with Zhang Xinjie at night compared to the morning, when their circumstances were reversed.

While the others were logging into the game, Chen Guo was casually browsing the Glory website. She saw that yesterday’s headline piece of Lin Jingyan transferring to Tyranny had already been removed. Another transfer had replaced it.

Team Hundred Blossom’s All Star player, Tang Hao, has been transferred to Team Wind Howl for a price of 10,000,000!

Club Wind Howl convened a press conference at noon. It had already ended at this time. Discussion over this transfer littered the various Glory news sites. This transfer was simply too astonishing.

10,000,000 yuan was the most expensive transfer in the history of competitive Glory as well as the first trade to reach a price of ten million yuan. Of course, the outside world didn’t know about Samsara’s 20,000,000 yuan deal with Ye Xiu for his skill book guide.

Moreover, this transfer was interconnected with Lin Jingyan’s transfer yesterday. It was a distinction between a new generation and an old generation Brawler expert. At the All Stars Rookie Challenge, the junior succeeded the senior. When Tang Hao defeated Lin Jingyan, many rumors started to spread about how Team Hundred Blossoms would purchase Three Hits for Tang Hao. However, it now appeared that Tang Hao instead sought out Team Wind Howl.

The moment Lin Jingyan transferred out of Team Wind Howl, Tang Hao transferred in. A transfer between ace players wasn’t a decision that could be made in a single day. As a result, most believed that Team Wind Howl had been planning to have Tang Hao succeed Lin Jingyan long ago. Lin Jingyan just happened to transfer out of the team before Tang Hao joined, saving the team from any awkwardness in Lin Jingyan’s succession. At the same time, Team Wind Howl exposed their ferociousness in this transfer.

Team Tyranny took in the old general, Lin Jingyan. It seemed as if Team Tyranny was offering him shelter. On the other hand, Team Wind Howl bought Tang Hao, an uprising star, for a record-breaking ten million yuan. It gave off a more valiant sense of determination and courage towards the team’s goal to be champions. At this moment, the fans to the officials of Team Wind Howl felt incredibly excited. Up until now, Team Wind Howl had never entered the finals, yet with a single leap, countless eyes now saw them as a new competitor for the championships.

The powerful Tang Hao, the master of playing dirty Fang Rui, the Best Rookie Zhao Yuzhe along with their other teammates, who weren’t lacking either, Team Wind Howl’s future looked very bright.

On the other hand, Team Hundred Blossoms let go of the only core member, who could be relied upon. At first glance, it seemed inconceivable why they would make the trade. However, from a practical point, this trade was more reliable than them purchasing Three Hits.

Every team had their own style, the majority of which was constructed around their core player. The core player could not be without a core character. As a result, every team’s style frequently revolved around both the core player’s style as well as the core character’s class. Team Hundred Blossoms revolved around their Spitfire. As a result, they were very skilled at Spitfire tactics. On the other hand, Team Wind Howl played around their Brawler.

If Team Hundred Blossoms bought Three Hits and constructed their team around Tang Hao, their familiar style would need to be completely changed. Last season, Team Hundred Blossoms had pretty much changed their style because of Tang Hao’s outstanding performance and the mediocreness of their Spitfite player, Zou Yuan. Their achievements weren’t satisfactory though. Tang Hao’s Brawler character, Delilo, wasn’t particularly good. It was still at a pro level though, so it wouldn’t be too bad. With a skilled player like Tang Hao controlling it, Team Hundred Blossoms naturally put in effort to upgrade this character. The reason for their poor performance wasn’t because of their lacking strength, but the team’s unfamiliarity with new tactics.

In the next season, even if Team Hundred Blossoms purchased Three Hits for Tang Hao, would the team be able to welcome the coming of a new spring? Team Hundred Blossoms clearly didn’t think so, so they let go of Tang Hao. As for Team Wind Howl? A Brawler had always been their core. With the strongest Brawler character in their possession, the best Brawler player would naturally be extremely valuable. Under these conditions, Tang Hao was successfully transferred over for a record-breaking price.

Team Wind Howl got what they wanted, but what about Team Hundred Blossoms? After getting this sum of money, they would have enough to look for an outstanding Spitfire to replace their mediocre Zou Yuan. As a result, it was a win-win situation for both sides.

Chen Guo was wondering: "Why is Tang Hao going to Wind Howl? Wasn’t Hundred Blossoms supposed to buy Three Hits?", when Ye Xiu commented: "A beautiful transfer." Most of the analyses on the transfer gave the same comment as Ye Xiu. The reasoning behind why Team Wind Howl and Team Hundred Blossoms would make this deal was very obvious and logical. It made a lot more sense than Team Tyranny purchasing an old soldier like Lin Jingyan and claiming that it was "to be the champions".

From this record-breaking deal onwards, the summer transfer window swung open. There were three other small transfers that day. However, these transfers were between middle or lower tier teams. The purchases or trades weren’t for anyone valuable, so none of them got as much attention as Tang Hao’s transfer.

After Team Happy discussed about the transfer, they logged into the game. Loulan Slash and the other three guild leaders came on too. They first exchanged information, checking to see which bosses had spawned during the daytime.

Four wild bosses had spawned in the morning and afternoon. It was an average amount. Their prayers weren’t met though. Zhang Xinjie was still on. Everyone gave a sigh. The four guild leaders readied their troops. While the guild leaders weren’t there, the guild members wouldn’t bother with the bosses. They either went to rest or had fun.

It was about time for Zhang Xinjie to rest, but the two sides would certainly meet beforehand. However, the alliance wasn’t too afraid. Tyrannical Ambition had slightly stronger troops, but it only made it so that their chances at getting the boss was somewhat higher. Even with a God in command, no side had a hundred percent chance at getting the boss. Sometimes, another guild might take it.

Not long after they logged on, the two sides encountered each other.

The alliance wasn’t able to win any easy advantages though.

This time, Tyrannical Ambition split their troops along two paths. While one path defended, the other path made a flank. Ye Xiu led the elite troops to try and directly smash the flank. His Battle Mage Let There Be Light led the charge like a great general, when a mysterious black brick suddenly flew at him, interrupting his charge.

"Who’s randomly throwing bricks?" Ye Xiu shouted. Let There Be Light looked around, but didn’t see anyone. At this moment, he suddenly guessed who it might be. Lin Jingyan! There was an eighty percent chance it was him. He didn’t rotate shifts with Zhang Xinjie and instead fought alongside him.

Brawlers could be played in a variety of ways They could be aggressive and they could play dirty. Lin Jingyan could play them all. His condition wasn’t the same as before. His reaction speed and hand speed was on the decline, but his experience and knowledge was great. Right now, it was a large-scale battle. Relying on the cover of many, even Ye Xiu couldn’t tell where this brick had been thrown from. This Brawler’s skill level couldn’t be ordinary.

Let There Be Light’s momentum was broken. Tyrannical Ambition’s troops immediately rushed over. Lin Jingyan wasn’t only attacking with his character, but also commanding his troops to seize the correct opportunities.

But Ye Xiu’s group of elites wasn’t so easy to deal with. All of them surpassed a normal player’s skill level. Against the assault, they could rely on their overwhelming skill to endure!

"Oh, he really is troublesome." Lin Jingyan’s Brawler was currently in the middle of his troops. He watched over the state of the battle as he messaged Zhang Xinjie.

"Yes." Zhang Xinjie had clearly introduced to Lin Jingyan who he might end up facing or else Lin Jingyan wouldn’t have responded with just a sigh.

"Su Mucheng is also here." Lin Jingyan saw Let There Be Light coordinate exceptionally well with a Launcher.

"Mm, every member in that small group of elites is very formidable. Fighting them head-on won’t work. The best way is still to make use of our stronger troops to restrict their small group of elites and nibble away at the rest of their troops." Zhang Xinjie said.

"Mm, that should be the way to do it." Lin Jingyan replied, but before he could finish typing, his many years of experience instinctively let him know that there was something coming at him from behind. He immediately had his character dodge and saw a Brick whistle past him.

This brick gave Lin Jingyan a fright. Where did this brick come from? Lin Jingyan turned to look around and saw a very domineering Brawler punch and kick his way over.

What the heck? Did that Brick just happen to fly over here? Lin Jingyan thought the brick was aimed at him, but from the looks of it, the Brawler was fighting with other people. He didn’t even seem to notice him!

Under normal circumstances, Lin Jingyan would have definitely taken time to observe this Brawler. However, today, he remembered that his main task was to command the troops and use the troop’s strength to obtain the boss.

Chapter 753: Try Hard and Struggle

"Old Lin, you’re not going to come out and practice?"

Lin Jingyan could hear Ye Qiu calling out his name. In terms of age, Lin Jingyan was actually even older than Ye Xiu. However, in terms of experience with Glory, Lin Jingyan would be considered his junior. This wasn’t anything strange. A pro player who joined the Alliance earlier could be younger than a pro player who joined later.

Ye Qiu’s Let There Be Light was turning in circles, clearly trying to search for his whereabouts. Lin Jingyan was neither Lu Hanwen nor Zhao Yuzhe. He ignored Ye Qiu’s challenge. Ye Qiu had Su Mucheng and a bunch of other extraordinarily skilled experts on his side. Leaping out to meet the challenge was simply suicide. In terms of individual strength, Lin Jingyan’s side was weaker. But in terms of overall strength, Tyrannical Ambition was stronger. Restrain the few outstanding individuals and utilize their greater overall strength to win. Zhang Xinjie’s strategy was very logical. Lin Jingyan wouldn’t run out and duel anyone. This wasn’t a pro match anyways.

After playing alongside a master at playing dirty for several years, Lin Jingyan couldn’t help but pick up some of his teammate’s strengths. At this moment, his Brawler played exceptionally dirty. He threw a brick to the left and a gas can to the right. He never threw a projectile from the front, allowing him to restrain his side’s opponents as much as possible, while bringing out their troop’s greater overall strength.

Ye Xiu continued to lead his team in battle. He clearly understood that Lin Jingyan was much more difficult to deal with in a large-scale battle than Zhao Yuzhe or Lu Hanwen. It seemed like today was revenge for allying with Xiao Shiqin to bully Zhang Xinjie. Two veterans had joined together to clash against him. Already possessing superior troops, these two veterans steadily controlled the situation. Even though Ye Xiu’s side hadn’t yet retreated in defeat, in this stalemate, Tyrannical Ambition had already gained enough time. A system announcement soon followed. The wild boss had fallen. Tyrannical Ambition had killed the boss.

Ye Xiu still hadn’t pinpointed Lin Jinyan yet. Lin Jingyan didn’t take the initiative to greet him either. After taking down the boss, he disappeared silently along with Tyrannical Ambition.

It was a very oppressive battle. Everyone was feeling a bit sullen. This battle made them feel powerless. If the two sides clashed in a head-on fight, Ye Xiu’s side might even have a slight upper hand, but what did that matter? Their goal was the boss. Now that Tyrannical Ambition had killed the boss, the four guild alliance was only left with injuries and casualties. This battle could be considered as an overwhelming victory by Tyrannical Ambition.

With Lin Jingyan now helping Zhang Xinjie, Tyrannical Ambition took down the next two bosses as well. Afterwards, it was about time for Zhang Xinjie to go to bed. Would Lin Jingyan stay? No one knew the answer because Ye Xiu still didn’t know which character Lin Jingyan was playing on. Lin Jingyan didn’t use a character with powerful equipment. He simply used a very ordinary Brawler character from Tyrannical Ambition. After playing together with the master at playing dirty, not only did Lin Jingyan pick up how to play dirty, even his decision-making had been affected.

Ye Xiu was only able to confirm that Lin Jingyan was not online when the next boss spawned.

In the end, Ye Xiu’s side took this boss. When they split the drops, Ye Xiu also gave them some good news and some bad news.

"The good news is that it looks like Liln Jingyan won’t be staying up all night to continue competing with us."

"The bad news is that it looks like both Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan will be teaming up to contend against us. Beating Tyrannical Ambition will be more difficult now. I’m sure you guys already know what I’m talking about from the previous three boss fights, right?"

"Then what do we do?" Loulan Slash asked.

Ye Xiu called out the other three guild leaders, Yue Ziqin, White Stream, and Martial Awareness: "I say why aren’t there any pro players from your teams helping us out?"

The three guild leaders refuted in unison: "That isn’t something we can do anything about!"

Indeed. No pro player had a clause in their contract, requiring them to work in a situation like this. Let alone the guild leader, even the Club had no grounds to order their pro players to help the guild. It was either the pro player helped out on his own volition or someone like the guild leader played the sympathy card to ask for help.

Asking someone to help for one or two battles was doable, but asking someone to put in all of his time and effort, working from morning to night, like Zhang Xinjie wasn’t. And with the current pro scene’s common practices, very few were willing to contribute. What’s more, it was currently the summer transfer window for pro players. The season hadn’t started yet. If they laboured away their summer, obtaining materials and strengthening the team, what if they were traded away to another team? Didn’t that just mean they worked all summer for nothing?

The Alliance’s original common practices disappeared as the Alliance rapidly developed. Back then, many pro players would contend against each other in the game during the summer. That custom would probably never appear again.

It seemed as if Ye Xiu pointed out those three guild leaders to complain about their pro players not working hard, but he was also complaining about how the entire Alliance had changed. Everyone had become more practical, whether it was the teams or the player. The emotional attachment felt by Ye Xiu and other old players towards their original teams was difficult to find in a rookie nowadays. Sun Xiang and Tang Hao, these two recent outstanding rookies, changed teams after just a year or two since their rise. They left their original team to a team with more potential just like that.

It wasn’t just the players changing. It was the entire scene. Clubs, teams, and players were just a part of the picture.

Ye Xiu thought about the past. In the beginning, Excellent Era hadn’t been so crazy about pursuing commercialization. Tao Xuan had originally considered victory as the greatest joy too. However, Tao Xuan was more involved in the scene. As the scene changed, he adapted, adjusted, and changed too.

Ye Xiu kept his love for the game. He thought of victory as the greatest glory and always strived to win. In fact, this was the reason behind Glory's name. The company spread the message that everything in the game was for glory. Perhaps this was just a form of marketing. But there were people who truly believed the message and worked hard to fulfill it. A dream should have no distinction between being noble or being lowly. For these people, their dream was to be the best at this game and gain whatever they believed to be as glory.

Ever since Ye Xiu walked this path, his dream had never changed.

He recalled his two friends, who once held that same dream. One lost everything before he could even step onto the path towards his dream. The other had once obtained everything along the way, but eventually went to pursue other goals. Now only Ye Xiu remained. Only he had never strayed from his path: his dream was Glory and nothing more.

Nowadays, numerous pro players may look down at these dreams, but they were also striving for their own dreams and their own glory.

Tonight, the system seemed to favor Ye Xiu’s side. A total of eight bosses spawned. Everyone ran around busily. In the end, they were able to take down six of the eight bosses. The two that they failed to get were because their information didn’t arrive fast enough. In the end, other guilds took it away. Wei Chen’s contribution towards these six bosses wasn’t small. He cleverly manipulated Samsara’s second elite group. The trick that he liked to use was help their first elite group until only Ye Xiu’s side became their only opponent.

How could the first elite group compare with Ye Xiu and the four guild alliance? The first elite group suffered defeat in every battle. In the end, they could only feel ashamed in front of their second group leader, Wei Chen. In their eyes, the second group leader beautifully completed their task every time, but their first elite group could never seize the opportunity.

Wei Chen consoled them every time with words like "It’s okay. Don’t think about it." or "Our opponent is Ye Qiu. It’s already impressive that we could get this far." His fake somberness made everyone in Happy want to throw up.

Samsara really lost out big this time. Not only were they being manipulated in the dark, the first and second elite group were on the verge of fighting with each other. Who cares if your first group leader was ashamed. The first group always failed to complete their task. How could the second group, who always completed their task beautifully, not have any objections? All groups within the guild competed with each other, whether that was the first elite group or the second elite group. In the second group’s perspective, the first group was too stupid. Next time, the first group should be the ones to assist the second group, while the second group snatched the boss.

Wei Chen always stepped in to resolve the dispute. This was because his current work was putting his role as a spy to perfect use. As a result, in the second group’s eyes, Wei Chen knew what was right for the guild and was adept at tactics. In the first group’s eyes, Wei Chen

was someone of noble character and unquestionable integrity.

"I feel like with me uniting Samsara, it’s only a matter of time before I become their ruler. What should I do if Samsara one day recognizes my talent and actually assigns me as their guild leader?" Wei Chen was in a good mood after playing the entire night. In the morning, Zhang Xinjie logged on. Everyone decisively logged off. When they went to eat breakfast together, he boasted shamelessly.

"You need me to tell you? Empty out their guild storage and then beat it." Ye Xiu said.

"F*ck, that’s too far. Won’t Samsara call the police?" Wei Chen said.

"You brute, you were actually thinking of doing it?" Ye Xiu said.

"If I haven’t been discovered, who knows!" Wei Chen said.

"Then you’d better work hard. Maybe you’ll actually get the opportunity to be Samsara’s guild leader. If you can actually get their guild storage, we won’t need to worry about anything anymore." Ye Xiu said.

"Your way of thinking isn’t correct. Haven’t you ever heard of the saying "Sit idle and eat. In time, even a mountain can be nibbled away." It’s only by understanding this concept can you firmly grasp their entire fortune." Wei Chen lectured Ye Xiu.

"I’m done eating. I’m going to go to bed." Ye Xiu got up.

"B*stard! I’m not done talking yet! You degenerate! You’ve already got a huge apartment all to yourself, but you go to the girl’s rooms everyday. What evil thoughts could you be harboring? I’m not a picky person, but Sister Su, if I were you, I definitely wouldn’t be able to bear it." Wei Chen said as he turned towards Su Mucheng.

"I just want to walk less and save some time." Ye Xiu said.

"Listen youngster, exercise is vital to being healthy!" Wei Chen said.

"Old people are always so long-winded." Ye Xiu shook his head and sighed. He went upstairs to rest.

Chapter 754: Team Blue Rain’s Important "Transfer"

A week passed swiftly. Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan both joined hands to help Tyrannical Ambition, stirring up trouble in the competition for wild bosses. The other guilds could only admire Tyrannical Ambition for having these kinds of pro players helping. In any case, that was current situation. They braced themselves for battle. Even if they couldn’t get the boss, they still needed to try their best! None of this could be considered new for the Club guilds for these two months in the summer. It was just the first time Tyrannical Ambition came out with such force.

As for the other Club guilds, it wasn’t like no pro players came to their aid. At Blue Brook Guild, Lu Hanwen was as diligent and fierce as before. This youth seemed to have an endless amount of energy and no matter how many times he failed, his spirit stayed strong. After a day of defeats, he was still full of energy the next day. His yelling invigorated the morale of the other members in the guild.

At Herb Garden, the pro player Liu Xiaobie participated. He became famous in the competitive scene for his hand speed, but because his control never fully matured, he was never able to completely utilize his advantage in hand speed. In a large-scale group battle, he was just another strong individual like Lu Hanwen. His value to Herb Garden wasn’t as high as the value of an expert tactician like Zhang Xinjie.

At the same time, although Team Excellent Era may have been relegated, their guild Excellent Dynasty couldn’t be counted out. However, their competitive strength was just so-so. Their performance wasn’t anything special.

As for the newly championed Samsara, their record this week wasn’t great either. They continued to be disappointed at being unable to fulfill their reputation as the new champions. In addition, there were rumors of sparks flying between their first and second elite group. It seemed like their relationships weren’t good. Quite a few guilds caught the smell of it and found out that a lot of small teams were becoming restless.

In comparison, Howling Heights stood out. Their Team Wind Howl’s newly joined Tang Hao was exceptionally diligent. From time to time, he would go into the game and help the guild. Last season’s Best Rookie, Zhao Yuzhe, also frequently appeared in the game.

However, Tyrannical Ambition was still the guild, which won the most. The pro players of the other guilds showed up randomly like the boss. They didn’t often stay on for long. On the other hand, Tyranny’s two pro players helped out the guild everyday as if it were their full time job.

Even though Tyrannical Ambition was dazzling, Ye Xiu and the four guild alliance still drew in the most attention. It was simply because these guilds had never been opponents in the eyes of other guilds. However, now that they had joined together, they were second only to Tyrannical Ambition this week.

Tyrannical Ambition ruled the daytime. The four guild alliance ruled the night. In any case, it wasn’t any other guild.

As for Ye Xiu, apart from being second only to Tyrannical Ambition in the wild boss competition, he had killed Deception numerous times this week. Besides the main account Deception, there was his alternate account called Not White. He even discovered a second alternate account called White Not. It was the so-called the crafty bunny has three burrows. Deception had three accounts and occasionally appeared in the wild boss battlefields. But he encountered Ye Xiu every time and his death was inevitable. Deception sometimes died in confusion, while other times with a clear understanding of what had happened. But after realizing why he was dying, he could guess the reasons for his confusing deaths.

Poor Deception! This week, his harvests had decreased considerably. Even worse, Ye Xiu’s power surpassed his imagination. He couldn’t just avoid those few players that he recognized. Deception had no idea which people belonged to Ye Xiu. In any case, no matter which account he used or which wild boss battlefield he went to, there would always be people shouting and trying to kill him.

Deception really wanted to find Ye Xiu and ask him what exactly he wanted, but in his recent four deaths, he had yet to see Ye Xiu’s character, so he had no way of throwing out his question.

That was more or less how his week progressed. Outside of the game, there were quite a few other transfers, but the only two important transfers were Lin Jingyan and Tang Hao. Xiao Shiqin was a big name too, but he had joined Excellent Era, which wouldn’t be a part of the Alliance next season. After being criticized as an idiot, very few paid any further attention to his situation.

News of the competitive scene during the summer mostly consisted of transfers. Rumors and guesses filled the air. This week, most of the discussion was focused on who Team Hundred Blossoms, which now had ten million in their hands, would pick up to inherit their core Spitfire character, Dazzling Blossoms.

The problem was that after Zhang Jiale retired, there was no other Spitfire player at his level. No Spitfire player looked to be qualified enough to become the team’s core player. Thus, there were actually more potential recruits to choose from. Team Blue Rain’s Zheng Xuan, Team Royal Style’s Shen Wanhe, and Team Void’s Ge Zhaolan were all relatively good players, but they were still lacking compared to a God like Zhang Jiale. Become a team’s ace player and core? Did the above-mentioned players have that potential? Many people believed that since there weren’t any outstanding Spitfire players currently in the Alliance, Team Hundred Blossoms might be better off giving Zou Yuan another chance. Zou Yuan was at least familiar with Team Hundred Blossom’s environment and tactics. Last season, Tang Hao’s outstanding performance caused them to change their style. Zou Yuan’s position as the core wasn’t well established as a result. This season, if they firmly established Zou Yuan as the core and polished him over the course of the season, he might not be any worse than any player that could be bought.

Opinions flew around, but Team Hundred Blossoms still didn’t seem to be making any movements. For transfers, making the first move was an advantage. If they waited too long, it might not be possible to make a pick. They might not be able to spend their ten million yuan check because a player could only be transferred once during the transfer window. If another team picked up a player that Team Hundred Blossoms had been eyeing, Team Hundred Blossoms had no way of re-signing that player this summer. Team Hundred Blossoms didn’t make any hints at a transfer nor did they say anything about Zou Yuan’s position. The fans were currently very worried. Quite a few thought of their retired captain Zhang Jiale again.

Zhang Jiale’s retirement was very sudden. No one thought that it was time for him to retire yet. Zhang Jiale was an old player, who had joined the competitive scene in season two. This year, he would be 25, which was considered quite old. However, it wasn’t so old that he couldn’t keep playing. As the Alliance grew, innovations in tactics and playstyles were constantly being developed. As a result, the length of a player’s career extended too. Lin Jingyan had joined Team Tyranny. Han Wenqin proclaimed their goal to be the champions. These two old generals were two years older than Zhang Jiale. They were still as ambitious as ever. Why couldn’t the younger Zhang Jiale come back?

These were just the fan’s hopes and guesses. Club Hundred Blossoms hadn’t given out any statements yet.　　

Week two of the transfer window had no big transfers. However, Team Blue Rain announced a promotion for someone in their training camp. A new young player would be officially joining their team next season: Lu Hanwen.

An unknown newcomer usually wouldn’t receive much attention, but Team Blue Rain convened a press conference solely for him, calling it an important "transfer" for this new season. Their bombast and confident statement drew in much curiosity.

The media did some digging and was shocked.

Lu Hanwen was only 14 years old. After registering as an official player, he would be the youngest player ever to join the Alliance.

In the early years of professional Glory, there were strict requirements. A player must be at least 18 years old to join, possess the capacity for civil conduct, and independently assume any civil obligations according to the law. These requirements had to do with the social environment at that time. Going into eSports wasn’t considered as a respectable job. Investing in the game as a pro player was looked down on even more. Under these concerns, a minor would only have their education delayed and also be pushed in the wrong direction.

As the Glory competitive scene rapidly grew, people became more accepting of a career as a pro player and no longer saw it as something terrible like in the early days. Many started looking upon the Glory competitive scene like traditional sports such as football and basketball.The Alliance constantlyrevised their regulations and the age limit was removed. However, a 14 year old like Lu Hanwen becoming a pro player was worthy of shock.

In the press conference, everyone saw Glory’s youngest pro player ever. His innocent face and voice didn’t appear nervous at all in front of the media. He said whatever he was thinking and answered any questions that came at him. His behavior was enough to make them think of him as the opposite of the current number one player in Glory, Zhou Zekai. The experienced reporters could tell that Lu Hanwen had never received any special training for interviews. He was just acting like a kid would. The media liked energetic players like him. However, as a pro player, his actual skill was still a question.

Unfortunately, there was still a long time before the start of the new season. Even when the season started, it was hard to say when a new player like him would come up on stage. It wasn’t like there hadn’t been cases of a reserve player sitting on the bench for the entire season. What’s more, most of these cases were new recruits. Didn’t Team Tiny Herb have a reserve player who never appeared on stage in the entire last season?

Poor Qiao Yifan. Many were comparing him to Team Blue Rain’s newcomer, but practically no one knew his name. They just vaguely remembered that there was such a player. In many people’s eyes, Team Tiny Herb only had one newcomer that season, Gao Yingjie. As for Team Blue Rain’s new recruit? He was completely unknown. Even though Team Blue Rain spread news of his addition to the team, they didn’t give any concrete information. The media didn’t even know what class this kid played.　

Would he be a new star in Glory?

People now had even more to look forward to next season.

Chapter 755: Incredible Newcomer

Lu Hanwen…...

In the outside world, the media only knew this tiny bit of information about this child. His skill was a mystery. On the other hand, Ye Xiu and the others at Happy had already witnessed this child’s skill many times in the game. But because he kept losing one battle after the other, Chen Guo and the others didn’t think much of him. Only Ye Xiu regarded him highly. When he saw Team Blue Rain’s statement, his expression turned serious: "This kid will definitely astonish everyone."

"Because of his eight shadowed Shadow Steps?" Chen Guo laughed. After being with Ye Xiu for awhile, Chen Guo had seen the large world. In the past, she would have very shocked to see Lu Hanwen perform eight shadows with Shadow Steps. Now she had Ye Xiu to comment on things though. She knew that Lu Hanwen’s eight shadows were good enough to trick her, but in the pro scene, it was full of holes. Those eight shadows would be equivalent to merely four shadows.

"Don’t underestimate him just because he keeps getting killed in the game. This is the game. It’s different from the pro scene." Ye Xiu said. Ye Xiu was very familiar with people like Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan. Once he knew that they were his opponents, he stopped paying anymore particular attention to them. On the other hand, Ye Xiu frequently took note of Team Blue Rain’s Lu Hanwen. This kid’s energy and unwavering spirit left a deep impression on Ye Xiu. He even had thoughts of trying to pull him into the team. Unfortunately, he wouldn’t have a chance to do that anymore. Team Blue Rain was decisive. They directly accepted this 14 year old into the team as an official member.

Then again, even if Team Blue Rain didn’t sign him, it would have been difficult for Ye Xiu to rope in Lu Hanwen anyways because 14 years old would be categorized as child labor. Team Blue Rain could sign him because eSports had gradually become more accepted. Lu Hanwen would be under the category of an athlete and would be approved as a result. Only an official club under the Alliance like Club Blue Rain could get this type of approval without any problems. It would be a thorny issue for Ye Xiu’s side.

It was good that Team Blue Rain decisively promoted Lu Hanwen to the team though. Ye Xiu no longer needed to worry about that issue. He thought highly of this kid’s future in the pro scene.

"God! Boss!" White Stream sent a message to him at this moment. Guild Radiant had discovered information of a wild boss spawning.　　

"Who’s there already? Has Tyrannical Ambition arrived?" Everyone hurried over, while asking. Tyrannical Ambition was their biggest concern. Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan were extremely difficult to deal with. If they didn’t make proper preparations, they would have no chance.　　

"We haven’t seen them yet, but Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild are already here." White Stream passed along the news.　　

After Ye Xiu and the others arrived at the wild boss’s location, they found out that Tyrannical Ambition had arrived too. Tyrannical Ambition was only watching from the sidelines though and didn’t hurry forward. The boss was currently being contested over by Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild.

"What is Tyrannical Ambition doing?" Ye Xiu observed them carefully. Tyrannical Ambition wasn’t arranged in any sort of formation. They just stood there casually. The four guild alliance was used to Tyrannical Ambition being their main opponent. Seeing that Tyrannical Ambition wasn’t moving, they didn’t dare make any hasty moves.

Ye Xiu’s Let There Be Light walked out from his troops and headed towards Tyrannical Ambition’s side. Tyrannical Ambition suddenly became nervous and hastily went into formation. Ye Xiu considered Tyrannical Ambition as his main opponent. How could Tyrannical Ambition not also consider Ye Xiu’s four guild alliance as troublesome? Recently, everyone knew that Ye Qiu was the Battle Mage Let There Be Light. Ye Qiu frequently led the charge too. Seeing him come out, everyone in Tyrannical Ambition felt like an attack was coming and immediately fell into formation. Tyrannical Ambition had been under the lead of their team’s vice captain for several days now. Their combat ability had improved.

Then they heard Ye Xiu shout: "What are you all panicking for? Where’s Zhang Xijie? Tell him to come out."

Tyrannical Ambition hissed in return. Of all the teams in Glory, Team Tyranny regarded Ye Qiu as their worst enemy. They disliked him the most.

Zhang Xinjie quickly received the message. Misty Mountains walked out from the crowd not long afterwards.　　

"Where’s Old Lin?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Haha." Zhang Xinjie laughed. Lin Jingyan’s Brawler was still hiding and playing dirty. How could Zhang Xinjie reveal Lin Jinyan’s character?

"You still haven’t moved yet. What kind of scheme are you plotting?" Ye Xiu asked directly.

"We’re watching first and then we’ll see what to do after." Zhang Xinjie said.

"What’s there to see?" This was what Ye Xiu actually wanted to ask. If the other side had a plan in mind, the other side wouldn’t just tell him if he asked. Tyrannical Ambition had just been sitting there, not moving. It really looked like they were watching something. When he asked the question, he turned to look where Zhang Xinjie’s Misty Mountain was looking. He soon found out what exactly Zhang Xinjie was observing.

In that direction, in the middle of the battle between Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild, two Blade Masters were fighting intensely. Cold light flashed and sword aura weaved. These two were clearly beyond a normal player’s skill level.

"That Blue Rain one is Lu Hanwen, the one who was just signed today, right? Zhang Xinjie was talking about one of the Blade Masters, Blue Brook Guild’s Flowing Cloud. It seems like Lu Hanwen never introduced himself to Zhang Xinjie. It was only up until today that Zhang Xinjie knew of him.

"Yeah, he’s quite an impressive newcomer." Ye Xiu sighed.

Neither of them talked about the Blade Master on Herb Garden. Seeing that rampant hand speed, that person must be Liu Xiaobie.

Lu Hanwen was currently fighting against this unique main roster player in an even battle. In their fight, besides an occasional heal, no one else assisted them.

Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie watched. The players on both sides gradually found this battle taking place and began to watch as well. Chen Guo finally knew that she had underestimated Lu Hanwen. To be able to fight evenly with a Blade Master from Team Tiny Herb, Lu Hanwen’s skill level wasn’t at all like a newly joined 14 year old. With his current skill and his record-breaking young age, he would certainly shock all of Glory.

"Liu Xiaobie might lose."

Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie were just a few units apart from each other as they watched the two Blade Masters fight. They suddenly heard a voice from between them. The two turned to see who it was and saw a Brawler standing there.

"Old Lin, you’re willing to come out?" Ye Xiu looked down on him.

"I can just switch accounts and then you won’t know who I am." Lin Jingyan said.

"You’re becoming more and more crafty." Ye Xiu sighed.

"That’s a must." Lin Jingyan said.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t pay much attention to their conversation. Instead, he answered Lin Jingyan’s first words: "Yes. If there weren’t any heals, Liu Xiaobie might have already lost."

"This newcomer is quite amazing." Lin Jingyan said.　　

"He could be a part of the main roster." Zhang Xinjie said.

"He’s only 14 years old." Ye Xiu said.

"How long are we going to chat for?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"It’s about time." Right when Ye Xiu said this, Let There Be Light suddenly stabbed towards Lin Jingyan’s Brawler. Lin Jingyan was prepared though. His character used Receiving Throw and instead grabbed Let There Be Light’s spear.

Receiving Throw was a dismantle skill. It had an even higher priority than a grab skill like Circle Swing. Ye Xiu wasn’t going to be countered like that and immediately canceled the skill. Lin Jingyan also switched attacks and threw a handful of sand. Ye Xiu’s Let There Be Light leaped up and spun 360 degrees. While dodging the Sand Toss, he threw out a Tyrant’s Destruction. Lin Jingyan jumped backwards and dodged it.

In just an instant, the two exchanged several moves. These were old generals. Their decision-making always walked in front of their mechanics. Their hand speed might not be fast, but their variations would always be faster.

Neither side had the upper hand. Lin Jingyan chuckled, wanting to say something, when he suddenly noticed a flash of light from the corner of his eye. He lowered his head and saw a marker lighting up beneath his feet. It was still glowing!

Lin Jingyan hastily dodged in surprise. With the marker already there, how could the Heat-Seeking Missiles be slower than a character’s running speed? Just when Lin Jingyan’s Brawler jumped, the missiles exploded and a mushroom cloud rose up. Lin Jingyan tried to control his character, but he still tumbled in the air several times.

Ye Xiu wasn’t going to wait for him to land. He seized the opportunity and chased after him.

Zhang Xinjie had taken action though. He cast a heal onto Lin Jingyan’s Brawler, while casting a Hypnotism in Let There Be Light’s direction.

Hypnotism required the caster to be facing the front of the target. The spell didn’t work from behind. However, it wasn’t a material object like sand, so it was much more difficult to dodge than Sand Toss. Ye Xiu was experienced though. As soon as he noticed Misty Mountains lift his cross into the air, he didn’t wait for the spell to complete before turning around.

Zhang Xinjie wasn’t hoping that the skill would actually hit Ye Xiu’s Let There Be Light. Sometimes all the skill needed to do was force the opponent to turn in the other direction. While the other couldn’t see him, he would cast a spell. At this moment, Zhang Xinjie immediately lit up a Sacred Fire.

How could Ye Xiu not know a simple trick like that? He moved with a Z-Shake and went around the sudden blaze of white fire. His spear pointed upwards with a Sky Strike to hit Lin Jingyan’s Brawler back into the air. Right when it was about to hit, a brick suddenly came out flying from underneath him.

This attack was too sudden. Ye Xiu hastily jumped backwards and knocked the brick aside. But because of this, Lin Jingyan’s Brawler was able to escape from his range. This was no longer a duel. Tyrannical Ambition began providing support. The four guild alliance wasn’t any slower though. The four guild leaders had already rushed forward.

The boss was still between Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild, but Tyrannical Ambition and the four guild alliance had begun fighting each other already.

Chapter 756: A Fierce Youth

Ye Xiu and the four guild alliance wasn’t going to fight with Tyrannical Ambition until one side lost. Everyone was here for the wild boss, after all. However, Lin Jingyan had been lured out with their little chat together. Ye Xiu wanted to seize this rare opportunity to see if he could throw the enemy troops into confusion. Unfortunately, Lin Jingyan wasn’t just ordinarily cunning. He was a wily old fox. When he exposed himself, he had thought that this might happen. He soon hid to who knew where.

After some time, the two sides eventually joined Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden in the fight for the boss. Three other guilds joined shortly afterwards and the field became a mess.

The battle continued until a system announcement came out. Guild Radiant stole the boss. It was a victory for Ye Xiu’s side. Tyrannical Ambition may have Zhang Xinjie, Lin Jingyan, and stronger troops, it didn’t mean that they were unstoppable. Let alone Ye Xiu’s four guild alliance, even the other guilds often had opportunities to attack the boss. It was just rarer, that’s all.

When the system announcement appeared, the battle immediately stopped. The various guilds had withdrawn their troops, but there was still a battle going on.

Liu Xiaobie and Lu Hanwen.

The two had been fighting, when Ye Xiu’s side arrived, and they were still fighting now.

26 minutes.

That length of time didn’t even include however much time they had been fighting before Ye Xiu’s side arrived. These two had unexpectedly kept fighting.　

The other guilds didn’t really know the identities of these two Blade Masters, so they weren’t too curious. It wasn’t any secret that Team Blue Rain and Team Tiny Herb were rivals nor was it strange to see the two sides unable to stop fighting with each other. As a result, the other guilds had already dispersed. In the end, only Ye Xiu’s four guild alliance and Tyrannical Ambition remained.

"Congratulations. You’ve gotten another boss." Zhang Xinjie saw that Ye Xiu’s Let There Be Light had also come over to watch the fight. He called him over. It was as if he were politely congratulating his opponent after the end of a match.

"It’s really only a fifth of a boss." Ye Xiu said.

"It’s still better than nothing." Zhang Xinjie said.

"True. Let’s watch those two!" Ye Xiu said.

Liu Xiaobie and Lu Hanwen were still in battle against each other. Neither of the two had any intentions of retreating as if they needed to decide the winner. But at this moment, the two sides had summoned their Clerics and Paladins to join in. No matter how hard the two fought, with a bunch of healers healing them, how could any of them ever fall!

Before, in order to restrain the other side, the healing couldn’t lag behind. But now the battle had ended, yet the two still wanted a winner and a loser. Should they stop healing? The two sides clearly didn’t know what to do. If we don’t stop, won’t this go on forever? If we stop….. What if the other side doesn’t? Won’t our side suffer?

As a result, the two sides observed each other’s movements and neither side let up. Finally, someone shouted: "Will this ever end? How about you all stop healing or else this will go on forever."

Many players followed the voice and found out that the speaker was neither from Blue Brook Guild nor Herb Garden. The player’s name sounded very lofty: Let There Be Light. This guy was telling them not to heal.

How could the two guilds not understand this logic? But the other side wasn’t stopping, so although they heard his shout, the two sides still had their misgivings and didn’t stop. Then, they heard him speak again: "What is everyone else standing there for? Kill the healers!"

"Stop stop stop! Everyone stop healing!!"

The guild leaders of Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden leaped out. If they do something, the two sides might start beating each other up.

Once the two guild leaders gave the order, the heals stopped. A large circle was formed. The battle between Liu Xiaobie and Lu Hanwen didn’t change because the heals suddenly stopped. The two continued to fight.

"Young people are amazing. To think they could fight for so long without knowing what tired means." Lin Jingyan had his Brawler slip out again and expressed his admiration.

"Time waits for no one!" Ye Xiu empathized with him.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t say anything. The players of the golden generation were at their peaks right now. Agreeing with Ye Xiu and Lin Jingyan wasn’t appropriate.

"Is Tyranny working so hard for these wild bosses to help you create your Brawler’s equipment?" Ye Xiu said.

"How could I answer that?" Lin Jingyan said.

"I really can’t stand the scene. Even trivial matters always need to be kept a secret. It’s as if you guys are hiding something." Ye Xiu remarked with disdain.

"Cough….…" Lin Jingyan almost coughed blood. It had only been half a year since Ye Qiu had retired and he was acting as if he were completely clean from the scene now. Ye Qiu was criticizing the pro scene, but it didn’t feel right to Lin Jingyan.

"If you’ve got any needs, tell them to me! I’ve got a few extra in my hands!" Ye Xiu followed up.

"Oh? What needs do you have?" Lin Jingyan was indeed cunning. This type of trade wouldn’t give the other side any way to cheat you. Usually, if you urgently needed something and you wanted to find someone to trade with, it was very difficult to find a fair trade. You need it badly, but who says we don’t either?

Thus, it was best if the two sides could trade for materials that they needed. Neither side would lose out in that case. If only your side urgently needed something, that was equivalent to slicing your own throat. So when Ye Xiu asked this question, he obviously wasn’t doing it for Lin Jinyan’s sake. Ye Xiu must want something too, so he wanted to see if he could make a fair trade with Tyranny.

But how many years had Club Tyranny been accumulating materials? It was unlikely that they urgently lacked any material. If they really did need something, trading was the correct way to go. In the game, a boss only spawned once a week. No one knew when it would spawn, let alone guaranteeing that they could snatch the boss from everyone else. Even if they did, it might not even drop, so a trade was the most reliable option. They mainly fought for wild bosses because it was always better to be prepared just in case. More importantly, it was because these old team members were willing to contribute to the team.

As a result, if Ye Xiu wanted a trade, Lin Jingyan wouldn’t be impatient. He instead asked Ye Xiu what he needed.

Ye Xiu’s needs would be more pressing than Tyranny’s. Ye Xiu had only just started getting materials. He might not have any amount of what he needed!

"I have a lot of things I need, but if I don’t know what you guys want, how am I supposed to trade?" Ye Xiu put it plainly. He showed clearly that he wanted an equal trade. He also knew that with Club Tyranny’s foundation, the club probably didn’t need anything right now. But who knew if they got stuck in some area and needed to use more materials? By asking, if Tyranny needed something, they might look for him first. He had materials that he needed, so an equal trade would be possible! If Tyranny looked for another Club to trade with, they would need to spend much more to get what they wanted!

"Okay, I got it. If we have any needs, I’ll talk to the club about it." Lin Jingyan understood Ye Xiu’s intentions and nodded his head. His words were very fitting. He had just joined Team Tyranny. If he slammed down the hammer saying I’ll definitely look for you, acting like he were the owner, he would appear too domineering. Old players knew what conduct was considered appropriate to the club.

As the two talked, the fight between the two never stopped. Both players fought at an extremely fast pace. Their figures were constantly moving about, exchanging various skills. For a moment, no one could tell who held the upper hand.

Lin Jingyan soon called out: "Oh, it looks like our little friend is about to run out of mana."

"Liu Xiaobie is about to run out too." Ye Xiu said.

Without any support, the two Blade Masters were actually unable to decide a winner before running out of mana. They didn’t stop though. They began using normal attacks, which didn’t require mana, to continue.　

Hack, strike, slash, sweep....

Normal attacks were very flexible. The player could control the path of each attack with his mouse. Sword aura had disappeared. Only sword light could be seen now with the two using normal attacks. The crisp sound of metal clashing rang like a torrential rain, showing the fast speed of their fighting.

The surrounding players watched in awe. If these normal attacks were used against them, these normal attacks wouldn’t be much different than skills. They would probably have several holes through them in the blink of an eye.

But these two! Despite such a fast pace, the two could see the other side’s weapon and accurately block it with their own.

Everyone knew that the two weren’t a part of a wuxia performance. The two were blocking by using their attacks to neutralize their opponent’s attacks. Because the two were both using normal attacks and of the same class, the priority of their attacks were the same. Using attacks to defend worked very well.

In the eyes of everyone watching, they couldn’t help but think the two had choreographed this beforehand. How could they be so accurate every time?

While the normal players were in awe, Ye Xiu and the other experts were judging the two sides.

"Fighting with normal attacks is advantageous for Liu Xiaobie. He doesn’t need to control his hand speed." Lin Jingyan said.

"But the kid is actually able to block them all." Ye Xiu said.

From their words, Liu Xiaobie held the initiative. He was the one on the offense.

"With his onslaught of attacks, a single mistake could be very troublesome." Lin Jingyan said.

"But he’s been able to defend the entire time." Ye Xiu said.　　

"Do you think he has some sort of hidden trick up his sleeve?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"How am I supposed to know? I’m not familiar with him." Ye Xiu said.

"Just make a guess!" Lin Jingyan said.

"I think so." Ye Xiu said.

"Why do you think that?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"Didn’t you just tell me to make a guess?" Ye Xiu retorted.

"F*ck!" Lin Jingyan was speechless. Even if you’re guessing, you can still give a reason, no? Did you actually just flip a coin to come up with an answer?

Suddenly, a blue aura emanated from Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud. Everyone stared blankly. No one here was a noob. They recognized this skill. Liu Xiaobie was astonished. Flowing Cloud slashed with his sword, carrying a blue sword aura. Only a skill that used mana could release sword aura.

A skill had higher priority than a normal attack. The attack passed through Liu Xiaobie’s guard. Lu Hanwen followed up the attack with several more hits, killing Liu Xiaobie’s Blade Master. The two had been fighting for a long time, so neither of them had much health left.

"I win!" Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud lifted his sword high up into the air and cheered.

"Despicable!" The players on Herb Garden realized what had happened and were furious.

"It’s a group battle, who told you it was a 1v1?" Lu Hanwen refuted in his high-pitched voice.

Everyone in Happy Internet Cafe glanced at Ye Xiu. Why did that sound so familiar! This kid wasn’t going to be led astray just from coming across Ye Xiu a few times, right?

Chapter 757: Ace Player Sub Seventh Person

Ye Xiu was also astonished. He understood why Herb Garden was pointing furiously at Lu Hanwen and calling him despicable. The blue aura surrounding Lu Hanwen wasn’t a Blade Master skill. It was a Cleric skill: Wish Prayer.

This skill helped a character recover mana. Everyone thought that the two Blade Masters were fighting in a duel. Who would have thought that a Cleric on Lu Hanwen’s side would cast a Wish Prayer on him? Mana meant skills could be used. No mana was equivalent to being silenced. Liu Xiaobie had been caught off guard, seeing a blue aura suddenly surround Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud. He wasn’t able to react in time before Lu Hanwen counterattacked using skills. Neither of them had much health left. With this kind of overwhelming advantage, Lu Hanwen easily disposed of him in a few moves. It was only then did Herb Garden realize what had happened. Then, they saw him gleefully cheer "I win!" and immediately became furious at the results.

Not only was Lu Hanwen not ashamed, he even argued as if he were not wrong.

The people in Happy suspected that he had been influenced by Ye Xiu in some way. Herb Garden wouldn’t think of that though. They had already begun spitting insults. Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild had never been on good terms with each other. Seeing their own pro player get defeated in such a despicable manner, how could they bear to stand by and watch? Everyone in Herb Garden charged at Blue Brook Guild. Even if the guild leader tried to stop them, it would be pointless.

The spectating pro players had no plans on intervening. They quickly retreated from the chaotic battlefield.

"If it wasn’t for the fact that you aren’t using a Cleric, I would have suspected that you had been the one to cast Wish Prayer." Zhang Xinjie said.　　

"Randomly guessing like that doesn’t suit your careful personality." Ye Xiu said.

"If I were more careful, I would ask if you had ordered a Cleric to cast it." Zhang Xinjie asked.

"I think you did it!" Ye Xiu said.

"I didn’t." Zhang Xinjie actually gave a proper response.

"If that kid asked for someone to cast it..." Lin Jingyan paused, "I can’t help but think of an old friend."

"Old Wei?" Ye Xiu said.

"Yup!" Lin Jingyan said.

"Blue Rain’s former captain?" Zhang Xinjie asked.

"Yes. If it’s him….." Lin Jingyan paused again as if he were trying to find the appropriate words to say.

"Extremely unscrupulous. Extremely shameless. Extremely underhanded." Ye Xiu didn’t hold back.

"Haha….." Lin Jingyan felt a bit embarrassed just hearing it. Although he agreed with the description, Lin Jingyan didn’t really like talking behind people’s backs, which was why he had hesitated. He couldn’t think of any other words to describe Wei Chen.

"It’s definitely possible if it was him." Ye Xiu said.

"Haha..." Lin Jinyan laughed dryly.

Zhang Xinjie was a bit puzzled. He had become a pro player in season four. At that time, he didn’t have any opportunity to meet Team Blue Rain’s former captain. There weren’t even many rumors of him left. In season four, the rise of the two new players that joined Team Blue Rain completely overshadowed their senior. If it wasn’t for Han Wenqin, Zhang Xinjie probably wouldn’t even know of the name Wei Chen. Nowadays, many people didn’t know about the famous characters back in the early days of the Alliance.

"Who were you introducing me to?" Wei Chen came over. He had heard Ye Xiu say "Old Wei".

"That kid from Blue Rain might be similar to you. He’s willing to do anything to win!" Ye Xiu said. He hadn’t expected Lu Hanwen to behave like that, but then again, he hadn’t had too many opportunities to meet him.

"Really? He’s got such a bright future ahead of him?" Wei Chen felt deeply moved. He praised this future star, or perhaps he was praising himself for being amazing.

The people, who originally wanted to jeer at Ye Xiu for leading this Blue Rain newcomer astray, couldn’t keep watching.

Completely ignoring the war between Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild, Ye Xiu’s side and Tyrannical Ambition dispersed. Everyone went to do their own business, until the next boss spawned.

During this free time, Ye Xiu would dungeon with and coach others, while accumulating dungeon materials for the future.

As for Zhang Xinjie and Ling Jingyan, if there wasn’t a wild boss, they wouldn’t waste their time in game. The two were discussing the newcomer to Team Blue Rain, Lu Hanwen.

"He’s quite good already. Even for a team like Team Blue Rain, he has the qualifications to be starter on the main roster." Lin Jingyan gave his opinion.

"Blue Rain already has Huang Shaotian’s Blade Master. I don’t know what they plan on doing with another Blade Master." Zhang Xinjie said.

"Just being a substitute for Huang Shaotian feels like a bit of a waste." Lin Jingyan said.

"It certainly would be." Zhang Xinjie nodded his head.

Esports didn’t require much physical effort. Matches were only once a week too. Stamina couldn’t be used as a reason for switching out a player. A substitute had far less opportunities to show up on stage compared to a main roster player, especially a substitute for a core and ace player like Huang Shaotian. Unless something unexpected happened to Huang Shaotian, there was almost no way he would ever be subbed out.

"But then again, it isn’t impossible for him to be Huang Shaotian’s sub. After all, he’s still young!" Lin Jingyan suddenly said.

"Mm." Zhang Xinjie nodded his head. He understood what Lin Jingyan meant.

It wasn’t easy to find a sub for an ace player because the team revolved around the ace player as the core. To ensure the team’s cohesiveness, it was best if this position wasn’t touched at all. As a result, if a sub was ever needed, the closer the sub’s strength was to the ace player the better. The sub for an ace player only had so many opportunities to appear on stage. How could a player close to the strength of the ace player be willing to idly sit on the bench for an entire season?　

This was what Lin Jingyan meant.

Because Lu Hanwen was skilled, but also young. It was common for a youth to be a sub. As a result, Team Blue Rain might have a sub that many could only dream of for their ace player.

"It’d be good if he was just a sub." Zhang Xinjie said.

"Mm, but in the individual competition or group arena, I feel like Team Blue Rain will definitely give him chances to appear." Lin JIngyan said, "Ace player sub seventh player. Oh, if you look at it from this perspective, it isn’t anything new."

Ace player sub seventh person was commonly done by many teams. It felt more like a standard choice.

The sixth person to come out in the team competition could be considered as part of the main roster. The individual competition and group arena required six people to come on stage. These six could be the same six as those from the team competition, so for most teams, the six main players would play in the team competition and either the individual or group arena.

However, because the classes of the starting six usually had a healer or support player like a Cleric or Paladin, which weren’t suited for 1v1 battles like the individual competition ro group arena. As a result, there was usually a seventh player in the team that would appear in either the individual competition or group arena.

Many teams left this position to the sub for the ace player.

The sub for the ace player was almost always the best among the subs, often approaching the strength of a main roster player. This type of player wouldn’t stay if there was no opportunity to appear on stage. Thus, many teams would provide this opportunity by allowing them play in the individual competition or group arena. The ace player sub might appear in the team competition too, so it felt like they were a part of the main team. Thus, "ace player sub seventh player" was the term used to refer to this type of player.

But as the Glory competitive scene developed, there were more and more outstanding players. It was already becoming difficult to see the difference in strength between main players and subs. Right now, more and more teams pursued flexible tactics. Nine or ten players were often rotated for the team competition. Sometimes, the sub played better than a main roster player. This sub would become a part of the main roster and the the main roster player would become a sub. It wasn’t like this situation had never happened before. However, these were mainly between ordinary main roster players. The ace players of each team were truly much better than the others members. A sub wouldn’t easily take over their spot. As a result, an ace player sub wasn’t always in a better position than the other subs. The identity as an "ace player sub seventh person" was a special, yet awkward position. Many teams had studied how to get rid of this issue. An "ace player sub seventh person" might not be enough to satisfy teams nowadays.

Lin Jingyan and Zhang Xinjie talked quite a bit about Lu Hanwen’s position in Team Blue Rain. They would obviously be more concerned about Lu Hanwen than Ye Xiu because if they wanted to be the next season’s champion, Team Blue Rain couldn’t be ignored. Team Blue Rain might very well be their opponent in the playoffs. An incredible newcomer, who was only 14 years old, could create a huge problem for Tyranny in the future. They couldn’t just sit and wait.

Their discussion was mostly about this topic. For the details, they would need to wait until the new season started to see how Team Blue Rain arranged their roster.

Today, Lu Hanwen had become the focus in Glory. Many were talking about him. Once his addition to the team was announced, quite a few people were beginning to match him with the Blade Master, Flowing Cloud. The first to take notice of him was Tyranny, but they weren’t the last. Liu Xiaobie, who had been defeated in a shameless manner by Lu Hanwen, wasn’t like his fans and could calm himself down. He quickly reported this Team Blue Rain newcomer to the team, telling them that next season’s Team Blue Rain would be different than it was in the past.

Chapter 758: The Inconceivable Transfer

In the blink of an eye, another week passed.

The battle for bosses continued to be a you-login-when-I-get-off scenario. Both sides would clash occasionally. Those fights always felt tough. However, this week something surprised both Ye Xiu and Tyrannical Ambition. From Herb Garden, a Witch actually appeared.

Even Wang Jiexi wanted to make a mess out of things?

At first, everyone felt depressed when they thought about this. If more and more Gods joined, wouldn’t boss fighting become way too tiring? Even pro matches wouldn’t be as exhausting. There was only one match per week, but wild bosses? More than a few per day. Trying to outwit all the Gods every time would drain the energy of even immortals!

Fortunately, Wang Jiexi soon made it obvious that he was not coming to fight for wild bosses. He was here to observe Lu Hanwen, the 14-year-old newcomer that had joined Team Blue Rain, who came to his attention in the tit-for-tat duel with Liu Xiaobie that day.

What conclusions Wang Jiexi drew from his observations would be unknown to outsiders. Anyway, the witch disappeared after a few battles. Those concentrated on snatching wild bosses let out a huge sigh of relief and continued on with their week.　　

During the second week, there were a lot of transfers. News of rookies like Lu Hanwen signing on, even when advertised by Team Blue Rain as their most important transfer, were soon buried by other news. Who didn’t know what PR was? These newcomers had neither the fame nor data. Who would care about them?

Despite the lack of All Star transfers, there were plenty of trades and adjustments in multiple team main rosters. All the big teams had started to prepare for the new season. From this week on, one could almost discern the direction many teams were going to go in for the new season. Were they going to re-build the team completely, or strengthen their weaknesses? Were they dissatisfied with certain positions and wanted to change those.

The newly crowned Samsara was one of those teams that made no moves in the first two weeks of the transfer window. This was not exactly unexpected. As the champions, of course they did not require too many changes in their team, and it was highly unlikely that someone would ask to leave because they were unhappy about winning the championship title. During these two weeks, they took part in many marketing events as the new champion.

Zhou Zekai was at such a peak in popularity that even Samsara had no idea how they could promote him more. With such popularity, simply keeping it at the same level would be a tremendous victory. Team Samsara had now started to try and promote their vice captain Jiang Botao. From some of their publicity moves, they apparently wanted to establish him as a Master Tactician of the new generation.

To be fair, Team Samsara’s declaration wasn’t without reason. Jiang Botao was indeed highly experienced in strategies and tactics. He was the actual commander of Samsara. He was the bridge between Zhou Zekai and the team. However, regarding him as a Master Tactician was still met with a lot of controversy. Many people thought that Jiang Botao only knew Zhou Zekai’s intentions very well. He was a player that had a strong connection, but only with Zhou Zekai. His tactics only worked well based on such foundation. Moveover, Zhou Zekai’s personal performance definitely contributed the most to Samsara’s victory. In many occasions, they did not break through because of tactics, but Zhou Zekai alone. Saying that Jiang Botao was already a Master Tactician was a bit of an overstatement.

Samsara was very experienced in promoting and advertising their players though. They did not boast or say anything definite at the very beginning. They mostly tried to raise their arguments in a less serious atmosphere, or in a joking manner. They were testing the waters for the public’s reactions. Now that they saw Jiang Botao needed more solid plays and the wind was not going in their favor, they stopped immediately. Their words were gone with the wind. At this point, those words would become their foreshadowing. Whenever Jiang Botao really gained such name and status, they could dig the words out: look, we told you so! If Jiang Botao didn’t in the end, the words could just be buried like a real joke.

Samsara’s publicity tactics were indeed masterful.

But Samsara’s publicity moves had too little gossip value to become the center of the spotlight. At this time, they were even less interesting than the current transfers from any main roster.

Once two weeks had passed, the fans and player looked forward to the upcoming week in hope of some big moves, as if transfers would spawn each week like wild bosses.

In reality, transfers did spawn randomly, similar to the wild bosses, but instead of spawning weekly, they spawned all throughout the entire transfer window.

In the first week, there weren’t a lot of transfers, but among the few were big names like Xiao Shiqin, Lin Jingyan, and Tang Hao.

In the second week, the number of transfers rose, but none of them were All Stars.

What would happen in the third week?

Everyone was waiting expectantly.

The first day, the second day, the third day…...

Little shrimps, little shrimps, and little shrimps. All the transfer news in the first three days were about little shrimps.

Until the fourth day came. At dusk, Ye Xiu and others were gathered for dinner on the first floor. Suddenly, a scream rose from one of the customers at Happy Internet Cafe. After some communication, the entire Happy Internet Cafe exploded. Chen Guo went up and asked what was going on, then threw her bowl and rushed to a computer to search for something. She wished she could move the monitor to the dinner table for everyone to see.

At the dusk of the fourth day in the third week, a gigantic bomb was dropped in the transfer market, more than enough to exceed everyone’s expectation. This was another record-breaking transfer, completed at 16 million yuan. However, this transfer was not for a player, but a character.

The core character of Team Hundred Blossoms, the Spitfire, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, was bought by Team Tyranny for the price of 16 million yuan.

Nobody knew what kind of expression they should put on in the face of this transfer.

Neither Hundred Blossoms nor Tyranny had made any public statements on this transfer. This recording-making news appeared quietly in the transfer list of the Glory Alliance official website. When it was dug out and posted online, some even thought it was a mistake, or a joke, or thought someone had hacked the Glory Alliance official website.

Once the journalists confirmed with the Alliance that it was not a joke nor a hack, everybody finally believed it, but at the same time they were all dazed by it.

They had no idea what the purpose of this transfer was.

Team Hundred Blossoms gave up their core character. Even though the record-breaking 16 million was deserving for a God-level character like Hundred Dazzling Blossoms, what about the future of Team Hundred Blossoms after this transfer? It was true that sometimes a team wanted to start over and reconstruct, but there was never a reconstruction as thorough as this before.

Their most valuable core player had been sold.

Their most powerful core character had been sold off.

What’s next? Was Hundred Blossoms going to change their names, and treat themselves as a new team in the Alliance?

People were so shocked that they didn’t know how to respond.

As for Tyranny, this was equally confusing.

They bought Lin Jingyan, but they had no Brawler character in their team, so they used a lot of resources to build a new one. Now they bought Hundred Dazzling Blossoms, another class that didn’t originally exist on their team, which meant that they did not have a player to use it either. What were they trying to do? Show off their tyrannical ambition through spending? Did they hold a grudge for not owning the transfer record, so they just found a record-breaking target to purchase?

Crazy. Both teams were crazy.

The comment section was full of opinions like that. Both teams were crazy, which made countless people who followed this transfer also crazy. They couldn’t give a rational reason for the contents of this transfer, because rational reasoning would never come to this decision.

Only Ye Xiu immediately understood it when he saw that news.

"So that guy’s going to Tyranny!" Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo had also more or less had figured it out. She knew the situation of Zhang Jiale, and even dreamt about this God joining their team, but unfortunately, Zhang Jiale was aiming for the championship title. He would only go to a team that could touch the title. A team that was struggling in the Challenger League, even with a god like Ye Qiu, offered no temptation for him.

His goal was clear, so it was not hard to guess where he would go. There were only a few teams in the Alliance with the championship as their goal. Ye Xiu was certain that Zhang Jiale would be going to one of those teams, but he didn’t know which one. For a player at the level of Zhang Jiale, he would not blindly believe the stats on paper. The team he would join needed to show him not only the strength to win the championship, but also the ambition for claiming the title, as well as their plan.

What about Tyranny at the moment?

They signed Lin Jingyan, then Zhang Jiale, plus Han Wenqing was already on their team…...

This was in no way a team of the future. The three players were all old players. They did not have much time left. However, their thirst for the championship was something that no young players could match up to. Because they didn’t have much time, because they didn’t have many more opportunities, they could burn everything they had towards the end, because there was no turning back.

"This team is so..." Ye Xiu didn’t know how to describe it.　

This would be a team that never lacked the fighting spirit or faith. Lin Jingyan, who had never once played in the finals; Zhang Jiale, who had reached the finals three time, but lost all of them; and Han Wenqing, the man who never knew what was retreat was. Their thirst for championship exceeded anything else.

However, this was also a bold and risky cooperation. They were a brand new team, with zero experience to follow up. The foundation of Tyranny was completely changed by these two transfers. It had become a team consisting of only gods and aces. How to combine them together would be their biggest issue.

But soon, Ye Xiu recalled the changes Han Wenqing adopted last season, and suddenly remembered Zhang Jiale seemed to have made the decision by that point.

"These old dudes. Had they planned for this long ago?" Ye Xiu slurred.

Chapter 759: A Discouraging Day for Team Hundred Blossoms

After this quiet character transfer was dug out, it immediately became the headlines of every site related to Glory or eSports. Posts on the various forums exponentially increased. The discussion was, of course, about the transfer of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Once the initial puzzlement and frenzy passed, logical analysis of the transfer gradually floated up to the surface.

Was Zhang Jiale planning on returning to the Alliance by joining Tyranny? There was originally no discussion over this question, but how fierce could gossip spread? Even an unfounded story could be told to make it extremely clear and logical. Zhang Jiale joining Tyranny was the truth and the most likely explanation for the transfer.

Because in the current competitive scene, there weren’t any particularly outstanding Spitfire players. Perhaps this was why Team Hundred Blossoms decided to give up on their core character. It was undoubtedly a daring decision. Once news of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms being sold exploded, the fans were outraged at Team Hundred Blossoms. None of them were in the correct mindset to rationally analyze it.

Maybe Team Hundred Blossoms couldn’t find a suitable core player, so they might as well completely rebuild the team, but why did Tyranny purchase Dazzling Hundred Blossoms? Did they have some sort of exceptional Spitfire player in hiding?

When Tang Hao transferred to Team Wind Howl, discussion over the good Spitfire players in the current competitive scene had already been done. The conclusion was that there was no Spitfire that had a transfer value of more than 4 million. None of them had the potential to be Gods either.

As a result, there were only two logical possibilities for Tyranny purchasing Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

The first possibility was that Tyranny had raised an exceptional new player, who was a Spitfire.

The second possibility was that Tyranny would be inviting the retired Zhang Jiale to join next season.

There were people who discussed both possibilities. Of course, Ye Xiu and the others in Happy knew that the second possibility was the truth.

Ye Xiu even guessed that when he and Zhang Jiale met in the game, Tyranny had already started doing work for him.

Lin Jingyan’s transfer seemed sudden, but perhaps Tyranny had already made plans beforehand. It was also possible that these plans were the deciding factor for Zhang Jiale.

Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Lin Jingyan, and Zhang Jiale would be an All Star line up that had never once appeared before in the history of the Alliance. Even though a few powerhouses possessed three All Stars, their circumstances were completely different from Tyranny.

Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, and Zhang Jiale could easily be the ace player of any team. They had all been the core of their former teams, and now these three core players had gathered together. It was absolutely unprecedented. If this couldn’t move Zhang Jiale, then was he even aiming for the championships?

However, the argument against this reason was that if he really was returning, Team Hundred Blossoms wouldn’t sell Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Team Hundred Blossoms was Zhang Jiale’s home. He had served the team for six years!

Without a doubt, those who held this perspective were loyal fans of Team Hundred Blossoms and Zhang Jiale.

Ye Xiu and the others in Happy, who knew the truth, couldn’t keep looking any further. They were already thinking of how many people would be heartbroken once the truth actually came out.

Per the Alliance’s rules, retired players could only return after a year of retirement. Zhang Jiale had decided to retire at the beginning of the season last year, catching Team Hundred Blossoms unprepared. At that point, the transfer window was about to close. In addition, there weren’t any particularly outstanding Spitfires, so Zou Yuan had no choice but to fill in.

This rule only indicated when a player could officially register and join a team though. A public announcement could be made earlier.

As a result, that night, the truth came out. There wasn’t much news of Zhang Jiale before, but he received an interview and admitted his return to the Alliance. He told the reporter that he had already long since reached an agreement with Team Tyranny. He would be joining Team Tyranny next season.

A lot of gossip had been made, but the power of the truth would always be greater than mere gossip. News of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms being purchased by Team Tyranny and Zhang Jiale joining Team Tyranny became a stickied post everywhere. The entire scene in Glory went wild. In comparison, Tang Hao’s ten million yuan transfer appeared weak.

Just as Ye Xiu and the others in Happy expected, once the truth came out, many hearts were broken. The ones who spoke the loudest and the most intense were Team Hundred Blossom’s most loyal fans.

They could still endure Team Hundred Blossoms giving up on Tang Hao. After all, he wasn’t the core member that Team Hundred Blossoms needed. They preferred a Spitfire as the core.

But giving up on Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was something that they could not accept. By the time the news came out, what was done could not be undone. The Alliance had officially recorded the transfer. The fans had no chance to object because no matter how they objected, reality wouldn’t be changed.

They felt like the team wasn’t respecting the fans. They felt like they had been cheated, fooled, and betrayed. All of the loyal fans furiously shouted for the entire afternoon. They loudly criticized Club Hundred Blossom’s decision, calling it moronic, and demanded an explanation from the Club to the fans.

Those gossipers, who just wanted to stir things up, wrote about their conjecture that Zhang Jiale would join Team Tyranny, making them feel even angrier. In their fan’s eyes, even if Zhang Jiale did not take responsibility for suddenly retiring last season, he was still Team Hundred Blossom’s former ace player and team captain. He was a person of Hundred Blossoms. How could he go to Tyranny?

The fans lashed out at the Club, but also clashed with the gossipers to defend their Club’s current players. These loyal fans truly loved the team. They didn’t understand the Club’s decision, but when others began attacking a former player of their team, they immediately took up arms.

Up until night came.

When Zhang Jiale’s interview was released, the gossipers were ecstatic. They waved around this news, slapping Team Hundred Blossoms’ fans, who had argued with them that afternoon. At this moment, the Team Hundred Blossom fans were unable to retaliate.

The Club sold their most beloved character and their favorite player had given up on the team to go to another on his own accord. For a loyal Team Hundred Blossom fan, it was as if their entire world had collapsed. Today was a discouraging day for them.

They didn’t have the strength to argue anymore.

Nothing was more sorrowful than a withered heart.

What could the fans use to argue with?

Countless fans quietly shut down their computers. Today’s news caused their hearts to sink to rock bottom. Following afterwards, quite a few fans erupted out in anger. The lashed out at Club Hundred Blossoms with greater fury. This time, Zhang Jiale was enveloped in it.

Zhang Jiale had predicted this would happen. In the interview, once the reporter learned of his decision, they anticipated this would happen too. The reporter asked this question. Zhang Jiale’s reply sounded very calm. He apologized for not taking responsibility for his sudden retirement, and for not returning to Team Hundred Blossoms this season. He didn’t say anything like I hope my fans will understand. The reporter might have felt Zhang Jiale’s pain and worry and continued to ask Zhang Jiale why he made this decision.

His answer was simple: to be a champion.

To be a champion.

Some could understand the significance of these four words.

Amidst the storm of anger, quite a few fans wished Zhang Jiale good luck. Their good blessings didn’t receive widespread support though. They became another target to be spat on besides Club Hundred Blossom and Zhang Jiale.

The noise persisted for an entire week.

Even the pro players felt the vibrations. The pro players, who had gone on vacation or back home, suddenly popped up, discussing the news with other players and in their chat groups. Zhang Jiale was actually a part of a few of these groups, but as the person involved, he didn’t say anything. Team Tyranny’s players gave out a "he he". Their attitude towards this transfer went without saying.

However, everyone was a mature pro player. They wouldn’t go so far as to argue over who would win the championships next season. In the early days, there would be disputes over this topic, but nowadays, everyone was much more mature. This sort of transfer was shocking to the outside world, but most pro players would face the news calmly.

The reason was because they understood the words "to be a champion" more than anyone else.

Of course, there were also players who disagreed with Zhang Jiale’s actions, but no matter what they discussed in their chat groups, Zhang Jiale never appeared. It was just as if he were still in retirement. Who knew if he was lurking?

Team Tyranny’s new season plan was clearly displayed in front of the public. This was statistically the strongest line-up ever seen before in the history of Glory. It naturally attracted a lot of attention. The media even went so far as to say Team Tyranny could challenge the record for the most points in the season.

As for the issue of Han Wenqing’s, Lin Jingyan’s, and Zhang Jiale’s age, no one disregarded it. Age became their biggest power though. Many could see this point. The reports had already elaborated on this issue clearly and logically. They almost wrote how these three brothers would ignite their cosmo and blow up the earth. (TLN: A Saint Seiya reference I think)

As for Team Hundred Blossoms? These two transfers alone had earned them 26 million yuan. This itself was a record, but they were currently being looked at as pitiful creatures by everyone.

Chapter 760: Core Position

All the gossipers followed Team Tyranny’s movements closely. As for Team Hundred Blossom’s future? The gossipers would pay attention to this more momentous topic before turning around to take a look at the pitiful reality that had past. Even Team Hundred Blossom’s most loyal fans could only seethe with anger. Some could understand Zhang Jiale’s reasons for leaving and wished him well, but no one could understand Club Hundred Blossom’s string of transfers. The club’s decisions were faced with all sorts of harsh criticism.

Everyone was interested in the new Team Tyranny’s might and what new records the team could possibly achieve. For a moment, not many concerned themselves with a few follow-up questions. Team Hundred Blossom’s future was one such question. Another was that if two ace players joining the main roster of Team Tyranny, which of their current team members would be benched or leaving? Any one of Team Tyranny’s players was easily worthy of attention in the transfer market, but in light of the current circumstances, their existence appeared miniscule. The question of their future was also ignored.

Tyranny became the main topic for the rest of the week. Two sides formed. One side regarded Team Tyranny highly in the upcoming season, while the other side disagreed. The two sides argued without restraint. The optimistic side that supported Team Tyranny obviously did so because Team Tyranny had unprecedented strength on paper. The opposing side wasn’t as optimistic about the team’s future because of the age of their new ace players and the fundamental change that would certainly happen to the team. Everyone gave their own reasons. Smoke pervaded the air for a week. What made Ye Xiu and the others in Happy feel unfortunate was that this quarreling didn’t affect Team Tyranny’s players. Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan were still diligently competing for wild bosses.

Chen Guo had initially been worried about Zhang Jiale also appearing. His situation was different from the other two though. Guild Blossom Valley was a competitor in the wild boss battles. He had no way of avoiding Team Hundred Blossoms in their competitive matches with each other. He would also have to face his former team with a professional attitude. However, in the game, his opponents were all fans. Facing them there was much more difficult than facing his team in an official match.

The ones with the most passion would always be the fans. The various teams and clubs continued with their work like Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan. Several other transfers were completed this week, but none of them made as much of a splash as the news of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and Zhang Jiale, so they didn’t receive much attention. This lasted up until the final day of the week. All of the wild bosses had been cleared away for the week. For the guild elites, it was a rare period of resting time for them. That day, an important transfer was announced: Team Blue Rain’s All Star Yu Feng joins Team Hundred Blossoms for 6 million.

When news of this transfer appeared, many old memories came back. A few were mentioned by some. Old analyses that no one had originally paid any attention to were quickly uncovered.

Yu Feng was most adept at playing the Berserker. He was an All Star and also reputed as the number one Berserker currently in the Alliance. Many also considered that his Berserker character, Brilliant Edge, was also number one too.

But was that really the case?

After this transfer, analyses that no one had paid any attention to were dug out again. It was only then did many Glory fans remember that Team Hundred Blossoms also had a Berserker character. Several years ago, it had been considered the number one Berserker. Its fame had once surpassed Brilliant Edge.

Team Hundred Blossoms wasn’t just some cheerleader team. They were powerhouses that had made it all the way to the finals three times. In comparison, their guild’s development in the game wasn’t as outstanding. It gave off the feeling of an unstable foundation. The team had also lost all three finals. Everyone couldn’t help but feel like the team was missing something.

In any case, three finals was considered an outstanding achievement, surpassed only by Team Excellent Era and Team Tiny Herb. Such a team wouldn’t only be supported by a single powerful character like Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Falling Scattered Flowers!

Previously known as the number one Berserker. Before season five, this character was known to everybody. Along with Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, the duo coupled strength and gentleness and pushed Team Hundred Blossoms to the top in season three. Unfortunately, they were defeated by One Autumn Leaf, giving Team Excellent Era their third championship title.

In season four, the golden generation sprung up in the Alliance. That year, most people paid attention to the astonishing talent of the new rookies, along with the finals between the rivals Team Tyranny and Team Excellent Era. The two flowers of Team Hundred Blossoms had been eliminated in the first round of the playoffs that season.

In season five, the flower duo returned in a swirl of petals and smashed their way through the regular season. Who would have thought that more than halfway through the season, Team Hundred Blossom’s All Star player, the man behind Falling Scattered Flowers, and the number one Berserker Sun Zheping sustained an unexpected hand injury. He could no longer continue playing. Zhang Jiale single-handedly held up the team and was able to carry Team Hundred Blossoms into the finals. In the end, he was defeated by the Magician, Wang Jiexi.

Sun Zheping was unable to completely recover from his hand injury. At the end of the season, he quietly left the pro scene. The situation that Team Hundred Blossoms faced that day was similar to the one after Zhang Jiale’s retirement: at that time, besides Sun Zheping, there were no outstanding Berserkers to take his place.

The number one Berserker Falling Scattered Flowers faded from memory just like that. As luck would have it, in season six, a new star was born in Team Blue Rain. Besides Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian, an outstanding Berserker, Yu Feng, contributed to their championship victory. At the same time, Team Blue Rain created a powerful Berserker character: Brilliant Edge.

The championship light shone down on Yu Feng and Brilliant Edge. The silent Falling Scattered Flowers was quickly forgotten.

In season seven, although Team Hundred Blossoms made it to the playoffs, it had nothing to do with Falling Scattered Flowers. This former brilliance couldn’t be fully brought out because of a player’s mediocrity. In addition, as Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s most important partner, there were times where he couldn’t keep up with Zhang Jiale’s pace, causing numerous embarrassing moments that brought shame to the godly character. That year, Team Blue Rain’s Yu Feng improved rapidly. Brilliant Edge became more complete. Yu Feng and Brilliant Edge became All Stars, officially replacing Falling Scattered Flowers as Glory’s number one Berserker.

In season eight, Zhang Jiale suddenly retired and Team Hundred Blossoms turned into a mess. They had an outstanding rookie though. However, he was a Brawler, not one of the two flowers. That year, Falling Scattered Flowers didn’t even appear on stage. His position was given to Tang Hao and his Brawler, Delilo. The former number one Berserker had fallen to such a state, but who would notice? Everyone was worried about Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Up until today when Yu Feng’s transfer was announced, these old memories suddenly popped up. In particular, the fans, who had supported Team Hundred Blossoms for many years, suddenly remembered that their team had such a powerful character.

The subject of discussion began to revolve around Team Hundred Blossoms. It was very obvious why they wanted to purchase Yu Feng, but did they need to sell off Dazzling Hundred Blossoms? The price was six million. Let alone Tang Hao’s transfer being ten million, even without that transfer, Team Hundred Blossoms could still afford it. If they grabbed Yu Feng and found a new Spitfire player to restart the flower duo, how great would that be?

Many players didn’t understand. When Yu Feng received an interview, his answer slightly revealed the reason. The interview wouldn’t just be for the Hundred Blossoms fans, nor would it only be about Team Hundred Blossoms. In the interview, the reporter asked why Yu Feng chose to leave Team Blue Rain. Did the team give up on him or was it his own choice?

Ever since the start of the summer transfer window, the media was the most blessed and the most pained. They were blessed because of the numerous exciting transfers, that gave them much to write about. Painful because no heads up would be given for these exciting transfers. The transfer news just suddenly popped up out of nowhere, catching the media unprepared. Interviewers needed to prepare, but in order to be the first to get the news, the media was put in a difficult spot.

But what could they do? The first to get an interview with Yu Feng racked their brains to find topics. Why did Yu Feng choose to leave? This first question was not related to Team Hundred Blossoms. They weren’t worried about not getting an answer for those questions though. They were conducting an interview with Team Hundred Blossoms at the same time!

Yu Feng had chosen to leave Team Blue Rain on his own volition. In fact, Team Blue Rain didn’t really want to let go of their All Star player that they had poured resources into. As for Yu Feng’s reason for leaving, although he sort of hid his answer, his meaning came across.

Position!

This was why Yu Feng chose to leave Team Blue Rain.

Team Blue Rain wouldn’t give him a salary any lower than Team Hundred Blossoms would. Team Blue Rain had a better record than the current Team Hundred Blossoms. The only thing that Team Blue Rain couldn’t give to Yu Feng was a core position.

Despite being an All Star player and being considered the number one Berserker, in Team Blue Rain, he was always number three, and no matter how hard he tried, the two spots ahead of him were too far out of reach.

Yu Feng wanted to be the absolute core of a team. Team Blue Rain could not give that to him, so he finally decided to transfer.

Team Hundred Blossoms just happened to need a core player. They cleared away their former strengths and planned on completely rebuilding the team. Yu Feng would undoubtedly become their new core, along with the former number one Berserker, Falling Scattered Flowers.

Chapter 761: Some Stay, Some Leave

Chapter 761: Chapter 761 - Some Stay, Some Leave

Yu Feng’s interview received a lot of attention. The media didn’t want to mess things up for a headline article. A live interview and a plausible reason made it trustworthy information.

Yu Feng’s decision was controversial, but most people could understand his decision.

Fame, money, status....

No matter what one pursued, it would usually be one of these, whether that was in the competitive scene or life as a whole. In the Glory competitive scene, fame and glory reigned supreme. Every pro player pursued these two things. However, this didn’t mean everyone was willing to give up everything in their pursuit for glory.

Some could step back for a higher status, or for higher pay.

If Yu Feng wanted fame and glory, remaining in Team Blue Rain would be better than joining Team Hundred Blossoms. However, Yu Feng clearly placed more importance on his position in the team. As a currently rising All Star, his reason for transferring was completely understandable. No ambitious player would be satisfied with being stuck as the number three player on the team. Those who felt more intensely about their position might even think that they were underappreciated. Leaving was naturally unavoidable for them.

It was because of this reason that Team Tyranny’s strength on paper felt inconceivable. Because they were in the declining years of their career, their desire to be the champions exceeded everything else. Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale were their former team’s ace players. For them, choosing retirement might be a better option than retreating to become the ace player of a middle tier team.

After Yu Feng’s interview, Hundred Blossoms began making publicity statements for the new season. During the past few days, they had to shoulder way too much slander, yet they never responded with any PR. With this transfer, their PR would appear stronger. Hundred Blossoms also knew about the previous successive transfers. Just saying a few words probably wouldn’t be enough to calm their fans down. Only an actual move could make their words prove to be effective and carry weight.

Even so, many fans still didn’t understand why Dazzling Hundred Blossoms needed to be sold, but after Team Hundred Blossoms utilized media outlets to give a few statements, they finally understood the reason a little more.

Team Hundred Blossoms selling Dazzling Hundred Blossoms didn’t mean that they were abandoning the Spitfire class. Next season, Zou Yuan would continue to receive the club’s support. This time, their support would be a lot more intimate. The team wouldn’t force Zou Yuan to adapt to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Instead, they would create a brand new Spitfire character that fit Zou Yuan’s playstyle better.

A character was supposed to be a service to the team, not an obstacle. A powerful God-level character could greatly increase a team’s strength, but to a certain degree, it also inhibit a team’s structure, reducing flexibility and many other possibilities. Team Hundred Blossoms wished to get rid of such a roadblock, allowing the team rebuild and walk a path much more suitable with their current situation.

In front of the media, the spokesperson for Team Hundred Blossoms spoke frankly with assurance. His logical statement won the support of many fans.

Fact number one. There were no outstanding Spitfire players to inherit Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Zhang Jiale was willing to sacrifice everything to become a champion. No matter what Team Hundred Blossoms could have done, they wouldn’t be able to compete with Team Tyranny’s overwhelming force of four ace players. Zhang Jiale was already determined to join this team with the greatest chance at winning the championships. This was fact number two.

Facing these two facts, what was the point in holding onto Dazzling Hundred Blossoms? If it remained on the team, it would just sit there and collect dust. If they sold it for 16 million, the money would be used as a resource for their development in the future. From one perspective, the character would be serving the team one final time.

This topic lasted from the end of the third week, and all the way to the fourth week. The wild bosses refreshed. The elite players were busy once again. Many of them were feeling anxious after being teased with several successive transfers. Everyone was waiting to see which big transfer would happen this week.

What happened this week had been foreshadowed long ago, unlike the past three weeks with surprising transfers one after the other.

The contract for Team Tiny Herb’s vice captain, Deng Fusheng had ended last season. After a considering his options for a period of time, he eventually decided not to renew his contract with Team Tiny Herb. At the same time, he refused all offers from other teams and announced his retirement.

Deng Fusheng had been a pro player for six years. However, he wasn’t a God who had been brilliant as a rookie. He had been a drifter for the first three years. He switched teams three times in three years. This didn’t affect his mindset though. No matter which team he played for, he was always very diligent. Finally, he was noticed by a top team. In season six, the newly-crowned champion Team Tiny Herb sent him an invitation to join them. The following year, he and Team Tiny Herb won their second championship and became a championship team two years in a row.

Deng Fusheng was undoubtedly a very lucky player. Many incredible players gave their all only to achieve nothing. He had come from a middle-tier team and then rode Team Tiny Herb’s championship train to win a championship title. Who knew what magic was at work for that to happen?

Deng Fusheng was very content with his career. He understood that his talent was limited. Getting a position in a team like Tiny Herb was already pushing his limit. Not only did he get a position, but he even became the team’s vice captain, became an All Star player, and even won a championship with the team. He never fired back at those mocking remarks. He happily accepted their words when they called him lucky and never mentioned how much work he had put in.

Deng Fusheng wasn’t young. He had obtained everything he could have wanted from Team Tiny Herb. When Team Tiny Herb needed some fresh blood, he chose to give up his position. Deng Fusheng didn’t have any thoughts towards offers from other teams. He was content with what he had achieved and didn’t feel like he could get anything more from continuing to play the game.

Deng Fusheng’s retirement passed peacefully.

Because he was a very ordinary person. His achievements caused many to be jealous, but besides that, there was nothing to criticize him for. As for those sayings about his good luck, Wang Jiexi once returned fire, which he seldom did: if being lucky is a bad thing, I’d love to be lucky.

Deng Fusheng’s retirement wasn’t sudden. Most players would renew their contract half a year before they even expired. Deng Fusheng hadn’t renew his though, which indicated that he wanted to ponder his future. At his age, retirement was a conclusion that many easily jumped to.

And now he made his decision. Team Tiny Herb took the lead to show their sadness at his departure. They, of course, gave him their blessings for his future. At the same time, they announced a friendly exhibition match for Deng Fusheng that would take place during the break. This exhibition match would be held as thanks for all that Deng Fusheng had contributed to the team. As for the other teams that Deng Fusheng had once been a part of, they also stood up to say a few words. They recalled Deng Fusheng’s situation in the team and praised him. Even his former opponents put in a few good words.

His departure was sad, but also filled with warmth. The sparks flying around because of these past three weeks died down for this old general’s retirement.

Every summer, there would be huge noise over the transfers. At the same time, there was always an old general who retired. Last year, Zhang Jiale’s retirement was undoubtedly a huge event. It was also very sudden and controversial too. It wasn’t as warm or sorrowful as the retirement for most players. This summer, the transfer market was filled with things to see. Deng Fusheng’s retirement added a different feel. Of the retired players this summer, Deng Fusheng would probably be the most important to step down.

There was the passion of those who wanted to continue their struggle and the sorrow of those who no longer wanted to continue.

Deng Fusheng left the scene very peacefully. He didn’t create any miracles, nor was he any legend. However, he still left his mark in the Alliance. Deng Fusheng would begin his new life. The competitive scene would not be shaken because of the recent startling transfers, nor the retirement of a player though.

After Deng Fusheng retired, everyone quickly discussed who Team Tiny Herb would get to take his spot. For a powerhouse championship team like Tiny Herb, any transfer would be noticed by the Alliance.

Besides Deng Fusheng, the best Knight was undoubtedly Team 301’s Xu Bin. Many even considered Xu Bin better than Deng Fusheng. Xu Bin just didn’t look as good because his team wasn’t a championship one.

Xu Bin was the number one guess, but there were many other choices too. Compared to Spitfires, Knights were much more abundant in Glory. It had to do with the class. Knights were main tanks in the game and tanks were considered much more difficult to play than DPS or healer classes.

Glory didn’t completely depend on the Iron Triangle of a tank, a healer, and a damage dealer. However, tanks being an extremely difficult role had never changed.

Playing as a Knight was a show of confidence in one’s skill. Those who couldn’t play the class would have a hard time finding a spot in any party. This class was one that spawned experts. As a result, those who stood out from those experts and became pro players were especially outstanding. This was why many felt that Deng Fusheng was extremely lucky.

After Deng Fusheng’s departure, gossip immediately bounced about. Everyone was guessing what Team Tiny Herb might have in mind.

Chapter 762: Revenge

The fourth week passed fairly peacefully. Although rumors spread of who would take Deng Fusheng’s place, Team Tiny Herb didn’t make any moves. Of course, that was only to the outsiders. In reality, no outsider would know what was really happening within the team. The media did not get a heads up on any of the previous important transfers. They were caught off guard every time.

This time, they could finally see some first signs of a development. Every Knight player watched closely. Even the slightest sway of a blade of grass appeared in the news. Many of the players being talked about had no choice but to come out and deny the allegations. This was the trouble brought about by getting wind of a piece of information ahead of time. With so much disturbance sprouting from all sorts of places, something unexpected just might leak out.

"Who do you think Team Tiny Herb will look for to replace Deng Fusheng?"

How could those at Happy Internet Cafe not notice the gossip spreading around. Wei Chen idled around in the game and asked for Ye Xiu’s opinion out of boredom.

"Xu Bin!" Ye Xiu replied without thinking, "He’s also a very steady and patient player. He’s very similar to Deng Fusheng in that aspect. He could very easily ease into Deng Fusheng’s position in Tiny Herb. If he is signed over, there’s no one more suitable for Tiny Herb."

"If even you can see that, the transfer probably won’t be easy." Wei Chen spoke with a hint of sarcasm.　

"This type of successor is always the hardest to find. Everyone’s watching. How can they not hurry and take the opportunity to bring the hammer down?" Ye Xiu said.

It was as if reality wanted to prove that Ye Xiu was never wrong. After having so many rumors fly around, the dust finally settled. Team 301’s Knight Xu Bin announced that he would be joining Team Tiny Herb. This transfer was a trade. In order to obtain Xu Bin, Team Tiny Herb traded one of their own All Star players. The player for their Grappler, Flying Drops: Li Yihui.

Team Tiny Herb and Team Blue Rain were the only two teams in recent years to have three All Star players in a single team. However, everything had now been thrown into disorder this summer.

Yu Feng had left Team Blue Rain. On Team Tiny Herb, Deng Fusheng retired and Li Yihui had been let go. Although the new Xu Bin would very likely become an All Star this upcoming season, Team Tiny Herb would only have two All Stars until that happened.

The two teams were looking to cut their losses, searching for any breakthroughs this summer transfer window. In the beginning, the two teams remained quiet. Their first movements weakened the team’s strength. No one felt like these two powerhouses would just resign themselves to their losses. In the following few days, these two would most likely make huge moves. The gossip generals once again responded instantly, analyzing the future plans of these two teams. They ignored the needs of other teams and focused solely on their own team if they had the choice to pick whoever they wanted freely.

On the fifth week, the announcement of an enormous purchase offer made everyone’s glasses fall off. The important transfer wasn’t from Team Blue Rain or Team Tiny Herb, but the reigning champions, Team Samsara.

Champion teams rarely made any huge changes. They generally sought out small fixes. Team Samsara’s offer was to patch up one of their weaknesses. After Team Tiny Herb’s Li Yihui was traded for Xu Bin, Team Samsara offered a price of 8 million for the currently unused Grappler: Flying Drops.

Team Tiny Herb had yet to find a replacement for their loss and someone had put their hands in the pot. Their fans had a hard time enduring it. They pointed their fingers at Samsara and started throwing slander at them. It was an official purchase though. There was nothing wrong with what they did. In the end, the Tiny Herb fans could only say stuff like ‘don’t get carried away’.

The fans of both teams argued back and forth. The two teams haggled. In the end, Flying Drops was sold over to Team Samsara for a price of 9.5 million.

Tiny Herb’s fans shut their mouths in astonishment, which naturally drew mocking remarks from Samsara’s, but what could they do? The fans didn’t understand the Club’s intentions. Encountering a mishap and being slapped in the face was nothing new. After all, the clubs would never publicly reveal their plans. Even if the team had initially planned on selling Flying Drops, another team yelling out a price wasn’t a part of the plan. Why else did the initial offer of 8 million turn into 9.5 million? If the team wanted others to know of their intentions, Team Samsara probably wouldn’t have been able to quote a price of 8 million.

Flying Drops was also an All Star level Grappler. Samsara’s Grappler Lu Boyuan performed exceptionally well in the playoffs last season. The addition of an All Star character would perfectly complement the team’s needs.

As for Team Tiny Herb, what did they plan on doing by getting rid of both Li Yuhui and Flying Drops? No one understood. What Tiny Herb or Blue Rain would do next was a question on everyone’s minds.

Halfway through the fifth week, July ended and August began.

During this period of time, Happy Internet Cafe’s business was doing well. Their wild boss hunts in the Heavenly Domain were going quite smoothly as well. Rumors and gossip continued to fly about everyday. Along with having the opportunity to spend time with her idol, Chen Guo was having the summer of her life. It was the first day of August. When she woke up, she thought today would be just like any other day , but she discovered that she was actually the last one to arrive. The mood in the practice room was grave.

"Did something new happen?" This was Chen Guo’s first reaction. She immediately ran to the computer to check.

"Boss, it’s time to register." Ye Xiu said.　

"Register?" Chen Guo was puzzled.

"Register for the Challenger League!" Ye Xiu said.

"OH!" Chen Guo suddenly understood. The registration period for next season’s Challenger League began on the first day of August. During this month, a team could sign up for the Challenger League, as long as the team fulfilled the requirement of having six players. The winner of the Challenger League would win the right to join the Alliance and officially become a professional team.

All their work over the past few months had all been for this very day. To think she had forgotten! Chen Guo felt ashamed.

"Then we’re just going to register like this?" Chen Guo looked at the others in the room, "It’s just going to be who we have now?"

"There’s also Little Hands and Cold Light. Ah, no it’s Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light." Steamed Bun reminded Chen Guo.

Chen Guo thought about it for a second before nodding her head. She didn’t bother explaining to Steamed Bun that she said who we have now not who we have here, but when she nodded her head, she also asked: "What about Deception?"

"That guy still lacks discipline!" Ye Xiu sighed.

"In all the times that you’ve discipline him, have you ever told him who you were?" Chen Guo asked.

"I did occasionally." Ye Xiu said.

"Occasionally..." Chen Guo wanted to cry, so you’re saying Deception died for nothing countless times!

"But dying so many times, if he isn’t stupid, he should know that I’m the one behind it." Ye Xiu said.

"Why exactly do you keep on killing him for?" Chen Guo asked.

"He has no future in scrap picking, so he should go play for us!" Ye Xiu waved his hands.

"What type of logic is that?" Chen Guo wiped her forehead.

"Once his interest in scrap picking disappears completely, he will be more likely to consider my proposal, no?"

"So you’re saying you’re not certain." Chen Guo said.

"Well yeah, it’s not like we’re close friends or anything." Ye Xiu said.

"..."

"Now I see that this youngster has quite the willpower!" Ye Xiu looked at his monitor and sighed.

Tang Rou stuck her head into the conversation: "From the recent statistics provided by Little An, that guy has started showing up less and less."

"Could I have killed him too much and made him so depressed that he’s thinking of deleting his account?" Ye Xiu said.

"You’ve ruined a good seed." Chen Guo grieved.

"It’s also possible that he’s figured out your schedule, so he avoids you guys like how you guys avoid Zhang Xinjie." Wei Chen said.

"It’s us, not you guys. You’ve killed him many times too." Ye Xiu corrected Wei Chen first before nodding his head: "That’s also very likely. It seems like we need to ask for help!"

"Ask for help? ‘Chen Guo asked.

Soon afterwards, Ye Xiu opened up QQ and clicked on one of the many pro player group chats. He sent out a big horn emoji and started shouting wildly: "Zhang Xinjie, Zhang Xinjie, Old Lin, Old Lin, if you’re here, say here."

Amidst the eyes of a bunch of pro players, Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan wiped the sweat off their forehead through emojis.

Chen Guo watched with excitement! All of them were huge names in Glory. They were using the same sweat-wipe and black line emojis like ordinary people. It appeared very funny.

"PM." Ye Xiu said.

"Breaking news! There’s breaking news!!" Someone shouted. Chen Guo saw that it was Team Void’s Li Xu, a merciless Assassin. Who would have thought that he was a gossiper?

Ye Xiu ignored his groundless screeching. Zhang Xinjie messaged Ye Xiu: "What’s up?"

"Where’s Old Lin?" Ye Xiu asked.

"He’s with me. Is there something you need?"

"I need some help." Ye Xiu said.

"What help?"

"Help killing a person." Ye Xiu said.

He hastily added: "In the game! Don’t think too much!"

Chen Guo wiped some sweat away. Did he really need to say that? Zhang Xinjie was a serious person, but would he go so far as to think Ye Xiu actually meant "kill a person in real life."

"Who?" Zhang Xinjie ignored Ye Xiu’s comment and continued.

"He’s sometimes called Deception, sometimes called Not White, sometimes called White Not. He’s a scrap picker." Ye Xiu said.

"What did he do to offend you?" Zhang Xinjie asked.

"He’s a scrap picker. He stole my stuff. That’s a very serious crime!" Ye Xiu said.

"Do you really need to go so far? You even know what his alternate accounts are! You must have killed him several times already!" Zhang Xinjie said.

"How narrow-minded of you! You guys are taking advantage of me while I’m away to win a championship title. You guys have offended me too. Just wait for me to come back! I’ll destroy you guys!" Ye Xiu said.

"Speak after you pass through the Challenger League before talking!" Zhang Xinjie had already closed the chat window.

"Help me kill him!" Ye Xiu urged.

"If I see him." Zhang Xinjie continued to be serious. If he saw him, he’d kill him. If not, he wouldn’t go out of his way.

"What did Ye Qiu want?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"He says there’s a scrap picker who stole his stuff. He wants us to kill him if we see him." Zhang Xinjie said.

"Oh, then if we see him, we’ll kill him!" Lin Jingyan replied. It was a small matter. For these two Gods, it was as simple as moving their hands. If someone begged you to lift up your hands a bit, why should you refuse?

Chapter 763: Actually Collusion

Chen Guo was dumbstruck.

Poor Deception! At night, he would die to Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. During the day, he faced Zhang XInjie and Lin Jingyan. All Stars would be rotating shifts with a mission to kill him. How was he supposed to even play Glory? Seeing this set-up, Chen Guo felt like it must succeed, or else it would truly be too sad.

"Should we wait for him before registering?" Chen Guo asked.

"Sure. We just need to register before the month ends." Ye Xiu tapped the table.

"Will Little An and Luo Ji be coming over? When the time comes for Deception to join, we might be able to gather everyone together." Chen Guo said.

An Wenyi and Luo Ji were university students. They were currently on vacation. An Wenyi was first going to return home for a period of time. He said that he would pay a visit in August. Luo Ji was currently studying under his professor. He could only start once his break in August started, but he said that he would try to come and take a look.

August had arrived. Neither of the two said when exactly they would be coming. From what they said, they could be coming any day now.

Wei Chen had guessed Deception’s situation correctly. After being killed over and over again while scrap picking, he had figured out that it was all because of Ye Xiu. No one could stay up 24/7 without rest. Who didn’t know that? As a result, Deception began playing the time difference game with Ye Xiu. Sure enough, as soon as he started his activities during the day. His situation instantly improved.

Deception was quite cunning. He didn’t completely switch schedules. From time to time, he would intentionally play at night. He couldn’t play 24/7 either though. He left traces of his activity at night, but spent the majority of the time in the day. Unfortunately, An Wenyi had carefully kept track of his appearance rate. Along with someone as cunning as Wei Chen analyzing it, his trickery was easily exposed.

Deception knew very well that he would not encounter any of those guys during the early morning. That morning, Deception logged in full of joy. Those guys weren’t going to appear, so it didn’t matter if he was using his main or his alternate account. His alternates were useless anyways.

Deception went out for a stroll, obviously thinking about scrap picking, but as a lone wolf, what he lacked most was information, which restricted the scope of Deception’s scrap picking. However, he had been in the business for a long time and had accumulated plenty of work experience. He would notice details that could be used to infer things that were going on.

For example, he would do his best to keep track of which wild bosses had spawned each week. He would obviously avoid any areas where the wild boss had already been killed. He also took note of the teleportation portals, waiting at places where players had to pass through. If a huge number of guild players were moving towards a certain area, something was mostly likely happening.

Wild boss battles were Deception’s favorite scrap picking fields. It was like how people who often flew on planes didn’t want to ride on trains anymore. When there was so much profit to be earned, Deception could no longer look at small fights between normal players. No matter how much he scrap picked from normal players, they could never compare with what the elite guild players dropped.

Wild bosses were where the club guild’s most high-end battles took place. A high-end scrap picker like Deception would only scrap pick here.

After getting rid of his biggest obstacles using the time difference tactic, Deception excitedly started his day.

August 2nd was Friday of the fifth week of the summer transfer window. There were still three days until the end of the week. The majority of the boss had already been killed. In these situations, finding information was much easier because there was less information to look through.

Deception wasn’t able to make it to the previous boss. He only knew about it after the system announcement appeared. He wasn’t dispirited though. With just himself to rely on, he didn’t make it to most of the wild boss battles. It was almost the weekend too, which meant there were plenty more opportunities.

Finally, the movements resulting from the spawn of a new boss caught Deception’s eye. He quietly followed behind a group of Blue Brook Guild players that came out of a teleport portal to a leveling area outside of the city. Soon, he could see the boss as well as the competing guild, Guild Misty Castle.

Recently, the guilds who arrived first were always in a hurry because of the two dominating powers. If either of them showed up, it never spelled good news for them. No one dared to wait for these two opponents to arrive. Every guild would try to attack the boss as much as possible before they showed up. Accumulate more points in aggro before before they could do anything. Afterwards, they would play it by ear. Through this method, they just might be able to get a boss every few days. At least, they wouldn’t be completely empty-handed.

When Blue Brook Guild arrived, they saw Guild Misty Castle and immediately pounced on them. The two guilds clashed very lightly. It was as if they were peacefully fighting the boss together. They wanted to make preparations for Tyrannical Ambition’s arrival and didn’t want to bother with one another.

This scene wasn’t one that Deception liked. No PKing meant no equipment to pick up. The battle had just begun though. Deception didn’t go forward. He patiently waited on the side. Two other guilds soon arrived. One of them was Tyrannical Ambition. The guild tags lined the heads of their troops. Deception knew that the moment he was waiting had finally come.

All of the guilds tensed up when Tyrannical Ambition appeared. Deception could even hear gasps of terror from many of the players. Deception ignored their nervousness. It had nothing to do with him. Once the bloody battle began, he would rush forward to pick up equipment.

How much would he earn today?

Deception calculated in his mind. Tyrannical Ambition walked closer and closer to him. He was unexpectedly in the middle between the two Tyrannical Ambition groups.

Deception didn’t think too much of it. He thought it was one of Tyrannical Ambition’s tactics. Unfortunately, he didn’t know about the conversation that was taking place between the leaders of the two Tyrannical Ambition groups.

"Hm? Isn’t he that guy Ye Qiu was talling us about?" Lin Jingyan said.

"Deception. Yes, that’s the name." Zhang Xinjie replied.

"Look at how sneaky he’s acting. It looks like he really does intend on scrap picking." Lin Jingyan said.

"Mm, let’s hurry up and kill him. We shouldn’t waste any more time." Zhang Xinjie replied. He had already given the orders. Lin Jingyan did the same.

Tyrannical Ambition carried out their God’s orders and attacked Deception.

Deception was dead. He wasn’t even able to say anything before he died. The troops instantly burst him down. He was thinking right now: was it some sort of accident?

Because from his ghost’s perspective, he could see Tyrannical Ambition charging towards the boss. They didn’t stop in order to kill him. Killing him didn’t even seem to be intentional!

Yeah! There were two pro players commanding their hundred troops. Targeting him on purpose would be a joke.

Deception revived and returned. Good. The boss battle hadn’t ended yet. It was completely shrouded in chaos, the perfect opportunity for him to scrap pick. Deception immediately rushed over. Tyrannical Ambition’s players meticulously took note of whatever their two pro players were concerned about. Someone immediately reported: "That Ninja we previously killed has returned."

"Oh, kill him!" Zhang Xinjie said bluntly. Tyrannical Ambition immediately focused their fire onto Deception.

This time, Deception was aware and immediately dodged, but facing two Gods, he was unable to escape.

Deception stared stupidly at his screen.　　

In the past, he had never seen a club guild put in so much effort just for him, especially during a critical moment like for a wild boss.

Deception was very experienced. He always chose to move when the other side had no time to spare on him. If not, if he were to just directly charge into the middle of an intense exchange, no matter how skilled he was, he would still be smashed into a pulp! However, this time, the other side actually turned around to attack him, not caring about anything else. This situation was like when that b*stard was chasing him! Deception’s brain was drawing blanks. Those two were clearly from Team Tyranny. What’s going on?

"Oh? That guy’s got some skill!" At this moment, Lin Jingyan noticed that Deception was still in somewhat good shape. He started to gain some interest and personally threw a brick at him.

With an expert personally coming out along with the support of numerous others, Deception was unable to escape.

"Not bad. To think there was actually someone with that kind of skill in the game." Lin Jingyan said to Zhang Xinjie.

"No wonder that guy is interested in him. He probably doesn’t just want revenge does he?" Zhang Xinjie said.

"You actually believed the lie that he came up with!" Lin Jingyan laughed.

"Let’s see if he comes back." Zhang Xinjie said.

"If he comes back, do we kill him?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"Kill him. We agreed, so of course we’ll kill him." Zhang Xinjie didn’t hesitate.

Zhang Xinjie and Lin Jingyan were busy in the morning, while Ye Xiu and the others in Happy were fast asleep. The two pro players would definitely be able to see that Deception wasn’t an ordinary player. If they saw that, would they try to steal him away? Chen Guo was worried about this question. Ye Xiu nonchalantly said: "Two ace players just joined their team. Team Tyranny has way too many people right now and should be trying to get rid of them instead. You think they’re going to try to get more people in? Teams play the game to compete, but forming a team isn’t a game. Seeing someone pretty good and roping him into the team is something only those in the game would do."

That morning, Deception died a total of five times.

The first time may have been an accident. The second time was hard for him to believe, but the third and fourth time showed that Deception had finally been noticed, so he switched accounts and came back on again. His character Not White was the fifth contributor to the death count.

Deception finally understood now! He was still being targeted by that guy! Even during the day, he wouldn’t get a chance to scrap pick. He had been scrap picking the entire time. How could he not know that Tyrannical Ambition always happened to come on, when those guys weren’t!

"So those two groups were originally together! No wonder they split up to play at different times!" Deception thought angrily. His logic was a bit too simple though.

Chapter 764: Still Not Interested

Deception had originally found a way to avoid being pursued, but after being killed five times by Tyrannical Ambition, he was finally feeling despair. The strength of Ye Xiu and his guys were something that he couldn’t survive against. As for Tyrannical Ambition, Deception had been caught off guard at first, but later on, he was definitely aware of their hostility, yet he still couldn’t escape. He realized Tyrannical Ambition’s strength as well.

He paid attention to wild bosses day after day. How could he not know of Tyrannical Ambition’s recent dominance in the wild boss competition, so he was able to easily recognize that Tyrannical Ambition was an opponent that he could not handle.

Day and night…..

The entire day was occupied by the enemy! Deception felt like he had no way out. He needed to find that guy and make things clear! Deception thought with hatred.

Because he had been forced to sleep earlier, he could at least console himself for having a good sleep schedule. He yawned and waited resentfully.

Deception soon noticed some movements. Relying on his experience, he quickly found a new wild boss. At the same time, he saw Heavenly Justice, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade to no surprise.

Deception didn’t hide. He quickly stood in their line of sight. As a result, in the next second, he saw the other side rush towards him like a tidal wave.

Deception hastily ran. He had to at least wait for that guy to show his face! He couldn’t get drowned by these unknown people.

Let There Be Light was that guy’s most recently used account. Deception knew of this piece of information, so he searched for any signs of this Battle Mage.

Ye Xiu obviously wouldn’t hide like Lin Jingyan. On the contrary, whenever he found Deception, he would personally greet him. However, Deception always avoided him like a mouse running from a cat. Deception didn’t run this time though. Since he was looking for Ye Xiu’s character, the two quickly came across each other.

"How has your scrap picking been going these days?" When the two faced each other, Deception heard Let There Be Light ask.

Deception was trembling with anger. He really wanted to charge at him and start fighting, but he knew that, against this person, let alone him having a numbers advantage, he had no chance in a 1v1 either.

At this moment, Deception felt like he was being forced to lower his head. That wasn’t a good feeling at all. He was already thinking about abandoning his original plan and preparing to fight to the death with this person, but he suddenly felt the pressure lessen. The other side seemed to have calmed down. He didn’t need to dodge around anymore. Then, he heard that guy continue: "See! See as long as we put in more effort, scrap picking isn’t possible. What’s the point in doing something pointless?"

Deception was slightly startled.

Although his words weren’t entirely correct, it had some logic to it. Deception frequently scrap picked during wild boss battles. He obviously knew that, for the absolute majority of the time, it wasn’t that his individual skill was vastly superior, but rather the other side was busy with the wild boss and had no time to deal with him. Now he seemed to have encountered someone who was willing to put in the time and effort to kill him, so not only was he unable to scrap pick, he was turned into scrap time after time.

"Join our team! If you really find it boring, then it won’t be too late to go back to scrap picking." Ye Xiu said.

"Fine!" Deception spoke his first word since the start of the conversation.

"Oh?" Ye Xiu was surprised, but Deception’s reply sounded firm and decisive. He couldn’t waste time, so he asked: "Is it convenient for you to come over to our place?"

"Where?" Deception asked.

Ye Xiu told him their location. After Deception replied with an "Okay", he didn’t wait for Ye Xiu to ask anything further and his character suddenly stopped moving.

"DId he just log off?" Ye Xiu wondered. Not long afterwards, Deception had disappeared. Sure enough, he had forcefully closed the game.

"He agreed just like that?" Ye Xiu was still figuring out what had just happened. Deception’s decisiveness exceeded his expectations.

"No way. That fast? Didn’t he just arrive?" Wei Chen had been paying attention to their situation, but he only heard Ye Xiu talk. He couldn’t hear any of Deception’s replies.

"Yeah. I just said a few words and he agreed." Ye Xiu said.　　

"F*ck, so straightforward! There aren’t going to be any problems, right?" Wei Chen found it hard to believe.

"I have no idea!" Ye Xiu really didn’t know because he wasn’t familiar at all with Deception.

"F*ck, he’s not going to come over and PK you in real life because he knows your address now, right? I feel like it’s definitely possible!" Wei Chen said in a serious tone. Deception had been living in an abyss of suffering these past few days. Everyone here was a target of resentment for him!

"Mm, I can’t rule out that possibility. It’s a good thing I left him with your name." Ye Xiu said.

"What the f*ck!!" Wei Chen cursed. Ye Xiu messaged him with a typed answer, so it was easy for the other side to record it! Wei Chen didn’t know what he had written. Now that he heard about it, he was furious.

"You must be careful in the future." Ye Xiu said sincerely.

"You b*stard….." Wei Chen cursed. He wasn’t really scared though. After all, with his background, he might even be less scared of a real life fight than an in-game fight, but on the morning of the next day, when he left the Internet Cafe back to his living place, Wei Chen still looked around the Internet Cafe. He didn’t find any particularly good weapons to use though. In the end, he grabbed a few pull-top cans and put them in a plastic bag. He carried them firmly in his hands and left. Steamed Bun saw Wei Chen’s actions and seemed to think hard for a few moments before nodding his head: "He’s already grabbed so many, so I won’t need to." He left too.

Chen Guo was speechless. She would frequently look over at Ye Xiu’s screen when something happened. She had seen the message that Ye Xiu had given Deception. The person that he told Deception to look for was Ye Xiu, not Wei Chen.

Chen Guo didn’t reveal the truth to Wei Chen though. She was secretly hoping for those two shameless guys to fight each other. Perhaps that would make the world peaceful again? Chen Guo tried to justify her actions.

There was nothing to do today. Then, at 3:17AM, someone knocked on their practice door. An employee stuck his head in: "Boss, someone’s waiting downstairs?"

"What?" Chen Guo was surprised.

"Someone is looking for Brother Ye." The employee said.

Ever since Excellent Era came over without an invitation, Chen Guo had given her employees some instructions on what to do in such situations. If a person was looking for someone here, have them wait downstairs. Don’t directly lead them up here, especially to the practice room.

The employee followed her directions, but it was very unusual for a person to be looking for someone at 3:17AM.

He’s not trying to take advantage while it’s dark to take revenge, right? Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu and asked: "How many people?"

"Just one person." The employee replied.

"What did he bring?" Chen Guo asked.

"I don’t think he brought anything." The employee said.

"Shall we go down and have a look?’ Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

"Of course." Ye Xiu had already gotten up. The others also heard that someone had come looking for Ye Xiu at three in the morning and felt that it was very strange. They also got up.

Not long afterwards, they headed downstairs together and saw a guy standing by the front desk. He stared expressionlessly at the stairs. For him, that was where the employee had gone to go look for the people he was trying to find.

"Who’s looking for me?" Ye Xiu asked despite already knowing the answer. It could be considered as a "I’m Ye Xiu".

"Me." That person replied, "Deception."

"Oh, it really is you! Why did you come at this time?" Ye Xiu said.

"The flight was at 12." Deception said.

"Oh….." Everyone suddenly understood. It turns out that this brother was indeed very decisive! He said he would come and he had bought a plane ticket here immediately.

"Where did you come from?" Chen Guo asked.

"City K." Deception said.

"What’s your horoscope?" Steamed Bun also asked.

"..."

"Steamed Bun, stop with that nonsense." Ye Xiu interrupted Steamed Bun, "Let’s go upstairs and have a chat!"

They brought Deception upstairs to the practice room. Deception looked around left and right, but didn’t say anything. He just continued to stand there expressionlessly. Everyone was starting to carefully measure up this new person.

Deception wasn’t too tall. He was around 170cm tall. His hair was around medium length. He was neither handsome nor ugly. His expressionless face gave them a hostile feeling though. Besides the hostility, he even seemed to carry a bit of murderous intent. That was obvious though. Anyone who had gone through what Deception had experienced would definitely be angry at Ye Xiu too.

"What’s your name?" Ye Xiu asked for his real name.

"Mo Fan." Deception replied.

"Oh, shall I explain to your our team’s situation, then?" Ye Xiu said.

"No need." Mo Fan said.

"Oh?"

"Not interested." Mo Fan said.

"Tsk tsk. You’re being emotional. That’s not good." Ye Xiu sighed.

Everyone was speechless. It would be strange if he wasn’t feeling any emotion!

"Real matches will start in September. Experience the team for yourself until then. How about you stay here for a month!" Ye Xiu said.

"..." Mo Fan declined to comment.

"You weren’t planning on coming over to say you’re not interested and then going back to scrap pick, right?" Ye Xiu said.

Mo Fan didn’t reply, but from the looks of it, it seemed like that was indeed what he had planned on doing.

"How irresponsible! You’ve traveled such a long way to get here. Even if it’s cheaper to fly in the early morning, it still isn’t convenient! How about you stay here for a few days and then decide?" Ye Xiu arranged, "Pull an all nighter with us. Then, tomorrow you can follow those two back. There’s a place for you to live there. You don’t need to worry about anything. Did you bring anything with you?"

"My account card." Mo Fan said.

Chapter 765: Nothing to Do

Mo Fan stayed behind to pull an all nighter.

Mo Fan wasn’t a stranger to pulling all nighters, but it was his first doing it with so many other people. After sitting down expressionlessly at an empty seat, the person next to him gave him a smile.

"Hi..." Mo Fan couldn’t ignore Su Mucheng’s friendly smile and greeted her, but then he saw the character on her screen: Chasing Haze…...

Mo Fan wanted to retract his greeting. Chasing Haze had blasted him into dust numerous times over these past few days. She was the most troublesome enemy next to Ye Xiu. So it’s this girl? He couldn’t connect that warm smile with that fierce Launcher from the game!

Too deceitful! Mo Fan thought to himself, while quietly sizing up everyone else. Although the Launcher was sharper, the female Battle Mage was much more ferocious! Which one? Mo Fan looked at Chen Guo and Tang Rou. It was easy to connect beauty with kindness. Seeing those two girls, no matter which one was the Battle Mage, Mo Fan only had one evaluation: too deceitful.

After looking over everyone, Mo Fan had nothing to do. What should I do? After logging into the game, he felt a bit bored. Usually, he would organize his information on wild bosses and then pay attention to any potential areas, but did he need to do any of that now?

Mo Fan was staring blankly at his screen, when he suddenly heard Ye Xiu call out: "Mo Fan, how about you come and hunt wild bosses with us?"　

"Hm?"

"Add me as a friend first." Ye Xiu said.　

After going through their game settings, the two turned on the option to accept friend invites and eventually added each other as friends.

"If a boss spawns, I’ll PM you." Ye Xiu messaged.

"And if there isn’t one?" Mo Fan couldn’t help but ask.　

"You’re free to do whatever you want." Ye Xiu replied.

Thus, he just sat there staring at his screen up until the sun came up. Starting from when Mo Fan arrived at Happy Internet Cafe at around 3 o’clock until now, not a single wild boss had spawned. Wei Chen was in an extremely bad mood and looked at Mo Fan with hostility. It was as if he believed Mo Fan was the reason that no bosses were spawning today. Wei Chen even searched around for the weapons that he found yesterday, but he couldn’t even find them. Then, he remembered that Steamed Bun had finished all of the drinks long ago.

"Punk, come with us!" After breakfast, Wei Chen called out to Mo Fan fiercely.

Mo Fan wasn’t scared at all by Wei Chen’s gangster-like personality. He had finished his breakfast a while ago and was staring blankly out into the distance. He stood up and followed Wei Chen, Steamed Bun, and Qiao Yifan out. He didn’t say goodbye to Ye Xiu or the others who had stayed.

"This person..." Chen Guo stumbled on her words. She didn’t know what to say. After awhile, she asked Su Mucheng and Tang Rou: "Did any of you talk to him?"

"No." Tang Rou shook her head.

"I smiled at him once." Su Mucheng said.

"It seems like he isn’t the type who likes to socialize." Chen Guo said to Ye Xiu.

"Seems like it." Ye Xiu said.

"Then what do we do? What if he’s determined to remain uninterested in our team?" Chen Guo asked.

"If he really isn’t interested, then there’s no point in keeping him." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was surprised at first, but she soon understood Ye Xiu’s meaning.

"But what if his mood doesn’t change?" Chen Guo said.

"I hope not!" Ye Xiu sighed.

"Don’t be like you have nothing to do with this!" Chen Guo was angry, "He’s feeling like that all because of what you’ve done to him."

"We have to take things step by step!" Ye Xiu said, "I feel like our current situation isn’t too bad. At least, he’s here."

Then, they went to rest. When they woke up and logged into the game, they discovered that while they were away, the last six bosses of the week had all spawned. Tyrannical Ambition happily and easily took them all. Ye Xiu and the others could only sigh at their bad luck. Wei Chen gave Mo Fan a hateful look. It was a classic example of releasing one’s anger on someone who didn’t deserve it. Mo Fan ignored it though.

"He’s got a strong will." Ye Xiu continued to sigh.

With no wild bosses left, there wasn’t much point in playing the game for the people in this room. Ye Xiu went into the Arena and entered the equipment editor. He pulled up numerous resources for materials and began studying the next step of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Wei Chen wasn’t idle though! Samsara might not have anything to do for him, but that wasn’t his main work. In the competitive scene, a single Silver weapon wasn’t enough. Wei Chen began researching other equipment based on what he required.

As for Chen Guo, she needed to manage the guild. Quite a few players in the tenth server managed to reach Level 70. However, the majority of these new players from the new server were stuck on the Heavenly Domain quests. Players ambitious enough to enter the Heavenly Domain spent the majority of their time here. For these players, as long as they put in enough time and work, they would be able to pass the regular quests, but the Arena requirements actually required a certain amount of skill to pass. Why else did the saying "the Heavenly Domain had no noobs" exist?

The tenth server’s Guild Happy had no Ye Xiu to support them, so their development was rather mediocre, but they had a solid following now. Chen Guo frequently leaked out that the guild’s growth in the Heavenly Domain was flourishing. The guild was just waiting for them to join. Her words fired up the players. Was Guild Happy thriving in the Heavenly Domain? Everyone had their own opinions. From their competitiveness for wild bosses, Guild Happy could stand proud over all of the player guilds and even the majority of the Club guilds.

But from a numbers perspective, their guild level and size were terrible. Most of them were alternate accounts, which didn’t even appear online. The several friends that Chen Guo had urged to come pretty much left after making up for the shortage of members. They needed the guild’s Guardian buff. However, Happy’s guild level was so low. With just their few people, how could they ever hope to reach max level? That wasn’t something these stopgaps could accomplish.

Chen Guo felt like she could rally a great number of supporter through Ye Qiu’s name. However, considering that the guild would need to an integral foundation for their pro team, Guild Happy would also need trustworthy elite members. As a result, Chen Guo felt like it was better to develop slowly, so the guild didn’t randomly add members in order to hurry and level up the guild. Chen Guo was looking forward to those in the new server. Those new players had been with the guild the entire way. They could be considered as having a certain level of emotional attachment to the guild. Chen Guo awaited for the day that they poured into the Heavenly Domain.

Chen Guo busied herself with these things. When Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Qiao Yifan weren’t busy fighting for wild bosses, they dungeoned, killed monsters, or went to the Arena to carry out specialized and purposeful training.

Everyone seemed to have their own tasks to take care of. Mo Fan was at a loss though. He decided to observe what Su Mucheng and everyone else was busy with.

Then, he saw Su Mucheng log out of the game. She opened up a web browser and did a quick search. A window popped up on her screen and a TV show began playing. Su Mucheng took out a bag of melon seeds from her pocket, put it on the table, and started busying herself with those.

But... he couldn’t copy doing that!

Mo Fan’s poker face was about to change into a different expression. Was this what a rumored pro team was like? Watch TV and eat melon seeds when there was nothing to do….. Just like that?

Mo Fan was astonished. Su Mucheng felt Mo Fan looking towards her side and turned her head. She saw Mo Fan staring at the bag of melon seeds on her table, so she grabbed the bag and started pouring out melon seeds onto his side of the table.

"No need..." By the time Mo Fan responded, half the bag had been poured out onto the table. Su Mucheng gave him a friendly smile again before going back to watching her TV show.

Should I also watch a show? Mo Fan was at a loss. He glanced at Su Mucheng’s screen. The show’s name was called "A Familiar Stranger". She was 24 episodes in. If he started watching now, he wouldn’t be able to keep up.

Mo Fan felt stupid right now. He even forgot what he usually did when he wasn’t scrap picking. He stayed lost in thought all the way until dinner came, when Ye Xiu asked him "How are you feeling?" Mo Fan replied "Very bored."

"Yes." Ye Xiu said, "The season hasn’t started yet. It’s the preparation period right now."

"What do I need to prepare?" Mo Fan asked. When he asked this question, he couldn’t help but glanced at Su Mucheng. Even if he didn’t know how to prepare, he definitely knew that watching TV and eating melon seeds wasn’t preparing.

"For now, stealing bosses and wild boss materials to create Silver equipment are our main priorities." Ye Xiu said.

"Stealing wild boss materials!" Mo Fan’s expressionless face actually brightened up a bit.

"It’s more of killing wild bosses. We split the materials after killing a boss." Ye Xiu explained. It wouldn’t be good if Mo Fan followed along to help kill the boss and then when it was time to split the materials, it would be very embarrassing if he rushed forward to grab the materials that Loulan Slash or Yue Ziqin or White Stream or Martial Awareness dropped onto the ground.

"That’s because wild boss materials are the rarest and most important materials. As for other materials, there were other ways to obtain them. They’re easier to get, so there’s no need to fight over them." Chen Guo added. When the word "steal" was mentioned, Mo Fan’s spirited look gave her a fright.

"There aren’t anymore wild bosses left this week." Mo Fan said.

"Yeah, so everyone can relax for the rest of this week and then we start again next week." Ye Xiu said.

"...."

"But not for you." Ye Xiu suddenly switched topics, "You need to receive training. If not, how are you going to compete in a pro match?"

Before Mo Fan could reply, he suddenly heard a shout from the Internet Cafe downstairs: "D*mn, Zhao Yang is going to transfer too!!"

"What?" During the transfer window, everyone was sensitive towards this type of news. When everyone at the table heard this shout, they immediately got up and stood around a computer. Mo Fan was suddenly the only one at the table.

They weren’t the only ones excited. The entire Internet Cafe exploded into noises of discussion about the news of this Zhao Yang.

"Is the pro scene... really that interesting?" The liveliness of the Internet Cafe astonished Mo Fan. He took another bite and his mind began to wander.

Chapter 766: Student Luo Ji

"So it was just a rumor. Everyone’s making a fuss over nothing!!!" Ye Xiu and the others in the room got up quickly and came back just as quickly. They did a quick search and discovered that it was only speculation. Moreover, the reasoning wasn’t even very convincing. The person who shouted it out in a hurry was a brainless gossiper.

Chen Guo said as she hatefully glanced around the Internet Cafe. She wanted to see who that idiot was. Starting a rumor in this type of place should be considered a capital offense.

The others followed after her and sat back down. In reality, despite everyone jumping up together all at once to see the news, not everyone cared too much about the transfers. For example, Su Mucheng and Tang Rou both wore indifferent expressions on their faces. Steamed Bun was just blindly following the crowd…...

But in Mo Fan’s eyes, the attention given to this piece of news by these guys as well as the entire Internet Cafe made him quite curious about the pro scene.

Although Zhao Yang’s transfer was only a rumor, it wasn’t anything strange to hear about him.

Zhao Yang was an All Star player, but was always the most lacking compared to all the other All Stars. He and his Qi Master character Immeasurable Sea were a part of Team Seaside. Team Seaside was a classic example of a middle-tier team, which wasn’t good enough to reach the top, but still better than those on the bottom. Neither the playoffs nor relegations seemed to be any concern to the team.

No team with an All Star player and character had as little of a future as Team Seaside did. Even the relegated Team Excellent Era had once been a brilliant team. Despite being relegated, the team was still able to attract an All Star like Xiao Shiqin to join their ranks. Their case was extremely unusual. As for Team Seaside, although the team possessed an All Star player and character, they weren’t competitive enough to make it to the playoffs. It was truly a bit embarrassing.

Of course, Team Seaside had their reasons.

There were four teams with only one All Star player: Team Royal Style, Team Seaside, Team 301, and Team Thunderclap.

The other three had the competitive strength to make it into the playoffs. Team 301 and Team Thunderclap had even won a spot last season. Team 301 had their All Star captain Yang Cong and his character Scene Killer, but apart from that, the team also had Xu Bin, a very skilled player. Xu Bin was never considered any worse than the All Star Knight Deng Fusheng. Some even thought that he was better than Deng Fusheng.

Team Thunderclap used to have the All Star player, Xiao Shiqin. A Master Tactician could help a team shine. As a result, Team Thunderclap was much more threatening than Team Seaside.

As for Team Royal Style, although they failed to make it into the playoffs last season, they had a powerful background. In season one, the team had competed against Team Excellent Era in the finals. The team’s core Exorcist, Peaceful Hermit, had been famous since the start of the Alliance. It was a top-tier God character ranked alongside One Autumn Leaf and Desert Dust.

If one were to say that Peaceful Hermit was stronger than Team Seaside’s Immeasurable Sea, no one would have any objections.

Looking from this perspective, Team Seaside seemed to be somewhat inadequate. Their barely passable win record was very reasonable. However, the team’s All Star player might not think so. With so many big-name transfers this summer, who knew if he might transfer?

That was the logic behind the rumor of Zhao Yang’s transfer. Sure, it was possible, but coming to that conclusion with just that sort of weak reason was a bit far-fetched. After Ye Xiu and the others talked about Zhao Yang’s situation, they didn’t take the rumor to heart. As expected, on the second day, Team Seaside and Zhao Yang made a public announcement expressing that the two sides were content with their current situation and had no plans on separating.

Of course, a public statement wasn’t necessarily proof. It might just be a marketing method. The rumor from yesterday was truly unreliable. It was practically the same as someone taking a piece of fantasy work as non-fiction.

The day passed by and the new week began. During their resting time in the daytime, another guest arrived at the Internet Cafe. Luo Ji, Concealed Light’s owner, had finished helping his professor with his task and had now come to report to Happy Internet Cafe.

The employee working at the time knew that the boss was currently sleeping, but he still called for her. If something happened in the Internet Cafe, there were always ways to call for the boss!

When they woke up from the call, they headed downstairs to take a look. Luo Ji was standing beside the front desk with a big backpack on his shoulders. He wasn’t tall, but he was dressed neatly. He was looking around curiously in a pure and innocent manner.

"Concealed Light!" Ye Xiu greeted. He called him by his in-game name first because he was more used to it. Concealed Light wasn’t like Deception, who wouldn’t tell him his real name. He never really called him by his real name in the game either.

"Oh!" Student Luo Ji looked over and saw Ye Xiu. He immediately smiled.

"You’re here." Ye Xiu went over to pat him.

"Mm." Luo Ji nodded his head.

It was naturally time to introduce him to the others. Luo Ji said hi three times in a row, but didn’t say anything else. He had only started playing Glory when the tenth server had opened. Although he might admire pro players, he wouldn’t have that same zealotry as Chen Guo. Su Mucheng didn’t shock him too much.

"Let’s go up!" Then, they went to the second floor’s practice room.

"This is the practice room for now. It’s a bit simple." Chen Guo introduced as the boss, "Your living area is in a nearby area. It’s quite spacious. There are currently four people living there. Steamed Bun is over there too."

"Steamed Bun..." After hearing that name, Luo Ji looked as if he had come across an evil enemy. He felt a headache coming: "Please don’t make me room him with him!"

"Oh, that’s up to you guys... I haven’t made any fixed arrangements." Although Chen Guo said this, when she thought about how Steamed Bun might think, it was very possible that Steamed Bun might directly take Luo Ji’s backpack and find a place for it himself. Would Luo Ji even have a chance to choose? Chen Guo wanted to know too.

"Would you like to take a rest first? Have you eaten lunch?" Chen Guo asked.

"Not yet."

"Perfect."

Everyone ate a simple meal together. During their lunch together, Ye Xiu asked a question, which made Luo Ji want to cry: "Have you still not passed the Heavenly Domain challenge?"

"Yeah….." Luo Ji replied in embarrassment. He was like many others in the guild, still trying to finish the quests. Actually, for new players, it wasn’t unusual for them to be unable to pass the quests at this time. Even in December, when the eleventh server opened, it still wouldn’t be strange for many in the tenth server to be stuck on the quests, but the people that Luo Ji made friends with were on a higher level! Ye Xiu had completed the Heavenly Domain quests at Level 50. The other people that he was familiar with like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun led the pack. Compared to them, he could only feel ashamed!

"Don’t worry. Take your time. Have you kept on practicing the things that I arranged for you?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I’ve been practicing." Luo Ji nodded his head, "But I usually don’t have much free time."

"It’s currently the holidays. It’s the perfect time to intensify your practicing!" Ye Xiu said.

"Okay." Luo Ji didn’t object. He was also anxious about being so far behind everyone else! In the academic field, he was a top student. No matter how modest he was, it wasn’t unusual for him to be a bit arrogant. He didn’t have an easy time in the game though. In the beginning, his guides were criticized as being trash. It hurt him very much. Latter, after Ye Xiu gave him a few tips, he put in some more effort and finally proved the value of his guides. However, in real time in-game combat, compared to the people next to him, Luo Ji lagged behind considerably.

However, compared the rest of the guild’s progress with the Heavenly Domain quests, Luo Ji’s Concealed Light was actually at the front. After all, although the others in the guild might have started playing the game at the same time as Luo Ji, they didn’t have professional coaching and guidance from someone like Ye Xiu.

With the training methods provided to him, if Luo Ji wasn’t any better than other normal players, the practical and theoretical effectiveness would need to be discussed.

Reality proved that these training methods helped Luo Ji improve significantly. It was just that compared to the talented Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, his achievements felt feeble.

When they returned to the practice room after eating lunch, Ye Xiu stood behind Luo Ji to watch him do the quests. Being watched like this made Luo Ji extremely nervous. He had never been so flustered, even when world-class mathematicians watched him solve problems. It was simply because he was more confident in his ability to do math, but in the gaming world, Luo Ji knew that he wasn’t particularly bad, but he definitely wasn’t outstanding. In any case, he didn’t stand out in the game like he did in his studies. Right now, he needed to rise above the millions playing the game and enter the pro scene, where the top two hundred or so players competed. Luo Ji felt like he needed to be even more excellent in the game than he was in his studies. He didn’t dare to be negligent.

Ye Xiu saw his nervousness, so he didn’t say anything in the beginning. He just waited for Luo Ji to slowly get used to it. Once he calmed down and steadied himself, he began carefully observing his progress and his strengths and weaknesses.

Soon, Ye Xiu noticed a very obvious bad habit of Luo Ji’s.

He was too much of a perfectionist!

He would have all of the summons he would use appear on his summon list. Then, he would try and have every one of those summons perform to their maximum capability. He would set his heart towards accomplishing this goal.

This was in contrast to Team Blue Rain’s Lu Hanwen. Lu Hanwen wanted to perfect his eight shadowed Shadow Steps. In practice, there wasn’t any issues, but in real combat, his eight shadows were equivalent to just four shadows.

As a result, for real combat, Lu Hanwen settled for the next best thing and adapted by using six perfect shadows instead. As for Luo Ji, he was currently attempting the challenge quests. It was real combat, which he couldn’t be sloppy with, but because he kept trying to pursue perfection, he kept failing.

"Luo Ji, you’re being too stubborn." Ye Xiu finally spoke.

Chapter 767: Gathering (1)

Ye Xiu told Luo Ji his current problem and was brief and to the point about it. As a talented student of a famous university, his comprehension ability didn’t need to be questioned. Luo Ji nodded his head. He followed Ye Xiu’s suggestion, but his performance still wasn’t satisfactory.

Luo Ji felt ashamed. He turned his head towards Ye Xiu: "I always think I can do it in my mind, but when I try it in practice, it’s always harder than I imagine it to be!"

"It’s get better the more you practice." Ye Xiu urged for him to persevere. He knew that this might not be so easy for Luo Ji because it wasn’t an issue of unfamiliarity with the controls, but rather Luo Ji’s personality. He recalled Luo Ji’s guides and how tediously detailed they were. Those guides could only be completed by relying on that type of personality. Luo Ji wanted to make sure that each step that he took was perfect and without any flaws. Ye Xiu didn’t know if this habit was because he was a mathematician, but in any case, trying to control a character in the game with this mentality would be very difficult, especially when his mechanical skill wasn’t nearly good enough for that level of flawless control.

Luo Ji continued to struggle under Ye Xiu’s guidance. After a while, Ye Xiu couldn’t see any signs of improvement. Trying to overcome an innate habit wasn’t easy. Ye Xiu couldn’t come up with any suggestions. In order to change this situation, Luo Ji would either need to restrain his habit or improve his mechanical skill immensely so that he could pursue the perfection that he desired. Whatever the case was, it couldn’t be accomplished in just a day or two. Changing his habit would at least allow him to display a certain level of skill. It was due to this consideration that Ye Xiu chose to try and change his habit.

Luo Ji was determined. After listening to Ye Xiu’s instructions, he began trying his best to adapt. He forgot about the tiredness from his day of traveling. Ye Xiu and everyone else in Happy had gotten up early today, so the others hadn’t arrived yet. There wasn’t anything to do in the game for now. Ye Xiu continued to watch over Concealed Light. From time to time, he would give a few instruction and tips.

Around three in the afternoon, the door to the practice room was pushed open. Wei Chen strutted into the room with a cigarette hanging in his mouth. He looked like a big boss taking the lead. Steamed Bun and Qiao Yifan followed behind him. Mo Fan arrived a bit later and quietly walked in alone.

When Luo Ji heard them come in, he immediately put down the game and stood up. The people, who just arrived, noticed him.

"This is Luo Ji. Concealed Light." Ye Xiu introduced Luo Ji to them. Just when he was about to introduce Wei Chen and the others, Steamed Bun walked over with a wide grin: "Ha ha ha, it’s you! To think you actually had the chance to come! It seems like I didn’t misjudge you! It’s all due to my hard work!!"

Luo Ji didn’t need an introduction to know that this person was Steamed Bun. Wei Chen was a bit too old. Mo Fan’s cold and indifferent expression didn’t feel right. Qiao Yifan’s well-behaved and honest appearance didn’t seem to fit with his image of Steamed Bun. Sure enough, after solving by elimination, the funny looking fellow was that derailed Steamed Bun. Luo Ji was caught unprepared though as Steamed Bun rushed over to give him an enthusiastic greeting.

"Ha, this is Steamed Bun. You two should be quite familiar with each other!" Ye Xiu laughed.　　

"Of course! I watched Concealed Light grow up!" Steamed Bun was already standing next to Luo Ji, shaking his shoulders wildly. Luo Ji wasn’t tall. He was about half a head shorter than Steamed But. He wasn’t exactly thin and feeble though. However, after being shaken around by Steamed Bun, he suddenly gave off a feeling of being weak.

Luo Ji wanted to say something, but Steamed Bun never gave him an opportunity to speak.

Ye Xiu gave Luo Ji an introduction to the others. This is Wei Chen. That’s Qiao Yifan. Luo Ji had either spoken to them in the chat group or in the tenth server, so he wasn’t completely unfamiliar with them. Only Mo Fan was a stranger. Ye Xiu knew that Luo Ji wouldn’t know of him, so he added: "This is Mo Fan. He just joined."

"I haven’t yet." Mo Fan coldly threw out this phrase.

"Mm, not yet. He’s just here to check out our team."Ye XIu said.

"Check out! An expert!" Luo Ji’s gaze turned respectful.

"Ha ha ha, expert my ass. Let me tell you. Last time I hit him with a brick and he had no idea where it came from. He was killed over and over for an entire month. Who knew how much sand and how many bricks he ate..." Steamed Bun chattered on and on. Although Luo Ji knew that Steamed Bun’s mind was off the rails, he wouldn’t randomly start rumors with no basis. He just didn’t have the same comprehension ability as a normal person. What was he talking about?

Luo Ji didn’t really understand. He just saw, as that cold and expressionless guy hear Steamed Bun’s non-stop chatter, his eyebrows jumped up.

"Okay okay. Steamed Bun, you go sit with Concealed Light!" Ye Xiu interrupted Steamed Bun’s chattering.

"No need no need. I’ll just sit by myself." Luo Ji frantically threw off Steamed Bun’s right hand, which had been resting on his shoulder the entire time. He returned to his seat like a wisp of smoke. When he looked around, no one else was sitting next to him, but the next second, Steamed Bun’s butt came down into the seat next to him. His tone of voice sounded like he was doing him a favor: "Fine. Today I’ll reluctantly give you some personal guidance!"

Luo Ji was depressed! But he felt like switching seats was too disrespectful. He didn’t like making a fuss with others. Helpless, he could only focus on the game and continue following Ye Xiu’s instructions.

"NO no. Why are you such a loser!! Tell your dog to block that!" Steamed Bun shouted.

Dog…..

Luo Ji was speechless. That was a Summoner’s Fire Spirit. When the Fire Spirit attacked, it would look kind of like a dog. As a result, Steamed Bun referred the spirit as as a dog.

"Over there, over there!!"

"Over here, over here!!"

Steamed Bun pointed left and right on Luo Ji’s screen. Not only was he constantly blocking Luo Ji’s line of sight, his screen now had countless fingerprints plastered all over it.

"CAN YOU BE QUIET!!" Luo Ji flared up. He didn’t want to lose his temper, after just arriving at a new environment and meeting so many new friends, but he couldn’t bear it anymore! He admitted that Steamed Bun’s chattering was sometimes right, but his pointing wasn’t helping. It was just making things worse.

"To think you would speak to your senior with such a tone! Do you not want to live?" Steamed Bun clenched his fists. Normally, Luo Ji wouldn’t be afraid of shouting in the game, but looking at Steamed Bun’s posture, was this going to turn into a real life PK?

"Steamed Bun, stop bothering him! Go back to your seat!"

Luo Ji was finally rescued by Ye Xiu. He let out a sigh of relief once Steamed Bun was yelled back into his seat. After Ye Xiu shouted at Steamed Bun, he went to take a look at Luo Ji’s practicing. Seeing that he was still working hard, he gave a few words of encouragement and went back to his seat too.

"Pretty much everyone’s arrived. How about we tidy up that place, so we can eat, sleep, and practice in the same place?" Chen Guo saw Ye Xiu sit back down and turned her head over to talk to him. It felt a bit wasteful to just stop using the practice room in the Internet Cafe, after it had just been renovated, but the guys at Excellent Era and Xiao Shiqin strolling right in left a thorn in Chen Guo’s mind.

After all, the Internet Cafe needed to open up its doors for the business to run. It wasn’t convenient to keep things private here. To create a pro team, their tactics and training routines would need to be protected against leaks.

"Then what about here?" Ye Xiu a

"Here... do Clubs have two practice rooms?" Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu smiled: "If it’s for the pro players, just one. The others would be for the training camp. I don’t think we’ll be needing that anytime soon though?"

So it really is like that. Chen Guo thought to herself. They weren’t an official pro team until the team made it through the Challenger League. Even if Team Happy became a pro team one day and formed a club, many facilities couldn’t be completed within a short amount of time. A training camp was still far far away.

"I was just thinking that when official matches start, wouldn’t people suddenly intruding be a serious issue?" Chen Guo said. She understood how the Challenger League worked. In the beginning, when numerous teams were competing, the matches were conducted online. It would only be until the later stages of the Challenger League that the Alliance would host a place for teams to gather and play their matches there. As a result, for a long period of time, they would need to be in charge of creating a suitable competition environment. In addition, the Challenger League matches were played at a fixed time, which everyone had to follow. If some sort of enemy did something lowly like bother them outside of the game during their match time, it would be troublesome. A place like the Internet Cafe, where people often came in and out, clearly wouldn’t be a good location.

"You’re worrying too much. Nothing like that has ever happened before for the past many years. In online competitions, competitors don’t know each other’s details. Once the Alliance begins hosting the matches offline, that is even less likely to happen." Ye Xiu smiled.

"Aren’t we different? There’s that side!" Chen Guo pointed outside the window, naturally towards Excellent Era.

"That’s even less likely. Think about it." Ye Xiu started to sweat. No matter how it was said, Excellent Era was once a glorious club that had dominated the scene. Who would have thought that Chen Guo would think of them in such an unsportsmanlike light.

"I just can’t feel at peace." Chen Guo mumbled to herself.

"Once everyone gathers, we’ll see what everyone thinks!" Ye Xiu said.

"When is that last guy going to come?" Chen Guo asked. Right now, they were only missing An Wenyi. Once he arrived, the entire team would be at Happy Internet Cafe.

"Soon, I think?" Right when Ye Xiu gave this reply, he received a message from QQ. He checked it and saw that it was from An Wenyi. He would be arriving at City H at 7:35PM.

Chapter 768: Gathering (2)

It was only after Ye Xiu and Chen Guo saw An Wenyi’s message did they realize that out of everyone here, the only person who told them in advance around what time he would be arriving was An Wenyi.

Even though it wasn’t a big deal, it seemed like An Wenyi handled matters more thoughtfully than the others did.

"Then it looks like everyone will be here soon." Chen Guo was a little excited. All of Team Happy’s members would finally be together in one place. Chen Guo felt like the door to a new world was finally opening up. The wheels of history were beginning to turn.

An Wenyi was currently on his way here, so he obviously wasn’t online. There were no bosses left to fight for the rest of this week anyways. Even if there were, An Wenyi’s presence would not have affected the overall situation.

Time passed in the blink of an eye and it was now 7:00PM. The group at Happy hadn’t eaten dinner yet. They were waiting for An Wenyi to arrive. However, An Wenyi said that he would be arriving at City H at 7:35PM. In addition to that, it would take him some time to reach Happy Internet Cafe. Chen Guo and the others from City H knew how much time it would take, so there was no rush. At around 8:00PM, everyone stopped playing. If everything went smoothly for An Wenyi, he should be arriving any shortly.

An Wenyi once again proved that he was a reliable person. He showed up at Happy Internet Cafe precisely when Chen Guo thought he would.

Wearing a pair of eyeglasses, the refined and elegant looking An Wenyi greeted everyone in the same manner. He didn’t give any special gestures to his boss or Ye Xiu. He also didn’t seem to have any particular reaction to Steamed Bun’s hyperactiveness or Mo Fan’s cold expression.

"We’ve been waiting for you! Let’s go get dinner!" Chen Guo called out to An Wenyi as the host.

"Luo Ji and An Wenyi both arrived today. Let’s not go too far and eat something close by." Chen Guo directed. There weren’t any particularly excellent restaurants nearby, and Chen Guo didn’t want to make them feel uneasy when they had just arrived.

Clearly no one cared though and swarmed out the door. They had to do it quickly because they had Su Mucheng hidden within their group.

It was actually very dangerous for Su Mucheng to be in Happy Internet Cafe. If the fans recognized her, it would be disastrous. She was the most well known idol of Excellent Era, second only to Ye Xiu. While Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin were well-received, they couldn’t compare to Su Mucheng’s steady foundation, which had been built up throughout the years.

Surrounding Su Mucheng, they left the Internet Cafe and followed Chen Guo to a restaurant that she had reserved.

Chen Guo didn’t irk away from picking the dishes. She took care of everything. Once the drinks came out, she started gathering everyone’s opinions.

"Drinking? Haha, someone’s about to embarrass himself." Wei Chen shifted his gaze towards Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu said in deadly earnest: "I never drink."

"I don’t either." Qiao Yifan hastily added.

"Steamed Bun, you’re definitely a drinker." Wei Chen patted Steamed Bun.

Steamed Bun became invigorated at being regarded as important.. He rolled up his sleeves as if he were ready to start a fight: "Sure, I’ll drink."

"Who else?" Wei Chen held up the drink menu as he gazed at the remaining three. Those three just happened to be the ones, who just got here. They weren’t too familiar with everyone. Luo Ji looked at An Wenyi. An Wenyi looked him. They were waiting for someone else to speak up first. Then, Mo Fan, who no one was looking at, directly replied: "I’m not drinking."

"What about you two?" Wei Chen didn’t care too much about him.

"Let’s just drink a bit together then!" An Wenyi said.

"I can’t drink too much. Five glasses max!" The mathematician Luo Ji knew precisely how much he could intake. He examined the beer glass size and gave a reply.

"Weak." Wei Chen looked down in disdain. For that glass size, five glasses was just a bit over a bottle of beer. That capacity for liquor was truly too tragic. Even Ye Xiu seemed to have relaxed a bit, probably because he found someone around his tolerance level.

"We still have work to do tonight, so don’t drink too much. Everyone, pace yourself!" Wei Chen said. He called over the waiter: "Get me a case."

The faces of all those present including Mo Fan and An Wenyi changed color. Everyone was clearly frightened by Wei Chen’s liquor capacity. Steamed Bun was already intimidated and shouted: "A case! That’s amazing, right? How many are in a case?"

"Yeah! Very amazing. That’s 24 bottles!" Ye Xiu laughed.

"24 bottles. You’re too amazing Old Wei!" Steamed Bun continued to yell in awe.

Wei Chen’s face suddenly turned deathly pale, but he pretended like it was no big deal: "What? A case has 24 bottles?"

"Haha, what did you think?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"Cough... that’s nothing. How many are you guys drinking? If you’re not sure yet, you’re welcome to just take them from my case." Wei Chen said to the three, who would be drinking.

Luo Ji was just about to nod his head, when Ye Xiu interrupted: "That’s no good. What if someone drinks a bit too much and you won’t have enough left for yourself?"

"Couldn’t I just get more if I don’t have enough?" Wei Chen said.

"Another case?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Are you not happy about something?" Wei Chen asked.

"Haha!" Ye Xiu laughed.

"Ha, your sister!" Wei Chen knew that Ye Xiu had seen through his facade, so he didn’t try and insisting on it. He said resentfully: "Where I live, one case only has 12 bottles. Why are things so different in City H?"

Everyone understood that Wei Chen was making a joke and erupted into laughter. Wei Chen was able to keep the same expression on him. He lit up a cigarette and took the opportunity to tell everyone stories about his past.

When the case of beer came, no one called out Wei Chen to drink it all himself. The three girls, Ye Xiu, and Qiao Yifan drank a little for symbolic purposes. Mo Fan refused it with an astute "No." though. The rest left for the other four. Despite it being four people, Luo Ji’s five glasses didn’t really account for too much. Mathematicians were logical people. Five glasses of beer wasn’t no bottle of beer. It was just a very small amount.

As a result, the majority of the beer was decimated by Wei Chen, Steamed Bun, and An Wenyi. These three averaged around six bottles of beer. It wasn’t too much, but the effects of alcohol were beginning to show. Wei Chen and Steamed Bun clearly started talking a lot more. An Wenyi was still as quiet as ever. It was as if he hadn’t drank six bottles of beer.

"Wow, Little An! You’re still fine?" Wei Chen was also surprised.

"No, anymore and I’ll definitely get drunk." An Wenyi said, but no one believed him. From what everyone saw, Wei Chen and Steamed Bun would be getting drunk first.

"Not bad! You’ve got a good future ahead of you!" Wei Chen sighed.

"There’s no more. There’s no more." Steamed Bun poured out the last of a bottle of beer and rubbed his perfectly round belly.

"More?" Wei Chen tried to show his superiority again. Although he turned his shout for a case of beer into a joke, he really had intended on a small case of 12 beers. Wei Chen wouldn’t get so drunk that everyone could laugh at him. Twelve beers was obviously within his capabilities. Right now, he had drank around six beers, so another case was potentially still possible.

"Maybe next time? We’ll have plenty of opportunities to do so in the future. Luo Ji’s already fallen asleep." An Wenyi said.　　

Wei Chen glanced at Luo Ji, who was lying on the table. He was speechless. This mathematician was truly honest and sincere. When he said five glasses, he wasn’t saying any more than five glasses and he would be drunk, but he would directly get drunk after five glasses. Luo Ji lay on the table, completely gone.

"Okay, next time. We can drink again once these losers are gone." Wei Chen said.

"Don’t corrupt these young minds. Don’t you know that it’s better not to drink for pro players?" Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen was surprised. After a short pause and a puff of smoke, he nodded his head: "You’re right." He looked towards An Wenyi and his expression turned solemn: "You guys still have a future. How nice. Don’t drink too much in the future." After finishing his glass, he didn’t call out to Steamed Bun or An Wenyi. He stood up and said to everyone: "Let’s go back."

"Wake Luo Ji up." Chen Guo said.　　

"Get up, you useless person!" Steamed Bun whacked Luo Ji on the head.　　

"Steamed Bun, don’t act so recklessly. His brain is a national treasure!" Ye Xiu hastily stopped Steamed Bun.

"National treasure?" Steamed Bun was confused.

"Mathematician!" Ye Xiu said.

"Oh?" Steamed Bun seemed to understand. Luo Ji woke up with a daze because of the whack though. He had drunk the least, but was the most drunk. His eyes were still red after the short nap.

"Can you walk?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I can." Luo Ji said.

"Steamed Bun, support him." Ye Xiu said.

"What a piece of trash. Sigh. Why does my little bro have to be such trash?" Steamed Bun sighed with sadness. He dragged Luo Ji up: "Can you stand?"

"I don’t need your help. I can walk!" Luo Ji struggled.

They ate dinner late, so it was quite late by the time they left. All the bosses this week had been killed, so there wasn’t anything urgent to do in the game. Luo Ji and An Wenyi had just gotten here, so they might as well head over to their living place together.

Their living place was two stories with six bedrooms for twelve people. Everything had been arranged for two people per room. Wei Chen and the others lived here. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo had actually never stayed a night here before. When they went to take a look, the four people already living there had each taken a room for themselves. None of them shared a room with another.

An Wenyi and Luo Ji looked as if they would take the remaining two rooms for themselves, but Chen Guo stopped them: "I don’t think it’s good to occupy them all. It’s not too late to put people together later, but what if a girl were to come?"

Everyone heard her words. That was reasonable! They actually had a girl on the team already. She just wasn’t living with them for now.

"Mm. Then, Luo Ji go to Steamed Bun’s room. Little An and Qiao Yifan in a room. I usually smoke, so once Ye Xiu comes over we’ll room together." Wei Chen arranged everything.

"Mm, that’s a good arrangement. Should we try it out for tonight?" Chen Guo turned around to ask the others, who hadn’t even stayed a night before. Everything in those six rooms had already been tidied up for them.

"Sounds good!" Ye Xiu didn’t care.

Chapter 769: Inventory

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Chen Guo, and Tang Rou experienced what it was like to live here. The three girls took the two empty rooms. Ye Xiu went to Wei Chen’s room. Just as Wei Chen said, the room was filled with smoke. It wasn’t anything Ye Xiu had any problems with though.

"Everyone’s gathered together now." Wei Chen sighed as he handed Ye Xiu a cigarette.　

"Not bad, right?" Ye Xiu smiled.

"If our opponent wasn’t Excellent Era, it would have been great." Wei Chen couldn’t get rid himself of this worry because he was more worried than anyone else about this opportunity. Sometimes he even felt upset at himself. If he knew he could have done this earlier, why did he waste so many years of his life? Why didn’t he just try to return to the scene sooner?

"How about you try your hand at Tyranny and see if they’ll accept you. You can be together with them in an old people team." Ye Xiu lit his cigarette.

"Ah, it’s fine! I’m old already. I can’t struggle like I did before!" Wei Chen sighed.

"You’re worried that they don’t want you, no?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"Tch." Wei Chen objected, "What about you? You didn’t need to do this yourself. You’ve managed to keep your ability to play in good condition for all these years. Returning to the scene at the end of the year wouldn’t be difficult at all."

"If I don’t busy myself with this kind of goal, how would I be able to maintain my good condition?" Ye Xiu said.

"You’ve already gotten this far. Why are you thinking about all this? Stay on this path!" Wei Chen said.

"Aren’t you the one that’s thinking too much?"

"I can’t help myself." Wei Chen sighed. It wasn’t something that he could stop himself from doing.

"Who can’t?" Ye Xiu held his cigarette in his mouth as he looked out the window.

"If we fail to get through the Challenger League, what will you do?" Wei Chen suddenly asked.

"I’ll see when that time comes!" Ye Xiu said.

"You haven’t thought about it yet?"

"Not at all." Ye Xiu said.

"That’s good!" Wei Chen let out a sigh. It seems like he had been troubled by this question.

"What do you have to be worried about? Even if you fail, you’ve got 18 million yuan. Isn’t that good enough?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"Happiness can’t be bought!" Wei Chen refuted.

"How about you spend your money to hire a few hitmen and get rid of those guys at Excellent Era? Wouldn’t we certainly succeed then?" Ye Xiu said.

"Mm, I actually know a few people."

"D*mn!" Ye Xiu didn’t think that Wei Chen was actually serious.

"I’m just kidding." Wei Chen said.

"Excellent Era is going to be a very troublesome opponent." Ye Xiu said, "But there will always be opportunities in the future."

"You don’t need to preach to me." Wei Chen said.

"You’re such a good-for-nothing. You clearly understand the logic, yet you still get anxious and depressed from time to time. Did those glasses of beer bring up unnecessary worry?" Ye Xiu said.

"What do you think of everyone currently here?" Wei Chen didn’t want to talk about his feelings with Ye Xiu anymore and changed topics.　

"You’ve seen them too. What are your thoughts?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I think Tang Rou and Steamed Bun definitely have a good future ahead of them. You managed to pick up two treasures! I’m certain that after they shine in the Challenger League, there will definitely be pro teams who think highly of them." Wei Chen said.

"As if you need to tell me that." Ye Xiu smiled, "Wang Jiexi once invited Little Tang to join his team."

"Even something like that happened?" Wei Chen was astonished.

"Of course." Ye Xiu gave him a summary of the event.

"She refused? Why?" Wei Chen was a bit at a loss.

"That is her biggest problem. Her love and passion for Glory isn’t the same as ours. She only started playing because she lost to me in the Arena multiple times. She never had the ambition of becoming a pro player, so she didn’t think much of Wang Jiexi’s invitation." Ye Xiu said.

"What about now?" Wei Chen asked.

"Now? She’s been playing for so long already. It seems like she’s at least somewhat interested in playing Glory. The pro scene just so happens to have numerous experts to challenge. I think that’s most likely her motivation to continue playing." Ye Xiu said.

"Haha, that’s a good reason! Her personality is really fitting for a competitor! I think she’ll go very far." Wei Chen said.

"That might not be true." Ye Xiu said.

"Why?"

"She’s not that young. Her background is also a bit strange too. Look at how she carries herself. When I first came here, she was doing unskilled labor at Happy Internet Cafe. Would you believe that?" Ye Xiu said.

"F*ck, no way?" Wei Chen was astonished.

"I seriously think that she ran away from home, just like me." Ye Xiu said.

"You ran away from home?" Wei Chen continued to be astonished.

"F*ck, a slip of the tongue. I forgot that you didn’t know about that." Ye Xiu said.

"Tell me, tell me, tell me." Wei Chen hastily said.

"It was many years ago. There’s nothing to say." Ye Xiu looked down on Wei Chen.

Wei Chen wasn’t much of a gossiper. Seeing that Ye Xiu didn’t want to talk about it, he didn’t keep pestering. He continued to examine the strengths of Team Happy’s current members: "In any case, Tang Rou will probably be the most outstanding amongst them. Steamed Bun is quite good too, but he’s not very consistent. A few mistakes here and there are always fine, but it would be very troublesome during a crucial moment."

"Correct. That’s Steamed Bun’s main problem." Ye Xiu said.

"For this type of player, if it were an important match, I think most teams would place him as their sixth player." Wei Chen said.

"We don’t have that luxury right now though." Ye Xiu said.

"You’re right." Wei Chen sighed, "The others are quite a ways away from those two."

"Mo Fan isn’t too bad." Ye Xiu pointed him out.

"F*ck, that dead person. If you didn’t say anything, I wouldn’t even have mentioned him. You saying his name makes me want to go over there and punch him." Wei Chen said.

"I still don’t know what to do about him! I have no idea why he even plays Glory. I’m hoping that he’ll have a change in mind once he starts playing with us." Ye Xiu said.

"Seeing how he seems to insist on rejecting everything that we do, I don’t see much hope." Wei Chen said.

"He’ll reject anything new to him, but he’s familiar with Glory. This will help him gain a better understanding of Glory. Let’s see how things go before coming to any conclusions!" Ye Xiu said.

"Then there’s An Wenyi and Luo Ji." Wei Chen started talking about these two fresh arrivals: "I saw Luo Ji’s situation this afternoon. I’m afraid there’s not much hope of him getting on stage in the short term. The future will depend on how much he improves. How is he compared to when you first met him?"

"He’s definitely improved a lot, but he can’t compare to Tang Rou or Steamed Bun. I haven’t guided him that much though. We’ll see how things go after a month of intense practice!" Ye Xiu said.

"What about An Wenyi? You guys usually bring him along, but I haven’t actually seen his skill in-game." Wei Chen said.

"He still needs practice. His awareness and decision-making is quite remarkable. If it’s a 1v1 and he had to heal, his pacing and control is definitely at a pro level, but if you give him multiple targets, such as one healer for a team, he starts to mess up." Ye Xiu said.

"Hm. Then, we’ll have to see after this month!" Wei Chen said.

"There’s nothing to see. That’s everyone we can use." Ye Xiu said.

"Little Qiao is quite good. I heard that you wanted him to switch to a Phantom Demon?" Wei Chen said.

"I feel like his strengths would fit a Phantom Demon more." Ye Xiu said.　　

"His foundation is quite stable. Right now, he’s at the stage where he’s getting used to his class. I think highly of him, but honestly speaking, he isn’t any extraordinary talent. I hope he’ll work hard to make up for that!"

"Being able to pick up two talents is lucky enough." Ye Xiu said.

That’s true. That is very lucky."

"They’ll have to practice hard! It’s entirely on them." Wei Chen puffed out one final cloud of smoke and then extinguished the flame. "Let’s sleep!"

"Okay." Ye Xiu replied and also laid down.

After a moment of silence, Wei Chen suddenly said: "Our boss isn’t considered an official player, right?"

"Of course not." Ye Xiu said.

"Okay." Wei Chen replied. He didn’t say anything after that.

They had been pulling all nighters for the past month, so sleeping at this time wasn’t easy. Wei Chen borrowed the effects of alcohol to sleep soundly. Ye Xiu laid on his bed, not sleepy at all. He stared at the pitch black darkness outside. Who knew how long it would take for him to sleep.

Wei Chen slept early and woke up early. When he woke up, he immediately woke up Ye Xiu too.

"Hurry! Get up! While there’s still nothing to do, we should figure out everyone’s practice plan. We can’t be lazy." Wei Chen shouted.

"Lazy? I’ve already given each of them a practice plan to follow." Ye Xiu said.

"How can throwing them some plans to follow be considered anything? You have to be more rigorous. Time, content, levels. Everyone’s doing the same thing. Have the pace of their practice go up." Wei Chen yelled, "We need to make active preparations for the Challenger League, not just in equipment. Everyone’s individual strength is crucial too."

"Okay, that’s very reasonable. I’ll leave that to you then. I’ll keep on thinking about what to do with our equipment problem, so stop bothering me. I have an idea and I need some peace and quiet to think about it." Ye Xiu flipped over his body.

"D*mmit, get the f*ck up! We need to start regulating practices. Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan, you guys have experience with teams. Gather here! Meeting time!" Wei Chen roared.

Helpless, Ye Xiu was finally forced to get up. He didn’t know when he slept last night. He didn’t have any energy. But seeing how spirited Wei Chen was, he was also gratified, so he struggled to match up with him.

"Right now, we don’t have the software to utilize all those practice methods that the current pro teams use. But as pioneers from the early days, we shouldn’t be held up by this issue. The earliest teams didn’t have these resources either. They relied on things in the game. Weren’t they still able to practice?" Wei Chen said.

"As if you need to say that." Ye Xiu remarked.

"Good. What we need right now is for you guys to tell us the contents of the practice methods that you use in your Clubs and we’ll find a substitute for it in the game." Wei Chen said.

"I know. I’ve been doing that the entire time." Ye Xiu said.

"Now we have this senior helping. We’ll organize everything by the end of today." Wei Chen said.

"Wait. What training methods do you know of that are used by Clubs?" Ye Xiu asked.

"None. So hurry up and tell me everything you know about the theory and methodology behind their practice routines!" Wei Chen looked like he was planning a robbery.

Chapter 770: Training Program

Wei Chen woke up very early, earlier than anyone else, but as soon as he woke up, he started shouting at Ye Xiu, startling everyone awake. Most of them had a hard time sleeping because they were used to staying up all night. They came out of their rooms half-awake and saw Ye Xiu and Wei Chen chattering.

"What are you guys doing?" Everyone was puzzled.

"The bosses haven’t respawned yet, no?" Someone looked at the calendar.

"No." Someone confirmed it.

"Let’s go back to sleep?"

"I agree..."

Everyone climbed back into their beds.

Meanwhile, Ye Xiu talked quite a bit about practice methods, which Wei Chen wouldn’t know about unless he were part of a Club. Wei Chen immediately began racking his brains to figure out how these methods could be simulated in the game.

It had to be said that Wei Chen, who had continued playing in the game after retiring, had a much better understanding of in-game matters than a pro player like Ye Xiu did. As for Ye Xiu? It was similar to how he always needed to check dungeon guides. He had done it in the past, but he had practically forgotten everything from back then. His knowledge of the game couldn’t compare to Wei Chen in this aspect. After the two discussed for awhile, they came up with all sorts of creative ideas. They rushed to Happy Internet Cafe and the two began testing their newly formulated practice methods on the second floor.

The vast maps, various dungeons, and tremendous number of quests were all used as replacements for training software. The two tested and recorded the results. After two hours of testing, the two obtained plenty of insight. At this moment, the others finally arrived at the Internet Cafe.

"What were you two doing so early in the morning?" Chen Guo turned around to look. Ye Xiu and Wei Chen were sitting next to each other, playing the game. From time to time, they would start discussing something. Their characters were in the same place in the game. They weren’t fighting, just jumping around non-stop.

"Pear Wood Mountains. What are you doing there?" Chen Guo recognized the location of their two characters.

"We’re utilizing the cliff here to see if we can practice jumping." Ye Xiu pointed at the cliff in front of his character.

"You can jump here?" Chen Guo was surprised.

"Of course." Ye Xiu said. He controlled his character to jump onto a small protrusion on the cliff face. Then, he jumped left and right continuously, making his way up the cliff.

When the others heard them talking, they crowded around. Qiao Yifan came from a pro team, so he had practiced technical skill, such as jumping. The team would have a fixed practice routine everyday that each player needed to complete. He understood that Team Happy had limited conditions and resources here, so they were searching for suitable locations in the game to emulate the practice routines used by the Clubs.

"We’re preparing a practice routine for our team. Everyday, everyone must complete the basic tech skill practice, as well as class specific practices. There will also be team practice and so on. From now on, everyone will need to complete the scheduled practices everyday. We’re going to start taking a step towards making things official." Ye Xiu said.

"Good good!" Chen Guo was excited. She was happy to see the team move in the right direction.

"Mm. Wei Chen and I are currently arranging the practice routines. We hope to finish it by the end of today." Ye Xiu said.　　

"Keep up the good work." Chen Guo said.

The two had experienced the early stages of the competitive scene. One of them had continued to work hard in the pro scene, accumulating plenty of practical experience. The other had returned to the game, carrying knowledge and experience far surpassing that of a normal player, as well as going through the changes in the game throughout the years. The two progressed at a satisfying pace. They recorded the summaries and results of their tests in a shared document. The experienced Su Mucheng was also called over to help them out. She helped to organize their discoveries into a final complete plan.

They kept working until 7:00 PM. A document called "Team Happy’s Practice Routines" was born. This document only contained the basic tech skill practice content though. It still didn’t include any class-specific practice content.

The document was passed around for everyone to see. On it were both things that they were already doing in addition to some new things. There was a lot of content, but their style was mostly the same: demanding, repetitive, and dry. The purpose of it was to train a player’s precision and speed in his or her tech skill.

"Next week, which is starting tomorrow, everyone must complete the practice content in this document every day. Right now, we have to spend time fighting for wild bosses, so there isn’t a set time frame for you to follow. When we’re not fighting for wild bosses, this will be your number one priority. The practice content is very dull and boring, but it will be very helpful for everyone. Never disregard the importance of the basics, even when you become a God in the Alliance. Clearing this list of items must still be done every day." Ye Xiu said to everyone in a serious tone.

Everyone nodded their heads with solemn expressions. Only Mo Fan had no expression. He just stared blankly at the practice content in front of his screen.

"Mo Fan, you try them out too. It’ll help you improve." Ye Xiu picked him out in particular.

Mo Fan refused to comment. He just lifted his head and glanced at Ye Xiu.

But on the second day, Mo Fan also followed the practice routine. He started completing them on his Deception.

Everyone’s varying skill levels showed through this basic tech skill practice.

Qiao Yifan, whose hand speed wasn’t any slower than Tang Rou or Steamed Bun, completed these various tasks the best. He could complete each task in one try the majority of the time. He just wasn’t too used to it because practicing in the game was more crude. But because the theory was the same, the end results would be the same. It just wasn’t as convenient as the specialized software.

Just take the rolling practice. Using the Club’s software, if the roll direction was slightly off, their would immediately be a notification. However, in the game, there obviously wouldn’t be any notification. In order to determine whether his roll direction and distance satisfied the task’s requirements, he had to judge the direction and distance himself after rolling.

This definitely tested everyone’s self-control. In a pro team, the software would record any mistakes. Afterwards, everyone would know if they did well or poorly. It could be considered as a method of inspecting each player. But in Happy, it was entirely up to the individual. Ye Xiu alone couldn’t watch everyone, so he didn’t bother. He didn’t think that anyone in this group would be lazy and slack off. He believed that they would either do it to the best of their ability or not do it at all.

Qiao Yifan completed each task, inspecting his own practice.

Steamed Bun kept muttering to himself. It clearly wasn’t going smoothly for him. From time to time, he would look defeated.

Tang Rou wouldn’t mutter to herself like Steamed Bun, but her expression was grave too. Her brows were slightly furrowed, which was something that never happened when she rushed into a sea of people to battle. She was clearly having trouble facing these harsh training tasks.

In the beginning, Mo Fan continued to maintain an expressionless face, but his brows gradually started to furrow just like Tang Rou. He clearly wasn’t used to doing this type of practice.

It was even more painful for An Wenyi. He frequently couldn’t meet the requirements for the tasks. He even started to worry if he could even complete these tasks by the end of the day.

As for Luo Ji, he was still struggling in the normal server! Ye Xiu and Wei Chen mainly used the resources in the Heavenly Domain to devise the practice routine, so he couldn’t complete them in the tenth server. However, this practice routine had many similarities with the Heavenly Domain quests. In fact, when the Heavenly Domain first came out, many were surprised at how the Heavenly Domain quests were like an all-inclusive test of a player’s mechanics. Luo Ji’s attempts at the quests could be considered as tech skill practice too.

On the first day, using the gaps between the various wild boss battles, everyone apart from An Wenyi completed the tasks. The speed of their completion varied greatly though. Qiao Yifan was truly much faster than the other three. As for the other three, it was fortunate that the system wasn’t keeping track of their failures. Otherwise, if they used the Clubs’ software, their score would probably make them ashamed to death.

However, in the next few days, Mo Fan began showing that he wasn’t a new player at Glory. After getting used to the practice routine, he improved rapidly and began completing the tasks more and more smoothly. As for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, they were still paying for their rough precision. They were fast enough, but not precise enough. For example, it was similar to how Lu Hanwen could create eight shadows using Shadow Steps, but since those eight weren’t perfect, it couldn’t be considered as complete. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were still lacking in precision. It was because they hadn’t played the game long enough. To put it plainly, practice makes perfect.

An Wenyi was still doing the worst. He struggled with completing each task every day. Even though he had completed the Heavenly Domain quests before, you only needed to complete each of those quests once. It didn’t matter how many times you tried or if you did it by luck. However, these tasks eliminated the aspect of luck. An Wenyi couldn’t finish the practice routine within the necessary time limit. He could only keep repeating and failing the task over and over again. But he wasn’t discouraged. How many days had it been? If he could improve that quickly, Glory would be too simple.

An Wenyi was the one who spared them the most from worry. He may be the worst out of everyone, but he didn’t need anyone to encourage or console him. He even asked Ye Xiu if could skip the wild boss battles in order to spend more time on the practice routine.

Fighting for wild bosses was practically a break from this monotonous practice, but An Wenyi was willing to give up on his breaks.

"These guys certainly have a bright future ahead of them!" Wei Chen felt greatly moved.

Chapter 771: Official Registration

Tech skill practice made something as bothersome as fighting for bosses seem like vacation. The players at Happy followed this routine day after day. Apart from Steamed Bun occasionally crying out, no one else complained. As for Steamed Bun, no one took his crying to heart.

In the blink of an eye, a week passed. Besides basic tech skill practice, Ye Xiu and Wei Chen was able to complete the class-specific practice for each individual. Class-specific practice demanded more detailed work. Not only did the contents of the practice routine differ for each class, the player’s strength and weaknesses needed to be considered too.

This was result of continuous improvement in Glory’s professional scene over the years. In the early years, let alone detailed specialized practice, the pro players didn’t even practice basic tech skill. At the very start, everyone just practiced by fighting in the Arena. Now, that sort of practice was considered unorthodox. Unorthodox didn’t necessarily mean bad. Whether or not it was bad depended on the individual.　

Ye Xiu and Wei Chen finished the class-specific practice routines for each individual and explained it to them. It wasn’t something that could be completed in a short time though. Adjustments needed to be made according to their progress.

Rumors of transfers continued to fly around this week. But after this week ended, the actual transfer market was silent. This stillness didn’t mean that there weren’t any movements whatsoever, but there were simply too many astonishing transfers this summer, so most players were too lazy to care about transfers of less famous players.

As time continued to elapse day by day, teams were beginning to finalize their team roster and prepare for the new season. Summer break for the competitive scene wasn’t the same as summer break for students. Matches started September 1st, which meant everyone had to return by September 1st. Many teams had changed over the summer. Team Tyranny now had two new famous generals. Team Hundred Blossoms completely rebuilt the team. Team Wind Howl had invited the rising star Tang Hao as their core; Last seaon’s Best Rookie Zhao Yuzhe would also be part of the main roster next season. In addition, Team Blue Rain lost Yu Feng. Team Tiny Herb lost two All Star players, one due to retirement, another due to a transfer.

New players to new teams required time to adapt to each other. It would require time.

As a result, even though the new season started on September 1st, no team’s vacation period would end on September 1st. Vacation usually ended in the middle of August. The Clubs would send out orders for players to return and begin practicing for the new season. Even for teams without many changes, after taking a break for so long, the player still needed to get back into form! After all, only a few would continue practicing during the long break.

On 8/15, midway through August, the various Club guilds let out a sigh of relief. On this day, Team Tyranny’s two players, who caused their harvest to sharply drop, finally stopped showing up in the game. Around this day, Team Blue Rain’s Lu Hanwen, Team Tiny Herb’s Liu Xiaobie, Team Wind Howl’s Zhao Yuzhe, etc. also departed from the game. No one looked forward to their leave as much as Zhang Xinjie’s or Lin Jingyan’s departure though.

The balance in the game had finally returned to normal.

The various guild leaders felt a bit of emotion well up. After all, it wasn’t their first time experiencing this type of occurrence. This sort of tossing and turning usually happened every summer. This year’s was truly special though. The transfer market was especially lively. The game was just as crazy. A God like Zhang Xinjie helping the guild monopolize materials had never happened before. This year’s summer left them with a deep impression.

Vacation for players had ended, but the transfer window hadn’t closed yet. The Club managers were still busy, using these last two three weeks to improve the team, especially with practice starting again. They could receive feedback from their teams and make some final adjustments while they still could.

Those with experience waited expectantly because in the past, there would often be large important transfers during this ending period. These transfers were usually unexpected high price transfers too! After all, there wasn’t much time left!

Everyone waited and waited. Another "quiet" week passed. There weren’t any attention-grabbing transfers.

This was in the eyes of most people. However, at Happy, a piece of good news came to them.

Team Excellent Era’s Guo Yang had transferred to Team Wind Howl for 2.6 million.　　

In the end, Team Excellent Era, which refused to become a supermarket, still lost a player. If a Club couldn’t persuade a player to stay, they couldn’t force the player to stay. It would be a loss to both sides if they did.

Although Team Excellent Era had invited Xiao Shiqin and his Life Extinguisher, a player still needed to waste a year in the Challenger League. Not everyone could wait for that future to come and sacrifice this year.

Guo Yang had been on Team Excellent Era’s main roster, a Qi Master. His departure would certainly hurt Team Excellent Era, so for Team Happy, this was good news. The damage would be limited though. On paper, Team Excellent Era still possessed Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, and Su Mucheng, three All Stars. No one in the Alliance had that right now.

Team Tyranny had four, but among those four, three were already near the end of their career. On the other hand, the three on Team Excellent Era were at the peaks of their career. And because of their youth, they still had room to go up unlike Team Tyranny’s three old generals.

Such a monstrous team attracted quite a lot of attention. No one doubted that Team Excellent Era would make it through the Challenger League with ease. As for the other pro teams which would be participating such as the teams which got relegated the same season, the previous season, or even the previous previous season hadn’t yet dissolved the team. After all, only a single team could pass through the Challenger League. There would always be a team, which would be left behind.

Team Duskfire was one such tragic example.

They were relegated in season six, but failed to make it back in season seven and season eight. After being relegated, they would be treated as a supermarket. After failing to get through the Challenger, they would face a disbandment. Team Duskfire stayed strong. They failed the first time and tried again, but failed that too. Last season, they failed once more.

The only person who still remained from Team Duskfire’s original roster was their team captain. The others, who had the ability to compete at a pro level, had left long ago. The team could only find players from other eliminated teams or players who couldn’t find a team. Last season was their third attempt at the Challenger League and perhaps their last. After being in the unprofitable Challenger League for three years, the team probably couldn’t last much longer. The team captain, Hu Zheyi, couldn’t get the same salary as he did back in the pro scene, and the team had no chance at professionalization. This time would be their last chance, but how could they have known a powerhouse with three All Stars like Team Excellent Era would actually get relegated? When Xiao Shiqin announced that he would join Excellent Era, three of the members from Team Duskfire expressed their departure from the team to find other work. They felt that they had no hope.

Team Duskfire obviously wasn’t the only one. Team Mysterious Fantasy, which had dropped out along with Team Excellent Era, felt their hopes dim as well. If they wanted to make it through the Challenger League, they would need to beat Team Excellent Era. Who wouldn’t feel nervous?

These teams were the same as Team Happy. They watched Team Excellent Era closely. Team Excellent Era had a slight loss, but it was only one person. Plus, who knew if Excellent Era had been the one to force him out! After all, the team had switched out their vice-captain. They were rebuilding the team too.

But no matter how they felt, they still needed to register for the Challenger League. On Team Happy’s side, Chen Guo registered using everyone’s ID cards and characters. The initial period of the Challenger League wasn’t very strict. There wasn’t much of an audit. There were a lot of fine details to the registration, which should still be followed though. For example, players who weren’t of age yet could use their guardian’s ID card to register. However, in future investigations, the guardian would need to be present to vouch for the player.

Team Happy had quite a few young people, but all of them were adults. Chen Guo took their ID cards and registered. She was a bit stuck on Mo Fan though. Mo Fan had been in Happy Internet Cafe for half a month already. He still never spoke a word to anyone just like when he came on the first day. Was he in or not?

Chen Guo had no clue. She didn’t know what Ye Xiu was planning. She needed to register the team members though, so she could only ask.

"Are you going to register?" Chen Guo went straight to the point. She didn’t give any explanation to Mo Fan. Everyone talked about it everyday. Even if Mo Fan never said anything, he still had ears. There was no way he wouldn’t know what Chen Guo was talking about.

"Not interested." Mo Fan spoke two words.

"Just do it!" Ye Xiu saw Chen Guo talking to Mo Fan and took notice of it. He heard Mo Fan’s words and interjected, "Registering doesn’t mean anything. When the time comes and you don’t want to play, you just don’t play."

Mo Fan was silent. He refused to comment. But after half a month together, everyone was getting used to him. Silence usually meant that he wasn’t opposed to the idea most of the time. If he refused, he would always coldly give you a "No."

"ID card." Chen Guo said.

Mo Fan handed it over.

"Will you be using Deception?" Chen Guo asked.

"Doesn’t matter." Mo Fan’s expressionless face made Chen Guo angry, but she endured.

"So our team’s name will be Happy?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu for confirmation.　　

"Doesn’t matter." Ye Xiu smiled.

"I like this name." Chen Guo didn’t want the name to sound too domineering. The name Happy was a bit unconventional, but it held a lot of special meaning to her, so she wanted to register using this name.

"You’re the boss. You have the final say. If anyone objects, you can just kick them out." Ye Xiu said.　

"Okay." Chen Guo smiled.

The Challenger League registration was on the Glory official website. Information on everyone in Team Happy was officially up on the web.

Chapter 772: Repeat Names

On Glory’s official Challenger League website, the list of registered teams continued to update. After Chen Guo registered Team Happy, she immediately checked the home page and caught Team Happy’s name flash for an instant before disappearing.

"3647!" Chen Guo cried out in surprise. Before she had registered, there were only 3644 teams participating in the Challenger League. In the time it took her to put in information on everyone in the team, three more teams had joined. Chen Guo had never paid any attention to the Challenger League before, so she wouldn’t have gone on the Challenger League’s homepage during the registration period. She vaguely remembered that news of how many teams participating in the Challenger League would be reported at the start of every season, but she had no impression of the actual number.

"It’s nothing surprising." Ye Xiu laughed, "The registration period isn’t even over yet. We’re only halfway into August."

The requirements to register for the Challenger League were very low. The only requirements were to have six players and six max leveled characters. As a result, numerous players would join with their friends and play around. The average skill level was miserably low.

After Chen Guo registered, she stared at the webpage, watching the number of participating teams go up and the list of teams update. Right when she was feeling moved by the scene in front of her, the name Happy suddenly appeared again. Chen Guo excitedly pointed out: "Look, it’s us!"

Chen Guo proudly pulled over Ye Xiu to look.

"Are you sure that’s us?" Ye Xiu said.

"Who else could it be?"

"Haha, go search up Happy and you’ll see." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo stared blankly for a moment. She clicked on the search bar and typed in Happy. The webpage quickly loaded and the results came out. There were 40 teams with the name Happy.

"Cough." Ye Xiu went over to look at the results and coughed: "There’s only 45. Not bad, not bad. That’s not too many."

Chen Guo was speechless. She wasn’t happy at finding teams with the same name, but what could she do? Happy was a common word. It’s not like she had a patent on the word to prohibit others from using it. The Challenger League had lax policies and didn’t restrict repeat names, so of course there would be a bunch of common names.

"So many... which one is us?" Chen Guo asked.

"Click on them and check the detailed info….." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was very patient. She clicked on every name one by one until she actually found their team. Information on their team showed up. However, information on their real life identities weren’t shown, only their character IDs and classes. Information on their real life identities wouldn’t be seriously checked until the end of the Challenger League, when the Alliance needed to organize the offline matches. Only then would the information be announced publicly.

Chen Guo looked at their team and compared it to others. She immediately felt like their team had a good future ahead of them. The other Team Happy's all contained six player rosters. They only barely put the team together. Some didn’t even have a healing class like a Cleric or a Paladin. Such a team never did well competitively. They were certainly just there to have fun.

"When does the competition schedule come out?" Chen Guo clicked on the competition schedule link, but the webpage said that there was no information for it at the moment, so she asked Ye Xiu.

"That’ll have to be after the month finishes once the registration closes. The schedule will depend on the total number of teams. When the time comes, you can log in to the site using the registration information sent to you and check who our opponents will be." Ye Xiu said.

"What if we want to know who Excellent Era’s opponent will be?" Chen Guo asked.

"Then we’ll have to ask Mucheng." Ye Xiu said.

"..."

Chen Guo continued to be excited for several days after registering for the Challenger League. She strolled around Happy Internet Cafe to see who had joined the Challenger League. It turns out that there was only one team besides them at the Happy Internet Cafe.

"Sis Chen, we couldn’t think of a name, so we just borrowed your Internet Cafe’s name. Is that okay with you?" A person called Little Ming, who often came to the Internet Cafe, happened to bump into Chen Guo asking around and called out to her with a smile.

"Of course, use it!" Chen Guo didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. Who would have thought that she would be the reason for another team having the same name as them.

"Sis Chen, if you have time, would you like to play with our team. I think with your skill, you’ve got a good future ahead of you." Little Ming joked. He frequently visited the Internet Cafe, so he was familiar with Chen Guo. He came with other people he knew and planned on playing around in the Challenger League. He wanted to see if the boss wanted to join, but he was instead looked down upon.

"As if I’d play with you disgraces!"

That was what Chen Guo initially told him. Everyone knew that the boss was devout fan of Glory and worshipped pro players. She clearly thought of these random players at the Happy Internet Cafe joining the Challenger League as being disrespectful to the pro scene.

Who would have thought that after Little Ming asked jokingly, Chen Guo delightedly gave him a smile: "No need. I already have a team."

"What?" Little Ming’s eyes went wide: "Sis Chen, you have a team? Where’d the team come from?"

"I created it myself. I can’t do that?" Chen Guo said.

Little Ming looked at Chen Guo like he was looking at an alien. Finally, he snickered: "Sis Chen, when did you think it through? You’re planning on disgracing yourself?"

"Tch, how could my team be the same as yours. My team is planning on entering the pro scene." Chen Guo refuted.

"HAHAHAHAHA!!!!" Little Ming heard her big words and paused for a moment. Then, he clutched his stomach and roared with laughter. He wasn’t faking it. It was just that after laughing for awhile, he realized that Chen Guo’s expression was very unfriendly. Only then did he start to calm himself down: "Sis Chen, that wasn’t a joke?"

"Was that funny?" Chen Guo grinded her teeth.

"Sis Chen, you’re serious?" Little Ming was astonished.

"Of course."

"Sis Chen, look." Little Ming pointed to outside of the door.

"Look at what?" Chen Guo looked over there, but was puzzled.

"Look over there." Little Ming said.

"What’s over there?" Chen Guo was still confused.

"What do you see over there?" Little Ming said.

Chen Guo looked again and finally understood. What was over there? The entrance to Club Excellent Era!

"Sis Chen, if it was in the past, I would have just laughed it off as a joke. But this year, I think your joke is a bit too ridiculous!" Little Ming remarked.

"Hmph. You just watch!" Chen Guo humphed.

Little Ming saw Chen Guo’s attitude. It really didn’t look like she was joking. She suddenly asked curiously: "Sis Chen, from what I hear, you’re quite confident?"

"Hmph!"

"Forgive me for speaking bluntly, but if you called over Team Tyranny with their four big shots, even they wouldn’t be confident." Little Ming said.

"That’s where you’re wrong. If your team has no confidence in themselves, your team has no future." Chen Guo lectured Little Ming.

Little Ming giggled and then started laughing wildly again. Chen Guo was correct, but your Internet Cafe just had a bunch of random pieces of grass. How are they going to beat Team Excellent Era and their three stars? Wasn’t saying you had confidence versus them just nonsense?

"Sis Chen, talking like this is pointless! My guys will all be here soon. What about yours? If you’ve got the time, how about we practice together? We can warm up and have a friendly match!" Little Ming said.

"Practice with you guys? How could anyone improve by doing that?" Chen Guo smirked.

That remark was undisguised contempt, but the two were on friendly terms. Little Ming knew that boss Chen wasn’t the type of person, who looked down on others. From her words, her team might actually have some real skill. Little Ming was curious: "Let’s just play for fun! Give us a chance to widen our horizons! From what I can tell, I think your team might really be incredible. If they really are at a pro level, then give us the opportunity to experience it for ourselves. If you guys actually become champions one day, I can brag: our team practiced with the champion team back then!"

Little Ming picked out the sweetest words he could think of. Even he didn’t really believe himself. Chen Guo obviously knew that Little Ming was saying complete nonsense, but who cares? Chen Guo regarded these words as genuine and felt that it would be quite interesting. After thinking about it for a bit, she looked left and right: "Where’s your team?"

"Where else could they be? They’re at row 4 in Area A!" Little Ming pointed them out. He was as familiar with the Internet Cafe as his home.

"Oh, okay. I’ll go tell my team!" Chen Gou nodded her head and replied.

"Just like this?" Little Ming asked.

"I’ll PM you in the game in a bit." Chen Guo said and went upstairs. Those who frequently came to the Internet Cafe to play Glory would have each other as friends.

She went to the second floor and told everybody the news. Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry: "Are you setting up this friendly match, so you don’t let your own fertile water flow into others’ fields?"

"It’s just a friendly match. Just bully them a bit and let them know your might." Chen Guo sounded as if she were just.

"How good are they?" Ye Xiu asked.

"No matter how good they are. In your eyes, how good could they be?" Chen Guo was puzzled. She didn’t answer Ye Xiu’s words. How could they considered as anything but trash in front of a God’s eyes. Wasn’t asking this question just mocking them?"

"We don’t have anything to do right now. Shall we give it a go, everyone?" Ye Xiu asked for everyone’s opinion. It was the weekend again. All of the wild bosses had been killed this week, so no one had anything to do.

"It wouldn’t interfere with practice, right?" Chen Guo also asked.

No one had any objections.

"This can be considered as our team’s first battle together!" Ye Xiu felt moved.

"If I say we have to win, would that be inappropriate?" Chen Guo said.

"Not at all. If we lose, we might as well just disband!" Ye Xiu said.

"Okay, I’ll call them over!" Chen Guo immediately logged on to Chasing Haze and messaged Little Ming.

They could only compete in the Arena. Everyone went back to the main city, which took some time. The match would be quite formal, consisting of an individual competition, group arena, and team competition.

After around ten minutes, all three parts of the match were completed. Chen Guo was naturally delighted. Right when she was about to ask how Little Ming was feeling, she heard Little Ming’s shout from the second floor: "Sis Chen, Sis Chen!!"

Chapter 773: Paying Respects

"Haha, he’s coming to find me after losing?" Chen Guo heard Little Ming’s cry and became even more delighted. She could understand what Little Mang was feeling right now. Losing in ten minutes was utterly embarrassing. If he couldn’t see the difference in skill, Little Ming had played Glory so long for nothing. To be fair, before Chen Guo met Ye Xiu, she respected Little Ming’s skill. After all, at that time, pro players were a far-away existence to them. No one would talk about pro players, when comparing skill levels. However, after meeting Ye Xiu and hanging around him everyday, Chen Guo’s eye for measuring skill level had gradually begun to change. Compared to Ye Xiu, everyone at Happy Internet Cafe was trash!

"I’ll go get him." Chen Guo was quite excited, hearing Little Ming looking for her, so she went out to greet him.

"What are you yelling for? The second floor is my VIP area. Stop being so noisy." Chen Guo lectured Little Ming.

Little Ming looked like he was about to cry. He stopped shouting loudly and jogged over: "Sis Chen, I’m here to pay my respects."

"To who?" Chen Guo asked with a laugh.

"Stop pretending. Lord Grim is a legend in the outside world. Isn’t that God Ye Qiu? Why is he here? What’s going on? God Ye Qiu is planning on creating a team to make his way back into the Alliance?" Little Ming lowered his voice lower and lower as if he were whispering a secret.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had once been seen a long time ago at Happy Internet Cafe, when he played a money match with Tang Rou. At that time, only people from the tenth server paid attention to the name Lord Grim. The tenth server was a new server, consisting of mostly new players. Because Glory had the Heavenly Domain as a final destination, for older players, starting over in a new server wasn’t meaningful, unless they didn’t plan on going to the Heavenly Domain and only wanted to play in the normal servers.

The spectators at that time witnessed Ye Xiu’s skill and his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Even if people who knew what was what could see his impressive skill, they were just strangers coming together by chance. After chatting for a bit, that would be all that would happen. Who would be so thick-skinned as to follow around an expert, after seeing on? Those who felt like Ye Xiu was pretty good would never imagine that he was a famous God.

Later, Lord Grim’s fame grew and grew, but to onlookers, it had nothing to do with them. Some were jealous, but few would cling onto someone famous. After all, in the Internet Cafe was real life. It wasn’t so easy to shout out "Brothers, sisters, carry me!"

Even later, when rumors that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu came out, those who had spectated that money match awhile back didn’t know where he went. They were just customers, not employees. No matter how regular of a customer someone was, it wasn’t like you needed to tell him you wouldn’t be showing up anymore.

Ye Xiu and Lord Grim being in Happy Internet Cafe never spread mainly because the onlookers were new players from the new server. Little Ming played in the Heavenly Domain, so no matter how much of a regular he was, he wouldn’t know about it. Players in the Heavenly Domain wouldn’t care about what happened in the new server. By the time they heard the news of a Level 50 tenth server players entering the Heavenly Domain, how could they know Lord Grim was playing under the same roof as them?

As a result, when Little Ming played the friendly match and saw Lord Grim jump out, his eyes almost fell. He wasn’t in any mood to fight and accepted his loss. Then, he immediately rushed over to pay respects to a god.

"Quiet!" Chen Guo said.

"What? Lord Grim really is God Ye Qiu?" Little Ming was dumbstruck.

The pro scene and the core members of the Club guilds knew Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, but for anyone else, it was only rumors. Ye Xiu never came out and admitted it. As for the Club guilds, of course, they wouldn’t announce it! Ye Xiu alone was making them toss and turn and cough blood. If they helped him reveal his identity, the fans would swarm to him. Wouldn’t the Heavenly Domain be united?

"Yes, he is!" Chen Guo admitted. She didn’t need to hide it. People would know of the truth sooner or later. Ye Xiu never admitted it, but he also never denied it. In the beginning, Chen Guo didn’t understand, but she did later. He was very busy with his own work. He didn’t have time to be concerned about any of that.

"Can I see him?" Little Ming asked like a beggar.

"That’s... not good, I think?" Chen Guo said. She wasn’t trying to be arrogant. Ye Xiu never showed himself, when he was a pro player. Little Ming’s request felt difficult to complete.

"How could I not know about God Ye Qiu’s habit? Haven’t I come to you alone?" Little Ming said.

Chen Guo was hesitating, when the door behind her opened up. Ye Xiu walked out from the practice room.

Little Ming saw Chen Guo come out from this room and guessed that God Ye Qiu was probably in this room. When he saw the person come out, he immediately became excited, but after seeing who it was clearly, he let out a "Hm?"

"So it’s Little Ming!" Ye Xiu said.

"Hey, you’re still here? I thought you stopped working and left!" Little Ming had chatted with Ye Xiu before.

"Haha, I’m still here!" Ye Xiu said.

Little Ming was a frequent regular at Happy Internet Cafe. He knew Happy very well. He knew who came and who left as clearly as Chen Guo did. However, he wouldn’t know about Ye Xiu’s special arrangement. Chen Guo wouldn’t tell him either. Later, Ye Xiu mainly moved about on the second floor, so Little Ming no longer saw him and thought he left. Many employees came and went over the course of the year, so it wasn’t anything strange. Little Ming and Ye Xiu weren’t good friends, so he didn’t pay too much attention when he stopped showing up.

"You’re…... also a part of the team?" Little Ming was astonished, when he saw Ye Xiu walk out from the door. He knew that this manager also played Glory, but he didn’t pay too much attention to him. Glory was too common. Countless people played the game. The Internet Cafe was filled with screens of Glory, so it was nothing to be surprised about. But when he saw Ye Xiu come out from that room, he realized that Ye Xiu might be one of the super skilled opponents he had just played against. So it turns out there had been an expert beside him, which he hadn’t noticed at all.

‘Yup!" Ye Xiu nodded his head.

"Is God Ye Qiu in there?" Little Ming asked.

"That’s me!" Ye Xiu answered.

"..." Little Ming stared with wide eyes. His chin looked like it was about to fall off. After a moment of silence, he turned his head towards Chen Guo: "Sis Chen, don’t joke with me! You had Ye Qiu serve everyone as an employee?"

Chen Guo heard his question and wasn’t sure if she should be embarrassed for being blind or be proud for being so amazing that she could get a God to become one of her Internet Cafe employees. For a moment, she didn’t know what to answer.

"You guys keep chatting!" Ye Xiu called out, preparing to leave.

"Where are you going?" Chen Guo asked.

"To buy cigarettes. I ran out." Ye Xiu said.

Little Ming watched as his figure disappeared down the stairs before looking at Chen Guo: "Are you serious?"

"Yeah!" Chen Guo nodded her head.

"How did all this happen?" Little Ming was puzzled.

"Nothing really. He wanted to play Glory, but he had no computer. I just happened to have a bunch of computers and that’s how we met." Chen Guo said.

"I I I... give me some time to digest this. It’s too much information to take in….." Little Ming looked as if he couldn’t sit still, making Chen Guo feel extremely happy. Suddenly revealing a God and then watching others be dumbstruck was a scene she liked to see.

By the time Little Ming finished digesting all of the information, Ye Xiu had come back after buying cigarettes. His mouth was already holding a cigarette. When Ye Xiu saw the two still there, he nodded his head: "You’re still chatting?"

He said, while handing a cigarette over to Little Ming. Little Ming received it dumbly. Ye Xiu fished out a lighter and lit it. Little Ming went over stupidly to light his cigarette.

Ye Xiu nodded his head again: "I’ll be going in first."

Little Ming held the cigarette between his fingers and stood there staring blankly for half a minute. Then, he suddenly lifted his head to look at Chen Guo: "God Ye Qiu give me a cigarette and lit it?"

"Yes." Chen Guo answered. This Little Ming was like him before, always feeling like a god was high up in status unlike normal people. Handing over a cigarette and lighting it for him was a very normal set of actions, yet he felt like it was unbelievable. The difference was that Little Ming probably felt excited for God Ye Qiu performing such a kind act. As for her? She had felt her image of God Ye Qiu shattering.

"I I I..."

"Stop with the Is. Let’s go in!" Chen Guo called out. Ye Xiu wasn’t hiding himself, so what did she need to worry about?

She opened the door and went in. Everyone was playing the game as usual. Little Ming followed behind Chen Guo in reverence. He looked around. There were quite a few people in this room!

"Little Ming, you came in." Ye Xiu called out.

Chen Guo introduced to everyone: "This is Little Ming. He was in the match you guys played just now."

"Oh oh." Everyone replied.

Little Ming had to greet everyone after being introduced!

"Hi….. everyone….." Little Ming tried to find a way to address everyone, but this room had male, female, old, and young. It was difficult finding a word to account for everyone!

"Little Ming, come sit down!" Ye Xiu said.

Little Ming quickly dashed over to the sofa. He put his two hands on his knees as if he were at a formal event.

Qiao Yifan got up and poured a cup of water for Little Ming. Little Ming saw that it was a kid, but he didn’t forget to say thank you. Chen Guo introduced him slightly: "This is Qiao Yifan. He used to be a part of Team Tiny Herb."

"D*mn..." Little Ming was just about to take a sip, when he heard Chen Guo’s words and spilled a bit of water in surprise. Luckily, Qiao Yifan didn’t pour very hot water.

A player from a former champion team! Little Ming was astonished. But he had never heard of Qiao Yifan before? Little Ming was racking his brains, when his gaze shifted to behind a computer screen. She was wearing headphones, currently focused on the screen in front of her and smiling. She seems really familiar! He had been a bit frantic when he first entered the room, so he hadn’t noticed this area. This person is....

Little Ming’s head seemed to have short circuited. After a long while, he finally remembered who it was and this time, his brain completely short circuited.

Isn’t that Su Mucheng???

Chapter 774: No One Understands

Little Ming couldn’t figure out who Qiao Yifan was, but no matter how great of a background he came from, how could he compare to Su Mucheng? Little Ming could recite the names of every All Star, but there was no Qiao Yifan.

Little Ming didn’t dare to go say hi! He cautiously shifted his gaze away to see if he had missed any other big figures. When he turned around, he saw a pretty girl. He was a bit startled. The two of them were fairly close!

Isn’t that Sis Tang? The two were familiar with each other!

Seeing a friend excited Little Ming. He immediately spoke up and asked Chen Guo: "Hey! Little Tang is starting to play too?"

"Yeah! She was always talented!" Chen Guo said.

"But I thought she wasn’t interested in Glory?" Little Ming said.

"She isn’t interested if the opponent’s too weak." Chen Guo said.

"Which one was she among those characters?" Little Ming asked.

"Battle Mage, Soft Mist." Chen Guo answered.

"F*ck me..." Little Ming started to sweat. Their friendly match followed the official competitive format. In the individual competition, their side lost all three rounds. In the group arena, they were 1v3d. In the team competition, they couldn’t even get the other side’s sixth player to come out before their team was annihilated. And the one to 1v3 them in the group arena was the Battle Mage Soft Mist. Moreover, from what it looked like, the 1v3 wasn’t a struggle for her. If another two went up, those two would probably be crushed too.

"What do you think? My team’s pretty good, right?" Chen Guo said.

"Good, too good! They’re not any worse than the pros!" Little Ming exclaimed with admiration. He was being sincere, but unfortunately, his skill level might not be good enough to make such a claim. He felt like if they could beat his team so easily, they were probably at a pro level. His point of reference wasn’t right though. An elementary student and a university student were just as good at figuring out 1+1=2.

"Do you still think my words before are a joke?" Chen Guo said.

"Of course not. Sis Chen, once you enter the pro scene, I’ll be your number one fan." Little Ming said.

"You’re not going to support Excellent Era?" Chen Guo smiled. She obviously knew that Little Ming was an Excellent Era fan. If not, why would he be so excited, when he saw Lord Grim, or be so stunned, after meeting Ye Xiu.

"I support everyone." Little Ming said.

"But in the Challenger League, there’s only one winner." Chen Guo said.

"Ah, that….." Little Ming stared foolishly. He had remembered this fact, when he treated Chen Guo’s words as a joke, but he had completely forgotten about it. For a moment, his expression turned awkward. Even though he was more familiar with Chen Guo, he sincerely supported and loved Team Excellent Era. In comparison, his feelings towards Team Excellent Era might be deeper. But in that case, he couldn’t give his support to Chen Guo. It really made him feel uneasy!

"Now you’re thinking we’re troublesome and no longer want to pay your respects, right?" Chen Guo was still smiling. She had once been a loyal fan, so she could imagine Little Ming’s feelings.

"No way!" Little Ming blurted out. In his mind, God Ye Qiu and Excellent Era were one. Supporting God Ye Qiu meant supporting Excellent Era. At the same time, supporting Excellent Era meant supporting God Ye Qiu. He didn’t think that a day would arrive, where he would need to make a choice between the two. At this moment, Little Ming felt uncomfortable on the inside. He even felt a bit regretful. Why did he ask for a match today? Why did he have to know that Ye Qiu was creating his own team and trying to return through the Challenger League? He had heard rumors of it before, but now he knew the truth. This sort of feeling didn’t feel good at all.

After seeing God Ye Qiu, Little Ming had originally been nervous. But at this moment, he suddenly mustered up his courage and stood up: "God Ye Qiu, why do you need to create another team! If you want to return, why not go back to Excellent Era?"

Little Ming looked uneasy at first, but intense emotions took over, giving everyone a fright. The practice room instantly fell silent. Ye Xiu was as calm as ever. He slowly shook his head: "I want to go back too, but not to the current Excellent Era. Their way of thinking differs too much from mine."

"Any conflicting views can be talked out!"

"Some conflicts can’t be resolved through talking. One side must make a change. It’s too bad that we’re all persistent people." Ye Xiu said.

"But does it need to be like this? Both of you need to fight against each other for a single placing?" Little Ming was depressed.

"Those are the rules. We just happened to bump into each other." Ye Xiu said.

"..." Little Ming was unable to respond. He stood there dumbly, unsure what to say. He had to make a choice, but he didn’t want to. Little Ming believed that a lot of other fans would be heartbroken like him. Ye Qiu and Excellent Era would be enemies. It would be a life and death battlefield like the Challenger League too.

Before coming up, Little Ming just wanted to pay his respects to God Ye Qiu, but he hadn’t thought of this point. After realizing it, he found it difficult to face.

Chen Guo’s expression changed too. From the bantering to the digesting of information to now, she could completely understand Little Ming’s emotions.

"Are you okay?" Chen Guo asked. Little Ming standing there frozen frightened her a bit.

"I’m….. fine... sigh….." Little Ming sighed. His initial excitement at seeing God Ye Qiu was completely gone now.

"Think broader.. It’s the same in the Alliance." Chen Guo consoled.

"I know. I just didn’t think it’d happen to me. Everyone was waiting to watch the Hundred Blossoms show, but who would have thought….." Little Ming sighed. Team Hundred Blossom’s Zhang Jiale returned to join Team Tyranny. Some fans were angry. Some fans wished him well. At the same time, some were conflicted between the two sides.

However, the conflict between Zhang Jiale and Hundred Blossoms couldn’t compare to the intensity of the conflict between Ye Xiu and Excellent Era.

The Challenger League was a life or death battlefield! If you win, you return to the pro scene. If you lose, you would need to stay in the Challenger League for another year. There had never been a team, which stood back up after failing to make it back in the first time.

Excellent Era was rich and powerful, but the more rich and powerful they were, the less they could take such a downfall. A team that could once contend for the championship title was now participating in the Challenger League year after year. How could the fans bear that? The team’s pro players wouldn’t be able to either! It was already praiseworthy for the two Gods, Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin, to sacrifice a year. Another year wasn’t something the fans could keep watching. A pro player’s career only lasted a few years.

"Is there no other way?" Little Ming was unwilling to give up.

"If there were, we wouldn’t want to either. From a real combat perspective, who would want to fight against a strong opponent like Excellent Era?" Chen Guo said.

"I know. I obviously know. But can anyone understand our feelings?" Little Ming suddenly lost control and shouted.

"No one can understand."

Ye Xiu suddenly replied. Everyone looked at him in astonishment.

"To be honest, our reason for struggling is for our own personal dream. No one is doing it for anyone else. Only the Alliance is trying to please you guys. Don’t get the wrong idea. We are very grateful for your support and encouragement, but to be blunt: saying that I’m competing for you guys is fake. At least that’s the case for me." Ye Xiu said.

"That’s not right! If it’s not for our support, how could their be a pro scene or pro players!" Little Ming said.

"You’re correct. That’s why I said that I’m very grateful for your support. I sincerely think that. But I am not competing for the sake of my fans. Those are two different matters." Ye Xiu said.

Little Ming was stupefied.

Ye Xiu was a God who never showed himself, so no one had any direct interview material on him. Since the beginning of history, no pro player had ever said these kinds of words before. But after hearing them, Little Ming felt like they were reasonable.

Many teams claimed that their reason for winning was for the fans. Many players also showed their gratitude towards their fans, and just as Ye Xiu said, their gratitude was sincere. Pro players worked hard for victory in return for their fans’ support. However, that wasn’t their reason for becoming pro players.

Because no matter what fans did, there would always be a tomorrow. When a completely unknown player competed, why did he compete? For the fans? He didn’t have any fans, so wasn’t competing for the fans a joke?

Perhaps it was to win more fans and then play for the fans, but if others heard of that reason, they wouldn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

Little Ming suddenly realized that he previously said that pro players didn’t think of their fans, but in reality, the fans didn’t think of their pro players.

Zhang Jiale’s decision to join Team Tyranny was welcomed with backlash. Very few fans supported his decision.　

Did the pro players not care for their feelings or did the fans not value their pro players’ thoughts?

Little Ming couldn’t say anything more because had a premonition: if he continued to argue, he would be the one to be persuaded. He just didn’t want to see Ye Qiu and Excellent Era, who were originally one, fight against each other to the death, requiring him to make a choice. He could already see that his thinking was selfish. It didn’t seem like he ever thought about what the other side wanted.

After a long moment of silence, Little Ming calmed down and said slowly: "No matter the case, I still wish you guys the best of luck."

"Thanks." Chen Guo said. The mood in the room had turned serious.

"However, that’s just until you meet Excellent Era." Little Ming said.

Chapter 775: Why We Compete

Little Ming left without another word. The mood in the practice room was low. No matter how reasonable Ye Xiu’s words were, they weren’t suitable for the public to know. It wasn’t good for the relationship between pros and fans! Saying a few words in this private space didn’t count for much, but the people in the practice room weren’t the same people. They came from different backgrounds and had different views. Everyone had their own distinctive feelings towards Ye Xiu’s words.

Chen Guo was one of the ones, who felt rather sad. After all, she had once been a fangirl. She couldn’t help but feel the same way as Little Ming and feel her heart shatter into pieces. In reality, at her age, how could she not know that the sweet words said by the pro players and Clubs were mostly PR words. Her beliefs actually leaned towards Ye Xiu’s opinion. It was just that she had been a fan for so long and shied away from the truth, believing her own lies. Now that Ye Xiu had suddenly seen through it, Chen Guo even had the urge to ignore his words.

As for Qiao Yifan? He had once been a pro player. Unfortunately, an invisible person like him never had any fans! For him, he would be unbelievably excited to have a fan and be brimming with expectations for the future as a result. Fans were a form of approval. He longed for people to notice him. As for returning the fans’ support, he hadn’t reached that step yet!

He had heard numerous stories of encouragement in the scene. For example, how some pro player lost and felt very disappointed, but because of encouragement from fans, he stood back up. Or how some unknown pro player like him was only able to keep going because of the support from the few fans he had.

These kinds of stories seemed to happen for quite a lot of people. Not for Qiao Yifan though. In his most difficult moment, the fans weren’t the ones who gave him the confidence and motivation to stay. A pro player had. The words spoken to him weren’t any moving words of encouragement, but a very professional tip.

Would support from the fans be a reason for his motivation? Qiao Yifan had never experienced it before, so he didn’t know. However, he knew that although the pointer given to him by God Ye Qiu had only been a few words, it would save him from walking down many twists and turns in his career path. If he didn’t receive the pointer from God Ye Qiu and continue with that Assassin in Team Tiny Herb, where would he be now? Qiao Yifan somehow got to this question. The relationship between fans and pro players? He didn’t really think about it much.

The person sitting next to him, An Wenyi, who had a level of maturity and rationality surpassing that of his age, was actually the first to speak: "There was no need for you to say that."

Then, he added: "Even if that’s the truth."

"If he didn’t say the truth, he’d probably die, right?" Chen Guo spat out, after having her heart crushed. She recalled how many times during these past few months of living together that the truths told by Ye Xiu made her choke. But compared to those joking truths that made her angry and helpless, this time, the truth was heartless. It was a truth that people wanted to avoid looking at. Yet this guy actually laid the truth bare in front of you, not letting you look away. It was too merciless.

"Exactly. Wei Chen also said, "He was just a fan. Did you need to do that?"

"You guys are too naive!" Ye Xiu suddenly said, "I wasn’t saying those words for him, but for you guys!"

"What?" Everyone was startled.

"When you guys become pro players with numerous fans behind you and you see their support and encouragement, you’ll know they’re happy. But when you don’t see that support anymore, will you waver as a result?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That’s... quite deep?" Chen Guo was a little flabbergasted. For a moment, she couldn’t accept that Ye Xiu would actually say something so deep. Even though she knew that he could be profound from the very beginning, but who told Ye Xiu to destroy her image of her idol the very first thing he did after becoming her employee?

"This isn’t a trivial matter. It’s very important. Everyone needs to be clear about why you compete. This could decide what type of path you walk on and how far you go." Ye Xiu said, "Playing to please the fans is okay, but if you want to become a champion, then relying on this motivation will be very difficult. What the fans like might not be what is correct. What suits you best depends on you because you are the pro player."

"Correct." Wei Chen suddenly added to Ye Xiu’s words and said in a serious tone: "If you want to win, do what you think is most correct. None of this needs to be considered."

"That’s what we say, but abandoning all else to win and resorting to extremely underhanded methods shouldn’t be done. We’re still people, after all." Ye Xiu said.

"Yes, it shouldn’t be done. You should only give up on humanity, when you have no other choice. For example, to win three championships." Wei Chen said.

Everyone turned their heads to the side. Everything had been going well, especially Ye Xiu’s last point. It was another truth. As a pro player, how could winning but losing yourself in the process still be considered as your achievement? But then Wei Chen’s answer made it another insult war. The topic immediately became meaningless.

The other two had already begun attacking each other with their past win records. Unfortunately, the results put Wei Chen on the disadvantaged. Just when Wei Chen was about to lose, Ye Xiu suddenly changed topics: "In short, why you want to become a pro player and why you compete are easy yet also difficult questions to answer."

Switching topics like that! That’s too stiff!! Everyone screamed in their hearts. They couldn’t take it seriously. But they still remembered Ye Xiu’s words. Those questions were easy, yet difficult to answer! At this moment, everyone admired the simple-minded Steamed Bun. While everyone was taking these words seriously, Steamed Bun had gone over to the computer who knew when and was happily playing a flash game. He didn’t listen or think about anything Ye Xiu said. It was best to just not bother trying to think too hard about it.

"Tomorrow at this time, everyone needs to turn in an eight hundred word essay, describing why you want to become a pro player." Ye Xiu ordered.

Everyone looked at him in doubt. They weren’t sure if he was serious or not! Wei Chen had already started arguing: "Look! His abandon-everything-resort-to-underhanded method has come out!"

"It truly is a difficult task for an illiterate, who can’t write certain words. It’s no surprise that you think it’s underhanded." Ye Xiu calmly replied.

"F*ck you. If this senior can type out eight hundred different words on the screen, will you eat your monitor?" Wei Chen shouted.

"Type ahead. I’ll check the character count in a bit." Ye Xiu said.

"Tch. You think this senior will fall into your trap?" Wei Chen said.

The bantering started again. Everyone turned their heads. As for that eight hundred word essay, forget about it. Just pretend like it was never said.

Day after day passed. Little Ming’s emotional response to that day made Chen Guo feel a bit uneasy. She really regretted organizing a friendly match that day. At the same time, she also paid more attention to the neighboring team that would also be participating in the Challenger League. Players like Little Ming, who were just participating in it for fun, could be dismissed with a laugh. But the teams serious on entering the pro scene were major villains! This was Excellent Era’s home field. Ninety percent of the Glory players, who came in and out of Happy Internet Cafe, were Excellent Era fans. Many of them were loyal fans like Little Ming.

She had been so pleased, she lost her sense of measure. Chen Guo didn’t forget to examine herself. She also realized that it wasn’t suitable to reveal her team like this. Chen Guo had been running the Internet Cafe for many years. She had seen all sorts of fans walk through the doors. If their battle with Excellent Era reached a certain level of intensity, while Team Excellent Era might not step out of bounds, it was hard to say if the fans wouldn’t. In order for their team to win, what couldn’t fans do to the opponent? Chen Guo wasn’t powerful enough to protect everyone. It was indeed dangerous if they became the villain!

Luckily, Little Ming didn’t spread the word about his experience that day. The days afterwards were calm. However, Little Ming, who almost always showed up every day in the past, never came again from that day onwards. That included his friends, who he had teamed up with. Chen Guo knew that her team would be enemies with Excellent Era. As a fan of Excellent Era, how could Little Ming be willing to sit in the enemy nest?

One day, when Chen Guo went out, she passed by Grand Internet Cafe. She just happened to see Little Ming and his friends exit from there. Chen Guo knew that she had lost him forever as a frequent customer.

This was just the first wave. Once news of Team Happy spread and information was dug out, Chen Guo reckoned that it wouldn’t be possible to hide any longer. When that time came, everyone would know that Happy Internet Cafe’s team would be competing against Excellent Era. How would it affect her business? Would these fans rally together and refuse to go to Happy Internet Cafe? Would her business suffer a sharp decline?

Recently, she had only been enjoying herself. She had completely ignored that a lot of tricky issues existed! Little Ming’s visit woke her up. They were currently enemies in Excellent Era’s territory! It’s said that a strong dragon cannot repress a snake. The snake thinks that it’s better, so it barges into the dragon’s territory to push the dragon down. Facing Excellent Era, their pressure wouldn’t only be from the team’s might, but the pressure from outside the stage would be terrifying as well. It seems like I need to come up with a good plan!

Chapter 776: Unable to Be Serious

Chen Guo was someone, who did the things she said she would. After realizing this problem, she prepared to proactively resolve it, so she immediately called all of the members together to discuss their thoughts on the matter. As a result, the first meeting convened by Team Happy’s owner began. When everyone got the news and heard that Chen Guo wanted to hold a meeting, everyone’s expression became strange. Chen Guo didn’t really feel like a boss. She felt more like the team’s nanny, dealing with all of the odd jobs…...

"Cough, the boss wants to hold a meeting. Everyone, take this a bit more seriously." Seeing that everyone wanted to laugh, Ye Xiu hastily gave a reminder.　　

As a result, everyone sat up straight, while Ye Xiu asked the employee, who told them the news: "Did the boss say where she was going to hold the meeting?"

"Oh, the room over there." The employee replied.

"Can we fit?"

"We’ve moved chairs into it." The employee answered.

She prepared especially for this! Everyone looked each other in the eye. Ye Xiu nodded his head: "Tell the boss that we’ll be there immediately."　

The employee left. Everyone continued to look at each other incredulously.

"What does she want?" Wei Chen couldn’t help but ask.

"Won’t we know once we go?" Tang Rou got up and said.

They left the practice room together and went over to the area, where Chen Guo lived in. That area was separate from the rest of the second floor, but it wasn’t very large. The living room felt very crowded with so many people inside. Chen Guo was already in the room. She appeared very serious and nodded her head at seeing everyone arrive: "Everyone’s here."

The tea table in the living room was moved aside and the sofa was used. Along with other seats taken from the Internet Cafe, everyone had their own seat.

"Everyone sit down." Chen Guo called out and they took their seats. Chen Guo looked at all of them one by one. Midway through, she paused for a moment and seemed to hesitate, but she quickly moved on. Everyone was staring at her curiously. They noticed her pause and looked at who she had paused on: the person sitting on the right of Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng!

"Why are you here too? Go away! You’re an enemy!" Ye Xiu shooed away Su Mucheng.　　

"Oh oh, is that what’s happening?" Su Mucheng immediately got up.

"Then why are there enough seats?" Wei Chen suspected. It meant that Su Mucheng had been calculated into the planning.

"Yeah!" Su Mucheng was also baffled.

"She’s trying to sow dissension!" Wei Chen suddenly shouted.

"You’re retarded!" Ye Xiu looked down in disdain.

Then, Su Mucheng discovered the issue: ‘Mo Fan isn’t here."

"It’s normal for him not to be here. He’s not a team member, no?" Wei Chen said.

"I see that he practices very hard every day." Su Mucheng had been sitting together with Mo Fan, so she knew quite a bit about him.

"I’m sure he’s already felt that the practice content is the real deal." Ye Xiu said.

"He’s not planning on practicing to become an expert, so he can take revenge, right?" Tang Rou said.

"That’s possible….." Ye Xiu thought of Mo Fan’s personality and couldn’t eliminate that possibility.　　

"I’ll go exterminate him." Steamed Bun got up and even picked up his chair.　　

"Force isn’t the answer." Ye Xiu said, "Is you alone enough?"

"There’s Concealed Light too!" Steamed Bun grabbed Luo Ji. Even though Steamed Bun knew Luo Ji’s real name, he was still used to calling him by his in-game ID. The two interacted with other fairly often, so it was a habit now. He wasn’t like Ye Xiu and the others, who didn’t see Concealed Light often in the game, so their familiarity with Luo Ji in real life was greater than their familiarity with his character in the game. As a result, it felt more natural for everyone else to call Luo Ji by his real name.

"I won’t fight!" Luo Ji heard Steamed Bun’s words and was scared white. He frantically dodged Steamed Bun’s evil clutches.

"It’s just a joke..." An Wenyi laughed.

"It might not be for a certain someone!" Luo Ji emphasized. It wasn’t like he couldn’t tell that it was a joke, but it was hard to tell if Steamed Bun was actually joking or not.

"Okay okay, stop fighting." Su Mucheng said, "I’ll go over and get him. I’ll see if he’ll come or not!"

Su Mucheng left after saying those words. Wei Chen immediately looked towards Chen Guo with a smile: "Boss, if there’s anything you want to say, you should say it now. It doesn’t matter if that guy’s here or not. I’m afraid his sour face will ruin your mood."

"What’s that smell?" Ye Xiu suddenly interrupted.

"What?" Everyone was puzzled.

"You guys don’t smell the scent of a dog kissing up to his master?" Ye Xiu asked.

Everyone laughed. Even Chen Guo couldn’t help but laugh too. She wanted this to be serious, but it looked like a serious atmosphere couldn’t be done with this team! Just look at that other day how such a serious topic, which crushed her heart, eventually devolved into a verbal fight between those two guys. She didn’t know what to say.

Sometimes, Chen Guo just couldn’t understand. Whenever Ye Xiu said anything serious, she wasn’t sure if he was actually trying to tell everyone something or if it was all just nonsense. Just like the other day. Ye Xiu said that those words were to question themselves on why they want to become pro players. It sounded very logical. But Wei Chen came over and turned into a quarrel. Ye Xiu also followed the flow and began quarreling too. Chen Guo couldn’t help but suspect that those words were just a fluke.

This God usually seemed to be indifferent and carefree, but from time to time, he would suddenly jump out to say very serious words. However, no one could properly digest the information in time before he returned to his usual carefree state, making everyone doubt whether he was just messing with them!

Can’t this guy just act normal for once? Chen Guo felt like she couldn’t be like him. She needed to be proper. But now she realized that it was quite difficult to say anything serious to this team. The atmosphere was never right! She had initially been trying hard, but not long afterwards, she was laughing alongside everyone.

"We’re in a meeting! Everyone take this more seriously!" Wei Chen shouted.

"If there’s anything you want to say, you should say it." Ye Xiu said.

"Mm, it mainly has to do with what happened that day with Little Ming. That event made me seriously think about our current situation. I’m sure everyone already knows about our team’s strength, so I won’t talk about it. I want to talk about the environment on the outside. City H is Excellent Era’s home field. We’re right across street from Excellent Era. We can be considered as part of Excellent Era’s core region. Countless Excellent Era fans walk around here. My Internet Cafe’s business is indebted to them. But now, we’ve created a team that will need to fight to the death with Excellent Era, so in the majority of people’s eyes, we’re the evil villain. We might receive curses and insults from numerous Glory fans. I’ve been running this Internet Cafe for so many years. I’ve streamed their matches before and understand what the fans can be like." Chen Guo said.

"Oh, this problem!" Wei Chen nodded his head. The old soldier was the first to speak, "This is certainly a problem. As for myself, I won’t be affected in any way. This senior was still in the scene, these brats were still playing who knew what lame game! My worry is that you babies will cry, when everyone points their fingers at you."　

"Point their fingers? Middle finger? We can just return the favor! Just like this!" Steamed Bun immediately pointed both his middle fingers at Wei Chen.

"Okay, it’s not a problem for Steamed Bun. What about you guys?" Wei Chen said.

"I think it’s more fun like that!" Tang Rou smiled.

"How aggressive!" Wei Chen praised. He turned to Qiao Yifan: "What about you?"

"I think I can deal with it." Qiao Yifan didn’t say too much. Even though he was an invisible player, he still came from a champion team, so his experience was very different from the other rookies.

"Mm, what about you two?" Wei Chen looked at Luo Ji and An Wenyi.

"Me? I have enough on my hands with those summoned creatures. I don’t have the energy to pay attention to any of that." Luo Ji said gloomily. Everyone laughed. Whenever Luo Ji summoned a bunch of creatures, he would turn into a mess and it would be a huge spectacle.

Finally, An Wenyi said: "I don’t think this is a bad thing. As an unknown team, we can ride on Excellent Era’s fame and get more attention that way."　　

"Woah, you little punk..." Wei Chen was speechless. He didn’t bother asking Ye Xiu. If Ye Xiu was bothered by stuff like this, how could he have become a God? A God had to stand over who knew how many butthurt fans. He had even won the championships three times. He wasn’t a senior, who would be easily affected by fans.

"Everyone’s prepared. I can relax then. My plan is this..." Chen Guo didn’t wait for Mo Fan and just started talking. At the practice room, when Su Mucheng returned, she saw Mo Fan playing the game as usual.

"There’s a meeting. Why aren’t you going?" Su Mucheng went back to her seat and asked Mo Fan.　

Mo Fan turned his head to look at Su Mucheng. They had been sitting together for several days now. It was hard to avoid contact. In Su Mucheng’s eyes, Mo Fan was practicing diligently. But in Mo Fan’s eyes, this girl was just there as a pretty face. She never did any proper business. While everyone was practicing hard, if she wasn’t watching a TV show, she was playing some stupid game. She would even sometimes watch a show, while playing.

"I’m not going." Mo Fan glanced at Su Mucheng and then turned his head to continue playing the game. His reply said nothing.　　

"How’s practice going?’ Su Mucheng wasn’t going to bother arguing with him. Seeing that he was practicing, she asked casually.

"Good." Mo Fan said.

"Would you like me to help you practice?" Su Mucheng asked.

Mo Fan turned his head to look at Su Mucheng. His expression was filled with disdain: "You?"

"I can’t?" Su Mucheng smiled like a flower.　　

"Come!" Mo Fan returned to the city and went to the Arena.

Su Mucheng had already set up a room. She was using one of Ye Xiu’s alternate accounts, a random Launcher with terrible equipment.

"Start." Mo Fan didn’t look at any of this and entered the room.

After a minute, Mo Fan’s face was deathly pale. His Deception lay dead on the ground. His opponent’s health bar hadn’t even dropped by 25%.

"You’re not bad." Su Mucheng smiled like a flower just like before.

Chapter 777: Direct Challenge

"You….. you’re..." Mo Fan was never a nimble speaker. Now it became even more stuttered.

He had experienced Su Mucheng’s Launcher in the game before and had died to her hands. He admitted that her skill level wasn’t bad, but it had always been a one versus many situation every time. Ye Xiu was usually among them, so of course, he wasn’t too convinced.

After seeing Su Mucheng watch TV shows and play flash games all day, he became even more doubtful of Su Mucheng’s skill. He started to regard her as just a pretty flower vase. As a result, when he fought against her, he went all out, so he could teach that flower vase a lesson. But contrary to his expectations, it hadn’t even been a minute before that flower vase Launcher blasted him into smithereens.

At Mo Fan’s skill level, he could differentiate between a good and bad situation. Halfway through, he realized the flower vase that he wanted to kick to pieces was actually made of metal. She wasn’t just there to look pretty.

"I’m also a pro player!" Su Mucheng replied.

"Pro player….." Mo Fan frequently heard this term. He wasn’t someone without a conscious. He couldn’t help but be a bit curious about it, especially in this type of environment. The ones who he recognized beside him and in the Internet cafe all seemed very fascinated with pro players, puzzling Mo Fan.

Is it really that interesting?

Recently, Mo Fan constantly thought about this question, when he lay in bed. But he wasn’t the type of person, who would speak his thoughts to others. He quietly observed and paid attention. The others never knew whether he was interested in any of this. Now, a pro player had beaten him senseless in about a minute. This was another huge blow to him. If all pro players were this good, what was the competitive world like?

Mo Fan wouldn’t discuss it with anyone. He just pondered over it himself. After Su Mucheng replied, he just sat there dumbly. After a while, he regained his composure and looked to the side. Su Mucheng wasn’t paying attention to him anymore. She was watching a TV show again, continuing her progress from the day before.

After sensing Mo Fan look at her, Su Mucheng didn’t turn her head to look back. She poured out a handful of melon seeds onto Mo Fan’s table.

Mo Fan was used to this kind of scene. He felt like he had expressed his refusal before by not eating it, but Su Mucheng acted like she didn’t notice. Whenever she ate any snacks, she would occasionally give him some, but she wasn’t always very diligent with it. From time to time, she would forget to give him some. Sometimes, she would be eating and suddenly remember. Then, she would give him a bit of the snack. She wasn’t putting on any fake airs.

After getting crushed by her, Mo Fan’s disdain towards Su Mucheng was gone. He even felt like he had been mistaken and felt embarrassed. However, apologizing directly wasn’t his style. Finally, Mo Fan extended his hands. He had never eaten anything Su Mucheng had given to him, but this time, he made an exception. He thought it was a way of expressing his good will…...

As he shakily cracked open the melon seeds, Mo Fan glanced at Su Mucheng. Su Mucheng was fully engrossed into her TV show and wasn’t paying attention to his side.

Mo Fan didn’t take the initiative to say anything. He just quietly cracked open all of the melon seeds on his table.

In the other room, Chen Guo finally finished explaining her plan. Mo Fan never showed up. No one really bothered with him. Even if he came, he probably wouldn’t say anything, so him coming didn’t matter. Right now, everyone was reflecting on Chen Guo’s plan.

"How aggressive. I think it’s not bad." Wei Chen spoke first.

"A risky move!" Ye Xiu said.

These two usually shared their opinions. Ye Xiu didn’t need to be mentioned. Everyone knew how sharp he was. No one had any objections if he had the largest voice. As for Wei Chen! His background couldn’t compare to Ye Xiu’s, but he was also their senior. He also prided himself on his seniority, so he had the authority too.

As for the others, Tang Rou and An Wenyi were people with their own thoughts, but because of their unfamiliarity with the scene, even if they wanted to say something, they usually wouldn’t be the first to speak.

Qiao Yifan was used to quietly listening on the side. He was the type of person who only spoke if he was called on.

Luo Ji didn’t say much. As a mathematician, he wasn’t too good at things without definite answers. Steamed Bun didn’t need to be talked about. Anything he said would certainly be interpreting it through an extended meaning of the topic. It was that type of talking about the earth as a star kind of extended meaning too.

"Anyone else?" Chen Guo wanted to hear more opinions. Even though she didn’t think the others would be any better than Wei Chen’s or Ye Xiu’s.

"This….." An Wenyi seemed to be hesitant.

"If you have something you want to say, just say it." Chen Guo didn’t like people mumbling.

"Uh, I feel like this approach is kind of similar to cutting off our means of retreat, especially for you. After all, if it doesn’t work out for us, there might be other opportunities. But what about your Internet cafe?" An Wenyi said.

"You’re worrying about me? No need." Chen Guo waved her hands: "Just think about yourself!"

"I have no issues then." An Wenyi said.　　

"What about you, Little Tang?" Chen Guo asked Tang Rou. Chen Guo knew Tang Rou the best. Even though her understanding of Tang Rou wasn’t very thorough, she was good friends with her. She didn’t need her to speak to know how she felt.

"If you want to do it this way, then let’s do it!" Tang Rou said.

"Doing things however you want it to be done! You really are the boss!" Steamed Bun jumped up to say something. As expected, his words were off the mark. Chen Guo never said her word was law. That was what Tang Rou said.

Chen Guo could hear Tang Rou’s unconditional support and encouragement. She nodded her head and pretended like Steamed Bun didn’t exist. When she looked at Qiao Yifan and Luo Ji, they seemed to suddenly tense up as if they didn’t know what to say. Chen Guo might as well just end it: "Then I guess it’s decided."

"Ha ha, now we’ve really become the villains. Not bad!" Wei Chen said.

"With your shamelessness, of course something as trifling as this wouldn’t trouble you." Ye Xiu said.

"No way. The pressure on me definitely isn’t as great as yours. As Excellent Era’s former God, I highly suspect that you’ll be physically harmed. In the future, when you leave the door, be careful of any stray bricks!" Wei Chen said.

"I just need to be wary of you seizing any opportunities to take revenge and I’ll be fine." Ye Xiu said.

Their trash talk wasn’t a good use of their time, so everyone else left and returned to the practice room.

The real waves started two days later. That morning, Chen Guo had the Internet cafe employees start arranging things.

"Boss, are you planning some sort of event?" The Internet cafe employees asked to see what Chen Guo wanted them to hang up. All of them were stunned.

"What are you all standing there for. Hurry up and start moving." Chen Guo pointed.

"Boss, if you hang these up, what about your business?" Someone offered a word of advice.

"Less talking more action. Even if there’s no business, I won’t lower your wages, so just do it." Chen Guo said.

The Internet cafe employees didn’t get a percentage of the Internet cafe, so what did they need to worry about? Chen Guo was very kind to them and they trusted her, so they immediately started arranging the things that Chen Guo wanted. The arrangement was the same as when the Internet cafe hosted an event. Everyone was familiar with the procedure, so it was soon completed. There weren’t many customers early in the morning. Even so, Happy Internet Cafe’s promotion attracted numerous eyes.

Free!

This one word was enough to attract the eyes of the entire street. It didn’t matter if it was real or fake. Those who saw it couldn’t help but be curious.

Customers could use the computers at Happy Internet Cafe for free. In addition, there was no time limit. It would be lasting up until the start of Glory’s new season; the promotion would be for an entire two weeks of time.

Those who didn’t know about Glory were at a loss. Those who did know about Glory were already talking about this joke.

Two weeks for free? What type of scheme was this?

Everyone nowadays was shrewd. When they saw "free", they wouldn’t hastily go and enjoy it. Everyone understood the words "there’s no such thing as free lunch". The word "free" made everyone think that it was some sort of trap.

When Happy Internet Cafe’s employees were still hanging up the signs, the word "free" attracted quite a few people. Once they cleared up any questions on their mind, the whole truth was revealed.

Those who didn’t know about Glory still curiously listened. Those who knew about Glory, especially those who played it and followed the competitive scene, were in an uproar.

Why was Happy Internet Cafe going to be free?

Because Happy Internet Cafe had created a team. Those two weeks of free usage was a send off to their team participating in the Challenger League.

Why was the Internet cafe going so far for their team? Because the team’s goal was to enter the pro scene. Could they not see the building right across street from them?

"F*ck, where’d these nobodies come from? Are they delusional?" Someone from the crowd finally cursed. Not only was this person familiar with Glory, but he was certainly an Excellent Era fan too. If not, why would he go so far as to curse out loud?

"Haha, ignore him. It’s just a way to get attention." Someone mocked.

"People will do anything to make a name for themselves in this day and age!"

"Team Happy. I’m terrified! Ha ha ha ha!"

The crowd of Glory players were already starting to discuss with each other. They didn’t need to be Excellent Era fans to ridicule Happy.

Chen Guo had already expected such a reaction. She didn’t fear and calmly responded. She personally stood outside of the entrance and knocked on the billboard. She pointed at the banner hanging above: "Our new Team Happy is quite good. We have confidence in making it into the pro scene. Before 9/1, using the computers will be completely free. Friends who are interested may even have a chance to spar with our team!"

"Ha ha ha ha, sparring with you nobodies is stupid. Free usage isn’t so bad though. Can I just go in and start using a computer?" Someone sneered.

Chen Guo didn’t become angry. She just smiled: "Of course."

Chapter 778: An Incomprehensible Event

"Brothers! Let’s go! Let’s play for a bit."

After hearing Chen Guo’s confirmation, some began calling out to others. But it was evident that most of the spectators weren’t a part of the same group. Some began to stir, but the vast majority weren’t just out for an early morning stroll. They simply saw a commotion going on and stopped to watch. They still needed to go on with their day. How could they delay their work to take advantage of this kind of small convenience?

Only a few ended up entering the Internet cafe. Some of these few just came in to take another look. After clicking their tongue in astonishment seeing that they actually didn’t need to pay to use the computers, they continued on with their business.

For the first wave of people, the sound of thunder was loud, but the following raindrops were miniscule. Of course, the time of the day was the main reason. Relatively few people walked around in the early morning.

However, as time passed, Happy Internet Cafe became busier and busier. Chen Guo didn’t plan on going upstairs to play Glory. She prepared to stay at the front desk and keep watch.

Rumors had begun to spread already. Some of the customers came to the place after hearing about it. In the afternoon, even Grand Internet Cafe’s owner Ma Chenyi personally came to investigate. He stood outside the Internet cafe entrance, staring at the promotional banner waving around. Chen Guo saw him from the front desk and called out to him: "Hey, it’s boss Ma. What are you standing around for? Come in and take a seat!"

Ma Chenyi nodded his head. He walked in and looked around. Happy Internet Cafe was completely packed. Ma Chenyi ran an Internet cafe too. How could he not know the customer flow at different times of the day. Usually, the period of time between early morning and noon had the least number of customers. However, Happy Internet Cafe was unusually busy, obviously because it was free. This news had spread all the way to Ma Chenyi’s Grand Internet Cafe. At that time, a few customers directly logged out of their computers and booked it. Of course, not all of them were there to take advantage of the deal. The vast majority of the customers were Glory players. They ran over to Happy Internet Cafe because they were attracted by Happy’s ridiculous claim. The gossipers, who spread the rumors, emphasized that Happy Internet Cafe had formed a team, claiming that their goal was to make it into the pro scene.

Even ignoring the fact that this season, a powerhouse team like Excellent Era existed, Internet cafe teams were always just there for fun. How could there not be teams like that? A fair number of Glory players in Grand Internet Cafe were also participating in the Challenger League! But claiming to slaughter their way through to the Pro Alliance, wasn’t that too much of a boast? It was already ridiculous even without Excellent Era. But with Excellent Era participating, it only made Glory players even more furious. Who didn’t know that Team Excellent Era was in the Challenger League this season! You’re right across street from the club. What’s the meaning behind making such a claim?

This was the real reason why numerous Glory players rushed over. If it was just to say that they were going just because it was free would be a bit shameful. It was embarrassing to give that as a reason.

Some went because it was free, while others went because of the rumors. Little by little time, Grand Internet Cafe lost most of its customers.

Ma Chenyi was also a Glory player, but he was mostly a player to understand his customers better. When he heard customers talking about the rumors, he immediately guessed that Chen Guo was most likely running a promotion. When he thought about it some more, could this really be considered a promotion? The current Internet cafe industry relied on Glory. Chen Guo’s move offended these Glory players. In City H, the vast majority of Glory players were fans of Excellent Era. It wasn’t just because of Team Excellent Era’s achievements. The team was located in City H.

This kind of regional advantage couldn’t be ignored because fans gathered from the region were the most loyal. Even when the team was in dire straits, they were willing to stay with the team. They felt a deep connection with the team and tied their team together with their hometown.

Ma Chenyi pondered over it and felt like it didn’t make sense. But seeing that his side didn’t have many customers and that his employees were lying on the table, dozing off, he woke them up to keep watch and then went over to Happy to investigate.

After carefully taking a look from the entrance, he discovered that the rumors he heard from Grand Internet Cafe weren’t exaggerating it one bit. Happy Internet Cafe had formed a team and their statement was very clear and straightforward. The only thing it didn’t do was directly mention Excellent Era.

"Boss Chen, what are you trying to do? I don’t understand." Ma Chenyi entered. Chen Guo had personally come over to greet him. She obviously knew he wasn’t here to use the computer.

"I saw you standing around outside for awhile. Did I not write it clearly enough?" Chen Guo chuckled.

"It’s clear, but I really don’t understand the meaning hidden inside." Ma Chenyi said.　　

"Boss Ma, you’re too suspicious! There’s no hidden meaning. It’s just as you see." Chen Guo said.

"Just as I see?" Ma Chenyi stared blankly, "You actually think your team can make it into the pro scene? Are you joking?"　　

"Not at all. That’s really what I think." Chen Guo smiled.

Ma Chenyi was somewhat confused. Chen Guo was his competitor. They often came into conflict with each other. However, Ma Chenyi felt like Chen Guo wasn’t anyone too shrewd. Whatever she said was what she meant. She was very straightforward. If Chen Guo said there was no other hidden meaning, then she probably wasn’t lying. But it was just too incomprehensible! He couldn’t believe it even if you beat him to death!

"I say….." Ma Chenyi was still suspicious, "Last time, when we bet, you indeed had a few experts. Their skill level seemed quite good. In the past, if your team participated in the Challenger League with those experts, I would actually bet money on them making it through, but this time, Excellent Era is participating! Even if your team has some real skill, you don’t actually think they could beat a team with three All Stars, right?"

"We’ve never fought against them? How do you know it’s impossible? In order to find out a winner in Glory, you have to fight to actually know." Chen Guo said.

"Your words aren’t wrong, but that’s when both sides are fairly even. Your team is about as good as Team Excellent Era? Neither of us like to mince words when we talk to each other, so I won’t be polite. If you had such a team, I doubt they’d be under your control. Your Internet cafe... is it worth more than the price of a single All Star?" Ma Chenyi said, while sizing up Happy Internet Cafe.

"Hehe, nothing’s absolute!" Chen Guo laughed.

Ma Chenyi trusted in Chen Guo’s character. He believed that Chen Gou wouldn’t dupe him. She seemed to be very certain about her unimaginable claim. There was only one possibility. Che Guo had a trump card that he didn’t know about.

He and Chen Guo weren’t strangers, but as competitors, their relationship wasn’t great. If the other side wasn’t going to take the initiative to say it, Ma Chenyi reckoned that he wouldn’t be able to get an answer if he asked. As a result, he didn’t say much more. He turned his head to look at the busy Happy Internet Cafe and then said: "Are you really planning on keeping this up until the start of the new season?"

"Yeah!" Chen Guo nodded her head.

"Then it seems like I’ll have to take a break for this half a month." Ma Chenyi said.

"That might not be necessary. My place is already full. It’s almost peak hours. There definitely won’t be enough seats! At that time, there’ll definitely be people coming over to your place. I say, why don’t you do the same promotion as me?" Chen Guo said.

"Stop joking. Why should I be crazy like you?" Ma Chenyi said.

"Then don’t regret it!" Chen Guo said.

"More like you’d better not regret it. I’m quite interested in seeing what you’ll be doing next." Ma Chenyi waved his hands, "I’ll be going. I’ll go back and see if there needs to be any work done on the Internet cafe. Using this half a month, I’ll see if I can do a renovation."

"Take care! I won’t be sending you off." Chen Guo said.

"No need. You’re so busy. How could you have any time to spare?" Ma Chenyi said and then left.

Happy Internet Cafe was still packed. Some came in because it was free, but the majority of customers came because they were unconvinced by Happy’s claim. They went on the computers for free, while mocking Happy for not knowing the difference between heaven and earth. These people weren’t here to try out the computers at the Internet cafe. They enjoyed the free usage, while looking down on Happy’s promotion. They came in to laugh at Happy.

They said whatever bad thing you could think of, leaving those who didn’t understand Glory stunned. What’s going on? The Internet cafe was allowing them to use the computers for free, yet people were ridiculing them. The other customers couldn’t wrap their heads around it.

They didn’t understand it, but they didn’t need to. Chen Guo was mentally prepared for the insults and mockery coming her way, so she calmly sat there.

A few who recognized Chen Guo would sometime laugh at her.

"Boss, where’s your champion team? You’re not going to bring them out for everyone to see?"

‘Yeah, we’re here because of the rumors. We need to get a signature before we go. Maybe next year it’ll be worth a lot of money."

"What are you saying? What do you mean maybe? You mean definitely!"

All sorts of yelling bombarded her, but Chen Guo was uncharacteristically in a good mood. She just smiled, patiently replying to their insincere questions. She answered: "The team is currently practicing. It’s not convenient for them to come out and meet everyone."

"They’re even practicing! How professional!" Someone hollered, followed by a roar of laughter.　　

"Boss, it says outside that apart from being able to use the computers for free, we can have a chance to spar with the team! We’ve used the computers enough already. We’re waiting to spar with them."

"You’re not going to say, using the computers is free, but you have to pay money to spar them, right?"

"F*ck, could that be the real reason behind this event? Then I’d better run. The price for the champion team to come out must be really high. Can we afford it?"

Another roar of laughter. Chen Guo waited for the laughter to die down, before replying: "If you want to spar with them, wait until night time!"

Chapter 779: Who’s Going Up to Slap Their Face?

At Happy Internet Cafe, all sorts of terrible insults were thrown around. Many of the Internet cafe customers wouldn’t stop. Chen Guo handled the situation calmly though. One reason was because she was mentally prepared. A second reason was because she understood the passion from the fans. If it had been her in the past, if some random Internet cafe claimed that their team would defeat Excellent Era and make it into the pro scene, she would definitely have laughed at their arrogance.

Chen Guo relied on putting herself in their shoes to mentally prepare herself. As a result, she faced the mock and ridicule coming her way with great interest. Many people’s talents would burst out at these moments. It was a curious occurrence.

The Internet cafe was packed since noon. Quite a few people even lined up, asking when a computer would be open. The Internet cafe employees could only helplessly shrug their shoulders. Free usage with no limit. They wouldn’t know when someone would leave. Order could still be kept though. Even though customers didn’t need to pay, they still needed to register before using a computer, so there was still an order to customers coming and going.

However, the majority of customers were here to stir trouble. How could they be eager to comply? Quite a few of the employees suffered numerous grievances. In the end, Chen Guo had to work hard to calm down her employees’ feelings.

Night fell. The Internet cafe was at its peak hours. Several people discovered that Happy Internet Cafe a promotion going on. Unfortunately, there were no seats open in Happy. Ma Chenyi acted as if his business couldn’t survive if Chen Guo kept up this promotion, but it wasn’t actually that exaggerated. If there wasn’t enough room for two Internet cafes on one street, one of them would have closed long ago. Both of their Internet cafes were close to Club Excellent Era, so their business was exceptionally good. Who didn’t have a computer at this day and age? But many were still willing to come to an Internet cafe with their friends to play or perhaps they met friends in the Internet cafe and frequently played together there. People could communicate online, but it was a different feeling, sitting together in real life.

Happy Internet Cafe was packed with no seats open. In the end, many people had to go to Grand Internet Cafe. There was nothing to worry about.

Tonight, even though there weren’t any seats left, many people still stayed around because it was rumored that this arrogant team would come out and spar with them. A good deal of Glory players had been holding back their anger all day, waiting to give this team a serious beating! After supper time passed, someone shouted: "Boss, when is your team coming out to spar with us? Do you have a precise time?"

"7:30!" Chen Guo said.

It wasn’t long until 7:30. Some watched the time go by second by second. When it was time, they immediately started shouting. Many players had heard the news and stopped by the Internet cafe to take a look. But when they saw the situation, they found it difficult to stay. It wasn’t convenient for them to watch!

Boss Chen was considerate though! Once the clock hit 7:30, she immediately had her employees take out the large screen projector. Frequent Happy Internet Cafe customers knew what was going on. Happy Internet Cafe really wasn’t afraid of others watching!　　

When they saw this action, quite a few players started to lose confidence.

None of them believed that this team could actually beat Excellent Era, but it was hard to say if they could give this team any trouble, seeing that the other side appeared fearless. They really weren’t sure. Everyone here was just a normal player. After thinking about it, if the other side was actually so shameless as to make such a claim despite being unable to clean up random guys like them, then wouldn’t that be too embarrassing?

Chen Guo wasn’t trying to figure out their thoughts. After setting everything up, she smiled at the impatient bunch: "Are you guys ready?"

"Where’s your team?" The crowd looked around.

"In the Arena. Does it need to be face to face?" Chen Guo laughed.

Everyone listened, so it turns out the other side wouldn’t be appearing. They would only be online! An already unconfident guy used this pretext to make a fuss: "F*ck, they actually think they’re some big shot! This senior won’t stand for it!"

This person was the first to leave. After stomping out of the place, he sneaked back into the crowd to watch the upcoming show.

"Everyone’s here to play Glory. There’s no need to do anything offline! Many of the rounds in the Challenger League are played online." Chen Guo said and pointed to the projection screen: "I’ve already set up all of this so that everyone can see. It can’t be that no one’s going to come, right? Weren’t you guys yelling all afternoon? You there….. You’re not coming?"

Chen Guo directly pointed out the person with the loudest voice. How could she not have an impression of anyone? She remembered them very clearly!

This old bro could feel his heart thump! He didn’t think that the other side would be so evil as to point him out. Just as he was about to make an excuse, the people who had been hollering with him were also evil. They saw that they hadn’t been picked and that they wouldn’t be getting embarrassed, so they started egging him on: "Go up, go up! What’s there to be afraid of! Go!"

This old bro was furious! He now had a better understanding of the phrase "the shot hits the bird that pokes its head out". But since he had been picked out, it would be too shameful to back out. Anything he said would be treated as an excuse. How could he lose face?

　

No choice. I’ll have to brace myself and do it!

"I’ll go, I’ll go." This brother finally stood out. He didn’t dare to make any claims though. He first tried to play things down: "This little brother isn’t very good. My equipment isn’t good either. I’ll be a warm up!"

"Ha ha, it’s just a spar. It doesn’t matter if you’re good or bad. There’s no such thing as not being allowed to play because you’re bad." Chen Guo remarked.

This older bro felt like Chen Guo’s words sounded very reasonable and pleasing. For the first time, he returned a thanks and then asked: "Which room?"

The Arena room had obviously been created already. Chen Guo and Ye Xiu were in contact with each other! The projector screen showed the battle from a spectator view. Everyone soon saw which character the team put out: Battle Mage, Soft Mist.

Soft Mist was actually quite famous, but that was only in the upper circles in the game. She was bound together with Ye Xiu, so the Club guilds kept an eye on her too. For normal players, the name Soft Mist didn’t ring a bell.

Chen Guo didn’t know if there were any Club guild members among the crowd, but it didn’t seem like there was any reaction. Once that old bro’s character entered the room, the two began fighting. Numerous people had been waiting all day for this face-slapping moment to come. They watched the fight attentively and the Internet cafe became abnormally quiet. Only the sounds of battle could be heard, the sound of flesh getting butchered... this old bro was being torn apart by this Battle Mage! He lost shortly afterwards. He lost so badly that no one could say anything. It was a perfect victory. The old bro failed to even touch the other side.

Happy Internet Cafe was silent.

They were waiting for the face-slapping moment, but it turned out that it was their face instead! Their skill level wasn’t high enough. In the end, the loudest of them was picked to come out. As expected, the face slapper was sliced up by the other side’s spear. A perfect victory was a slap to their face. Slap slap.

"It seems I’m not good enough. Who’s coming next?" This old bro stood up. He was a classic example of someone who could only talk big. He despised Team Happy’s intentions, but when it was time for him to come out, he couldn’t back it up. If he was actually an expert, even if he couldn’t beat Tang Rou, it wouldn’t have ended in a perfect victory for her. This guy was truly lacking.

The Internet cafe instantly became quiet again. To be honest, they couldn’t tell how good the other Battle Mage was from the previous fight! All they could tell was that she at least wasn’t weak. No one had any confidence in beating her! The attempt at slapping the other side’s face became the reverse. It was best if someone else did it. It was better to be careful!

The previously loud crowd had been given a chance to embarrass the other side, but now they suddenly cowered. They still felt like Team happy was shameless, but they weren’t good enough to expose the other side’s facade. They could only wave their flags and shout battle cries, hoping some God would descend upon those fools. But right now, everyone was looking at one another. It seemed like everyone was just a flagbearer!

"Is that it?" Chen Guo was delighted, making everyone feel extremely unhappy. They were furious, but they couldn’t say anything back! If the other side said "Oh, then you go up!", what could you do? You couldn’t say "I’m not a good player, but I have good eyes." You would just be talking big! It was no different from getting your face slapped.

"I’ll try!" Someone finally came out. Everyone was excited. At this moment, if someone dared to jump out, he must be an expert with a lot of confidence, right?

Everyone excitedly watched this person enter the room. They looked at his equipment. It wasn’t anything glamorous though. Then, they saw the fight. Mm, this person was a bit better than the other guy, but….. It was just a bit better. Not long afterwards, he fell. It wasn’t a perfect victory for the other side at least.

Everyone was speechless. After being slapped in the face several times in a row, their faces had lost all color! But the issue was that they didn’t have the ability to do anything about it and even complained that the guy who jumped out overestimated himself. One person was enough to be a warm up. Being whipped by the other side was equivalent to everyone being whipped. Everyone was together! Do you not understand?

But they discovered that this guy truly didn’t understand! After losing, he didn’t seemed embarrassed at all. He felt it was very natural: "Wow, wow. Can I try again?"

Everyone suddenly understood. It seemed like this person wasn’t here to jeer at the other side. He was actually here to practice with the team!

Chapter 780: Search search search for an expert!

There were quite a few rowdy players, but not everyone. There were still a few rational ones. Just like this one here. Even though it wasn’t a perfect victory for the other side again, it wasn’t much better. But since he wasn’t trying to slap the other side’s face, he wouldn’t feel embarrassed for losing. He wasn’t the type of person, who felt like he was unrivalled under the heavens. Losing a few rounds in the Arena was very normal!

After losing a round, this person still wanted another. Chen Guo didn’t object. The challenger pressed ready and Tang Rou started the match. She went all out like before and the challenger lost again.

"Amazing! Too amazing!" The challenger praised sincerely, making the others in the crowd feel incredibly uncomfortable. But what could they do? This person didn’t have the same mindset as them. What could they criticize him for? He lost two rounds and then praised Team Happy. That wasn’t what they wanted to see! They wanted to expose Team Happy’s feebleness and show that even a three year old kid could mash the keyboard and win. Even though that obviously wasn’t possible, they could still dream.

"Is this guy someone they set up?" There was always someone shameless in the crowd, who would think about things from the most detestable perspective. Some people even supported this idea and nodded their heads: "It must be!"

Chen Guo started asking again: "Is there anyone else? Is there anyone else? What’s going on? Where’d your enthusiasm during the daytime go?"

Chen Guo said questioningly, but everyone could hear the ridicule in her voice. Her look of honesty didn’t agree with her words, making it seem all the more vengeful.

"How many people are in your team? What’s the point if it’s always an individual competition? Can your team play a group arena or team competition?" Someone suddenly asked. This brother’s head was turning. He suddenly thought: what if Team Happy only had a single expert to scare everyone? If that was the case, then if they played a group arena or team competition, wouldn’t that expose the other side’s trick?

When he asked these questions, several others immediately understood his intent. They started getting excited again. They didn’t wait for Chen Guo to reply and started chiming in: "Yeah! Can’t we play a group arena or a team competition? It’s more fun with more people!"

"Sure!" Chen Guo grinned.

Everyone heard her answer and their hearts fell. Sh*t. It looks like the fox isn’t exploiting the tiger’s might. They’re the real deal!

"Group arena or team competition. You can guys can pick." Chen Guo said.

They had already reached this step; they couldn’t back out now. Everyone began looking at each other. They had gathered at this Internet Cafe for a single reason. Most of them didn’t know each other, so they wouldn’t know each other’s skill level in Glory. They needed to form a team, but no one knew who to pick. Finally, someone stood out: "I’ll go!"

"Then I’ll go too!"

"I’ll go as well!"

As soon as one person stood out, others soon followed. In the blink of an eye, three people volunteered themselves forward. It was just enough people for a group arena round.

"Three people? Group arena?" Chen Guo said and sent a text on her cellphone. The Arena room quickly changed to a group arena format. Following Soft Mist, a Brawler Steamed Bun Invasion and a Warlock Windward Formation stepped onto stage.

As soon as they saw the lineup, many of them immediately thought: "Not good."

Soft Mist was put first. She had practically achieved perfect victories against those two challengers, which meant she would be around full health against the third. It would a 1v3! Soft Mist’s skill level was quite high. If their team couldn’t get past her, they wouldn’t have any way of exposing the people behind her! How good was their side? Probably better than the last two challengers, right? Could they take down Soft Mist?

Unwittingly, no one was thinking about whether they could win the match, but rather if those three could even beat Soft Mist.

Their predictions came true. Sure enough, all three challengers lost to Soft Mist. These three were indeed better than the last two, but the three could only take off half of Soft Mist’s health. If this continued, Soft Mist would have no problems with a 1v6.

It was a 1v3. Even if they didn’t want to believe it, she must be an expert. In the normal player circle, having half health remaining in a 1v3 would only happen when an experienced player fought against beginners. The gap between them could clearly be seen. Since Happy Internet Cafe dared to make such an arrogant claim, it seemed like they had indeed prepared well. Trying to challenge them was truly too naive.

When Chen Guo asked if anyone was up for a team competition, no one uttered a sound. In the end, someone asked if they could fight someone else other than Soft Mist.

Chen Guo happily agreed. In the end, Steamed Bun Invasion came out. Everyone was finally completely convinced: they alone couldn’t overturn Happy Internet Cafe. Happy had at least come prepared and wouldn’t be humiliated so easily.

That night, only players, who weren’t looking to stir trouble, gave it a try, and ended up praising Team Happy. In the end, those more extreme players were left in silence. The previous few, who were talented at insults, had already disappeared.

Chen Guo saw crowd die down and asked "Is there anyone else?" three times. After seeing that there was no response, she had her employees put away the projector. At the end, she said to everyone: "You’re welcome to come again tomorrow."

The crowd was furious! Without an expert, what was the point in coming again tomorrow?

For them, they parted the place on bad terms tonight. The crowd all left at practically the same time. They failed to meet their goal, so what was the point in staying? They weren’t here to take advantage of the free usage, but because of their dislike for Happy Internet Cafe.

After leaving the Internet cafe, talents from the crowd started cursing again. But no matter how much they cursed, they had to admit that Happy Internet Cafe had found impressive players.These people couldn’t bear it though. For a moment, everyone began talking about what experts they knew and how skilled these experts were, pointing out how could they crush eight Soft Mists.

No one took any notice of the brags. The more serious ones truly wanted to see if they could find any experts to challenge Happy Internet Cafe. They hated to see such shamelessness and arrogance!

In the end, they narrowed it down to a few dependable experts. The more reliable players left their contact info and prepared to contact these experts, asking them to come over and take down Happy Internet Cafe.

The next day, Happy Internet Cafe was as crowded as the previous day. The crowd of unruly players had been pushed back yesterday, but there were still no lack of them today. What happened the second day and the first day were extraordinarily similar. There were players mocking and ridiculing Happy Internet Cafe’s team from early in the morning. Chen Guo continued to handle the situation calmly, telling them they could spar the team at night.

At night, the unruly crowd excitedly tried to take down the team, but were trashed instead. They once again left dejectedly. After exiting the Internet cafe, they cursed together and started thinking of experts, who could squish those experts with a single finger.

Third day, fourth day....

The majority of players came arrogantly and left dejectedly. By the fifth day, news of Happy Internet Cafe’s team had spread online, attracting widespread attention. A team right across street from Club Excellent Era, planning on making their way through the Challenger League into the pro scene, was quite amusing.

But in the very beginning, everyone including the posters treated it as a joke. Everyone was laughing at this unknown Internet cafe for using such a stupid method to promote themselves. Did they not know that offending so many Glory fans would actually end up hurting their business? Did they actually think their infamy would make their business prosper? Did they not care about their reputation?

Everyone laughed, while waiting for Happy to be slapped in the face!

But one day, two days, three days, four days passed. On the fifth day, more and more people couldn’t stand it anymore: this Team Happy really did have some skill. Some were already making guesses. Could this be Excellent Era’s work? After all, Excellent Era wouldn’t receive as much attention in the Challenger League. Hyping their team up in this way could be considered a method.

While others were arguing online, some decent players finally showed up on the fifth day. The crowd had been losers for the past several days. In the end, after much discussion, they were able to contact a real expert.

Speaking of which, it was that easy to find people in the scene. On the first, second, and third day, these people were all normal players, who didn’t know each other. But after searching for experts together and holding meetings, they became close. These experts had seen the rumors online and now that people had come looking for them, they felt like they should come out take care of things.

You’re looking. We’re looking. We come together and look together. At around seven in Happy Internet Cafe, eight rumored experts came. They even had two more than what was needed to play a team competition.

These eight experts felt like even though they couldn’t compare to pro players, they were still big figures in the Glory community! As soon as they announced their IDs, everyone paid their respects. The players who invited them were running around like servants, completely forgetting how they had left Happy Internet Cafe crestfallen these past few days. One of them saw Chen Guo and immediately went over to issue a challenge.

The eight experts had been told about this Internet cafe’s boss. Their eyes lit up. A beauty!

One of them immediately rushed forward and followed after the person, who went looking for Chen Guo. They reached there together. That person gave him a glance and gave an introduction: "This is Flying Cloud Internet Cafe’s Easy Bro. I’m sure you’ve heard of him before, boss."

Chapter 781: Easy Bro

Chapter 781: Chapter 781 - Easy Bro

He was called Easy Bro because his character’s name was Easy Life. Adding a "Bro" to the name represented everyone’s approval and respect for him. Chen Guo actually did recognize this name. As a part of the Glory community in City H’s Internet cafes, Easy Life was quite famous. City H’s Internet cafes would occasionally organize Glory tournaments. This was how Easy Life became famous. Flying Cloud Internet Cafe was naturally the Internet cafe, which he frequented.

In the past, Chen Guo would have certainly admired this kind of expert. But things were different now. One of Glory’s Gods had hung around Chen Guo for so long now. It would be stranger if Chen Guo was still frightened by an expert at this level.

"Easy Life, right? I’ve heard of him." Chen Guo nodded her head, after listening to his introduction.

It was a rather dull response, which made Easy Bro feel quite disappointed. How could he know that in the world that Boss Chen now lived in, it was already nice of her not to look down on him?

"The atmosphere is pretty good!" Easy Bro wasn’t in a hurry to shift to the main topic. He looked around and commented on Chen Guo’s Happy Internet Cafe.

"It’s not bad." Chen Guo replied.

"I heard there are a few skilled experts here. How about you call them out for everyone to get to know?" Easy Bro said. In the time it took him to say these few words, the other seven experts had gathered over to his side. If their expressions weren’t arrogant, they were arrogant. All of them acted as if they were unrivaled under the heavens.

"Mm, everyone, take a seat!" Chen Guo said.

"What? You’re not going to let us meet them first?" Easy Bro said.

"Is there a need to do that?" Chen Guo didn’t understand.

There really was no need for that. In any case, who was better or worse would be decided in the game. Whether or not they met in real life wouldn’t decide anything. Not meeting was logical for this reason, but what was so hard about meeting each other? Team Happy had never showed themselves these past few days. These people were constantly plotting how to embarrass Team Happy, so they had all kinds of weird and clever thoughts. They naturally liked to think about possible conspiracy theories. As a result, the more that team Happy refused to show their faces to everyone, the more they wanted to see them. No matter what, they always raised this question.

But Chen Guo refused to relent. There was nothing they could do about it. The eight experts weren’t here to chat around. Someone had already found seats for them.

These past few days, the Internet cafe stopped bothering to put away the projector setup. As soon as the eight experts found seats, Chen Guo messaged Ye Xiu and the others and went over to spectate.

The faceslapping group was very confident about this time’s attack and glared at Chen Guo provocatively. Easy Bro was still showing off his free and easy attitude. He looked at Chen Guo and smiled: "How are we playing this?"

"Anything you like. When you enter the room, just say whatever method you choose." Chen Guo announced the room ID to everyone. Soon, spectators swarmed to the room. The eight experts logged into the game with their account cards and entered the room.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist was once again the lead for Team Happy. Someone immediately whispered something to Easy Bro, which Easy Bro responded with a disapproving look. He smiled at Chen Guo: "Then how about a 1v1?" This guy seemed to pay particularly close attention to Chen Guo’s attitude.

"Do as you wish." Chen Guo said.

"Then I’ll go first?" Easy Bro called out to the other seven experts. These eight experts weren’t really friends with each other. They just knew each other’s names or perhaps met each other at a competition or an event. Even though they had been pulled into the same car together, none of them believed to be worse than the others. Liking each other was out of the question. Easy Bro was more talkative than the others and considered himself to be the leader. The other seven didn’t like it. Seeing that he wanted to fight first and move the spotlight onto him, the other seven had a few objections. Easy Bro was merely stating his intent though. He wasn’t up for any discussion. After giving them a heads up, he pressed ready. Tang Rou was decisive! The two immediately entered the playing field.

"Amazing!"

When the two characters appeared on the opposite corners of the arena, the spectators already let out gasps of surprise. Easy Bro was a Blade Master. His equipment was rather eye-catching. In the eyes of normal players, his equipment was enough to arouse envy. Everyone looked at his equipment. Thoughts of "he deserves his reputation" floated into their minds, and they exclaimed in admiration in response.

These gasps of surprise naturally made Easy Bro very happy.

"Ahem!" He cleared his throat. Just when he was about to say something, he saw something on his screen move. Soft Mist had already started charging towards him.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Tang Rou started with a powerful high-level skill. Soft Mist thrust her battle spear straight towards Easy Bro with astonishing might.

Easy Bro simply smiled.

"Is there a need to be in such a hurry?" Easy Bro freely and easily remarked. His swiped his mouse and his character Easy Life sidestepped it. A powerful skill like Dragon Breaks the Ranks didn’t pose any threat in Easy Bro’s eyes. This kind of playstyle was very beginner-like. And these guys were saying she was good?

Easy Bro was starting to have doubts. The instant that Soft Mist swept past Easy Bro, he tapped his keyboard and swiped his mouse. Easy Life leaped into the air and released a sword light: Sword Draw.

Easy Bro was ambitious with this move. He had already started his next follow-ups. But Soft Mist suddenly halted. She twisted her body and faced the incoming attack with her own: Tyrant’s Destruction.

Both skills attacked in an arc. However, the spear was longer than the sword, so the arc radius was longer. Easy Bro had already started preparing a follow-up, when he realized that the other side had returned the blow. He quickly thought to Guard against it, but it was too late.

His Sword Draw came out first though. It was also faster than Tyrant’s Destruction, so it reached Soft Mist first. Sword Draw didn’t have higher priority than the Battle Mage’s Tyrant’s Destruction, so it couldn’t interrupt it. The sword light hit Soft Mist, but Soft MIst’s spear also hit Easy Life.　　

A trade!

That seemed to be the result of the trade. Neither attacks dealt too much damage, but not too little either. Neither side gained any advantage from it though.

That was just damage though.

What about the skill effects?

Soft Mist was forced back two steps from the Sword Slash, but Easy Life was knocked into the air by the Tyrant’s Destruction. The spear struck his legs, causing him to tumble backwards with his legs up and head down.

Pu!

Easy Life ate dirt. The attack had flipped him upside down too quickly. A pro player would have been able to stabilize himself. Easy Bro was embarrassed. He knew what to do, but he couldn’t complete the correct actions, so his character hit the ground face first.

This flip was obviously very ugly looking, especially with it being displayed on the big projector screen. Even if Easy Bro couldn’t see what the scene looked like because of his first-person perspective, he could see the projector screen. His character’s head was planted into the ground. Such an ugly appearance could be seen by everyone.

Easy Bro was furious! In his eyes, the other side had used a dirty method and traded with him irrationally. It might look unsightly, but in terms of the results, wasn’t there not much of a difference? The flip only made it seem like he was in a disadvantageous situation.

"Despicable!" Easy Bro denounced angrily. He mainly wanted to refute what just happened. He quick recovered and prepared to roll away, when the spectators cried out.

The spectators were looking from a bird’s eye perspective and could see the battle in full view. Easy Life was still rolling on the ground, when Soft Mist strode over. She still seemed a bit far away, when she thrust her spear. But with the next step, her spear just happened to hit Easy Bro at the perfect distance.

Easy Life was launched into the air and started tumbling again. His head once again face planted into the ground. This time, even if he had the reaction speed, it wouldn’t have made a difference. Circle Swing was a high priority grab skill.

This time, he was clearly at a disadvantage. Easy Bro started to panic. As he got up, he put up a Guard. The spectators could once again see the situation more clearly though. When Easy Life got up, Soft Mist intentionally appeared behind him. Easy Life’s sword was placed in front of him, preparing to block incoming attacks, but there was no one there.

Easy Bro realized that the situation wasn’t good and immediately turned his body. The spear had already reached him though. It had to be said that Easy Bro really was quite skilled for a normal player. Just being able to turn around and try to jump away was fairly impressive awareness. Unfortunately, Soft Mist was faster. Soft Mist used Sky Strike, launching Easy Life even higher into the air.

The Internet cafe was silent.

It was already the fifth night of absolute silence this week. Everyone originally thought that they could slap Team Happy’s face, but what’s going on with Easy Bro? He seems to be losing?

Easy Bro didn’t know what was going on either. He felt like he couldn’t do anything. He kept trying things, but he had already completely fallen into the opponent’s pace.

"Not bad." On the second floor, Ye Xiu and the others were also using the projector to watch the match! After seeing Tang Rou hold the advantage, Ye Xiu nodded his head and commented: "This person today is pretty decent, but Little Tang is very good at utilizing her advantage. She’s completely controlled him. She’s improved a lot recently, especially her precision."

"Not bad, not bad." Wei Chen also praised. Tang Rou remained unmoved. She continued to let out fierce attacks until Easy Life lay dead on the ground.

Chapter 782: Losing face alone isn’t as good as everyone losing face

The Internet cafe kept its silenced status. It was a persistent effect, starting from day one, when Team Happy was attacked on all sides by the crowd, to Easy Bro being launched into the air by Soft Mist’s Sky Strike.

The projector screen displayed a giant "Glory!" It looked repulsive in everyone’s eyes. Easy Bro felt ashamed.

But he refused to accept the result. He felt like he had the ability, but he somehow wasn’t able to fully display it. He thought it was most likely because his hands weren’t warmed up yet or perhaps because he had underestimated the opponent.

"Oh? Not bad. It looks like I’ll need to be serious." Easy Bro hastily said, propping himself up.

There were no cheers of support from the crowd.

The crowd didn’t know what Easy Bro was thinking right now, but from what they saw, Easy Bro had been on the losing side the entire time. He was led around the nose up until his death. That should be because of a wide gap in skill, not an issue of being serious, no?

Anxious to win back his pride, Easy Bro immediately pressed ready again. He was even a bit worried that his opponent wouldn’t accept. Luckily for him, the other side was considerate of his feelings and immediately pressed ready as well. A new match began.

This time, I have to be serious.

Easy Bro reminded himself.

The battlefield appeared on the projector screen. The two characters quickly started fighting.

Dragon Tooth, Sky Strike, Falling Flower Palm, Circle Swing…..

Magic chasers filled the sky. The magical aura from Battle Spirit glowed with a golden light.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart, Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Rising Dragon Soars the Sky…..

Soft Mist became braver as the battle continued.

Easy Bro, on the other hand... roll, roll, and another roll. Apart from a few skills used at the start of the battle, Easy Life seemed to only know to roll. This match seemed even more unsightly than the last match.

Finally, the projector screen displayed a huge "Glory!" The Internet cafe fell silent. Easy Bro pushed away the keyboard in disappointment. He got up and turned around. He saw everyone looking at him and opened his mouth, wanting to say something, but he didn’t know what to say. The opponent was supposed to be pretty good, but that good?

Easy Bro was at a loss. He recalled how high-spirited he had been initially. Now he was hoping there was a hole for him to jump into.

The other seven experts also felt uneasy. Easy Bro had lost two matches in a row. No matter what the reason was, both losses had been pitiful. That itself said something. Whether it was a bad mistake by Easy Bro or luck from the opponent, it wasn’t likely for that to happen two times in a row, no? Moreover, Easy Bro himself had already stood up, meaning he was well aware of his own capabilities.

Even though the other experts weren’t willing to accept it, thinking themselves as the best, if they fought against one another, being able to win in such a dominating manner would be extremely difficult.

Easy Bro had stepped down. Who would take his place?

The seven players looked at one another. From the expressions they saw, all of them wanted to escape. Yes, none of them wanted to go up.

The onlooking crowd, which had invited these experts to come, were also speechless. They didn’t think Soft Mist would actually be so strong. They thought these eight famed experts would be enough to take her down. But Easy Bro lost just as badly as they had. How skilled was this Soft Mist?

The crowd was motionless. The eight experts as well as the players who invited them couldn’t show their faces. They huddled together and started muttering to each other. They couldn’t conceal how difficult Soft Mist proved to be for them. They could only face the obstacle and come up with a counterplan.

Chen Guo had seen everything. She was overjoyed! Hiding such strong emotions was difficult for Boss Chen. She quietly calmed herself down. After making sure she wouldn’t burst out into laughter as soon as she opened her mouth, she asked: "Is there anyone else who wants to come up?"

What an ordinary question! But to these guys, it was no different than a slap to their faces. Everyone saw that they had invited eight experts to come. As soon as one of them was beaten, the other seven cowered. How embarrassing!

Even so, the seven experts decided that they wouldn’t play anymore 1v1s. They didn’t want to be reduced to Easy Bro’s state. Easy Bro had originally been in high-spirits, but now he wasn’t saying a word, acting quiet and careful.

"Then that’ll be it for 1v1s!" Someone from the crowd finally said. It was clearly a way to avoid it, so the experts themselves wouldn’t say it. This type of excuse was a burden on the ones who invited them too.

"How about we just go directly with a team competition? I don’t think we’ve done in a team competition before." The same person asked.

This was the solution that they came up with. Soft Mist was strong, too strong. She would crush all of them in a 1v1. In a group arena, it would be difficult to win with such a strong enemy leading. As a result, the only way to win back their pride was through the team competition. They were still suspecting that Team Happy only had this single expert holding up the team. In a team competition, a someone might be dragged into the dirt by those weaker!

"Team competition? No problem!" Chen Guo replied delightedly. Everyone’s expressions immediately dimmed. Chen Guo wasn’t pretending or acting haughty, but she wasn’t being quiet about it either. Seeing her usual attitude, it looked like no one in the entire team would be much worse than Soft Mist!

But they had already requested it. It wasn’t possible to back down now. Easy Bro declined. He had ample reason to refuse. Of the remaining seven, one of them wouldn’t have to appear on stage. As a result, all seven immediately became modest. Too bad for the one Cleric among them though. Being modest wouldn’t affect him at all. As the only healer among the eight experts, he had choice but to participate in the team competition.

The talking back and forth took five minutes. In the end, six people were decided upon. According to the official tournament rules, five players would start the match and a sixth player would be a reserve player. The room switched to a team competition format.

Team Happy’s side: Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, Windward Formation, One Inch Ash, Little Cold Hands. The reserve player... the reserve player still wasn’t here. Everyone was waiting. But after their six experts pressed ready, the match started. Team Happy didn’t even want a reserve player.

5v6….. Even though the sixth player wouldn’t appear until he was subbed in, the advantage was still enormous. Was Team Happy really that confident?

The crowd was in an uproar. The battle had begun. For team competition between normal players, tactics weren’t much of a thing. And the easiest mistake to make was that everyone felt like they were correct and everyone else was stupid. When everything was going smoothly, it wasn’t a big deal. But as soon as they were in a predicament, raging was highly probable.

After about a minute and a half, the raging had already started.

"Grappler, where the f*ck are you going? Do you not know what target the healer first means?" The first expert to take the lead, cursed the Grappler among his team. He thought the Grappler not attacking the healer first was extremely stupid.

"Are you f*cking blind? The healer is being protected. If I could get through them alone, why the f*ck would you guys even be here? Elementalist, give me cover!" The Grappler explained himself, while shifting the topic to the Elementalist.

"F*ck, you’re not even giving me cover so I can cast anything and you want me to give you f*cking cover? Have you seen me cast anything yet? Do you guys know how to play the game?" The Elementalist was quite aggressive. He directly blamed the entire team. The crowd at Happy Internet Cafe had spent a lot of effort to find these experts and now they were being criticized for not knowing how to play.

"You actually f*cking think we don’t know how to play? As if you know how. Who’s ever seen a mage just stand there and cast spells. You might as well be a dog!" Someone immediately fired back.

"Can’t you be nicer? You think I want to just stand there? The other side’s not letting me move." The Elementalist explained himself.

No one could watch the match seriously anymore. All they could hear were the curses and insults being thrown around by those experts. To summarize it: "You’re stupid! He’s stupid! Apart from me, everyone’s stupid!"

Everyone wanted to cry, when they saw this scene. Could they take advantage of the team competition? They knew it was a dream now. The team competition didn’t go any better than the individual competition. And seeing these experts blaming each other because of the situation made everyone’s image of them completely shatter. The expert, who lucked out and didn’t have to go on stage, rejoiced inwardly. It was good thing that he shamelessly refused to fight. If there were any Glory players on Mars, they would all message him, showing their disdain.

"Calm down! Calm down! Calm down!" Someone in the team was shouting, but all he received was four cold humphs. At this point, anyone who said anything would be looked down on by the others.

One of the five players finally fell. The reserve player automatically entered the field, but it didn’t change the situation in any way. Without any suspense, the six experts turned into corpses. As for their opponents? Let alone anyone dead, they couldn’t even look at how much health had been lost. In the team competition, the conditions for a perfect victory weren’t no loss in health, but no deaths. In this battle, Team Happy had earned a perfect victory.

"F*ck this sh*t!"

As soon as the battle ended, one of the experts got up. His face showed an expression of "it’s not my fault, but my idiot teammates". He turned around and left.

The original plan was to expose Team Happy’s weak members and have the weak legs of the team drag them down. But everyone of their team members felt like their other teammates were the ones dragging them down.

The first expert to get up didn’t say anything and rushed out of Happy Internet Cafe. The remaining few were furious! All of them glared at each other. Easy Bro snickered on the side. The words "sharing your happiness is much better than enjoying your happiness by your own" were too true. Losing face alone truly isn’t as gratifying as everyone losing face together!

Chapter 783: Not on the Same Level

Apart from the one person who waved his sleeve and left, the remaining experts were still raging at their idiot teammates. None of them would give in. The players, who had invited these experts, looked at each other, unsure what to do. Chen Guo walked over, laughing: "It’s just a game. Losing is normal. How about another match?"

"Another? I’m leaving!" Another player got up and left. After the match was over, an opportunity to get away was taken by someone else. Copying him felt too cheap, but the other experts couldn’t come up with any excuses to escape for awhile. But when Chen Guo walked over and spoke, someone immediately used the topic to run. From the way he walked, it seemed as if he were afraid of someone suddenly jumping out and blocking him.

Chen Guo wouldn’t block him. On the other hand, the players, who had invited this expert, should be the ones trying to stop him according to proper etiquette. But proper etiquette depended on the situation! Usually, if the guest was about to leave, you should stop the guest from leaving. But in the current situation, the guest had been harmed! If they stopped the guest, the guest might think that they were intentionally trying to embarrass him!

When this person left, he also said "I’m not playing anymore", giving the others an easy opportunity to continue with the topic.

"He doesn’t want to play? Then I’ll be going too." Another person got up. The other five fought to be the first to speak: "I’m going too." These experts were on the same page at this moment.

The experts left together. The players who had invited the experts were originally quite arrogant as foxes exploiting the tigers’ might, but as soon as they saw the situation go bad, they didn’t dare stick out and be noticed by others. All of them kept silent with their tails behind their legs. They were waiting to sneakily leave when no one was looking!

This time, Team Happy demonstrated that true gold fears no fire. Easy Bro and the other seven experts might not be too famous in the entire Glory scene, but in City H, especially in the City H Internet cafe community, their names resounded loud and clear. But they stepped onto the field arrogantly and left covered in dirt. Moreover, their losses to Team Happy didn’t seem any better than the other random challengers. These experts were also crushed in a devastating manner. Team Happy’s strength was still unable to be measured.

"Is there anyone else who wants to try?" Chen Guo’s mood was quite good as she happily asked. Following afterwards, the only ones who tried were the ones, who weren’t trying to humiliate Team Happy and were simply curious. Chen Guo didn’t know, but her expression right now was a signal to many.

If she had an indifferent expression, then it would make others feel like Team Happy’s strength was bottomless. However, after beating a few experts, she clearly looked excited. As a result, their evaluation of Team Happy couldn’t help but lower a bit.

Chen Guo really hadn’t thought about this. She had been with Ye Xiu for awhile now. Her scope had indeed broadened quite significantly. However, she wasn’t a God herself. Ye Xiu definitely wouldn’t feel anything special after beating these opponents, but that wasn’t the case for Chen Guo. She had once regarded these opponents as experts, so her mood was extremely good, seeing them lose.

After a few players challenged Team Happy to a friendly match, the day was about over. The Internet cafe was still free, but Ye Xiu and the others needed to sleep. Chen Guo couldn’t watch over the Internet cafe 24/7. She went upstairs to look for everyone and explained how arrogant these eight experts had been, when they came in, and how disappointed they were, when they left. Chen Guo didn’t like standing guard downstairs all day. It didn’t fit with her personality.

For the following two days, Happy Internet Cafe calmed down quite a bit. The Internet cafe was still crowded as ever because of the promotion, but the sounds of people jeering at Team Happy for not knowing their place had died down. There were still some though. Even though the team’s performance these past few days showed their strength, it was still delusional to think that they could take down Excellent Era. After all, Exellent Era had three All Star players. On paper, compared to the other pro teams, only Team Tyranny was above them.

It was just that now the incoming customers could only use Excellent Era to say anything. They didn’t dare jump up themselves to do anything. As for finding experts... they were looking, but they didn’t dare make any definitive statements.

Online, Happy’s fame gradually began to spread. The Internet cafe was free to use. No one really paid much attention to that. What everyone did pay attention to was that Team Happy had been challenged for an entire week, but hadn’t lost a single match. It seemed like their strength truly wasn’t just talk.

However, there were sounds of hype as well. There should be. A part of Chen Guo’s reason for doing this kind of promotion was for hype. In any case, they would need to face Excellent Era sooner or later. It would be better to jump out earlier and become the villain from the start. Even though they would certainly face ridicule all along the way, Chen Guo didn’t think that they wouldn’t be able to get any fans whatsoever. Excellent Era wasn't so amazing that they could hide the sky with one hand! City H didn’t only consist of Excellent Era fans. Excellent Era had the home terrain advantage, but so did Happy. If they were noticed from the start, players could follow Happy’s journey the entire way through. They would definitely win a few fans over. But under the circumstances of the Challenger League, stealing away Excellent Era’s fans was too difficult. As a result, Chen Guo was decisive. She directly challenged Excellent Era as opponents and didn’t attempt to win their fans. She wanted the neutral ones.

Chen Guo didn’t have a scientific statistic for the exact number of neutral fans, but as an owner of an Internet cafe, she interacted with Glory players more than normal people. Not everyone in City H liked Excellent Era. She was certain of this.

Following the defeat of Easy Bro and co., Team Happy’s fame in City H spread. The new week began. The players, who wanted to beat Team Happy, still hadn’t found any experts, but experts were coming over on their own now.

The experts, who came on their own, immediately gathered the attention of all the Glory players in the Internet cafe as soon as they told their IDs. Unfortunately, the results were always the same. No one could pass Tang Rou in a 1v1. Tang Rou had been better than a normal player since the start. Now that she was more experienced and underwent training, she no longer made beginner mistakes. For normal players, there was no difference in trying to beat her and trying to beat a pro player. In fact, a pro player might not take things seriously and accidentally lose. But with Tang Rou’s personality, no matter the situation, she would go all out. Lose? There was no reason to lose!

Experts challenged Happy wave after wave. The skill level of these experts were higher with every wave. Easy Bro and the other seven experts might be famous in City H, but they became famous through activities hosted by City H Internet cafes; they placed high in these local tournaments and gained attention that way. Inside this local community, they might be recognized, but outside? Who were they?

Players like Easy Bro weren’t even as famous as Deception in the Glory scene.

Deception relied on his own skill to make a name for himself in the game. If you talked about scrap pickers and didn’t know about the name Deception, you probably didn’t know anything about scrap picking.

Players who became famous through their skill alone like Deception were true top experts in the game.

These experts were certainly on another level than Easy Bro. It was clear that players at Easy Bro’s level weren’t good enough. Those eight experts didn’t produce any responses from Soft Mist or Steamed Bun Invasion.

Soft Mist’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s fame couldn’t compare with Lord Grim’s fame but they were bound together with Lord Grim. The uppermost circle in Glory knew of this background. This uppermost circle consisted of the Club guilds; the top experts in the game.

Those eight experts weren’t at that level, so they didn’t know the background of these two, but as Team Happy’s fame spread online and the skill level of experts coming to challenge them increased, Team Happy’s background was finally revealed.

The reveal came online. Someone pointed out that Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were from the tenth server. They were always together with Lord Grim, the most famous character in the game at the moment. While Lord Grim was in the tenth server, he summoned the wind and called storms. As soon as this information came out, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were tossed to the side. The famous Lord Grim was immediately picked out. Who was Lord Grim? Ye Qiu! This rumor had been around for a long time, but no one could prove it. Lord Grim never said it either, so those who wanted to believe it, believed it, while those who didn’t want to believe it, didn’t believe it. But there was no doubt that Lord Grim was incredibly skilled! Clearing the Heavenly Domain challenges at Level 50 was more than enough to convince everyone!

Soon, others began to sneer: City H’s skill level was so poor. They had been challenging the team for so long, yet they couldn’t even pass through the underlings. How long would it take until they saw the final boss?

The people who said these words obviously weren’t Excellent Era fans. They were probably still rejoicing at Excellent Era’s relegation! Now that they saw a rival had appeared for Excellent Era, despite being astonished at their arrogance, they still cheered and supported this Team Happy or whatever.

They didn’t actually like Happy, but rather detested Excellent Era and their fans.

This made Excellent Era’s fans even angrier. They didn’t need to be City H player to challenge Team Happy! In any case, the match took place online, so technically anyone could participate!

The player group wanting to take down Team Happy grew enormously. There were still experts, who came through the door, and others from the game. Despite the increasing number of challenges being made, the results were still the same: defeat.

The gap was simply too big!

With Tang Rou’s skill level and competitiveness, the only way she would lose to these players was if her Internet disconnected for a minute. With her standing on the field alive all the time, those who didn’t support Excellent Era attacked: you want to meet the final boss, yet you can’t even beat the first monster that appears on the screen! Excellent Era, be scared!

Chapter 784: New Heights

Excellent Era fans were unable to restrain their anger. Whether it was because of the mock and ridicule from the outside world, or the failure to take down Team Happy.

News spread rapidly. Guild Excellent Dynasty had numerous players. A few had noticed this event, but because they weren’t in City H, they didn’t pay too much attention to it. Who would have thought the matter would get worse and worse? In the end, it became a hot topic. Under the push from players, who rejoiced at Excellent Era’s misfortune, a small unknown character like Team Happy became described as the nemesis of Excellent Era.

How could fans bear to see this? How could this kind of team be a threat to Excellent Era? But the problem was that this team truly did have some skill. Excellent Era fans, who couldn’t sit idly and watch, ran over to slap their faces, but ended up running back with bloody noses instead.　　

They couldn’t sit still and watch!

The guild was a gathering place for the team’s fans. Apart from supporting the team through wild bosses, they could be considered the leaders for fans. At this moment, quite a few voices from the fans had reached Guild Excellent Dynasty. After all, the guild contained the true experts among Excellent Era fans. Thus, Excellent Era fans requested the guild to send out experts and eliminate Team Happy.

Excellent Dynasty’s normal players were eager to give it a try. They felt like it was their moment to shine, but when the news reached Excellent Dynasty’s core group, the elites of the elites, everyone fell silent. When their guild leader Chen Yehui heard the news, tears were already streaming down his cheeks.

Happy is so arrogant! I know! I’m standing at the window, looking at them!

Coming out with a promotion for free usage, attracting attention, creating the challenge, and then withstanding the ridicule from Excellent Era fans.

In fact, Chen Yehui, who was located right across street from Happy, had heard the news much earlier than most of the guild players. When he went out to eat at night one day, he even sneakily left to take a look at all the commotion going on at Happy Internet Cafe. Then, he saw the so-called expert turn into dough against Soft Mist and the disappointed Excellent Era fans.

That day, Chen Yehui’s heart thumped. He realized that, if this matter continued, it would likely reach him! Chen Yehui didn’t want that to happen, but he couldn’t stop it from happening at all. Hope that Team Happy would be defeated before then? What a joke! Chen Yehui knew very well how strong that team was! Let alone, these guys trying to take them down, even if Guild Excellent Dynasty formed at team of their best players to challenge them, they would still lose terribly. Ye Qiu was keeping watch! He had even heard news of some of the other players on the team: Team Blue Rain’s former captain, a rookie from Team Tiny Herb. How could in-game level players hope to beat these kinds of people?

Chen Yehui had looked for the Club manager Cui Li about this matter to see if they should stop Happy from continuing this trend.

Cui Li obviously didn’t want to see Happy shadowing over Excellent Era, but what could he do? Happy Internet Cafe providing free service was a way to attract eyes and provoke people. Their team truly did have the strength to back up their statement. The challengers trying to take them down kept trying again and again, but never succeeded. That was the root problem.

"Could we... maybe send people over to put out their flames?" Chen Yehui cautiously suggested a proposal.

"Send people over? Send who? Your people?" Cui Li asked.

"My people probably aren’t good enough." Chen Yehui laughed bitterly.

"I obviously know that your people aren’t good enough. If not, I would have sent them over a long time ago, but if we send pro players over, have you ever thought that... what if, I’m saying what if, they also lose, what can we do then? It would affect the team’s confidence and morale. Are you willing to take responsibility if something like that happens?" Cui Li asked.

"That….." Chen Yehui didn’t dare bear that responsibility.

"So not only can we not send our pro players over, we have to stop them from going. If they truly have strong feelings for this matter, then it would be a good thing for them to release those feelings when they actually encounter Team Happy. Later, I’ll contact everyone, prohibiting them from challenging Happy in private. Team Happy isn’t simple. You and I know very well how strong Ye Qiu is. How do you know if this isn’t a scheme that Ye Qiu intentionally set down, hoping we would lose our calm and throw us into disorder? Winning against them is what should happen. But if we lose, even once or luck, it would be a huge boost of confidence for them and a huge blow to us. Ye Qiu maybe provoking us to mess up our state of mind. We cannot fall into that trap. I’m going to go call them now." Cui Li analyzed, while talking to Chen Yehui. The more he talked, the more worried he became. He immediately started calling afterwards.

Happy was a very hot topic on the web, right now. Excellent Era would only be in the Challenger League next season, so they didn’t need to prepare as early as the other teams. They were still on vacation and weren’t in the Club. It was possible that a pro player would notice all the commotion and run over to challenge them out of anger. That pro player might fall to Ye Qiu’s scheme!

Especially Sun Xiang. If that guy saw the news, he might immediately put on his suit to go to battle.

Cui Li thought about this and felt like the other side might really be aiming for Sun Xiang! Cui Li immediately called Sun Xiang and warned him repeatedly. Sun Xiang had been with the team for more than half a year. As the manager, how could he not know what type of personality he had? He did a basic analysis in a way that Sun Xiang liked to hear. In the end, he felt like the results were good.

After Sun Xiang, he contacted the other pro players one after the other. Cui Li hesitated on the last name on the list: Su Mucheng.

Su Mucheng was an All Star, but when Cui Li contacted the players on the team, he put her last. It could be seen that her position in Excellent Era was on the edge. This wasn’t strange. Since they knew she would leaving next season, it wasn’t weird to make her existence in the team weaker this season. They couldn’t make her a core member, clearly knowing that she would leave next season. That would make improving the team much more difficult next year. As the Club’s manager, who considered the future, he couldn’t only look at the present.

"Su Mucheng isn’t over there, right?" Cui Li quietly thought to himself, accidentally thinking of the truth. After thinking about it for a bit, he still gave the call. No matter the case, Su Mucheng was still a member of Excellent Era at the moment.　　

"Hello?" The phone was quickly answered.

"Mucheng ah, where are you?" Cui Li asked.

"Happy Internet Cafe!" Su Mucheng said.

"Cough...." Cui Li coughed. You’re there, but can’t you hide that fact? So blunt and towards your manager too, are you not taking things seriously?

Cui Li cursed silently, but he still needed to say what he intended to say. After some thinking, he squeezed out: "Is your vacation going well?"

"It’s going well. What’s up?" Su Mucheng said.

"Nothing really. It’s almost time for the team to gather. I was afraid that you’d gone far, so I called to remind you." Cui Li said.

"Oh! I’m not far. I’m just across street! If you need me for anything, I can come back at any time." Su Mucheng said.

"Then I won’t bother you any longer... I’ll contact you again when I set the date for the team to gather." Cui Li said.　　

"Okay, bye."

"Bye."

Cui Li hung up the phone. He couldn’t describe his feelings. He obviously wasn’t happy, but he wasn’t really angry either. He felt like he was hanging in midair. He didn’t even know how he should vent his feelings.

He might as well not tell Su Mucheng what he said to the others. It was already quite good that she wasn’t helping Team Happy.

Chen Yehui seeked out Cui Li for help. The result was that the pro players were prohibited from helping. Thus, there was nothing Chen Yehui could do about Happy’s situation. That side had a God. No matter who you looked for in the game, no one would be able to take him down! Chen Yehui might as well not bother with it. He could only hope for a miracle, even if aliens from outer space suddenly came down to beat Happy, it would at least put a stop this show!

Unfortunately, no aliens from outer space came to attack earth. Team Happy continued making a commotion. Those Excellent Era fans, who didn’t know the truth, thought that Guild Excellent Dynasty was an especially grand existence. The experts sent out by the guild would be enough to destroy Team Happy. These experts finally arrived at the door.

Chen Yehui heard the clamor from Excellent Era fans and felt like dying. Sending people out wasn’t anything big, but all it would do was fan the enemy flames. Fans! You’re helping the enemy, you know?

Chen Yehui was conflicted! He thought of throwing together a team to call out Ye Qiu. That would be one way of paying back the fans. Just when he thought about this, he felt a sudden sense of inspiration. Chen Yehui had many years of battle experience. He had to find Cu Li first to discuss it though.

After asking Cui Li for advice, the two schemed together. Cui Li even asked for their boss Tao Xuan’s opinion. In the end, they came to a decision: that’s what they would do.

As a result, while Excellent Era fans hoped for the guild to hurry and bring out elite experts to destroy Team Happy, the guild finally stood out. The guild leader, Chen Yehui, replied with complicated feelings towards the fans. He rejected their request to dispatch experts to send to Team Happy because Lord Grim was Team Excellent Era’s former captain and legend, Ye Qiu. Guild Excellent Dynasty didn’t have the heart to go to war with their beloved and respected God…....

Everyone was dumbstruck.

Lord Grim really is Ye Qiu? This time, it wasn’t a rumor. An official statement from Guild Excellent Dynasty could be considered as a statement from Team Excellent Era. This could be considered as an example of the phrase: don’t pass judgement on a person’s life until the lid is on the coffin.

Ye Qiu had formed a team that would be fighting to the death with Team Excellent Era in the Challenger League?

The fires of this event burned to new heights.

Chapter 785: Not Ye Qiu

Lord Grim is Ye Qiu.

This news could shock the entire Glory world. Those in the upper echelons of the scene already knew this information though. Those in the lower and middle echelons had only heard the rumors long ago. Whether or not they believed the rumor didn’t matter. They would still be mentally prepared if the truth came out. This news originally wouldn’t garner too much of a reaction.

But Excellent Dynasty chose to jump out at this moment to verify the rumor. This timing contained a few subtle hints.

Team Happy would be participating in the Challenger League. There was no doubt that Team Happy regarded Team Excellent Era as an enemy. Because of this reality, people overturned the rumor of Lord Grim being Ye Qiu for this reason: Lord Grim couldn’t be Ye Qiu. How could Ye Qiu fight against Team Excellent Era?

Excellent Dynasty confirmed that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, making the heads of many people spin. Now people were certain that Ye Qiu and Excellent Era had a huge conflict. Wasn’t he locked in a deathmatch with Excellent Era now?

Players, who weren’t Excellent Era or Ye Qiu fans, watched the spectacle as a matter with no concern to themselves. Countless discussion threads popped up. At this moment, numerous Excellent Era fans were like Little Ming from before. When they heard the news, they started to lose self control.　

In the past few days, Excellent Era fans had vilified Team Happy. In their eyes, Team Happy was an evil enemy that could commit any misdeed imaginable, but this enemy suddenly changed shape with a single shake. The boss of this despicable team actually turned out to be Excellent Era’s beloved God Ye Qiu. A year ago, they had waved their flags and given their support to that very same ace player. How could Excellent Era fans accept it?

Some questioned it, some started swearing.

Team Excellent Era getting relegated was without a doubt the biggest crisis that the team had ever faced. At this moment, not only did their team’s former captain not provide help, he had even formed a new team from scratch to take down Team Excellent Era in the Challenger League.

Because of this reason, Excellent Era received a lot of support. No one was discussing how to crush Team Happy. Instead, everyone was denouncing Ye Qiu for his contemptuous actions. In comparison, the voices supporting Ye Qiu weakened.

Excellent Era was very satisfied with the outcome. Cui Li and Chen Yehui were looking out from the window and seeing a crowd of fans surrounding Happy Internet Cafe, demanding Ye Qiu to explain himself.

What a familiar scene!

Last season, when Team Excellent Era’s win record was in shambles, these zealous fans had also gathered in front of the Club entrance not just once or twice. It seems like Ye Qiu had reached this point. Cui Li and the others felt refreshed. What followed next would depend on Happy’s PR ability. Happy was just an insignificant Internet cafe though. How could it have a professional PR team on call for emergencies?

Excellent Era reckoned that Happy would at best expose the conflict between Ye Qiu and Excellent Era, pointing out that Ye Qiu had been forced to retire, but this was only Ye Qiu’s perspective. There was no concrete evidence. Even if Su Mucheng chimed in, it was just two people. Excellent Era could argue back and forth with them until the outcome was inconclusive.

Excellent Era had made preparations for this debate. There was nothing to fear. The PR department had taken precautions for this day! No one feared Ye Qiu’s influence more than Excellent Era. Before Ye Qiu’s influence faded completely, it was necessary to be on guard against the possibility of a leak. If Ye Qiu revealed the truth about his retirement to fire back at them, it would be exactly what Excellent Era was hoping to happen.

Tao Xuan, Cui Li, and Chen Yehui all hid in the Club, observing the commotion. Excellent Era didn’t stop taking action. After Excellent Dynasty confirmed Lord Grim’s identity, the Club’s spokesperson Wang Sheng put out a statement, verifying that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. He even mentioned that when Team Excellent Era’s situation was looking grim, they contacted Ye Qiu, asking for him to help the team. Unfortunately, Ye Qiu rejected their offer. Wang Sheng pointed out that Excellent Era felt it was a shame that he had refused, but the Club respected Ye Qiu’s decision.

It didn’t matter if Excellent Era had actually done this. More importantly, it brought up another issue at this moment, beautifully seizing a good opportunity. To the fans, the team asked you to come back, yet you refused. Now you’ve created your own team to participate in the Challenger League. Are you sincerely planning on becoming enemies with Team Excellent Era?

Countless fans felt bitterly disappointed. Reporters rushed over to Happy Internet Cafe and Club Excellent Era. The transfer market recently hadn’t been too interesting. Who would have thought that such a juicy topic relating to the Challenger League would pop up? With an enormous entity like Excellent Era being a central part of the news, the media did not need to worry about no one caring.

Of course, the reporters couldn’t speak without thinking. Doing their homework could enrich the contents of their report. As a result, reporters rushed to the two locations, while searching for any information on Team Happy, especially information relating to the Challenger League. The media directly asked the Glory Alliance.

They were greatly taken back when they heard the results. The Glory Alliance clearly expressed that the identity registered to Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu.

The Glory Alliance wouldn’t know about the details of Ye Xiu’s origins. The Challenger League only required an effective identity card to register. If the team passed through the registration process, Ye Xiu’s name and identity card number were genuine. Ye Xiu was a real person and was the person using Lord Grim. What relationship did he have with Ye Qiu? The Glory Alliance had information on Ye Qiu. They would keep files on all registered pro players. The two names were similar and the identity card numbers were extraordinarily similar, but they weren’t the same. Both identity cards were different, meaning Ye Qiu and Ye Xiu were two different people.

For the Glory Alliance, the identity cards were legitimate. There was no reason to question it. As for the outside world, the Challenger League did not publicly reveal information on names and surnames of participants because, in the beginning stage, the identities of the participating players weren’t necessarily trustworthy.

This allowed for more players to participate. The Challenger League only required a valid identity to register. The early stages of the league were done online. The company relied only on the players themselves to abide by the rules of the early stages. If someone was doing something fishy and playing on the behalf of someone else, it was difficult for the company to prove anything.

However, in the later stages of the Challenger League, the matches would take place in an offline studio. Thus, it wouldn’t be possible to do anything like playing on the behalf of someone else. Teams that reached this step through dubious means would have no way of hiding it. As a result, the Challenger League would only publicly reveal information in the later stages, after verifying the identities of each player offline.

The person who registered Lord Grim was called Ye Xiu, a legitimate identity. The staff members of the company could only question it in private, but from a company perspective, there was no reason to doubt it. They could only tell the media about what information that they had: Lord Grim was not Ye Qiu, at least according to the registration information. According to the rules, the player using Lord Grim could only be the person called Ye Xiu. If Ye Qiu was playing on his behalf, according to the rules, the company would ban the account and investigations into fraud would be made. The team would also be disqualified.

The media looked in dismay at the information that they had received from official sources. This was information from the Glory Alliance. The media obviously knew that the company was using Lord Grim’s registration information as evidence. Their credibility was undeniable.

This piece of information was soon reported by the media. The Glory Alliance was certain that the player, who was registered as Lord Grim, was not Ye Qiu.

The fans were suddenly dumbstruck. They had been shouting and cursing all day, but it turned out that Club Excellent Era had made an unexpected mistake?

Club Excellent Era.

From Tao Xuan to Chen Yehui, all of them were feeling great. Revealing Ye Qiu’s identity at this moment was undoubtedly a perfect opportunity. Tao Xuan was overjoyed upon seeing the crowd surrounding Happy Internet Cafe.

Just when everything was looking pristine, he suddenly saw the crowd become more and more restless.

What were they going to do? Tao Xuan looked forward to it. Then, he saw the crowd start to expand outwards. Players were turning around and talking about something. Soon afterwards, the crowd turned and crossed the street, straight towards Club Excellent Era’s entrance.

What’s going on? Tao Xuan was startled. He immediately thought that the fans were looking for Excellent Era to say something because of Ye Qiu’s reveal.

"Thinking of this point, Tao Xuan didn’t get angry. He had made preparations for this, after all. Ye Qiu ah. Ye Qiu. In the end, you couldn’t remain calm? Tao Xuan thought. He returned to his desk and grabbed the phone. The PR department would start the next step in the plan. Before he could even punch in the numbers for the call, he suddenly heard a knock on the door.

"Come in." Tao Xuan dialed the numbers while speaking. The door was pushed open. The manager Cui Li rushed in; his expression was gloomy. He clearly didn’t have any good news.

"What’s wrong?" Tao Xuan stopped dialing. He suddenly felt a bad premonition.

"News was just released. The media reports that Lord Grim is not Ye Qiu, but someone else. The Glory Alliance has already confirmed it." Cui Li said.

"What? What news? Which media reported it?" Tao Xuan was startled.

"ESports Home..." Cui Li said.

Tao Xuan couldn’t call it into question. ESports Home was the the country’s most reputable eSports news outlet. They weren’t tabloid newspapers, publishing gossip. If ESports Home was giving the report, they must have obtained proof from the Alliance themselves.

"What’s going on? Get Chen Yehui over here!" Tao Xuan was furious. Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. This news had come from the guild. Tao Xuan was going to get to the bottom of this. 　

As for the fans crowded around the entrance of Club Excellent Era, Tao Xuan obviously knew that it wasn’t because Ye Qiu had said anything. The fans had seen the news and immediately ran over to Excellent Era to criticize them.

Chapter 786: A Dull Conclusion

Chen Yehui ran to the boss’s office. When he entered the room, he could swear an oath to everything within a five hundred meter area. Ye Qiu was using Lord Grim. He had personally confirmed it in game. The two of them had even spoken face to face!

But a character was linked to an account card. Ye Qiu could use an account card. Others could use it too. Chen Yehui could only bet on that single interaction. It only proved that when he met Lord Grim, the person who was using Lord Grim had been Ye Qiu. Yet now, the person who registered Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu.

This was completely possible. The mistake was that no one had realized this point. Chen Yehui felt very wronged because what he concluded wasn’t wrong. As for Lord Grim not being Ye Qiu right now wasn’t a question that he had thought of, but Cui Li and Tao Xuan hadn’t either, no? When they came up with the plan to reveal Ye Qiu’s identity, all three of them had agreed on it. Even though Chen Yehui had proposed the idea, he was unwilling to take full blame for this mistake!

Tao Xuan was muddle-headed from anger. His logic was all over the place: "Could he have intentionally plotted for you to make this kind of misunderstanding?

Chen Yehui pondered over this question for awhile. He couldn’t penetrate the profoundness of this theory. He looked attentively at Tao Xuan and cautiously said: "Ye Qiu... intentionally making us think he’s Ye Qiu... then isn’t he still Ye Qiu?"

"Boss..." Cui Li couldn’t understand Tao Xuan’s confusing logic either and hastily said: "Ye Qiu is hiding behind Lord Grim. That’s for certain. We’ve talked with him before. He’s right across the street at Happy Internet Cafe, no? Team Happy cannot be unrelated to him. It’s just that now, we know that Lord Grim isn’t registered under Ye Qiu’s name."

This reasoning wasn’t complicated. Tao Xuan wasn’t stupid. When he received the news, he had thought of this conclusion. Understanding what had happened was one matter though. Because of their carelessness, they neglected this possibility and committed a grave error. How were they supposed to explain all of this to the fans outside their door?

Tao Xuan felt like he had lost face. In his search for an explanation, his reasoning became convoluted.

"Tell me your thoughts on how we should wind down this situation." Tao Xuan composed himself. Getting angry wouldn’t solve the problem. Looking into who was responsible was unnecessary too. It wasn’t any single person’s fault, but everyone’s.

"If Ye Qiu isn’t using Lord Grim, could he be registered under another character’s name in Team Happy?" Cui Li said.

Tao Xuan immediately went to the Challenger League website. When he searched "Happy", the site came up with 62 results.

Several days had passed since Chen Guo had registered the team. The Happy family had 17 new members. To know which one was the Happy next door, they would need to look through the details of each one. Tao Xuan was feeling impatient. He wasn’t in the mood to investigate each one right now. Cui Li had sharp eyes though. After glancing at the screen, he volunteered himself for the task: "Shall I take a look?"

"No need." Tao Xuan clicked on a Team Happy. He wasn’t lucky enough to click on Ye Xiu’s team on the first try, "There won’t be any information on their real names here. We’ll have to call the Alliance and ask."

The PR spokesperson, Wang Sheng, who arrived at around the same time as Chen Yehui, interjected: "Did the reports say that there was no Ye Qiu?"

"Did they?" Tao Xuan had heard the news straight from Cui Li. When he saw the fans change sides, he knew that it wasn’t fake news, so he didn’t personally look it up himself. After hearing Wang Sheng’s words, he asked Cui Li for verification.

Cui Li couldn’t answer it. He had heard the news from a subordinate too. He hadn’t read the actual article. Wang Sheng immediately followed up: "They did. The reports said that the Alliance confirmed that Team Happy has no one with the name Ye Qiu in their records."

The media had clearly spent more effort in digging up details than them. When they heard Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu, they also asked if Team Happy had a Ye Qiu and received this reply. The public statement was like a slap to Excellent Era’s face.

Fortunately, ESports Home was very fair. The article analyzed: even though the Alliance has confirmed that Team Happy does not have Ye Qiu registered, Excellent Era had no reason to speak without thinking. Team Happy must be related to Ye Qiu in some way. Lord Grim should be related to Ye Qiu. It’s just that Ye Qiu didn’t use this character to register for the Challenger League.

Tao Xuan finally grasped the full picture of the report. The author had helped them understand everything that could be understood. What else could they ask about? They couldn’t just barge into the Internet cafe and press down on Ye Qiu’s head until he gave them a proper statement!

"Then let’s explain it from this perspective... emphasize how Ye Qiu is connected to Team Happy." Tao Xuan instructed.

"Okay, I understand..."Wang Sheng nodded his head. He was in charge of the PR department. He was a professional in this area. He asked the boss for advice in order to get a general direction so that he wouldn’t be fully blamed if a problem arose. If he could get an instruction from the boss, it would be equivalent to obtaining an imperial sword. When he did things, it was more official, no?

Wang Sheng immediately got busy. Talking to the media and fans was his job.

Cui Li and Chen Yehui remained in Tao Xuan’s office. The mood was heavy. The boss was still clearly angry! The two looked at each other, and then Cui Li opened his mouth: "If there’s no other business, we’ll be going too."

"Okay…... " Tao Xuan replied. Cui Li and Chen Yehui promptly left.

In the office, Tao Xuan sat there gloomily for a long time before getting up to look out the window. The fans gathered at the Club entrance had already dispersed. Happy Internet Cafe was the same. Numerous fans were pacing back and forth, unsure of what to do. They would go that way and then head back the other way. The fans needed face too. Before, Happy had caused a huge ruckus. Then, the media reported that Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu. There was no Ye Qiu in Team Happy. Not only was this a slap to Excellent Era’s face, but to the fans, jeering at Team Happy. How could the fans not feel embarrassed when Excellent Era was embarrassed?

Excellent Era had explained their actions to the fans, recognizing that they might have made an error in certain areas, but they also emphasized Ye Qiu’s involvement in Team Happy. They had no real proof though. The fans weren’t so stupid as to believe whatever they were told. Being able to accept the club’s explanation was already quite good. As for Happy Internet Cafe, no one was in the mood to make another commotion over there again.

The commotion winded down. Excellent Era and their fans were left with red faces. As for Happy? They didn’t say anything from start to finish. Once the media found the truth, Excellent Era’s statement crumbled. Getting relegated was bad enough. After committing this mistake, no one in Excellent Era even dared to look at the Glory forums. There would certainly be a lot of ridicule towards them flying around everywhere.

Of course, people would mock them. There wouldn’t be any lack of gossip either though. Just like the report pointed out, although Excellent Era made a huge mistake, their mistake wasn’t without reason. Ye Qiu and Happy and Lord Grim must be related in some way. There was no question about that.

If Ye Qiu registered, was that allowed? Couldn’t retired players only return after a year? The Alliance was the authority over these rules. The employee from the Alliance, who was interviewed, felt a bit embarrassed too. Rules related to retired players never mentioned the Challenger League. Thus, according to the rules, the employee could only admit that there was no violation of said rules.

Apart from that, there was all sorts of gossip such as the conflict between Ye Qiu and Excellent Era, the bloody winds and rain set off by Lord Grim from the tenth server to the Heavenly Domain, and even the other registered characters in Team Happy.

The person most thankful for all of this was Zhang Jiale. Before, even though he said he would join Team Tyranny, it had not even been a year since he retired. It had only been confirmed verbally. No actual action could be taken. He could only officially return on August 29th.

During this time, there was still gossip floating around about Zhang Jiale, especially a few unresigned Hundred Blossom fans. They even created a petition for Zhang Jiale to return to Team Hundred Blossoms, which obviously didn’t conform with Team Hundred Blossom’s own plans, but fans were like this. The team could influence them, but they couldn’t control them. Fans would do as they pleased. These die-hard Zhang Jiale fans didn’t care if you were going to be the new core of a team, nor did they care about Club Hundred Blossoms trying to get them to understand that the past was the past and we should be looking at the future together.　

Club Hundred Blossoms was a bit scared too! They hadn’t left a spot for Zhang Jiale in their plans. They even sold off Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. The fans actually made such a move. If Zhang Jiale was moved and suddenly decided to change his mind, deciding to return to Hundred Blossoms, that would put the team in an awkward situation.

Fortunately, it seemed like Zhang Jiale was firm with his decision. When he announced his return, he once again expressed his thanks and regret to Hundred Blossoms.

"But no matter the case, there are things I must pursue." Zhang Jiale said during the press conference.

"Are you talking about the championships?" The reporter asked.

"Yes." Zhang Jiale nodded his head.

"Is being the champion really so important?" A reporter had asked slightly disdainfully. Hundred Blossom fans were doing their utmost to win Zhang Jiale back. They were practically hugging his leg and begging. Zhang Jiale refused to turn back. Quite a few couldn’t accept it, including a few reporters. It was hard to avoid feeling a bit emotional.

"Yes, very important." Zhang Jiale looked straight into the reporter’s eyes, "It’s more important than anything else."

Chapter 787: Going Full Circle

Zhang Jiale returning to the scene and joining Team Tyranny would happen just like he said he would. The fans’ entreaty failed to change a thing. This topic was enough to attract controversy. However, the entire Glory scene’s attention had now been stolen away by the Challenger League.

The Challenger League had the old powerhouse Excellent Era, gossip about Ye Qiu, and an Internet cafe team that even dared to challenge Excellent Era.

Zhang Jiale’s official return didn’t go unnoticed, but the attention received was lessened. This was obviously good for Zhang Jiale. His return came with a lot of pressure. He wasn’t completely unmoved by the fans’ requests. For an instant, he even felt the urge to return to Team Hundred Blossoms, so that he could meet his fans’ expectations. But in the end, his desire to win the championships was too great, so he stuck with his original path.　

He prepared for the incoming attacks, but who would have thought news of the Challenger League would be so explosive, lowering the pressure on him. Zhang Jiale was glad.

"What did he do now?" He had seen how Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, but also not Ye Qiu. He was Ye Qiu in the game, but in the Challenger League, he wasn’t Ye Qiu. Zhang Jiale felt a bit dizzy, but in any case, getting through the Challenger League would require overcoming Excellent Era.

"It seems like it won’t be so easy for us to meet again..." Zhang Jiale mumbled to himself. Excellent Era’s current competitive strength was truly a waste in the Challenger League.

"What’s not so easy?" Zhang Jiale was muttering to himself, when he suddenly heard someone behind him ask him a question. He turned around to see who it was. The other three aces of Tyranny, Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, and Lin Jingyan had all walked in together. Zhang Jiale had gone alone to the press conference, announcing his official addition to Team Tyranny. Even though Tyranny had arranged for Han Wenqing to come with him, Zhang Jiale refused it politely. He didn’t want too much pressure, but he didn’t fear it either. He felt like this pressure should be assumed by him alone.

"Oh, I’m talking about this guy. I’m saying it won’t be easy for him." Zhang Jiale pointed at the newspaper he was holding. It was the ESports Weekly, which belonged to ESports Home, the most reputable source of eSports news in the country. The newspaper was issued twice a week on Mondays and Thursdays, reporting all eSports news both inside and outside of the country. Glory was the number one game in eSports at the moment, so it occupied the majority of the front page.

It was Thursday today. Zhang Jiale had the most recent issue of the ESports Weekly. The news couldn’t be the most immediate news. Zhang Jiale had officially announced his return today, so this issue obviously wouldn’t have anything related to his announcement. The majority of the front page consisted of the commotion caused by Excellent Era two days ago.

Han Wenqing and the other two didn’t participate in the press conference with Zhang Jiale, but they knew that the press conference couldn’t have been a relaxing one for him. Whether it was a good topic to write about, or because of their actual feelings on the subject, the reporters would certainly have many difficult and penetrating questions for Zhang Jiale.

The three were a bit worried that he would be feeling downcast, but from the looks of it, he was still in the mood to look at gossip. It seemed like he could completely handle the pressure!

"Let me see." Lin Jingyan took the newspaper from Zhang Jiale’s hands and skimmed over the article. Then, he pointed at the complicated relationship between Lord Grim and Ye Qiu: "What’s there to say? That guy’s definitely at Happy, but he didn’t register, when it was time to. Although it’s a bit strange..."

"Challenger League rules allow you to add team members whenever you wish." Zhang Xinjie said.

"So you’re saying that he might appear after the team fights for some time?" Lin Jingyan said.　　

"Could he have made a mistake? Maybe he thought the retirement period wouldn’t allow him to participate in the Challenger League, so he held off on registering?" Zhang Jiale laughed.

"I don’t think he’d be so unclear about what he’s doing." Zhang Xinjie said.

Han Wenqing took the newspaper from Lin Jingyan’s hands and skimmed over it too: "Apart from him, no one else can use Lord Grim."

The other three fell silent. Lord Grim was an unspecialized character. That was no secret, and as pro players, they obviously knew how difficult it was to use an unspecialized. It was quite possible that only the one known as the Glory Encyclopedia could properly control this character.

"But then who’s the person who registered as Lord Grim?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"That’s a problem for Excellent Era to worry about." Han Wenqing said.

"Oh, let me ask you guys! If you had to choose between that guy’s team and Team Excellent Era to return, who would you rather choose?" Zhang Jiale suddenly said.

Those three hadn’t expected this question to come out. They stared blankly for a moment until Lin Jingyan asked back: "What about you?"

"Me….. even though Excellent Era appears extremely strong on paper, I still think that guy’s much more difficult to deal with. If we’re thinking about winning the championships, then I would rather choose Excellent Era." Zhang Jiale said.

"Mm, Excellent Era then!" Zhang Xinjie said. He didn’t say the reason, but his "mm" represented his approval towards Zhang Jiale’s reasoning.

"Indeed, if it’s that guy, and since we don’t know anything about his team, then I’d choose Excellent Era!" Lin Jingyan said.

The three turned their heads to look at their captain, Han Wenqing.

"It doesn’t matter who returns." Han Wenqing said, "They’ll be opponents we need to beat anyways."

"Hahaha." Zhang Jiale laughed, "You really are Tyranny’s captain!" He extended his right hand: "I hope for a pleasant cooperation."

"I hope for a pleasant cooperation." Han Wenqing shook his hand. As the representative for Team Tyranny, he officially admitted their new team member.

Happy Internet Cafe.

There were only three days remaining for Chen Guo’s promotion deal. The Internet cafe was still packed, but the sounds of ridicule towards Happy had lessened greatly.

Those players didn’t have the face to keep on mocking them anymore. They kept on trying to slap their face, but Happy slapped them back instead. They didn’t have the qualifications to call out Happy for not knowing the difference between heaven and earth. If you wanted to say something, you at least needed to back it up, no? Happy received all sorts of challenges, but they never lost a single one!

Despite all of this, their anger hadn’t completely dissipated, especially after Excellent Era’s reveal, which received a lot of controversy. Although Happy was no longer surrounded by angry fans, there were still plenty of people trying to figure out if Ye Qiu really was there or not. The media didn’t only come once to dig out the truth. Happy Internet Cafe’s owner and self-proclaimed owner of the team, Chen Guo, refused to budge. She refused to leak anything regarding the team. She simply told everyone that they would find out sooner or later.

They would obviously know sooner or later. Once they reached the final stages of the Challenger League and went to the offline studio, every member would be revealed, but who wanted to wait until then? There were still three days left and the number of participating teams had already passed ten thousand. According to the past, the last few days remaining would also have a sudden spike in registrations. The number of teams participating this year was clearly more than last year’s. This was also proof of the Glory Alliance’s continued growth.

More teams meant more rounds in the early stages of the Challenger League. The offline studios wouldn’t be played in until even later in the year. The spectators wanted to know the answer, but it was going to be dragged out for so long. They couldn’t bear it!

But what could they do? Happy’s owner refused to say anything. It’s not like they could put a knife to her throat and demand it!

There were a few impolite players who barged into Happy Internet Cafe to search, but how could they come up with anything? At this point, if Ye Xiu and the others stayed in the second floor, they would too overconfident. Ye Xiu and the others had already moved into their gaming house.

In the end, nothing else about Happy came out to the dismay of countless gossipers. The noise from Excellent Era fans had also died down significantly too, because it proved that their so-called experts had all been crushed in front of Happy. Their ability wasn’t enough to take down Happy. Even though a few refused to admit their mistake and argued noisily despite having nothing on their hands to back them up, these people were the minority. They continued to shout loudly, but they didn’t get anywhere with it.

Excellent Era fans were still thinking of slapping Happy’s face, but their most powerful force was Guild Excellent Dynasty. Demands started rushing in again. When Chen Yehui received the news, he felt like dying. How did it all come back full circle? Before, he had come across this problem and knowing that his guild’s experts would only get crushed too, he thought of revealing Lord Grim’s identity, using this topic to divert attention.

But before Happy could even respond to their statement, the media revealed the truth, destroying all their efforts. The fans turned this way and that, before shouting at Guild Excellent Dynasty to save them again.

"Did they not see the news! Ye Qiu isn’t registered, but he’s certainly in Happy! How could people in the game even hope to beat him? That Soft Mist just might be Ye Qiu, which is why she’s so strong! Why is everyone turning a blind eye to all of the analysis going on out there?" Chen Yehui wanted to say this to the fans, but as someone who represented the club, he couldn’t make any inappropriate statements.

Cui Li had already emphasized that Chen Yehui could not receive help from pro players either.

Hm... just when he was thinking about how pro players were no good, Chen Yehui suddenly had an idea.

Pro players weren’t convenient to use, but what about the training camp? The little demons of the training camp had received professional training. In terms of their skill, they were certainly better than any in-game expert. If he gathered a few of them, maybe they could beat Happy? Management would support this idea, right?